The mailman takes off.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS33
SOMEONE chases him to the truck and across the street. A car almost hits the mailman.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS34
SOMEONE tackles him to the ground, sending envelopes flying into the air. The FBI agent grabs the bulky Duke University letter and stands.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS35
He sprints back to his SUV.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS36
Now, SOMEONE parks in his driveway.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS37
He hurries up the front walkway to his house and enters.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS38
He peeks into the vacant living room, then heads upstairs.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS39
Now, he reaches into a box.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS40
He pulls out his own Duke University diploma, then makes a call on his cell.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS41
SOMEONE eyes his phone, then answers an incoming call.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS42
The man glances around.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS43
SOMEONE takes another call.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS44
SOMEONE hangs up.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS45
Meanwhile, a crowd stands around an outdoor stage where a young performer raps and dances.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS46
He points to a large banner reading Prodi-G, then notices a pretty girl in the crowd.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS47
She rolls her eyes and leaves.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS48
SOMEONE unplugs the amplifiers. The rapper's mic goes dead.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS49
SOMEONE beckons him from behind the stage.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS50
SOMEONE goes over to his stepfather with two friends.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS51
He and Rembrandt pound fists.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS52
He mimes spanking a child.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS53
His friends leave.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS55
sitting in the SUV's front passenger seat, SOMEONE mopes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS56
SOMEONE glances over at his sullen face, then smiles.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS57
Now at home,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS58
SOMEONE takes his jacket.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS59
SOMEONE follow him. He has a contract in hand.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS60
SOMEONE beatbox it.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS61
He exits and waves.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS62
SOMEONE answers his phone.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS63
He hangs up his phone and hurries off.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS64
Now, at night, our view glides over a highway, its lanes glittering from the lights of traffic below.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS65
SOMEONE's SUV cruises down a quiet road,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS66
then turns into a parking lot.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS67
A neon palm tree glows on a sign that reads Oasis Motel.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS68
SOMEONE parks his SUV in front of some rooms.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS69
He climbs out with his briefcase, sweeping his cautious gaze around the area.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS70
He hurries to a motel room door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS71
Another SUV pulls into the lot.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS72
Inside the motel room, SOMEONE sticks a microphone to his informant's undershirt.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS73
As the scruffy, unshaven man scratches his chest right by the mic,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS74
the FBI agent swats at him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS75
Digging into a pocket, he pulls out a flash drive and hands it over.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS76
As the informant buttons his shirt up over the microphone on his chest,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS77
SOMEONE inserts the drive into a laptop.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS78
He glances around, then leans in close.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS79
The informant dons a fedora. SOMEONE makes a call.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS80
Checking himself out in a mirror, SOMEONE puts up his dukes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS81
Now, the rear lights on SOMEONE's car flash on.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS82
In a smaller adjacent lot partially hidden behind a fence, SOMEONE watches from the driver's seat of the other SUV.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS83
He sees SOMEONE pull out of the parking lot in a beat up sedan.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS84
SOMEONE's SUV heads after it.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS85
SOMEONE ducks as the headlight shine into his vehicle.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS86
Sitting back up, he starts his engine.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS87
He backs out of his parking spot and follows after the others.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS88
Later, the beat up sedan speeds down a dimly lit road with the FBI agent following close behind.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS89
As SOMEONE rounds a corner onto another street, SOMEONE turns off his headlights.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS90
He follows the informant through a gate into an industrial complex, then parks his car behind stacks of pallets, hiding it from view.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS91
The FBI agent watches SOMEONE park in front of a warehouse. SOMEONE turns a dial on his CB radio.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS92
The informant climbs out of his car. Through binoculars, he watches SOMEONE greet two thugs by the door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS93
He heads into the warehouse and the thugs follow.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS94
SOMEONE turns up his radio's volume.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS95
SOMEONE appears at the window. SOMEONE draws his gun.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS96
SOMEONE opens the door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS98
SOMEONE rips open SOMEONE's shirt, revealing his mic.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS99
They both climb out.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS100
He points a gun.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS101
SOMEONE creeps inside.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS102
He grabs SOMEONE and aims his gun at the thug's neck.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS103
SOMEONE tosses his gun.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS104
SOMEONE yanks the informant away and SOMEONE jumps out from a hiding place. As the henchmen shoots at SOMEONE, SOMEONE frees himself. SOMEONE runs off.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS105
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE who retaliates with a right hook.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS106
SOMEONE chases SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS107
As the informant sprints out of the warehouse, the mobster shoots him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS108
Hiding in an alley around the corner, SOMEONE flinches. He sees SOMEONE fall to the ground. The informant looks at him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS109
SOMEONE's face contorts in pain.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS110
SOMEONE walks over to him and aims point blank.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS111
SOMEONE presses his back to a wall, concealing himself behind some barrels.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS112
He grabs his phone from his pocket and turns it off.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS113
SOMEONE spots him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS114
The mobster aims his gun.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS115
SOMEONE appears and shoots SOMEONE in the leg. The mobster slips away. SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS116
They race toward SOMEONE's SUV.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS117
As SOMEONE backs his SUV out of its hiding spot, SOMEONE shoots at them.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS118
Bullets hit the hood, sending sparks flying. As the SUV speeds toward a closed gate, SOMEONE steps in front of it with his gun raised.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS119
SOMEONE shoots through the windshield, then jumps away as the SUV closes in. The vehicle breaks the gate and speeds off. SOMEONE glares.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS120
SOMEONE's black SUV returns to the Oasis Motel.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS121
Now, in a nightclub, SOMEONE and SOMEONE meet SOMEONE who talks on a cell.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS122
Now, SOMEONE proofreads his handwritten last will and testament.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS123
SOMEONE web surfs on a laptop.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS124
SOMEONE shuts the laptop and smiles.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS125
SOMEONE puffs up.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS127
On a mall escalator, SOMEONE and SOMEONE descend, both now buxom and lady-like.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS128
SOMEONE wears argyle knee socks, a prairie skirt, and a yellow sweater.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS129
A rotund SOMEONE wears a floral dress.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS130
SOMEONE torques his crotch.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS131
He yanks on his cardigan and storms off.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS132
He stumbles.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS133
A passing shopper addresses SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS134
Now, a sign reads, "Georgia Girls School for the Arts".
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS135
A taxi van arrives.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS136
A side door slides open and a duffel bag hits the pavement.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS137
SOMEONE steps out as SOMEONE and kicks the duffel aside with one of his orthopedic shoes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS138
SOMEONE, aka SOMEONE, clumsily steps out in loafer pumps.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS139
The two would-be ladies pick up their bags and shuffle through a gate up some front steps.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS140
SOMEONE tosses SOMEONE his duffel bag.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS141
Carrying their bags, the rapper in drag waves to a girl, then sits on a bench.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS142
Inside, SOMEONE brushes past a secretary's desk.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS143
He enters the headmistress' office and shuts the door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS144
A woman enters covered in shaving cream and toilet paper.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS145
She reveals a bald patch.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS146
Beverly marches to the door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS147
She storms out.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS149
SOMEONE waves to a group of passing girls.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS150
He checks out beauties on the quad.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS151
SOMEONE smacks him on the sly.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS152
They tour the campus.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS153
He takes SOMEONE's arm.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS154
On their way upstairs, he glances back at SOMEONE who sneers and points. Now, in a dorm,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS155
the lovely Asian girl wears only a towel.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS156
SOMEONE stomps SOMEONE's foot.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS157
Crying, SOMEONE fans himself.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS158
SOMEONE scowls and mutters damn.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS159
They enter a cozy suite.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS160
A willowy blonde girl sits on the bed.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS161
Putting down a roll of toilet paper, SOMEONE walks out of the room.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS162
SOMEONE sets his duffel on a bed.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS163
Now, in a busy cafeteria, SOMEONE and SOMEONE carry their meal trays.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS164
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and several other students march ahead of them and sit together.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS165
SOMEONE pulls out a chair at the head of their long table.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS166
SOMEONE looks for an empty seat.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS167
The pretty girl notices it.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS168
His tray tilts askew as he plunks down.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS169
SOMEONE gestures at cut it and points to his voice box.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS170
SOMEONE bangs on a napkin dispenser with a fork.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS171
SOMEONE and the girls shift awkwardly.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS172
SOMEONE makes a peace sign.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS173
SOMEONE stands on her chair.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS174
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap a look.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS175
The pretty girl chants amiably, smiling at SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS176
He confidently rises from his seat.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS177
SOMEONE intercepts him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS178
With Prodi-G's swagger, SOMEONE takes the stage with a mic.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS179
SOMEONE shoots a snarky glance toward SOMEONE who wears a slack-jawed frown.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS180
SOMEONE glances at her peers, then eagerly leaves her seat.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS181
SOMEONE eyes his uncomfortable son who stands alone onstage.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS182
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE playing a nearby baby grand piano.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS183
Several classmates dance a little. SOMEONE resumes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS184
SOMEONE sings.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS185
SOMEONE gapes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS186
He dances.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS187
Another student dances among the lunch tables.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS188
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE and crouches.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS189
SOMEONE watches two dancers.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS190
One pirouettes, the other does a high kick.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS191
Throughout the cafeteria, students dance together and clap their hands.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS192
A dissatisfied SOMEONE looks over her peers.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS193
Still seated, SOMEONE shakes to the beat.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS194
Standing on a table, a girl claps. SOMEONE waves his fat lady arms overhead.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS195
Now dancing among the students, SOMEONE claps and spins in his red dress.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS196
He pops his chest, bouncing his large fake breasts.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS197
As SOMEONE keeps grooving onstage, SOMEONE has a go dancing on a table.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS198
As SOMEONE pumps his arms, the students rally around. He circles his right arm and shakes his wide hips.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS199
SOMEONE stands aloofly among the other girls.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS200
An enthusiastic SOMEONE claps along.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS201
He slips and falls on his back, splintering the lunch table in two.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS202
The student gape.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS203
SOMEONE covers her mouth.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS204
SOMEONE and a friend rush over.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS206
SOMEONE sits at the head of the seated group.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS207
With the table gone, all of the girls sit in their same seats, their trays on their laps.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS208
SOMEONE eats a tiny morsel from a small bowl.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS209
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's cellphone and reads the text.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS210
As SOMEONE keeps eating, the girls stare.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS211
SOMEONE stares too. SOMEONE notices their disapproval.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS212
SOMEONE runs off with her tray.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS214
Later outside, SOMEONE walks away.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS215
SOMEONE runs up a flight of steps and hurries off with his purse in hand.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS217
Now, he enters his room, throws down his purse, and rushes into a bathroom.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS218
Turning on the light, he pulls the door shut, then hikes up his skirt to find his padded girdle in the way.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS219
He tries to push it down.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS220
Gritting his teeth, he forces it down.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS221
He lifts the toilet seat, then holds up the front of his dress.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS222
SOMEONE enters the bedroom.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS223
She waits outside the door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS224
SOMEONE struggles to pull up his girdle.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS225
SOMEONE listens through the door as he slips backward and lands in the bath tub.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS226
He opens the door and sees her in her nightgown.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS227
He jogs over to a couch with the back of his skirt caught in the girdle.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS228
She reaches down to tug on the hiked skirt.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS229
SOMEONE fixes it.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS230
She steps out. SOMEONE turns around and widens his eyes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS231
Now, a bald heavyset guard turns up a boombox on top of his security control panel.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS233
He bobs his shoulders, then flips a few switches.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS234
Outside, SOMEONE waddles up to a door in his SOMEONE disguise.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS235
He peers through a window to find the security guard dancing with a screwdriver in his mouth.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS236
The rotund man strikes a series of poses before resuming his work on the panel.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS237
SOMEONE shakes his head, then waves to catch his attention.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS238
The guard continues dancing.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS239
He turns off his music and looks at SOMEONE with interest.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS240
He opens the door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS242
He goes into his office and turns on the lights.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS243
A framed photo shows SOMEONE with SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS244
Back at the dorm, a sign on a door reads, "Divas in Session, Members Only".
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS245
a sign on a door reads, "Divas in Session, Members Only".
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS246
Wearing a nightgown, SOMEONE finds nine girls seating at a round table topped with candles.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS247
They all stare.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS248
SOMEONE smiles.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS249
She stands up to greet her new friend.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS250
SOMEONE brings SOMEONE over to the table.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS251
The girls rise to their feet, SOMEONE does the same.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS252
SOMEONE turns for SOMEONE to wrap the necklace around her neck.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS254
SOMEONE watches, then eyes the other smiling girls.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS255
At the library, SOMEONE reads a plaque on a broken glass case.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS256
SOMEONE notices a necklace on the floor and grabs it.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS257
SOMEONE stops him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS258
The smitten security guard watches SOMEONE go.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS259
Back in the common room, girls hurry in with armfuls of clothing.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS260
SOMEONE sits on a reclining chair with a look of amazement as they try on outfits.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS261
SOMEONE puts a hat on his head.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS262
He watches a girl dance in a skimpy nightie and gives her two thumbs up.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS263
SOMEONE wraps a scarf around his neck, then dances the Charleston on the low, round table.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS264
SOMEONE grooves along from his chair.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS265
SOMEONE and SOMEONE grab his arms and urge him to his feet.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS266
He climbs on the table and dances for the girls who stand circled around him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS267
He twirls his right hand as if spinning a lasso.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS268
The doors open and SOMEONE steps through the curtains in a robe and nightgown.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS269
SOMEONE watches his son dance for the girls.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS270
He leans over to the stereo.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS271
The girls file out.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS272
He smacks SOMEONE on the back of the head. Now, SOMEONE reads Cosmopolitan.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS273
He lowers the magazine and takes out a subscription insert.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS274
SOMEONE enters in plain clothes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS275
SOMEONE puts up his feet, then notices SOMEONE holding the necklace from the library.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS276
He opens his magazine and gives it a shake.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS277
SOMEONE frowns.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS280
SOMEONE closes his magazine and extends his hand. SOMEONE reluctantly shakes it.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS281
Now, a Mercedes sits parked outside SOMEONE's house. SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE walk up the front steps.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS282
In SOMEONE's room, SOMEONE dumps a pile of demo CDs on the bed.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS284
He opens a CD case, takes out a disc, and puts it in a stereo.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS285
SOMEONE moves his shoulders to the beat.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS286
SOMEONE bobs his head.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS287
SOMEONE studies the back of the CD case.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS288
The next day at the girls school,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS289
disguised as SOMEONE, SOMEONE awkwardly squats beside SOMEONE who eyes him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS290
A teacher corrects his form.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS291
He grimaces.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS292
She extends his arm. SOMEONE plays the piano.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS294
The teacher pushes SOMEONE down into a deep knee bend.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS295
He falls on his back.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS297
SOMEONE and two of her peers dance in perfect unison while the other students look on.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS298
In the next trio, SOMEONE dances clumsily and out of sync.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS299
The whole class lowers into a split. As they lie on the floor, SOMEONE does one arm push-ups. He tries to split.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS300
He flash dances.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS301
Later, some girls bend forward in horizontal splits while others sit on their lower backs.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS302
SOMEONE nearly crushes his partner.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS303
In pairs, dancers leap across the stage.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS304
The frustrated teacher eyes SOMEONE's awkward moves.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS305
Out of breath, he grabs a curtain to brace himself.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS306
SOMEONE enters the auditorium.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS307
SOMEONE leaps across the stage. SOMEONE peeks around some of the other girls for a better look.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS308
Spinning out of control, SOMEONE falls off the stage and lands on his stepfather.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS309
The students gather above them.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS310
Outside a public high school, SOMEONE shows SOMEONE's CD to passing students.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS311
Scratch and Rembrandt swap a look.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS313
Back at the girls school, a teacher greets SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS314
A beautiful young woman arrives.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS315
SOMEONE quickly finds a seat.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS316
SOMEONE stops the model from disrobing.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS317
SOMEONE peeks in.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS318
Everyone turns to look at him. He quickly grabs his radio.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS319
He steps out.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS320
Later, we drift from SOMEONE's socks up his chunky bare legs.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS321
He lies on his side with the sheet covering his torso, his head propped up on his forearm.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS322
The girls sit at easels, stretching bulbous renditions of the obese woman.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS323
In the front row, SOMEONE wears a look of disgust.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS324
Two girls get up from their easels.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS325
He posed his thick leg in a new position.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS326
She yanks off the sheet.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS327
SOMEONE pulls a fire alarm.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS328
The students flee.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS330
SOMEONE wears the sheet like a toga.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS332
He talks into his radio.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS334
SOMEONE races over.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS338
In the dorm, the girls lead SOMEONE down a hall.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS340
They follow red droplets on the floor.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS341
SOMEONE sits up in bed, her hair dyed bright red.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS343
SOMEONE nods and smiles, then eyes her fried and dyed hair.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS346
Meanwhile in a clothing store, SOMEONE pulls a sweater off a rack,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS347
and holds it up to SOMEONE. She grabs another top.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS350
Grabbing SOMEONE's hand, she pulls him into a dressing room.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS351
He watches confusedly as she hangs their selections on a hook.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS352
She pulls the curtains closed.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS353
Facing a full-length mirror, SOMEONE gawks at SOMEONE's reflection as she pulls off her pants.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS354
He turns to her.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS355
SOMEONE strips down to her bra. SOMEONE turns away.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS356
He sneaks a look at her well-filled bra cups.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS357
SOMEONE unclasps her bra.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS358
He rushes out.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS359
Back at the dorm, SOMEONE washes SOMEONE's hair in a sink.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS360
Later, SOMEONE's dark hair looks frizzy and dry.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS361
SOMEONE grabs a product.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS364
She slathers her hair.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS365
Now, he blow-drys it. SOMEONE looks at her smooth, shiny, dark hair with gentle curls.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS367
She grins at SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS368
She hugs him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS369
He escorts her outside.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS370
SOMEONE glances around.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS371
SOMEONE blinks shrewdly.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS372
In town, SOMEONE wears leggings, a new short-sleeved cardigan, and a scarf.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS373
As he puts away some new sunglasses, SOMEONE hands her a cup of ice cream.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS374
Some guys in varsity jackets approach.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS375
SOMEONE forces a grin.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS376
He and a friend swap a cocky handshake.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS377
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE away.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS378
He stares after her, then gives a smug nod.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS379
They stroll a sidewalk.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS380
SOMEONE tosses out her ice cream dish, then browses the sunglasses stand.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS381
SOMEONE leans in close, transfixed.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS382
SOMEONE turns.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS383
He snaps out of it.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS384
SOMEONE watches her apply lip gloss.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS386
Night time. From a window, SOMEONE scans the quad with his binoculars.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS387
SOMEONE reaches over.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS388
Out of costume, the two men look out the window.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS390
SOMEONE faces him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS391
He sidesteps.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS392
They sidestep in unison.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS393
They swivel their hips.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS394
With one foot raised, they rotate.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS395
SOMEONE shuffles.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS396
As they spin around again, SOMEONE crouches by the window and raises his binoculars.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS397
SOMEONE hands over a bag.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS398
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE watches through the binoculars as SOMEONE glances around, heading to his on-campus apartment.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS399
Later in his living room, the big-bellied guard wears headphones and a track suit as he scratches on a turntable setup.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS400
Outside, SOMEONE sneaks up to a window as SOMEONE in a plus-size track suit.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS401
He watches SOMEONE scratching.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS402
Snapping his fingers, SOMEONE bobs his head.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS403
He sets his headphones by his turntables, then dances backward out of SOMEONE's view.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS404
As the FBI agent shifts to another window trying to find the guard,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS405
SOMEONE emerges from a door right beside him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS406
He steps closer to SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS407
He gives a longing look.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS408
SOMEONE glances aside.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS409
Shooting SOMEONE a wary look, SOMEONE heads inside.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS410
The guard ogles the disguised man's full figure then follows, enthusiastically waggling his head.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS411
Meanwhile, a neon sign glows above a restaurant, Marietta Diner.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS412
SOMEONE enters.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS413
Wearing a leather jacket and a loose scarf around his neck, he plucks a flower from a vase as he heads to SOMEONE's table.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS414
He leans on the booth facing her and gives a smoldering look.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS415
She glances up from her schoolwork and winces.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS416
He sits.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS417
SOMEONE gives him a shocked smile.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS418
He leans closer.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS419
He offers the flower.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS420
She takes it and sets it aside. SOMEONE sits back with a smile.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS421
He sets down Buddhist prayer beads.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS422
He removes his scarf and shrugs. SOMEONE attentively folds her hands.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS423
SOMEONE shakes his head.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS424
SOMEONE regards him amiably.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS425
He extends his hand.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS426
Now, SOMEONE brings SOMEONE a wine cooler.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS427
SOMEONE pokes his belly.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS428
They sit together on a couch.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS429
He leans closer.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS430
SOMEONE winks.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS431
The guard eyes his guest.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS432
He tickles SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS433
He talks at SOMEONE's ample chest.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS434
As SOMEONE takes a drink, SOMEONE touches the wig's blonde curls.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS435
As he leans closer, SOMEONE jumps up from the couch.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS436
SOMEONE's brow lifts.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS437
Meanwhile, SOMEONE walks with SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS438
They pass fountains on the promenade.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS439
Nearby, Scratch and Rembrandt check out girls.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS440
Rembrandt dials a number from a slip of paper.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS441
A short distance down a street, a sedan turns on its headlights and crawls toward the promenade.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS442
SOMEONE's friends rush over to him and SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS443
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS444
The couple heads away.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS445
The sedan tails them.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS446
SOMEONE hangs up while SOMEONE drives.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS447
Back at his apartment, SOMEONE spreads a Twister mat on the floor. He grins.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS448
He grabs the spinner.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS450
They each step on a red dot on the map.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS451
SOMEONE spins.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS452
SOMEONE's back presses against SOMEONE's stomach.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS453
SOMEONE rubs against SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS454
SOMEONE leans closer.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS455
The agent in drag covers his nose.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS456
SOMEONE flicks the spinner.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS457
SOMEONE looks back.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS458
With a cringe, SOMEONE drops a hand to the mat.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS459
His padded big bottom looms waist-high to SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS460
SOMEONE huddles in, his body leaning over SOMEONE's.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS461
A montage shows their game play.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS462
Facing SOMEONE, SOMEONE presses the guard's head down and reaches over his back.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS464
SOMEONE lies on the mat and SOMEONE stretches over his stomach.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS466
Now, SOMEONE sits on the mat, his rear and hands taking up most of the green dots. SOMEONE eyes the mat.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS467
He lifts his rear, revealing two green dots under his widespread crotch.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS468
SOMEONE frowns.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS469
SOMEONE stands.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS470
SOMEONE scurries to his feet. He points.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS471
SOMEONE stares. SOMEONE grimaces tearfully.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS472
Flinching, SOMEONE heads to a closet door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS473
SOMEONE unlocks the door and retrieves a knapsack from the closet.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS474
Snatching the bag away, SOMEONE searches it and finds a bag of bird seed.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS475
He checks the knapsack again, then turns on the closet's overhead light.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS476
A rooster flies out.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS477
SOMEONE eyes the bird.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS478
As the rooster hops onto a table, SOMEONE cringes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS479
SOMEONE addresses him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS480
SOMEONE glares.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS481
Outside, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE onto campus.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS482
They fail to notice the Russians' Mercedes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS483
SOMEONE shows SOMEONE her studio.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS484
SOMEONE sets down her purse.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS485
She sits at the piano and brushes her long, dark hair from her face.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS486
SOMEONE shakes his head and holds his heart.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS487
SOMEONE rubs his hands together, then sets up a microphone.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS488
He flips open a laptop and punches a few keys.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS489
With a humorous smirk and shrug, SOMEONE pleads clueless.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS490
They hover outside, withdrawing from the window-framed
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS491
view of the two singers.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS492
Later, they return to the dorm.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS493
She hugs him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS494
SOMEONE holds her close.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS495
SOMEONE demurely steps back.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS496
SOMEONE leans in. SOMEONE closes her eyes and they kiss.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS497
As the kiss ends, the two lovebirds remain close, their lips inches apart.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS498
SOMEONE smiles.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS499
On her way up the front steps, she glances back.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS500
SOMEONE watches her go, then walks off.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS501
SOMEONE spies on him with binoculars, while SOMEONE talks on his cellphone.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS502
SOMEONE hangs up.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS503
They watch SOMEONE skirt around a building.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS504
SOMEONE points as the teen disappears into a side door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS505
They duck down as a night watchman walks past the door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS506
The watchman looks around skeptically, then moves on.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS508
SOMEONE peers through his binoculars.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS509
The full-bodied and now fashion-forward SOMEONE emerges from the side door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS510
SOMEONE watches the husky girlish student back to the dorm, then lowers his binoculars.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS511
He pats his blonde partner's shoulder and they approach the side door, pistols in hand.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS513
SOMEONE nods. SOMEONE opens the door and they rush into the small utility room.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS514
They find it empty.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS515
The two henchmen look around.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS517
Now at the nightclub, they swap a look.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS519
in SOMEONE's campus suite,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS520
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit before the rooster.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS521
The girls swap a look.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS522
SOMEONE arrives.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS523
SOMEONE glances at the two nervous students.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS524
Both girls turn to speak.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS525
SOMEONE spots the Russians outside.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS526
He heads out.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS527
He hurries out the door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS528
The agent in drag runs outside to find the henchmen about 50 yards away.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS529
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's arm.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS530
SOMEONE chases them out through a gate.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS531
He watches them get in their Mercedes, then spots SOMEONE in a parked car.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS532
He gets in and grabs her cell.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS533
He forces her foot to the pedal and they leave her driving instructor behind.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS534
On the road, the car speeds toward a box truck.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS535
She cranks the wheel and they turn onto a cross street.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS536
SOMEONE's car cuts in front of the yellow box truck.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS537
The sedan bears a student driver sticker on its hood and trunk.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS538
SOMEONE steps on the gas.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS539
In the Mercedes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS540
The Mercedes drifts through a hard right turn past a road work site. SOMEONE points.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS541
He cranks the wheel from SOMEONE and they turn into a parking lot.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS542
The car slides into a sharp turn, then grinds up against a stone wall. Sparks fly as SOMEONE regains control of the vehicle.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS543
They hit a bump and catch air over a cross street.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS544
The Mercedes barely zips pass a truck which blocks the road.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS545
SOMEONE shifts into reverse. The car's tail end raises ten feet off of the pavement and it slides to a stop on its nose.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS546
SOMEONE fixes his wig.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS547
Now at the dorm,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS548
SOMEONE faces his son.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS549
As SOMEONE heads out, SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS550
SOMEONE nods.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS551
At night, students file into an auditorium.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS552
Inside, SOMEONE leads her friends to a 10 x 3 foot painting of SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS553
Backstage, a worried SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS554
They hug.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS555
SOMEONE rests her head on SOMEONE's shoulder and frowns uneasily.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS557
they hug again.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS558
As SOMEONE hurries onstage with several dancers, SOMEONE heads off.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS559
Onstage, the ballet dancers twirl and lift.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS560
SOMEONE flutters her arms overhead.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS561
In a dressing room, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE put on make-up.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS562
She stands and faces him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS563
SOMEONE arrives.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS564
SOMEONE notices the young man.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS565
He points, then leaves.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS566
Standing in the wings, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE perform.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS567
SOMEONE finds them.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS568
SOMEONE waves.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS569
They peer into the auditorium. SOMEONE bows, then exits the stage with the other dancers.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS570
The house is full of enthused faces.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS571
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE step out onto stage.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS572
On stage, she glances at SOMEONE and takes a seat at the piano.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS573
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, then obeys SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS574
On stage, SOMEONE sets her fingers on the keys and nervously looks over the crowd.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS575
A frustrated SOMEONE throws up his arms. Audience members look on uneasily.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS576
SOMEONE runs out and sits beside her.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS577
He cues up the laptop.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS578
SOMEONE returns to the wings and watches them.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS579
SOMEONE sees the Russians enter the theater.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS580
In SOMEONE's fat suit, he hurries down a staircase,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS581
disappearing briefly behind the spotlights and curtains, and reemerges in the auditorium.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS582
SOMEONE confronts SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE in an aisle.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS583
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE with a confused expression.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS584
SOMEONE gapes at him. As SOMEONE glances back at the stage, SOMEONE pulls off SOMEONE's wig.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS585
SOMEONE rips off SOMEONE's mask, throws down the disguise, and backs away.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS586
She smacks him, then storms offstage past a group of her peers.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS587
As SOMEONE runs after her, SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS588
The Russian lets him go.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS589
As SOMEONE notices, the criminals flee.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS590
SOMEONE and SOMEONE confer.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS591
As he races away, SOMEONE turns to the audience.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS592
Meanwhile, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE rush out of the building.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS593
On the quad, SOMEONE searches for SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS594
SOMEONE and his posse approach.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS595
One of the guys shoves him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS596
SOMEONE pushes back and SOMEONE's guys knock him down. SOMEONE arrives.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS597
The teens scatter.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS598
He drags SOMEONE to the utility room.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS599
SOMEONE unlocks the door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS600
He shoves SOMEONE inside and locks the door. He eyes SOMEONE through a window.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS601
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE leave.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS602
He leans against a wall, chest heaving.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS603
His gaze drifts to a duffel bag on the floor. He heaves it onto a workbench. Unzipping it, he pulls out his regular clothes. Meanwhile, SOMEONE runs on to the quad.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS604
Slowing his pace, he sweeps his gaze around the area, gun raised,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS605
then takes off again.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS606
SOMEONE, now wearing his own clothes, spots SOMEONE as she strides down a walkway.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS607
She hurries toward the library.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS608
SOMEONE opens a window and climbs out.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS609
He runs after her.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS610
SOMEONE spots him and uses his phone.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS611
He chases SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS612
Inside the library, SOMEONE strides toward the broken display case.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS613
SOMEONE catches up to her.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS614
As SOMEONE opens the box, SOMEONE enters and hides behind a bookshelf.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS615
SOMEONE takes out the flash drive.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS616
He sends a text on his phone.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS617
Outside, Big Momma-clad SOMEONE reads the text, "Library, have FD".
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS618
SOMEONE steps out, gun raised.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS619
SOMEONE arrives.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS620
SOMEONE shoots at SOMEONE, who leaps behind the librarian's desk, then fires at SOMEONE and SOMEONE. They race away.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS621
Outside, SOMEONE answers his phone.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS622
He leads her by the hand. As SOMEONE peeks over the counter, a gun points at the back of his head.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS623
SOMEONE stands, hands up.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS624
Held at gun point, SOMEONE falters.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS625
As the thugs swap a look, SOMEONE grabs a World Atlas and knocks them unconscious with it.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS627
Elsewhere in the library, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS628
He leads SOMEONE down a flight of stairs.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS629
Meanwhile, SOMEONE races past rows of bookshelves, looking down each aisle. Outside, SOMEONE and SOMEONE run across a patio, then enter the library through another door.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS630
SOMEONE stays on them. They return to the main floor.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS631
SOMEONE takes aim at them. SOMEONE arrives. She's packing too.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS632
SOMEONE tosses him the drive. SOMEONE grabs the teens.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS633
Racing in, SOMEONE and SOMEONE aim their guns at SOMEONE's head.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS635
Blinking resignedly, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE who snatches the gun away.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS636
SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE to SOMEONE, and SOMEONE to SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS637
He turns his weapon on SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS638
The disguised agent hands it over.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS639
SOMEONE glances at it, then tucks it into his jacket.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS640
SOMEONE steps closer, his eyes fixed on the undercover agent.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS641
He rips off SOMEONE's blonde wig and mask.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS642
SOMEONE reaches back and undoes his dress.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS643
He shakes his padded SOMEONE suit to the floor.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS645
SOMEONE glances.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS646
SOMEONE crooks a smile.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS647
SOMEONE releases his grip on SOMEONE's shoulder.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS648
They sidestep.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS649
They bounce their hips, then they each kick a thug in the crotch.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS650
As they drop both Russians, SOMEONE returns and shoots the ceiling.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS651
He aims his weapon at SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS652
A Taser fires its electrodes.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS653
SOMEONE convulses, then drops to the floor, revealing SOMEONE behind him.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS654
Agents swarm into the library.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS655
SOMEONE smiles at the guard.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS656
He salutes SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS657
As agents drag the thugs out of the library, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE enter.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS658
SOMEONE shakes his hand.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS659
Later, agents haul the criminals to vehicles parked in front of the school.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS660
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE outside the library.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS661
With a smile, he pulls SOMEONE's papers from his pocket.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS662
SOMEONE eyes the signed papers.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS663
He beams.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS664
SOMEONE twitches a satisfied smile.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS665
SOMEONE lifts his serious gaze from the contract,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS666
then tears it in half.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS667
SOMEONE frowns.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS668
SOMEONE's face lights up.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS669
They shake hands, hug, then head to SOMEONE's SUV.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS670
SOMEONE holds up his SOMEONE padding.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS671
As the SUV drives off, our view lifts to the Atlanta skyline.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS672
Now, in a music video,
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS673
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sing and dance in a crowded club.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS674
A caption reads, "Notorious PhD, Lyrical Miracle, Prodi-G, SOMEONE's Records.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS677
Now the divas strut to the center of a dance floor, while students hang from scaffoldings, and SOMEONE dances behind SOMEONE.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS678
SOMEONE struts toward us, dressed in his SOMEONE disguise.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS679
A skyward view shows puffy clouds behind SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE who wear sunglasses and lip sync.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS680
Now, we see SOMEONE behind his turntables with his headphones propped on his head like mouse ears.
BIG_MOMMAS_LIKE_FATHER_LIKE_SON_DVS681
Now, the mailman dances on the roof of his truck.