His date gives a thumbs up, mouths SOMEONE Mayer, and rushes inside.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS15
SOMEONE's date hugs her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS16
A Castle Rock Entertainment Production.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS17
Behind SOMEONE and her friend a flyer reads Friends with Benefits. Now the web designer rides in an airplane. A flight attendant
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS18
flirtatiously close.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS19
She jerks his seat up and turns away.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS20
In a hired car, SOMEONE uses her cell.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS21
She changes clothes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS22
As the driver eyes the building, she changes her top.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS23
Now at the airport, she approaches a driver holding a name card.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS24
She takes the card and writes SOMEONE on the back with lipstick. As the web designer walks through a sliding door, an air gust blows the sign from her hands. It lands on a baggage carousel.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS25
She chases after it.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS26
She removes her shoes, climbs up on the conveyer, and runs past suitcases.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS27
SOMEONE notices her handing a man a suitcase.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS28
She trots down to the other end of the carousel, hopping over bags.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS29
She and SOMEONE both reach for her sign.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS30
Now they sit in the car.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS32
He hands her an iced green tea beverage and goes inside. SOMEONE takes a sip, then spits it out. Rinsing her mouth with water, she spits again, nearly hitting a passerby.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS33
As we peer out from the lobby through its glass doors, day becomes night. SOMEONE leaves the building. Seated at a nearby cafe, SOMEONE springs to her feet at his approach.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS34
As he checks his phone, she suddenly puts hers away.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS35
He turns away, staring at his cell.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS36
She pouts and lifts her brow.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS37
She starts across the street, but SOMEONE remains on the sidewalk.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS39
Later they sip drinks at an intimate table.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS40
They share a smile.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS41
SOMEONE walks by.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS42
He bumps into the table.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS43
He hugs SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS44
Later on a sidewalk.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS45
They reach a gyros stand.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS46
Now at a partially open security gate.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS47
SOMEONE rolls underneath.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS48
SOMEONE follows suit. Now SOMEONE leads him up a stairwell.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS49
She carefully swings her legs over a security gate at the top and strides onward. SOMEONE opens the gate and steps through. Now SOMEONE leads him through a door. Both clutching their gyros they step out on a high rooftop overlooking Manhattan.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS50
They walk to a corner with a view of the Empire State Building.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS51
Later they eat.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS52
SOMEONE's chewing slows and he averts his
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS53
SOMEONE steps away.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS54
She sits down.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS55
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie back side-by-side.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS57
They move through a crowd.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS58
SOMEONE halts.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS59
Nearby a man holds up a boom box while another starts break dancing. The crowd parts for them.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS60
Two other dancers join the first. All three strike stylized poses and nod their heads in unison. As they move into a Broadway style dance number, young people approach from all over the crowd. The performers slump down.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS61
As they spring up and break into another set of moves, the dozens of young people join them. SOMEONE looks around bewilderedly.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS62
He spots a huge monitor broadcasting the flash mob.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS63
She raises her arms and waves them in unison with the dancers.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS64
The dancers lean over and back up, edging close to SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS65
They bend over, too. The dancers straighten and point skyward. A forward leaning pose radiates from the back of the flash mob.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS66
The boom box holder stands erect among the participants, as onlookers watch delightedly. The dancers straighten and raise their arms skyward, some with jazz hands.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS67
They clap along as they converse.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS68
The dance concludes with a flourish.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS69
On a plane, he talks with someone.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS70
Now at night, a New York City cab drops SOMEONE off in an urban neighborhood.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS71
He gazes about, full of wonder.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS72
He grabs his bags.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS73
Later he enters a sleek apartment, decorated in grays and browns. SOMEONE drops his bags. He steps past a black granite galley kitchen and descends into a sunken living room. A gift basket of bed sheets includes a note, SOMEONE, welcome to NYC. In case you shit the bed. Excuse the expression. Best, SOMEONE. SOMEONE runs to his bed and vaults hard on the mattress, jamming his shoulder. Now at GQ.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS74
SOMEONE removes the door from its frame.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS75
A fit balding guy greets him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS76
He strokes SOMEONE's cheeks.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS77
He starts off, then backtracks.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS78
SOMEONE peers off, stunned. Later, as he works, SOMEONE enters his office.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS79
He shows her a web video of a woman dunking her breasts in cake batter.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS80
Another shows the Time Square flash mob.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS81
The rows of dancers form the GQ logo.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS82
SOMEONE takes a look at the inch-thick stack of documents.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS84
Later in a corner diner.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS85
He gets a call from SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS86
They share an amused smile.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS87
Later SOMEONE opens her door to SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS88
Later they play virtual table tennis. Now SOMEONE and others stick playing cards to their foreheads.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS89
His reads Curious SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS90
Playing Jenga, SOMEONE intentionally topples the block tower. SOMEONE swigs beer, then passes out. SOMEONE graffities his face with marker. At GQ he notices traces of the graffiti. Now as SOMEONE holds up a lipstick sign at the airport, she sees SOMEONE's GQ flash mob ad on a kiosk. She photographs herself with it. At home SOMEONE grins at her email. At a party they view a canvas that features industrial looking stenciling.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS91
SOMEONE passes out. As SOMEONE draws on her face, the marker leaves no apparent lines.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS92
SOMEONE now addresses three executives.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS93
As she dims the lights for a slideshow, glow-in-the-dark graffiti shows on her face, including eyebrows, the word Loser and cat whiskers. SOMEONE rubs her nose. Glowing ink transfers to her hand and she gawks.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS94
Now in a movie, SOMEONE and SOMEONE co-star.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS95
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch together.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS96
In the movie, the leading man runs with flowers.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS97
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE lip sync every word.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS98
SOMEONE drops the flowers and kisses SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS99
SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a hansom cab.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS100
They both swig a beer.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS101
In shorts and a tank top SOMEONE bends over to clear some clutter. Her cute butt mesmerizes SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS102
He watches her rear as he is sitting on the couch.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS103
SOMEONE steps away then return.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS104
He puts his hand on the virtual Bible. SOMEONE adds hers, and SOMEONE tops it.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS105
They peer closely at each other.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS107
He cups her bosom.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS108
She walks away.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS109
They get undressed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS110
With her back to us, she faces SOMEONE and ditches her bra.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS111
SOMEONE drops his briefs. We view his bare butt, SOMEONE his front.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS112
Now they fall back onto the bed, making out.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS114
He pulls a shaggy teddy bear out from under the sheets.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS115
She grabs his head by the hair, pulls his head to hers and pinches his tongue.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS116
Now SOMEONE shuts her eyes ecstatically.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS117
SOMEONE surfaces from the bed sheets then gives her a smug smile.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS118
He flops down beside SOMEONE. Now she dives under the sheets.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS119
He makes an Oh-face.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS120
SOMEONE emerges from the
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS121
She kisses him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS122
They flop down beside each other.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS123
Now at the GQ offices, SOMEONE compares to cover mockups, one featuring SOMEONE, the other President Obama.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS124
SOMEONE goes to a waiting area where SOMEONE sits.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS125
They greet each other with a
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS126
Now the two stroll past artists.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS127
Central Park, each avoiding the others' gaze.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS128
SOMEONE gestures for her
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS129
An artist holds up a sketchpad. Now SOMEONE clutches a caricature of him and SOMEONE, as they burst into her apartment, kissing passionately.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS130
They collapse on a chair.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS131
Undressing her he spots a dog tattoo.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS132
He shows his own tattoo.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS133
A series of images show SOMEONE and SOMEONE having sex on numerous occasions.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS134
Now they watch a Mets game in their underwear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS135
They high-five, slap hands, and bump chests. SOMEONE leaps into SOMEONE's arms. Later they have sex in his bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS136
Now they make out on a couch.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS137
At another point he wears his socks in the shower with her. Now she lies on top of him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS138
They chew gum as they have sex.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS139
Their legs flail awkwardly under the covers as he rolls on top of her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS140
In her bed, SOMEONE lies with her back to SOMEONE as their hips ungulate.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS141
SOMEONE totters naked to the bathroom with one hand cupped over his crotch. He leaves the door open as he steps out of view. In bed, SOMEONE puffs out a breath, then frowns.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS142
She shrugs and taps her abdomen. Looking into the bathroom, she finds SOMEONE sitting on the toilet.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS143
She starts to lie down.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS144
She sits up again.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS145
The doorway shows one of SOMEONE's legs jerking upward.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS146
He leans over awkwardly, bracing a hand on the bathtub.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS147
He finishes and returns to the bedroom.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS148
He dashes bare ass back into the bathroom. Now he stretches his legs.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS149
A naked SOMEONE joins him in bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS150
She grins and they start to have sex. An older woman saunters in.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS151
She hugs SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS152
She eyes SOMEONE's crotch.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS153
SOMEONE leaves the room.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS154
He carries her shoes past the
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS155
Now SOMEONE plays basketball.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS156
He passes the ball high and SOMEONE jams it into the hoop for a slam-dunk.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS157
Later he dribbles and passes to SOMEONE who shoots and scores.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS158
Later they sit at a SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS159
SOMEONE leaps over a railing, separating the peer from the water. SOMEONE dashes over and finds him in a motor boat.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS160
SOMEONE drily lowers his
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS161
Grinning SOMEONE puts on sunglasses then speeds of across the water. Now in her living room, SOMEONE sits on the floor in front of her mother, who arranges her hair into a chaotic mass of thick braids as they drink wine.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS162
She joins SOMEONE on the sofa.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS163
Her mother hugs her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS164
SOMEONE eyes her hair in a mirror.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS165
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE remove their jewelry as they lie in his bed in their underwear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS166
Her gaze grows pensive as her
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS167
some friend leans over her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS168
They pick through clothes, strewn about the room.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS169
Now in Central Park they carry sandwiches
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS170
Bethesda fountain.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS171
He hands SOMEONE his sandwich. She looks on as he approaches the beauty.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS172
SOMEONE rolls her eyes and looks away. SOMEONE shakes the beauty's hand.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS173
SOMEONE smiles and spreads her arms as he rejoins her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS174
He knocks the sandwich out of her hand. Later.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS175
She heads over.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS176
She pauses to shoot SOMEONE a glare before reaching the stranger.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS177
He waves cordially at her friend.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS178
SOMEONE looks around then waves back.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS179
She rejoins her friend.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS180
They high-five.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS182
On her date. He mimes surgery.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS183
He pretends to peek under the patient's sheet. A waitress brings the check.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS184
SOMEONE covers his eyes with her hands, then removes them.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS186
SOMEONE lays a sympathetic hand on SOMEONE's.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS187
Now a lunch date.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS188
She gets a text from SOMEONE. It reads, How's it going with Stares at Trees? @ GQ.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS189
SOMEONE gets a photo message showing SOMEONE with SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS190
Now SOMEONE makes out with SOMEONE on her couch. She falls back and smiles at him, meaningfully.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS191
He moves in for another kiss. SOMEONE lies back and he leans over her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS192
She switches off a lamp.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS194
A woman snarls amorously in his ear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS195
In short shorts she straddles his leg.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS196
As SOMEONE picks up his cell phone, his date lifts his arm, smells his armpit and licks his tricep. SOMEONE puts the phone to his ear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS197
She grins, licks her fingertip, and strokes his ear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS198
The woman plants kisses down his lifted arms toward his armpit. Moving his sleeve aside she sniffs deeply.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS199
She exhales in SOMEONE's face. He raises a finger, gesturing for her to pause. She demurely backs off.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS200
The woman runs her fingers through his hair as he ends the call.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS201
She takes SOMEONE's hands and pounds them against her chest.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS202
Now sunlight shines on SOMEONE's hair as she sleeps, spooning with SOMEONE on her sofa. She wakes and gets up groggily. Clad in a T-shirt and panties, she digs behind a sofa cushion, pulls out her cellphone. The display shows SOMEONE's photo and she
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS203
She finds SOMEONE conked out on her bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS204
SOMEONE pulls on cut-off jeans shorts.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS205
With a bra in one hand, she open a door and glances at him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS207
As she shuts the door he stirs and stretches.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS208
Now SOMEONE arrives on the sidewalk.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS209
SOMEONE buys coffees.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS210
SOMEONE spies SOMEONE on the move, buttoning his shirt.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS211
She jogs over with the coffees.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS212
She drops his coffee in a trash bin, then marches off drinking her own. SOMEONE stares after her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS213
He goes. Later she visits SOMEONE as he packs for his trip.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS214
SOMEONE presents a large graphic art canvas, featuring a rider on a horse. In one corner stenciled letters follow the @ symbol with ftail.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS215
SOMEONE glares, then paddles her feet on the bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS216
He grabs her ankles. Later SOMEONE arrives home with the painting.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS217
She sets it down and crosses her home.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS218
Heading back through the kitchen she spots a hand scrawled note posted on the fridge. It reads, SOMEONE, sorry, back to Cleveland with Lombard Victor, xoxo, love mom. SOMEONE digs her cellphone from her bag and photographs the note. On his way to a cab, SOMEONE receives the photo.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS219
Now beyond Griffith Observatory's Hilltop, downtown L. A. spans the horizon. An aerial view glides over rows of houses, boats in a marina, and a freeway interchange. SOMEONE occupies a window seat on a plane, SOMEONE's on the aisle.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS220
Two young girls in front of them look at SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS221
They turn away. Now we float over Hollywood, then track a car on a meandering frontage road boarded by luxury homes. We arrive at an upscale Oceanside neighborhood.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS222
SOMEONE gets their bags.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS223
They enter a friendly stylish home where open double doors reveal a beachfront patio.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS224
They go out to the patio.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS225
He hugs a boy in a tuxedo.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS226
SOMEONE produces a flame from his fingertips.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS227
His sleeve bursts into flames. SOMEONE and SOMEONE remove his jacket.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS228
A tall blond woman arrives.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS229
SOMEONE high-fives them and goes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS230
She lifts him in a hug.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS232
by the ocean, SOMEONE kisses her father's cheek.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS233
As his father goes inside in his shirt and skivvies, SOMEONE shoots a look at SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS234
SOMEONE escorts SOMEONE down to the beach and SOMEONE goes inside. Later the two friends throw stones at the curling waves, then trot off over the sand. At night, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on the patio, looking through a photo album. A fire burns in a nearby sandpit.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS236
SOMEONE goes inside.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS237
Later, SOMEONE checks on SOMEONE who reads in bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS238
He unties his bathrobe.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS239
He peels it back.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS241
Everyday math for dummies. Now the friends drink wine and dance around the room. Later SOMEONE kneels on the bed and swigs from the bottle. Later still, as he snoozes, she dips his hand in a glass of wine, then hides. He wakes and rushes out, holding his crotch. As he returns she pops up.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS242
Now they lounge in bed, barefoot.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS244
She catches SOMEONE smiling fondly at her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS245
He shyly zips his
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS246
SOMEONE gives a wry, knowing smirk, and sets his wine aside. Facing SOMEONE again, he finds her staring longingly at him. Holding his gaze, she leans in, lays a hand on his chest and plants a tender kiss on his lips. SOMEONE kisses her back then gives a
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS247
Her lips coyly brush his.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS248
Cradling his head in her hand, she draws his mouth to hers again. SOMEONE's hand slides down his chest.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS249
SOMEONE slips her hand beneath his robe. She pushes it open, caressing his chest and looks up at him coyly.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS250
They lock gazes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS251
Playful smiles fade.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS252
SOMEONE leans close, bringing her lips to him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS253
SOMEONE's hand brushes under her hair and his gentle kisses grow more impassioned.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS254
Later he lies on top of her as their mouths meet in a series of light caresses.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS255
With SOMEONE between her legs SOMEONE brings one leg toward her chest.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS256
Now he rests a hand on her heaving chest as he plants kisses along her thigh.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS257
Later they lie beneath the sheets as they kiss with mounting intensity. As SOMEONE lies on his back, SOMEONE plants a row of kisses down his abdomen. His hand caresses her back.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS258
Now the two gaze into each other’s eyes emotionally as their lips brush. Later SOMEONE lies on top of SOMEONE, regarding him with a tender smile.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS259
He draws her into a kiss and their interlocked hands drift off the mattress.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS260
Later, SOMEONE's leg pokes out from under a sheet.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS261
SOMEONE's arm lies draped across his stomach, her hand to his, as she sleeps with her
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS262
SOMEONE slumbers.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS263
In the hall, SOMEONE groggily walks into the Saw a Woman in half box.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS264
SOMEONE wakes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS265
As his sister limps down the hall, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE, who slumbers on.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS266
He gingerly removes her hand and sits up.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS267
He slips out of bed without waking her and pulls his hand.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS268
SOMEONE glimpses SOMEONE sneaking out of SOMEONE's room in his robe.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS270
In the morning, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and their dad have breakfast on the patio right in front of ocean.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS271
Mr. SOMEONE lets SOMEONE take his
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS272
SOMEONE's sleeve dispenses coffee.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS273
SOMEONE bows, then leaves. Smiling SOMEONE wipes the corner of SOMEONE's mouth. SOMEONE and Mr. SOMEONE just
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS274
He aloofly sips his coffee. SOMEONE's smile fades.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS275
Now on jet skis.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS276
The two riders cruise by floating kelp. Two dolphins swim near.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS277
At night, they all dine by a marina.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS278
He angrily pushes away from the table and stands, then trips and falls.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS279
A stranger tries to help. SOMEONE intervenes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS280
SOMEONE keeps his hands off and looks helplessly to SOMEONE. Their dad walks away.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS281
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a parting caress then hurries after her dad. SOMEONE uneasily notices diners staring.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS282
SOMEONE rubs SOMEONE's back.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS284
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hike a city overlook.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS285
The Hollywood sign stands tall downhill of them behind a fence. SOMEONE climbs the fence.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS286
He gives the cameras a thumbs up.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS287
An airborne view orbits the huge white letters. SOMEONE and SOMEONE dangle their legs from the second O.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS288
A helicopter rises in front of them.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS289
SOMEONE stares at the chopper.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS290
Later a newscast shows SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS291
They fight for the remote.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS292
Now SOMEONE lies in a long box.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS293
As SOMEONE leaves, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE enter. SOMEONE ducks completely inside the box.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS294
SOMEONE stares.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS295
SOMEONE steps out toward the beach. SOMEONE slouches then follows.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS296
Left alone, SOMEONE lifts away a top panel of the box and climbs out. She replaces the cover, glances outside and jogs out of the room in the opposite direction.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS297
Nighttime. SOMEONE and his family occupy four of the five chairs around the table.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS298
SOMEONE enters the room.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS299
SOMEONE steps over to SOMEONE.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS300
She leaves the house. SOMEONE gawks at his family and shrugs.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS301
He shakes his head and hustles after her. SOMEONE glances tentatively at their dad.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS302
SOMEONE returns to the dining nook.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS303
He retakes his seat at the untouched
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS304
spread of wine, salad, pasta, and bread. SOMEONE takes a resigned breath.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS305
SOMEONE smiles.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS306
His smile fades and his eyes grows wide.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS307
In New York City, morning sunlight washes across the horizon of buildings. In an airport concourse, SOMEONE walks sadly within the flow of travelers. Later she enters her apartment.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS308
She checks her cellphone. A text from SOMEONE reads, Get home okay? She exits the screen and puts down the phone. Now at GQ SOMEONE works at his desk. SOMEONE arrives in his open doorway.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS309
In another office, SOMEONE reads up on Chelsie Shallenburger on her laptop.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS310
An IM comes in from her mom. So sorry I bailed last weekend, can I please come back?
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS311
SOMEONE sends a cell call from SOMEONE to her voicemail.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS312
Now SOMEONE and her mom play the table
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS313
Her mother sees SOMEONE's face on SOMEONE's cell display.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS314
SOMEONE ignores the call.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS315
SOMEONE gives her daughter an unassuming glance and plods away with her drink.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS316
SOMEONE picks up a game controller.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS317
She talks into it like a microphone.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS318
Now on a busy sidewalk, SOMEONE tries calling.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS319
The glass face of his smart phone reflects
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS320
A steeple and high-rise behind him. He turns to look at the actual structures. Now SOMEONE peers out from the rooftop overlooking Manhattan. SOMEONE joins her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS321
As SOMEONE strides away, SOMEONE
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS322
nonplussed in the stark sunlight.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS323
A nearby security guard sees
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS324
At night, SOMEONE cries as she crosses a street.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS325
Now the SOMEONE and SOMEONE movie plays on SOMEONE's TV.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS326
SOMEONE swigs a beer watching their screen kiss.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS329
Now SOMEONE gets a call from the office.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS330
She hangs up and speed dials a number
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS331
She hangs up and strides out of the lady's room. Later at GQ, SOMEONE marches over to SOMEONE's office. He's not there.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS332
She indicates her nose.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS333
At the photo shoot.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS334
Male models pose with sports items held in front of their flesh colored jockstraps.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS335
Topless females join them.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS336
He takes SOMEONE aside.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS337
As she leaves, SOMEONE frowns to himself. SOMEONE directs a Caucasian male model.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS338
An Asian male model spreads his arms as the other man holds him horizontally.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS339
That night, SOMEONE walks into his kitchen, throws down his bag and turns on the lights. He gets a beer from his windowed refrigerator. As he goes to open it, he notices the note he received with the gift basket of sheets. SOMEONE, welcome to NYC. In case you shit the bed.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS342
SOMEONE faces his reflection in a window.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS343
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in Central Park together.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS344
Sitting side-by-side on a boulder, they hug.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS345
Now SOMEONE waits at the airport.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS346
Through a wall of windows he watches his dad get pushed up a boarding ramp in a wheel chair. SOMEONE follows and meets them at the gate.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS348
He approaches a hostess at the airport restaurant.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS349
SOMEONE turns away and finds his father gone.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS350
Returning to the hostess stand he peers inside the crowded restaurant, then proceeds inside.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS351
He finds his father hanging his trousers over a railing, then sitting down at an empty table in his shirt, jacket, and boxers. SOMEONE frowns. As Mr. SOMEONE casually opens a menu, his son trudges over.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS352
SOMEONE takes a heavy breath. Patrons at the nearby tables begin to stare. A man and woman trade a sober look. Standing frozen to the spot, SOMEONE narrows his eyes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS353
He removes his shoes, pulls out a chair at the table, and takes off his own pants.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS354
Later the father and son eat lunch together in their boxers. Mr. SOMEONE notices a young woman using her cellphone outside the restaurant.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS355
She walks away obliviously.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS356
As the other patrons look over at Mr. SOMEONE again, he lowers his befuddled gaze. SOMEONE studies him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS357
Mr. SOMEONE snaps out of his reverie and takes a few deeps breaths.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS358
He gestures to his head.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS359
He sees SOMEONE's somber face.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS360
His son hangs his head. Mr. SOMEONE stares at him with a knitted brow.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS361
Now SOMEONE uses his phone.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS362
His dad bumps into SOMEONE and drops his bag.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS363
SOMEONE bumps into him.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS364
He indicates SOMEONE,then himself.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS366
He tucks a loose lock of hair behind Shaun's ear.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS367
Now traffic comes to a standstill where seven lanes merge into two.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS368
SOMEONE sends a text message.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS369
Now he and his dad speed across the Hudson river with SOMEONE in his boat.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS370
SOMEONE makes a phone call on his cell.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS371
That night in his apartment he gives his father his business card.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS372
He eyes a copy of GQ.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS373
He passes a guy in the kitchen.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS374
Akron, central  terminal.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS375
The bustling crowd around SOMEONE suddenly stops and dances.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS376
In her apartment her mother smiles.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS377
SOMEONE looks at the stairs and sees SOMEONE standing there. He shrugs at her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS378
The people in the flash mob stop their frenetic jumping and square off.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS379
SOMEONE mouths the lyrics.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS380
He beams. The flash mob performs a choreographed routine.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS381
Watching the dancers twirl their partners all around her, SOMEONE allows an emotional smile. SOMEONE stands watching her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS382
He comes down from the stairs and walks closer to her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS383
He takes her hand and leads her to a balcony, overlooking the ballroom dancing flash mob.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS384
He kneels before her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS385
He stands facing her.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS386
The flash mob freezes mid dance.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS387
He cuts her off with a deep, passionate kiss and lifts her off her feet while the performers remain perfectly still below them. With their lips still pressed together, SOMEONE opens her eyes and smiles.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS388
The members of the flash mob abruptly disburse as if they're just commuters going about their business.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS389
SOMEONE wipes tears from her big almond shaped eyes.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS390
Outside, a horse drawn carriage waits at the curb.
FRIENDS_WITH_BENEFITS_DVS391
SOMEONE and SOMEONE cross the street to Pershing Square Central Cafe and have their date.