Sitting across from them, a younger inmate glances up. The two men dig through large spools of white thread. They each pull out a gun and using the spools to conceal them, pass them to the young inmate and man sitting next to him. They stealthily tuck the weapons in their pants. From the same box, the older inmate and the sandy-haired man retrieve guns of their own. Crossing between two rows of workbenches, the sandy-haired man drops a load of shirts.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS20
The guards. The younger inmate punches another guard in his chest.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS21
As the older inmate punches punches another guard in the gut.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS24
Another guard at a door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS25
SOMEONE leaves.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS26
SOMEONE opens the steel door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS27
SOMEONE shuts the door behind him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS28
Outside, SOMEONE leaves the metal gate behind and crosses the open ground toward the sedan. He glances back to the lookout turret.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS31
He reaches for the younger inmate's gun. The younger inmate shoots him, which captures the rest of the room's attention. Outside, SOMEONE walks backward 20 yards from the gate. Inside, the criminals run out, leaving their hostages behind.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS33
getaway car, another guard fires a rifle.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS34
Shot in the back, SOMEONE collapses.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS35
Standing on the running board he sticks to his arm as they drive away.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS36
His body dragging across the dirt, SOMEONE hangs onto SOMEONE's arm, grimacing in pain. SOMEONE struggles to keep his grip while holding on to the moving car himself. SOMEONE looks up to his old friend and grins, then his hardened face goes blank.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS37
His grip on SOMEONE's forearm gives way and the gang leader lets him go. SOMEONE's body slides to a stop in the dirt as the car drives off leaving a cloud of dust behind.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS39
SOMEONE lingers for a moment, then climbs into the back of the moving sedan. As the sandy-haired escapee shuts the door, SOMEONE puts a handgun to SOMEONE's neck.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS40
SOMEONE drives, sitting next to the younger escapee.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS41
SOMEONE lowers his handgun, then punches SOMEONE in the face a couple of times.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS42
Out of the moving vehicle. SOMEONE lands
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS43
face down in the grass. SOMEONE closes the sedan's door and sits back in his seat next to the sandy-haired SOMEONE. Gathering himself, he sniffs, flaring his nostrils. Then stares forward with a steely gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS44
SOMEONE peers out the smeared windshield with a solemn expression. Now, SOMEONE stands below an overcast sky. Strands of his greasy black hair hang over his forehead. His gaze drifts to a road which cuts through a desolate field toward the flat horizon. In a farmhouse, gang members change clothes while eating. A woman wraps food in newspapers and brings it over to their table.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS45
SOMEONE buttons up next to another escapee.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS46
SOMEONE puts out a cigarette.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS47
Outside, SOMEONE walks alone. Without his overcoat, he wears a black vest and a leather gun holster. The woman stops him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS48
They hold eye contact, and she lets go. As SOMEONE turns and walks away from the farmhouse, the woman continues to gaze after him. A little boy in overalls comes up and takes her hand. Together, they wander a few steps without taking their eyes off of him. Now in the car as SOMEONE drives, SOMEONE looks back at SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS49
He faces forward and glances at SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS50
Now, a man in a blue suit hurries through lush green woods with a SOMEONE gun. He trips, then climbs to his feet and runs on. A clean-cut man wearing suspenders swiftly moves after him toting a rifle. A group of armed lawmen follow behind, charging up a hill.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS51
Races downhill into an apple orchard.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS52
Flyod runs backwards firing wildly.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS53
The lawman's shot misses and Floyd runs off.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS54
The trigger. Floyd sprints through the trees.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS55
The shot blasts through Floyd's belly and he flops on the grass. The shooter gazes.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS56
Floyd takes out a pistol which the lawman kicks out of his hand. He aims his rifle at the wounded outlaw who lies on his back.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS60
As the other looks out the window.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS61
A large man in suspenders peers through the blinds. He turns away from the window and hurries out of the room.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS62
Outside, SOMEONE and his men step out of their car.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS63
As they approach the house, a young blonde woman greets them.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS64
He grins and gives the blonde a kiss.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS65
They head inside.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS66
Later in a garage, SOMEONE sits across from a gunsmith as he disassembles a SOMEONE gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS67
Trigger handle and pulls out a coil.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS68
Outside a window behind the gunsmith, two cars arrive.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS69
SOMEONE steps out of the safe house. SOMEONE glances at the door where the blonde nods to him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS70
He gets up and leaves the garage. As he crosses to the house, SOMEONE tosses a set of keys to SOMEONE who joins SOMEONE to see the new car.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS71
Inside, SOMEONE enters the kitchen.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS72
A man leans against the refrigerator. SOMEONE washes his hands. A woman smokes at the table.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS73
SOMEONE hands him a stuffed envelope.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS74
He goes around the table. He kisses her cheek.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS75
SOMEONE leaves the kitchen. Now, three men in fedoras and overcoats ascend a wide staircase separated from each other by two center railings. Reaching the top, SOMEONE stops, scanning a huge bank with angular walls lined with tellers. His two cohorts split off. SOMEONE approaches a guard.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS76
He bashes his face.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS77
Parades the bank president around the counter and across the floor. They pass a trembling customer.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS78
SOMEONE pushes the president forward to a metal gate.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS79
Men collects cash from a teller.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS80
Sorts keys. SOMEONE smacks him in the head with his pistol and points it.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS82
SOMEONE hops up on the counter, aiming his machine gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS83
Outside, Homer discretely holds a rifle at his side. He sees an arriving police car and backs into a recess by a set of double doors. He knocks with the butt of his rifle.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS84
Inside the bank, SOMEONE waits as the president fills a sack with money from the safe. In a getaway car, SOMEONE checks the time on a pocket watch, then drives.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS85
And run across the street toward the bank.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS86
Inside, SOMEONE pushes the president forward. He notice.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS87
And change set out on the counter, and faces the customer it belongs to.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS88
As shield and fires.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS89
Inside, a young female teller hurries to SOMEONE and they head back down the stairs.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS90
Another police car arrives down the block.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS91
In his car as the robbers exit with four hostages. Down the road, lawmen aim rifles over the car's hood. SOMEONE and his men, using their hostages as shields, cross to the getaway car. SOMEONE aims at the police over the president's shoulder.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS92
Officer fires first.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS93
Coats flap in the breeze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS94
The car comes to a stop under a bridge.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS95
SOMEONE faces Homer's hostage.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS96
Two hostages run off. SOMEONE notices his young hostage shivering. He wraps his overcoat around her and guides her into the backseat. SOMEONE drives off.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS97
The car heads down a dirt road leading toward a forest.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS98
Tie the president and the young teller to a tree.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS99
The bank robbers leave their hostages and stride out of the trees.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS100
They get in and drive.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS102
Now in a marble hearing room, a square-jawed man faces a committee.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS104
He tilts his ear toward the chairman.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS105
The mustached senator looks Director Hoover in the eye.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS106
Hoover whispers to a bespectacled man.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS107
out with the bespectacled Suydam and a slender young man. As they walk down a hall, Suydam takes notes.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS108
Hoover looks to his young associate.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS109
Now, a fedora sits on a burgundy leather couch by SOMEONE who gazes off thoughtfully. As Hoover exits a nearby office, SOMEONE stands.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS110
They cross an FBI bullpen.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS111
The men step onto a sunny veranda where reporters gather. Hoover faces a microphone.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS112
Hoover motions for SOMEONE to take his place at the mic.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS113
He checks his watch and look.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS114
Rubbing the tip of his nose, he shifts his gaze to the dance floor where a brunette in a red dress dances with a man.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS115
Fixed on her. His attention shifts as a scrawny guy with glasses approaches. SOMEONE stands and shakes his hand.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS116
The scrawny SOMEONE takes a seat beside SOMEONE and leans close.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS120
SOMEONE nods and heads off.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS121
SOMEONE and Homer swagger off. SOMEONE leans toward SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS122
SOMEONE eyes the brunette in the red dress as she returns to her table.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS123
SOMEONE leads a young woman to SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS124
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE and Veronica as they stroll away, leaving SOMEONE alone. He stares at the brunette in the red dress who laughs and beams. The gang leader sips his drink and stands, keeping his eyes locked on the exotic woman. He strides resolutely through the crowd and halts just behind her, and leans onto her chair. She looks up at him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS125
He gives his head a stunned shake.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS126
Her bright red lips smile coyly.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS127
She grins at the other women seated at her table, then SOMEONE off with SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS128
He warily locks eyes with her, then looks away.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS129
Leads the way to the dance floor.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS130
He takes her hand and she places her other hand on his shoulder. They sway together.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS131
SOMEONE smiles.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS132
SOMEONE gazes off shyly, then finds her lovely face.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS133
SOMEONE stares back defiantly.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS134
Her dark eyes probe his as they sway with the music. She allows a faint smile.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS135
SOMEONE summons up a breath and arches his brows.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS136
Her smile broadens.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS139
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stride through the club's foyer.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS141
A gust of wind, SOMEONE turns her to face him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS142
Her coat over her shoulders.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS143
And continues down the sidewalk with his jacket and arm around her.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS144
Later in an elegant restaurant, SOMEONE uneasily scans her surroundings, then looks to SOMEONE. She smiles, the glances at a female diner. The snobbish woman gives her the eye.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS145
SOMEONE's smile briefly falters.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS146
He flashes an amused smile and sits back.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS147
SOMEONE breaks off, eyeing another table.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS148
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lock gazes.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS149
A faint smile curls the corners of her lips.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS150
SOMEONE stands and holds her chair as she gets up, then guides her through the restaurant with a hand at her back. Now, they face a coat check counter. At a bar, a stocky man with slick back hair notices them.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS151
SOMEONE glances at the man over his shoulder, then leans toward SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS152
He steps away. SOMEONE irritably shifts her gaze, then glares at him and yanks on her coat.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS153
She storms out.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS154
The two men shake hands.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS155
SOMEONE, a lean man with dark, sleek hair and a handlebar mustache slouches as he eats. A short husky man with SOMEONE skin and a toothbrush mustache approaches SOMEONE. They shake hands.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS158
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE swaps looks with Gilbert, then shoves through a revolving door. Outside, he finds only a wealthy young couple.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS159
The gang leader glances around the sidewalk.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS161
On SOMEONE' Pierce-Arrow.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS162
FBI field office, a chubby agent shows a jacket.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS163
SOMEONE paces, then addresses his assembled task force.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS164
He faces a secretary.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS165
SOMEONE gazes out a window at a neighboring high-rise, then faces his men.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS166
One agent briefly drops his gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS167
Now at a telephone exchange with SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS168
He plays a 78 record.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS169
Nighttime, SOMEONE strides past a bright city park. Later, he marches through a crowd
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS170
She notices SOMEONE as a male guest holds out his coat to her.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS172
Yanking the man's wrist over the counter, SOMEONE snatches his claim ticket. SOMEONE stares as he finds the man's coat. The exotic beauty drops her gaze and SOMEONE throws the coat at its owner.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS173
He gets SOMEONE's coat.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS174
He holds her coat open. SOMEONE eyes it, then looks to a staring co-worker.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS175
With a coy smirk, she steps out from behind the counter and slips into her coat. Now in an apartment, a hand drops a rabbit's foot key chain by a tabletop sculpture of two racing greyhounds. SOMEONE leads SOMEONE down a hall into a luxurious living room. As she takes in the space, he sets a chair near a sofa and looks to her.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS176
SOMEONE joins him, slipping off her coat.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS177
SOMEONE sets a simple cardboard box on the coffee table.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS178
SOMEONE complies and looks around with a faint smile.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS179
Behind her, SOMEONE appears in his undershirt and leans through an open-air interior window. He gets a couple of glasses from a counter, then saunters off with two women. SOMEONE sits facing SOMEONE and lays his hand on the large box. The exotic beauty eyes it coolly.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS180
SOMEONE allows a subdued smile then shifts boyishly in his seat. SOMEONE removes the lid, finding forest green tissue paper over the contents. Folding back the layer, she finds a camel hair coat with a thick fur collar. SOMEONE lifts the present from its box, staring at it. She swallows, then raises her tender gaze to meet SOMEONE's.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS181
Her full lips curl into a smile and the crime boss grins. They gaze into each other's eyes.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS182
Later on a bed, they smother each other with kisses.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS184
Her head, revealing a silvery blue slip, then leans over on top of SOMEONE. Glimpses of SOMEONE thrusting into SOMEONE from behind interspersed with their nuzzling face-to-face.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS185
A recent flashback shows them writhing ecstatically.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS186
Another flash shows SOMEONE kiss her mouth. His face withdraws down her chest. Later as they cuddle, they share a warm smile. Later still, SOMEONE strolls in her slip to a window seat. Open suitcases occupy every inch, filled to the brim with neatly packed clothes. SOMEONE caresses their contents, then rejoins SOMEONE in bed.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS187
She lays her head on his shoulder. Rolling over to face her, he strokes her cheek and neck.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS188
His thumb gently rubs her graceful jawline.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS189
His gaze pours over her face and he grins.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS190
SOMEONE gazes dreamily at him and he gives her another smile.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS191
His thumb caresses her cheek in a gently rhythm.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS192
He flashes a puckish grin.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS194
To his ear and a handheld mic at his lips.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS195
Later, the Pierce-Arrow pulls up to a curb. SOMEONE drives with SOMEONE at his side. Two other G-Men approach the luxury car.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS196
One of the street agents looks to his young partner who bows his head.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS197
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS198
He points, then gets out and faces the young G-Man.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS199
SOMEONE leads him across the street to a tawny white apartment building. Inside, they enter a long, dim hallway. SOMEONE leads Agent Barton to a door, then readies his hand on his gun. We watch the agents from afar as they prepare, the lengthy corridor dwarfing their trench-coated forms. SOMEONE lifts his knuckles to the door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS200
It opens, revealing a young woman in a demure house dress, her strawberry blonde hair frames her face in a curly SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS201
SOMEONE steps toward the doorway.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS202
As he enters, Barton lingers in the hall. At a table, a stout man eats.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS203
The baby-faced man nods.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS204
She steps away.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS205
Returning, the woman shows off her shoes.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS206
She holds out the open wallet as well. SOMEONE eyes it and gives a nod.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS207
SOMEONE leaves, shutting the door. The woman looks wearily to the stout gentleman at the dining table. Now, SOMEONE and Barton enter a stairwell.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS208
SOMEONE hurries downstairs. Rushing from the building, he runs across the street to Agent SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS209
In the stairwell, Barton peers through a window in the door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS210
Squinting, he steps into the hallway and lets the door swing shut behind him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS211
From the stairwell, our gaze lingers on the door, then drifts over to a set of elevators.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS212
Opens, revealing a tall man with rugged features.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS213
He steps off and heads for the door. In the hallway,
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS214
Barton sees the rugged man behind him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS216
The stranger stops.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS217
Behind Barton, a stout, baby-faced man steps into the hall and shoots him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS218
G-Man lurches and falls. In the street, SOMEONE turns. The shooter and his rugged associate leave.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS219
SOMEONE races toward the building. SOMEONE whips out his gun and peers at a car parked in the alley. Inside, SOMEONE enters the hallway and raises his gun. He advances cautiously.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS220
SOMEONE stops, looking down.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS221
Glancing warily ahead, he crouches. SOMEONE' mouth drops open as he stares downward. On the floor, a blood pool spreads beneath Barton. As the wounded man twitches feebly, SOMEONE watches with a clenched jaw. His expression grows solemn and he glares down the hall. He rises, leaving a lifeless Barton. Outside, SOMEONE sees two men hurrying down the alley steps. The baby-faced shooter raises a SOMEONE gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS222
pulling out. He takes cover behind a garden plant.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS223
As the two criminals get into the parked car.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS224
a panic Maulin leans out an open window.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS225
Outside, two agents pull their car up as their superior exits the building.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS226
SOMEONE stops, staring with his mouth agape.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS227
They agent shifts his rueful gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS228
With a slow, deliberate stride, SOMEONE steps closer to his man.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS229
His frustrated gaze scans the agents, his breath puffing visibly in the night air. He steps away.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS230
Daytime, a bank's door is open and three men in long coats enter. Our gaze drifts up to find SOMEONE between SOMEONE and a heavyset thug. The two leaner men split off together. SOMEONE encounters a guard, sucker punches him, and bangs his head against the counter. Without breaking his stride, SOMEONE draws a gun in each hand.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS232
The bankers all obey.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS233
SOMEONE shifts his aim.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS234
A banker leads SOMEONE to a vault.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS235
As Hoover talks on the phone.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS236
Hoover shifts his resentful gaze and works his jaw.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS237
In Chicago, SOMEONE grimly lowers the phone and shifts his troubled gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS239
Features disembarks flanked by two associates. He peers down the platform
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS240
The three newcomers make their way down the platform, suitcases in hand.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS241
Now, travelers mill about on a vast terminal's marble floors. The three arriving.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS242
pause taking in their surroundings. Now, at a shoeshine stand.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS243
Older newcomer takes a seat, SOMEONE approaches.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS244
SOMEONE summons a breath, squinting in the sunlight.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS245
SOMEONE waves at SOMEONE across the corral.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS246
SOMEONE glances around. Later, SOMEONE plops into a chair in the grandstand. SOMEONE sits beside him. One row down, SOMEONE leans closer.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS249
glares at him, then drops her gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS250
SOMEONE joins him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS251
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE stares off.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS252
SOMEONE frowns, shifts in his seat, and squarely faces SOMEONE. She hangs her head.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS253
SOMEONE allows a thoughtful smile. Leaning forward, she cups the back of SOMEONE's head in her hand and presses her lips to his. He pulls away.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS255
Bush grows by a burrowed cactus and a healthy saguaro. Across the street, a sign on a large brick building reads Hotel Congress. SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter the lobby and stroll toward the front desk. A balding clerk faces them.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS256
The clerk hands SOMEONE a pen, and the gang leader signs a guest register.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS257
SOMEONE notices a True Detective magazine in a rack.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS258
SOMEONE picks up a suitcase and heads off with SOMEONE. Now, in a hotel room, he opens the suitcase, takes out his SOMEONE gun, and cocks it. Later, he opens a window and pulls the sheer curtains closed. The gang leader takes off his suit coat and handgun, then ambles to a set of closed double doors. Pushing one open, he peeks into a bathroom. SOMEONE sits nude in the tub. As he opens the door all the way, she seductively slides her hands up the porcelain, out of the water, then lifts one shapely leg and caresses the tub's rim with her foot.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS259
She runs her toes along a soap dish.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS260
As Johnny turns back to the bedroom, the door bursts open. The balding man from the front desk leads other men in and clouts SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS261
Handcuffs and SOMEONE runs out wearing a towel.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS263
The door showing an isolated cell block. Inside, the officers lock SOMEONE inside a holding cell and remove his handcuffs through the bars.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS264
Wearing cowboy hats, the officer's head out. SOMEONE massages his wrists, gazing off. He paces forward and leans tensely on a rail attaching the cell bars one to the next. Now, the balding undercover officer knocks on the cell block door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS265
In his cell, SOMEONE flips through a magazine. He looks up.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS266
The balding officer leads SOMEONE into the cell block. Other lawmen observe from a side table. Wearing a crisp suit.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS267
SOMEONE's cell and the gang leader sets down his magazine.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS268
He stands and ambles toward the bars.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS269
The two men size each other up. SOMEONE curiously cocks his head and SOMEONE stares at him calmly.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS270
The other officers and agents watch closely.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS271
SOMEONE's eyes flit up and down the stoic G-Man.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS272
SOMEONE shakes his head, his brow knit.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS273
Blinking thoughtfully, SOMEONE allows a faint smile. SOMEONE straightens to his full height.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS274
Chewing some gum, the criminal gives a cocky smile.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS275
SOMEONE pauses on his way out and faces SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS276
Sunlight outlines SOMEONE' clean-shaven face.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS277
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE from inside his cell.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS278
Both men walk with their hands in their pockets. His back to SOMEONE, SOMEONE barely slows his leisurely stride and leaves with his agents. The balding officer stays behind.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS279
SOMEONE chews his gum.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS280
Nighttime, a three-propeller plane cruises through the sky,
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS283
Journalists crank movie cameras. A black-and-white view through one shows a police officer.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS284
SOMEONE's plane moves closer. Other journalists wait with flashbulb cameras and three lawmen hold rifles.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS286
Another flare goes up.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS287
Wind whips at two trench-coated lawmen.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS293
On motorbikes accompany.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS294
Inside the prisoner's car, SOMEONE slouches, his head bobbing.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS295
Seated between two of his captors, SOMEONE keeps his pensive gaze aimed downward.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS296
along a dim street.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS297
SOMEONE's car, the criminal stares off glumly, then smiles out the window.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS300
Woman paces in an office. She strides out to the crowd.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS301
As arriving lawmen lead SOMEONE inside, cameras flash. The robber skeptically furrows his brow.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS302
A chubby lawyer puts an arm around SOMEONE who rests an elbow on the man's shoulder.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS303
The female sheriff glowers.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS304
SOMEONE shrugs his brows.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS306
The lawyer nonchalantly follows a second guard farther ahead. Now, a hulking black inmate strides past a row of cells and enters a common room where SOMEONE reads a newspaper. The hulking man leans to SOMEONE's ear.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS307
SOMEONE scowls toward his cell, then heads over. The hulking inmate positions himself just outside.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS308
He waves two prisoners on. Now, SOMEONE faces the bars in the back of his cell. The lawyer, SOMEONE, sits in a corridor on the other side.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS311
sits back and heaves a misty sigh in the cold air.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS312
Now in a courtroom, SOMEONE sits at a council bench.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS313
A deputy escorts SOMEONE in in shackles.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS314
The judge folds his hands thoughtfully.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS315
SOMEONE turns away with a humorless look.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS316
As the crowd rises, SOMEONE winks at SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS317
The lawyer steps away. As the deputy approaches, SOMEONE lowers his gaze. Later outside the jail, a cluster of National Guards stand watch by a waist-high wall of sandbags. Inside, the prisoner's mill about the common room. As a few deputies and guards work in a front office, a janitor enters. Later, he hangs up his coat. A guard unlocks a barred door, then raises his baton to a second metal door just inside.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS318
The guard looks through a peephole then unlocks the door for the janitor. Carrying a mop and bucket, he crosses a hallway and waits for another guard to open the door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS319
another barred door. In the common room, SOMEONE tilts his head and clenches his jaw.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS320
The janitor enters and the guard shuts the door behind him. SOMEONE coolly glances over his shoulder.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS321
The janitor sets down his supplies and heads over.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS324
SOMEONE peeks through the bars.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS327
SOMEONE pokes Bryant with the gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS328
Still restraints SOMEONE. SOMEONE eyes the door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS330
The metal door. The guard on the other side peeks through then unlocks it. As he opens the door, SOMEONE shoves him into Max and his accomplice hits Bryant with his pipe. SOMEONE rushes into the office and holds his gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS332
As SOMEONE jams the barrel of his gun into the warden's neck, the warden spins the dial on a safe door. SOMEONE steps into the closet-sized safe, discards his fake, waxy gun, and grabs a pistol from the wall. He steps out with a rifle and hands a machine gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS333
The warden glances back as the accomplice leads him away. SOMEONE grabs a hat and coat from a nearby rack.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS334
He puts them on and tosses a jacket to the other inmate who grabs a hat from the rack as he ushers the deputy out behind SOMEONE. With his rifle raised, SOMEONE cautiously opens a metal door in the hallway. His accomplice follows close behind with one hand clutching the deputy between them. They make their way into a garage where a mechanic works on a police car.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS336
He strides to the Ford V8. Outside, four officers talk to each other on a porch, their guns perched casually against their shoulders. The sleek Ford passes undetected in the alley beside them. At the front of the jailhouse, the National Guardsmen mill about by their sandbag wall. They pay no attention as the Ford trundles by and turns on to the main street.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS337
As SOMEONE drives through the town, he nervously shifts his eyes back and forth under the tipped down brim of his fedora. The jailhouse mechanic sits beside him while his accomplice rides in back with the deputy.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS338
SOMEONE notices three National Guardsmen strolling down the sidewalk. He stops for a red traffic light on a corner where more National Guardsmen stand together talking, their guns strapped over their shoulders. They glance curiously at the car, then resume their conversation.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS340
Licks his lips, his head bowed slightly.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS341
Inches his left hand toward the gun nestled in his waistband.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS342
to green and SOMEONE puts the car in gear.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS343
On to another street.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS344
SOMEONE looks at the mechanic.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS345
He shakes his head lightheartedly.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS346
Befuddled mechanic shakes his head.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS348
Youngblood grins.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS349
Elsewhere, Hoover listens on the radio and pinches the bridge of his nose.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS351
Now at her apartment, SOMEONE sits in a chair, her hands fidgeting anxiously.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS352
On and leans against a wall as she holds the receiver to her ear.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS353
At the telephone exchange, SOMEONE listens.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS354
SOMEONE clutches the phone despondently.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS355
She lowers her sad, resigned eyes.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS356
SOMEONE stands inside a phone booth with a faint, tender smile.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS357
SOMEONE removes the receiver from her ear and clutches it against the base of her neck, resting her chin on her knuckles. Outside her apartment, two men watch from inside a car concealed underneath a bridge. Later, SOMEONE sits in a car outside the apartment. SOMEONE climbs into the passenger seat and hands him a file with the transcript from SOMEONE's phone call to SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS358
Behind them, an L train glides across a bridge, its interior lights glowing in the darkness. Daytime. A tan car pulls to a stop, and SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb out. As SOMEONE heads around the corner down an icy walkway, SOMEONE steps out of the safe house.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS359
SOMEONE perches on the side of the car, his gun raised. SOMEONE emerges from the house behind SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS360
SOMEONE narrows his eyes and tilts his head.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS361
He pulls out his machine gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS364
SOMEONE gives Gilbert a hard look. Gilbert leads SOMEONE and SOMEONE upstairs.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS365
SOMEONE takes in the chalkboard-covered walls and the rows of men at desks chattering on telephones. Small overhead lights with green lampshades hang from above next to dangling clusters of phone wires. SOMEONE sits on the corner of a desk. He looks at Gilbert.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS367
Grabs him in a choke hold and aims a gun at Gilbert.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS368
He cocks his head.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS369
SOMEONE looks at Gilbert whose hand rest on his gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS370
He turns to SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS371
SOMEONE tosses the blonde man away.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS372
SOMEONE sits calmly on the edge of a desk.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS373
SOMEONE holsters his gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS374
SOMEONE knits his brow thoughtfully, then meets SOMEONE's gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS375
SOMEONE shrugs.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS376
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE, his lips curved into a frown. The mustached gangster leans in closer.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS377
SOMEONE tilts his head, his eyes narrowing as he meets SOMEONE's gaze. He turns away.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS378
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exit. Now, Hoover and SOMEONE walk down a hall.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS379
Outside, Hoover turns from SOMEONE and heads over to a group of well-dressed boys standing in two lines.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS380
They shake hands. Hoover faces the press.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS383
SOMEONE nods his head at SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS384
SOMEONE appears on screen. SOMEONE subtly covers his face.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS385
Stands and SOMEONE yanks him back into his seat.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS386
Homer looks away nervously as SOMEONE sits with a worried look, his face tilted down. The overhead light turns on, bathing the audience members' faces
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS387
The audience turns, peering at the people to the right.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS388
The audience turns again.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS389
As the audience members settle their eyes back toward the front, the lights fade down and a new story begins. A lion's head appears onscreen with the title Ethiopia across its eyes. SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS390
SOMEONE rubs his lips thoughtfully as he looks at SOMEONE and nods.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS391
He exchanges a glance with SOMEONE and they rise, grabbing their coats. A few rows ahead, Homer puts on his hat and steps into the aisle behind them. As they exit the theater, SOMEONE moves closer to SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS392
Now, people mill around a town square. A stiff wind flutters the awnings of a storefront. On the far side of the square, a policeman pulls up on a motorcycle.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS393
Outside, Homer grabs a man and holds him hostage. Inside, SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange an exasperated look.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS394
SOMEONE tosses a bag to SOMEONE. He guides the bank president.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS395
A woman joins the bank president.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS396
Gangster shield themselves with the hostages as they exit the bank. They pass Homer who waits outside by their car with his own hostage.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS397
He aims a gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS398
SOMEONE lurches forward, his eyes wide.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS399
Notices SOMEONE who lies on his stomach.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS400
With its doors still open, the car pulls out of the town square leaving the hostages lying helplessly in the street. Now, the car speeds down an empty road lined with tall evergreens that just into the pale blue sky. Golden sunlight shines on its sleek exterior, reflecting the snow-covered ground bordering the woods. SOMEONE sits in the backseat, the wind from the open windows blowing against his disheveled hair.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS401
In the front passenger seat, Homer stares distantly. Behind him, SOMEONE drinks from a flask as SOMEONE administers an injection into his shoulder wound.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS403
Warmly through the windows. As Baby Face pulls the car to a halt, SOMEONE addresses him with a frown.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS404
The four gangsters the lodge.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS405
Upstairs, Baby Face bundles cash.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS408
He preps a dressing. Homer looks on.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS409
SOMEONE unrolls a bandage and dresses SOMEONE's wound.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS410
Homer grabs his take. Baby Face picks up two cash bundles and tosses one to SOMEONE. As they both clear out of the room, Homer hangs by in the doorway.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS411
He looks to SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS412
The leader gives a nod and Homer leaves. SOMEONE remains seated at SOMEONE's side.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS413
As SOMEONE wipes his hands, SOMEONE springs restlessly to his feet.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS414
The two men share a solemn look.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS415
He holds out SOMEONE's share.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS416
SOMEONE accepts the cash, gives his brow a resigned lift, and shoots a tentative smile at SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS417
He stows the cash in his bag and leaves.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS418
Now in a medical exam room, the gangster with the eye wound pleads with two G-Men.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS420
SOMEONE courteously gestures for the doctor to step away.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS422
Back to the torture session.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS424
The gangster spits at his tormentor.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS425
The stern-faced G-Man turns gravely toward SOMEONE and nods. SOMEONE' beady eyes peer downward, deep in thought.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS426
Later, SOMEONE uses a candlestick phone.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS429
It's SOMEONE. He lies down on a modest twin bed.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS430
SOMEONE picks up his pocket watch off the nightstand, opens it, and admires a photo of SOMEONE on the inside of the cover.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS431
SOMEONE's profile grows blurry as the view focuses on the radio beyond.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS432
Now in a forest road, two motorcars douse their headlights as they creep forward and park on the dirt shoulder.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS433
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and several others in trench coats climb out of the vehicles. SOMEONE closes his door most of the way, but leaves it cracked open. The men advance.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS434
Armed with their rifles and sub machine guns, the G-Men cross the shadowy woods. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand shoulder-to-shoulder as they spot the lodge a few hundred yards off.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS435
SOMEONE looks SOMEONE in the eye.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS436
The partnered G-Men filter outward through the trees toward the lodge. Now, inside a warmly lit barroom.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS437
Outside, SOMEONE passes in and out of light as he treads forward. Toting a rifle, SOMEONE comes up on his left. Meanwhile, SOMEONE rounds past a tree. Inside, Baby Face approaches a couple eating dinner.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS438
He pats a guy on a bar stool and faces the couple.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS439
Outside, SOMEONE spies a window framing a view of two women, a tuxedoed man, and a fourth person drinking and smoking inside. As he stalks closer, the three working-class men exit the lodge.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS440
SOMEONE watches them closely from behind a tree.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS441
The workmen get into a car.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS442
Inside SOMEONE's room, a framed religious icon hangs on the wall over his bed as he rests.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS443
Outside, the car backs up. SOMEONE aims his SOMEONE gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS444
SOMEONE springs awake, grabs his SOMEONE gun, and goes to a window.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS445
In the barroom, Baby Face returns fire through a window.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS446
SOMEONE takes cover.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS447
For the car shells fires from the lawn.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS448
One man sits slack-jawed, his head lolled back trailing blood from two holes. SOMEONE stares, stunned, then opens a rear door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS451
An adjacent windows shows a gangster taking aim.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS452
He hustles through a guest room next door and butts a window with his gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS453
SOMEONE and SOMEONE escape onto a rooftop and hop down to a dark yard at the other side of the lodge. Now in the barroom.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS454
Follows Baby Face who backs up to a side door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS455
Someone splinter the door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS456
The criminal is escaping.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS457
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS458
SOMEONE heads off. As SOMEONE shoots the side door, Homer fires back.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS459
On his way to intercept the fugitive.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS460
SOMEONE and SOMEONE make their own escape.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS461
SOMEONE spots them.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS463
The agents reach a stand of twin trees and split up. Hurt takes to higher ground while SOMEONE advances on the trail.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS464
A view through the leafy canopy shows the criminals scurrying off. SOMEONE pitches his hat, sights the men, and fires.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS466
SOMEONE kneels and opens fire.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS467
Cover behind a tree and SOMEONE
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS468
does the same. SOMEONE's shots clobber the trunk shielding
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS469
SOMEONE who calmly reloads, his breath mists in the cold night air. He leans out and fires.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS471
SOMEONE scans the hillside but finds no sign of anyone. SOMEONE peers over his shoulder from his tree. SOMEONE relaxes his aim.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS472
Both men start off.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS473
SOMEONE lies low behind a tree. Now in slow motion, the criminals run along the misty overlook with SOMEONE leading the way. Agent Hurt opens fire from uphill.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS474
SOMEONE to his feet and they move on.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS475
SOMEONE resumes tracking the pair. Now, SOMEONE accost an average man standing outside a cabin.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS476
Later, SOMEONE clutches his side. SOMEONE opens the heisted car's door for him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS477
Now, Baby Face reaches an unpaved road. Headed his way in a car, SOMEONE peers ahead over the steering wheel. Baby Face turns his back to the vehicle as its glaring headlights draw closer. The fugitive waves a hand low, paces backward, and keeps his SOMEONE gun under his coat. SOMEONE stops.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS478
SOMEONE climbs out the other door. Baby Face throws him down.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS480
Baby Face tosses SOMEONE's SOMEONE gun onto the front seat and gets behind the wheel. Now, SOMEONE comes running through the forest. As SOMEONE's car drives off, SOMEONE finds his fallen partner.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS481
Lead agent doffs his hat and crouches down to his fading colleague.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS482
SOMEONE glares after the car riding steadily away.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS484
Coming car while holding up one hand. It's SOMEONE's team.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS488
Further ahead. SOMEONE fires.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS493
He arrives and riddles SOMEONE with bullets.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS495
Agent SOMEONE fires at SOMEONE empties his pistol into the man.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS497
Baby Face drops onto his back. A plume of exhaled steam jets from his nose once. SOMEONE glares over his aimed pistol.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS498
Now outside a small town pharmacy, SOMEONE returns to the heisted car. SOMEONE leans sweating and bloody in the corner of the backseat. SOMEONE pours antiseptic over SOMEONE's wounded abdomen.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS499
SOMEONE fuses with other supplies.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS500
He applies gauze to the wound.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS501
SOMEONE trains his puffy, exhausted eyes on SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS502
A feeble smile on SOMEONE's lips fades.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS503
SOMEONE slumps a little then sits back.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS504
His blood-stained hand lets go of SOMEONE's shoulder.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS505
Eyes downcast, SOMEONE stays seated by his deceased partner. He swallows, glancing at SOMEONE, and his lips give a brief irritated sneer. He gazes downward.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS506
Now in a field office, SOMEONE faces his agents.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS507
SOMEONE checks her watch then turns up a radio, windows behind her show the passing train.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS508
SOMEONE crosses the roomy rundown apartment then doubles back to a door. A woman with similar short hair comes down a staircase, hands SOMEONE a large, brown paper bag, and follows her into the apartment. As SOMEONE dons her fur-collared coat, the newcomer takes SOMEONE's seat by the radio. The woman wears a top similar to SOMEONE's. As she skims a newspaper and turns up the radio, another elevated train passes in the windows.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS509
G-Men watch the apartment.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS510
In another car, two more agents see someone in an overcoat and fedora totting a paper bag across a dark alley.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS511
The stranger ducks down a narrow passage and reaches out with a delicate hand to a brick wall. It's SOMEONE in disguise.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS512
She comes to a street on the other end. Carrying the brown paper bag, she steps off the sidewalk between parked cars and looks around in the middle of the street.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS513
A car's headlights illuminate and shine on her anxious face. Situated about a block away, the car approaches and comes to a stop.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS516
Her head on his shoulder.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS518
The agents abruptly gaze out the door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS519
SOMEONE steps forward, arms folded across his chest.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS520
In the outer office, the solemn burly agent stands with his partner. As SOMEONE gazes at them, his eyes water and he works his lips.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS521
SOMEONE listens to the radio.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS528
And lists a phone number. As an agent stands by, two female operators work an adjacent switchboard. Now outside on a moonlit shoreline, SOMEONE sits by a sleeping SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS529
Her hair hangs in her face.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS530
SOMEONE gazes at her and brushes her dark hair aside to reveal her big eyes.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS531
She briefly lowers her gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS532
She smiles.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS533
Turn in his arms.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS534
Horizon sprawls perfectly flat between the sand and black sky.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS535
Daytime. SOMEONE's car parks on a street.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS537
Street between passing vehicles.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS538
She enters the building. In the car, SOMEONE faces the side mirror and brushes his bangs off his forehead. Inside, SOMEONE passes through another doorway and SOMEONE' men grab her.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS539
Uncomfortably glances at the agents.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS540
Outside, SOMEONE waits in the car.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS541
More armed agents exit a building directly in front of him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS543
SOMEONE glares into his side view mirror, then gets out of the car.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS544
The two lovers make eye contact.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS546
SOMEONE steps forward with a pistol in hand.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS547
Burly agent pushes SOMEONE into the backseat and gets in next to her. As they drive away, SOMEONE peers through the back window seating between two agents.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS548
A shocked SOMEONE stands out in the open watching the car drive off. Several armed agents remain behind who strides around a parked car.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS550
He calmly bows his head and collects his breath.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS552
SOMEONE sits in a chair. SOMEONE stands behind him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS553
She slouches, her left cheek bruised.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS554
He grabs her chin.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS555
He flings her head to the side and stands upright. The interrogator steps out of the room.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS556
SOMEONE trembles, her right hand cuffed to the chair. She holds her knees together.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS557
In the outer office, the burly agent downs a paper cup of water and passes Doris who glares at him as he returns to the interrogation room.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS558
Now, the interrogator returns, shuts the door, and eyes SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS559
He crosses to her and grabs her chin again.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS560
He grabs her chin.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS561
He shakes her.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS562
SOMEONE's mouth hangs open and she shudders.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS563
Her lips tremble as she finds words.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS564
Office, the interrogator points to Doris.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS565
She holds a telephone at her shoulder.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS566
He puts on his jacket.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS567
Things and move out. Doris dials a telephone.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS568
Agents run up a stairwell. Standing outside an apartment door, one shoots the top and bottom hinges.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS569
Through an open window. The place is empty. The burly agent stiffens his jaw.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS570
Now back in the interrogation room, SOMEONE sits with her head down. The two agents barge in. The burly one grabs a phone book.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS571
She keeps her head down and looks directly at him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS572
As SOMEONE enters the field office, Doris approaches.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS573
In the interrogation room.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS574
She lowers her head and wipes her mouth. The interrogator glares down at her and tensely wipes his mouth. SOMEONE looks him in the eye.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS575
He sneers and winds up with his fist. SOMEONE intercepts his arm and slams him
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS577
He uncuffs SOMEONE's right arm from the chair.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS578
As she holds her wrists, SOMEONE leans over to her.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS579
He stands upright. SOMEONE presses down on the arms of the chair to get up, then stops.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS580
SOMEONE glances at the other interrogator, then lifts SOMEONE from the chair and carries her out. In the hall, the rest of the agents stand aside as he passes with the weakened woman. In the interrogation room, SOMEONE lowers his arm from the burly agent's throat and leaves. Now, SOMEONE nods to Doris.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS581
In the interrogation room, the burly agent stays put beside the open door out of the sight line of his peers who's staring.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS582
SOMEONE dials a payphone.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS583
In his home, SOMEONE answers.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS584
Now, a woman sits at a bar. A door opens across the room.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS585
SOMEONE enters and takes a seat next to her.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS586
Her weary gaze hangs straight ahead, then she looks directly at SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS587
He takes her hand and gazes into her eyes.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS588
They pick up their drinks and share another glance.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS589
They both sip.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS590
Now at night, a lake reflects city lights. SOMEONE leads SOMEONE to a car.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS591
She gets in back and gazes at the unseen driver.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS592
SOMEONE seats at the wheel.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS593
SOMEONE averts her gaze. SOMEONE stares at the helpless informant.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS594
Gets out of the car. SOMEONE' gaze follows her as she walks around his vehicle.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS596
He wears a straw boater hat and sports a trim mustache. He steps out to meet SOMEONE and they sit on a roadside park bench.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS597
SOMEONE reaches into his coat.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS598
SOMEONE unfolds the page to reveal a handwritten message. Dear SOMEONE, don't try and break me out. I'm too well-guarded. Two years is not a long time anyway. Go someplace safe and wait for me. We will be together again. Your true love in life, SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS599
SOMEONE folds up the note.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS600
Stands and walks away. SOMEONE puts on his hat and heads off in the opposite direction.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS601
Now at a stone wall, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and other men look down at an idling steam locomotive.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS602
Now, SOMEONE sits at a kitchen table fanning herself with a magazine.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS604
He crosses the room. SOMEONE's fanning motion slows as her knowing gaze follows him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS605
SOMEONE glances around the living room, then returns to the kitchen. He goes to the sink and washes his hands.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS606
SOMEONE glances at a door.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS608
He dries his hands with a towel and leads the way through the house to the front door. They leave and our view returns to SOMEONE who remains at the table covering her mouth with her hand.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS609
Now, SOMEONE crosses the field office to SOMEONE who sits on a desk.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS610
As he eagerly takes the call.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS611
As he listens, SOMEONE looks up from a newspaper. SOMEONE lowers the phone and turns to his peers.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS612
The agents gather.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS613
All eyes turn to SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS614
He checks a newspaper.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS615
Now, SOMEONE pulls up to a building with Polly.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS616
Above the entrance, he sees the sign for the Chicago Police Department.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS617
They enter the building through a set of double doors.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS618
She goes off and SOMEONE steps forward, casually chewing gum as he glances around.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS619
An elevator door opens and SOMEONE steps aboard among a few other men, including a uniformed officer. He glances at the elevator operator and the door glides shut.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS620
On another floor, SOMEONE crosses a hall to a door bearing the words Detective Bureau SOMEONE Squad. He enters the quiet office, passing a row of empty chairs against the wall of a waiting area. Daylight shines in through a window.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS621
SOMEONE hikes up his pants as he enters the main office.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS622
He turns to a bulletin board where multiple mugshots of familiar criminals hang posted.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS623
He crosses to a desk and halts briefly by a secretary busy typing.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS624
A couple of yards ahead, an agent on the phone sits at his desk, unaware of SOMEONE's
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS625
presence. The gangster finds another bulletin board and scans its postings. A mugshot of Homer, photos of a robbed bank and a sprawled body, and a street map. A smile crosses SOMEONE's lips as he passes through a brilliant shot of sunlight. Further along the bulletin board, he finds black and white photos of himself - others show more buildings. SOMEONE lowers his sunglasses and views photos of the Little Bohemia Lodge, the wrecked Ford, and a pair of confiscated SOMEONE guns. Now, he crosses to a bulletin board showing mugshots of SOMEONE. One is ink-stamped with the words In Custody. SOMEONE's gaze roves down a line of mugshots showing Makley, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, Homer, SOMEONE, Gil, and Youngblood, all stamped with the word Deceased. The last mugshot of SOMEONE himself remains unstamped. SOMEONE lowers his shades and meets his mugshot's stern gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS626
SOMEONE rounds a corner and spies a group of agents surround the radio.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS627
One man glances over.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS628
Unrecognized, SOMEONE moves on.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS629
In a cinema lobby, using a public phone, a fair-haired agent scans his surroundings.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS630
using a public phone, a fair-haired agent scans his surroundings.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS631
Another agent ends the call. Gazing across the street, he shakes his head. A marquee reads Biograph Manhattan Melodrama.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS632
At the wheel of a parked car, SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE seated shotgun. Now, by a lamp's modest light, a shaving kit lies open on a small round table. A handgun lies beside it. Facing a mirror, SOMEONE drags a razor down his lathered cheek.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS633
He finishes shaving and opens his pocket watch, eyeing SOMEONE's photo and the time.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS634
He shuts the watch, puts it away, and pockets the gun.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS635
Parked near the Biograph, SOMEONE tensely rubs his thin-lipped mouth. At the box office, a few anonymous patrons mill into the theater. The agent looks away, shifting his anxious gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS636
He gets out of the car and paces down the sidewalk.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS637
He stops, turns, and puts his back to the cinema. Behind him, a man arrives with two blonde women, one of them in a conspicuous orange skirt.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS638
SOMEONE blinks, then looks over his shoulder. Spotting the trio, he looks away. Across the street, SOMEONE accompanies the two women into the cinema, passing a Manhattan Melodrama poster. Entering the packed house, the crime boss leaves SOMEONE at a seat, then proceeds down the aisle with Polly. They find adjacent seats as opening titles appear on the screen featuring the stars' pictures. They read Clark Gable, SOMEONE Powell, Manhattan Melodrama. In the packed audience, SOMEONE stares intently at the screen through his spectacles.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS641
Outside, SOMEONE addresses his agents.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS644
SOMEONE pats SOMEONE's shoulder.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS645
The team splits up.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS646
In the movie house, the crowd watches figures on screen playing hockey, then Clark Gable washing his hands in a men's room. Another character walks in.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS647
SOMEONE gazes at the screen with a boyish smirk.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS648
Sitting in her own, SOMEONE turns, peeking nervously over her shoulder. She faces the screen again, her chest heaving. Outside, the agents take their positions, SOMEONE and Hurt ducking to a storefront's recessed entryway. In the movie house, SOMEONE watches the screen with a furrowed brow.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS649
Leading lady Myrna Loy stares with her mouth agape. SOMEONE gazes at her with a knitted brow and clenched jaw. In a fur-collared coat, the exotically pretty actress wears a pensive expression. Later, she shifts her sober gaze. Later still, she turns away from a door, clad in black. Taking a deep breath, she manages a brave nod.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS650
Blinking back tears, she opens the door and hurries out. Clark Gable stares after her. SOMEONE watches with shining eyes. Outside, SOMEONE checks his watch. Posted near the box office, he looks across the street. SOMEONE and Hurt wait patiently in the recessed storefront. SOMEONE turns, gazing toward the cinema lobby.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS651
On the movie screen, Clark Gable faces SOMEONE Powell. He dons a cocky smile.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS652
SOMEONE watches with a defiant smirk. Onscreen, Gable turns away from Powell who draws a deep breath and heads into a cell block. A guard follows, closes a prison door, and locks it. Outside the theater, SOMEONE digs a box of matches from his pocket and takes one out. From his breast pocket, he produces a cigar and holds it ready. On the movie screen, Gable makes his way down the cell block flanked by guards.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS654
SOMEONE wears a faint sad smile as Gable faces a fellow convict.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS655
SOMEONE wears a faint half-smile, his eyes shining.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS656
Outside, SOMEONE shifts his tense, vigilant gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS657
In the movie house, words on the screen read The End. The patrons stand, filing out of their rows.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS658
A few rows down, SOMEONE stands with Polly and SOMEONE his straw hat.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS659
Outside, SOMEONE watches the exit.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS661
At the storefront, SOMEONE stand ready. In the parked car, the burly agent sweats at the wheel. His right hand trembles severely and he uses his left to steady it. Near the cinema door, SOMEONE watches movie patrons exiting the lobby. He faces the street, strikes the match, and lights his cigar.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS662
With a hostile sneer, the burly agent rushes out of the car. Now, SOMEONE steps into plain view walking between SOMEONE and Polly.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS663
Younger friend wears a carefree grin. Keeping apace.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS664
A bystander aside, SOMEONE heads down the sidewalk after them.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS665
Burly agent joins the flow of foot traffic with his gun raised. SOMEONE notices and roughly
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS667
Across the street, SOMEONE and Hurt leave the recessed storefront.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS668
Agent scowls, holding his aim as he gains on the crime boss.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS673
To his cheek, spewing blood and tissue. Two crimson stains bloom on his shirt front as Hurt fires twice from behind. SOMEONE falls face down, eyes staring off as blood streams from his ruptured cheek. SOMEONE stares, then ventures forward. As SOMEONE lies dying, his lips move.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS674
SOMEONE removes his hat, crouches, and leans his ear close to SOMEONE.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS675
The agent narrows his eye, glances at the fallen man, and withdraws, revealing SOMEONE's lifeless stare.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS676
SOMEONE gets to his feet, his sober gaze locked on the dead man.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS677
He holsters his gun and SOMEONE joins his side. As the younger G-Man eyes the body, SOMEONE dons his hat, his stare stoic and grim.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS678
The older man faces him.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS679
SOMEONE eyes him long and steady. SOMEONE glances away, then looks SOMEONE in the eye. SOMEONE leans in for a good look at SOMEONE's body, then heads off. Polly averts her gaze.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS682
SOMEONE lights a cigarette and pensively looks away. More onlookers converge on the scene.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS683
Flare's subtle light.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS686
Clad in a simple gray dress, she wears a dull expression. As the matron ushers her to another, the prisoner
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS687
maintains her dispassionate gaze. In the visiting room, the door opens. SOMEONE stands as SOMEONE enters. She stares guardedly at him, then takes the seat facing his.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS688
SOMEONE sits. Leaning forward, he faces her with a knitted brow.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS689
SOMEONE swallows, blinks her glistening eyes, then gives a stony nod.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS690
SOMEONE glares coldly. SOMEONE opens a gold cigarette case and briefly thumbs the contents. He turns the case, offering the grieving woman a cigarette. She sneers.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS691
Instead pockets the cigarette case.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS692
The agent stares solemnly.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS693
SOMEONE narrows her eyes.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS694
Her defiant sneer fades.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS697
Meeting SOMEONE's gaze, she gives a nod.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS701
Eyes closed, SOMEONE slowly shakes her head and takes a deep breath.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS702
Young woman gazes off with a solemn
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS703
and careworn expression.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS704
SOMEONE's lips hinted a wistful smile.
PUBLIC_ENEMIES_DVS705
In his head. The gray door opens and he steps out.