SOMEONE and the sharp-dressed man lock eyes as she passes the bar.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS19
The MC ogles SOMEONE as she steps to the mic.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS21
SOMEONE nods to the band.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS22
SOMEONE stage lights glisten on her shiny silver dress, as she swings her hips.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS23
Black approaches the sharp-dressed man.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS24
Black and the manager fixate on the seductive singer. SOMEONE beams and shakes her head.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS25
SOMEONE lip syncs as SOMEONE grabs the mic and a tambourine.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS27
SOMEONE shakes the tambourine overhead.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS29
She sets down the microphone and leaves the stage. SOMEONE applauds with a radiant smile as SOMEONE approaches.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS30
Black primps his hair as SOMEONE approaches.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS31
The swinging double doors close on the manager as SOMEONE and SOMEONE leave. Smiling, he turns back to the club.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS32
Now the sisters board a public bus and pay the fare. SOMEONE smiles adoringly, and follows SOMEONE past several other passengers to the back.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS34
SOMEONE removes her jacket and sees a man leering at her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS35
He smiles and turns back around. SOMEONE stands and spreads her coat's lapel, creating a screen behind which SOMEONE can change.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS36
Gazing out the window, she smiles at the Filmore marquee which reads, "MSOMEONE Gaye, Saturday 9:00 PM. "
SPARKLE_2012_DVS37
The image fades to colorful blurry lights and a title fades in on the foreground, SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS38
Now the sisters hurry up a quiet suburban driveway past a white Sedan, and approach a side entrance. A young woman wearing a pink nightie and curlers opens the door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS39
They follow her inside.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS40
SOMEONE carefully closes the door and hurries after them.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS41
Now they tiptoe up a square spiral staircase in the dark.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS42
An elegant chandelier hangs in the middle.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS43
At the top, the woman in pink hesitates, then leads them down the hallway and into a bedroom. The hallway light suddenly comes on, and a stern woman wearing a green nightgown and curlers emerges from an adjacent bedroom.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS44
The girls scurry into a queen-size bed and pull over the blankets, pretending to sleep.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS45
The woman enters and flicks the light switch on. She smiles and shakes her head.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS46
SOMEONE hides a smile as SOMEONE glares at her. And then at SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS47
She smacks SOMEONE's forehead.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS48
At church.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS49
The packed congregation sits before the reverend in the pulpit.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS50
The three sisters sit among the choir.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS51
In a pew, the manager sits with a stubble-faced man.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS53
The old woman sits back. SOMEONE rolls his neck and sits up straight. The guys look toward the choir. The manager chuckles.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS55
The manager approaches her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS56
She nervously glances around, and he smiles.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS58
SOMEONE, sporting a chin length SOMEONE, parks the car close by and moves to the passenger seat. SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS59
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS60
As she turns away, the big smile grows on her face.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS61
SOMEONE flashes a warm smile to her mother, who returns a stern glare.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS62
Now at the Anderson house, the Bible study group watches a comedian on the color TV.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS64
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a dirty look. SOMEONE whispers to SOMEONE, who shrugs.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS66
SOMEONE mugs a wide-mouth smile. Now SOMEONE finds SOMEONE smoking a cigarette.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS67
SOMEONE raises her brow.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS68
SOMEONE glances from her mother to SOMEONE. With a judgmental look, SOMEONE turns away. Smiling, SOMEONE draws on her cigarette and exhales.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS69
On the TV, a band plays.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS71
SOMEONE stops dancing.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS72
SOMEONE raises her brow, and sets her Bible down.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS73
As she leaves the room, SOMEONE faces the group.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS74
They sit with open Bibles as she turns the TV back on.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS75
SOMEONE dances and the others close their Bibles.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS76
SOMEONE sets hers down and smiles.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS78
SOMEONE rolls her eyes and clicks the TV off.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS79
As the group leaves, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE walk away from the front door, and deeper into the house.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS80
The rest of the group departs, leaving SOMEONE in the living room with SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS81
He hands her a Bible, and she sets it down.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS82
He eyes her as she walks away.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS83
He notices SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS85
SOMEONE ignores him and keeps walking.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS86
He tries to follow her, but ducks behind a wall avoiding SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS87
Standing in the archway, the resolute mother scans the room.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS88
SOMEONE steps out from his hiding place, and peers around the corner.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS89
The young manager creeps across the wood floor past the staircase.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS90
He approaches the door of the room SOMEONE entered and stops.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS91
He turns in a different direction.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS92
In another room, SOMEONE wears glasses and plays an upright piano alone.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS93
Unnoticed, SOMEONE approaches a doorway and finds the reserved beauty singing with her eyes closed.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS94
She notices SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS95
She smiles and looks away.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS96
She grabs her book from him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS97
As she plays, SOMEONE moves near her smiling.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS99
In the girl's bedroom, SOMEONE sits in bed wearing glasses and writing.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS100
She looks over at SOMEONE, who brushes her hair at a vanity table.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS101
SOMEONE looks to the side, and her face sours.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS102
SOMEONE goes to the window and peeks between the curtain.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS103
Then she turns around and smiles at SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS104
SOMEONE's hands fly to her glasses.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS105
She removes them and scurries to the window, as SOMEONE watches with an amused look.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS106
Below on the lawn, SOMEONE in a suit and tie waves up at SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS107
She opens the window and props it up with a thick red book.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS108
SOMEONE looks around nervous.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS109
SOMEONE shrugs playfully.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS110
She rubs her palms.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS114
One dancer wears a hat tilted over his eyes, a lit cigarette in his mouth.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS115
A couple kisses in the shadows. SOMEONE wearing a sleeveless dress, dances with SOMEONE. She looks around and sees a silhouetted couple kissing.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS117
She moves her body closer to his as they dance. She puts one hand around his neck.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS118
He shimmies up and down.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS119
Later, SOMEONE rides his motorcycle through a reflective white tiled tunnel as SOMEONE holds on to him from behind.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS120
She rests her cheek on his shoulder, looking to the side.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS122
As their legs stretched out in front of them.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS123
She ducks her chin in surprise.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS124
She raises an eyebrow.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS125
She furrows her brow.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS126
She pouts and looks down.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS127
They turn and see an upstairs light come on in the house.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS128
SOMEONE looks around nervously, then smiles at SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS129
She gets to her feet. He rises.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS130
He smiles, then takes her face in his hands.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS131
She closes her eyes as he kisses her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS132
Her eyes still closed, he pulls back from the kiss.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS133
She opens her eyes.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS134
He considers her challenging look.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS135
She shoulders past him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS136
Now SOMEONE talks to the sisters in the church cloakroom.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS137
SOMEONE smirks at him. He turns to SOMEONE who shrugs.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS138
He follows SOMEONE out, then looks back.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS139
He catches up with her and grabs her arm.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS140
She stalks off.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS141
Now at a greasy spoon, SOMEONE Douglas interviews SOMEONE Luther King Jr. on a black and white TV.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS142
SOMEONE sits at a table with SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS143
He lights her cigarette.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS144
She rolls her eyes.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS145
She shifts icily.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS146
He gazes into her eyes.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS147
He tilts his head and smiles.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS148
She takes a drag on her cigarette and looks down at the table.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS149
He reaches into his jacket and pulls out a small ring box. He sets it in front of her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS150
She stubs out her cigarette and picks it up.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS151
She opens the box, revealing a small black and white picture of a ring where the ring should be.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS152
They see SOMEONE Struthers in a fur trimmed overcoat beside an albino man and well-dressed woman.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS153
He comes to their table.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS154
SOMEONE chuckles with him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS155
SOMEONE frowns and smooths his shirt.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS156
He picks up the picture.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS157
SOMEONE wears jeweled rings on both hands.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS158
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE, who glances around the diner and twists his huge ring.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS159
He and SOMEONE share a long glance. He turns to SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS160
SOMEONE walks back to his friends where SOMEONE holds his pretty date on his lap. SOMEONE turns to watch them.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS161
SOMEONE puts on his cap.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS162
She collects her purse and jacket, and heads for the door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS163
She leaves the box and the little ring picture on the table with the half eaten food and drinks.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS164
SOMEONE slips the box and picture in his pocket.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS165
As SOMEONE opens the door for her, SOMEONE looks back at SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS166
He takes a flash photo of her, then lowers his camera and smiles.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS167
She smiles and leaves. Daytime. At SOMEONE's Fashions.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS168
SOMEONE looks at old snapshots with SOMEONE's friend Sara.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS169
SOMEONE approaches with a dark-skinned mannequin.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS170
She waves a photo.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS171
Sara follows SOMEONE to the dressing room. SOMEONE grabs her pocket book. She waves goodbye to a saleswoman and steps out from behind the counter.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS172
Now a girl wearing knee-high boots and a mini-dress crosses a busy street and enters a record store.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS173
Inside, two girls dance in slow motion inside a glass listening booth.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS174
In the next booth, a man wearing earphones, smokes and examines a record album cover.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS175
In the next booth, a young man in a hat talks to a young lady in a mini-skirt.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS176
SOMEONE sits alone in the next booth.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS177
She checks her watch, then examines a record album cover.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS178
SOMEONE knocks on the glass.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS179
He smiles and waves. But she turns her back to him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS180
He glances around, then talks through the glass.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS181
With her back to him, she breaks into a smile.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS182
Now in the SOMEONE's bedroom, SOMEONE wears curlers and straightens SOMEONE's hair. SOMEONE walks in wearily.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS183
SOMEONE hands her the check and tosses her purse on the bed.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS184
SOMEONE collapses on the bed.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS185
SOMEONE nudges SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS186
SOMEONE sits up.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS187
SOMEONE narrows her eyes.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS188
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a look. She softens and leans forward.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS190
Later the sisters get in a white Sedan. The Sedan drives off, and our view leaves a window to find SOMEONE asleep on the couch.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS191
At a nightclub, a drummer beats a rhythm. Outside, SOMEONE waits under an awning reading Cliff Bells.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS192
He checks his wrist watch.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS193
He sees SOMEONE toss the white Sedan's keys to the valet.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS197
The Anderson sisters spot the group on stage. Sister sighs.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS198
The trio follow SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS199
SOMEONE and Sister share a parting gaze. SOMEONE shakes hands with a bartender.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS200
With two lavender clad backup singers behind her, a beaming lead singer in a green dress struts across the stage.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS201
Sitting at the bar, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE enter with his entourage. A cameraman snaps a flash photo.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS202
A bartender brings SOMEONE a drink.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS203
SOMEONE fiddles with his jacket and collar as SOMEONE approaches.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS204
On stage, the lead singer holds her hand to her ear like a telephone.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS205
SOMEONE turns and notices SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS206
SOMEONE joins them.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS207
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange an excited look.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS209
SOMEONE looks down.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS210
SOMEONE crosses the room, smoking a cigarette. He takes a seat at a booth with SOMEONE and their dates.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS211
SOMEONE sits with them.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS212
SOMEONE's eyes dart around the room as he sips his drink.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS213
From backstage, Sister spots SOMEONE among the crowd. The performers struck a final pose.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS214
An MC steps to the stage and takes the mic.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS216
Backstage in an overcoat, Sister approaches her sisters already dressed.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS217
SOMEONE and SOMEONE head off.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS218
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step out on stage, each in a black conservative dress. SOMEONE blinks wearing a concerned frown. SOMEONE glances back at the drummer.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS219
Swaying to the music, SOMEONE trades a look with SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS220
Sitting at one of the tables, a woman calls out.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS221
SOMEONE mouths something to SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS222
SOMEONE shifts in his seat.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS223
SOMEONE smiles and tugs at his collar. SOMEONE shifts his uncertain gaze.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS224
Sister approaches a center microphone, walking seductively. Her face and body out of focus.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS225
SOMEONE and SOMEONE glance in her direction.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS226
Captivated, SOMEONE watches from the bar. SOMEONE and SOMEONE from their table.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS227
Her face now in focus, the stunning lead singer wraps her fingers around the microphone.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS228
She runs her hands up and down the mic stand.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS229
She gestures in SOMEONE's direction.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS230
The trio dances in unison. Sister wearing a sexy shoulder-less dress.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS231
Watching Sister's hand caress her thigh, SOMEONE sips his drink.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS232
Sister runs her hand up her arm.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS233
Sister glances at SOMEONE. Men in military uniforms watch from the back of the club.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS235
A smiling man in uniform claps his hands. The other patrons snap their fingers and clap.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS236
Sister points to SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS238
SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS239
SOMEONE waves to Sister, then trades a nod with SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS240
SOMEONE glares in SOMEONE's direction. Sister rejoins SOMEONE and SOMEONE. The trio performing a provocative dance.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS241
They cross their wrists over their chest, then freeze with them crossed at an angle overhead.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS242
Audience members stand. SOMEONE takes a flash picture of Sister. Later, SOMEONE walks the girls to the car.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS243
SOMEONE shuts the driver's door and pulls out.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS244
SOMEONE throws an air punch. Now in a pool hall.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS245
His opponent pounds his cue stick on the floor and slams a wad of cash on the table.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS246
In bed, SOMEONE writes a song.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS247
Now Sister and her sisters perform at the club.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS249
The frustrated opponent throws down his cue and storms out. Watching him go, SOMEONE chuckles. At the club.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS251
Now the club owner crosses the floor and greets the comedian as he and SOMEONE arrive on another night.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS253
Sister and her sisters perform on stage. Dancing in unison, their hair now short.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS254
Each wearing an identical black, silver, and red mini-dress.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS255
The sisters throw their hands overhead. They clap their hands, then turn around.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS256
SOMEONE takes a flash picture, and now they wear long black and white dresses in complimentary styles. A sign out front reads, Appearing tonight, Sister and Her Sisters, Sold Out. SOMEONE and the club owner clink their glasses.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS258
SOMEONE primps his hair.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS259
Then returns his attention to the performance. Sister stokes her quaffed chin length blonde hair.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS260
The sisters end on a hop, then stand hand in hand, beaming for the crowd.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS261
Later in the dressing room, Sister drinks a martini.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS262
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a kiss on the cheek.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS263
SOMEONE barges in with a handful of white lilies.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS264
He tries to give Sister a kiss, but she shies away.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS265
SOMEONE looks away.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS266
SOMEONE holds her gaze.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS267
He offers her a ring box.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS268
As SOMEONE glances at his lilies, Sister opens the box to find a diamond ring.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS270
Watching them tussle, Sister grins.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS271
With SOMEONE's help, SOMEONE drags SOMEONE out of the room.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS272
SOMEONE smiles at Sister.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS273
Sister nods. On his way out, SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, who looks down.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS274
Sister sets down the box, and tries on her ring.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS276
SOMEONE tightens his lips. He straightens his cousin's lapels, taps him on the chest, then turns and heads for the door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS277
With his chin jutting forward, SOMEONE turns back.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS279
Heading off, SOMEONE shrugs, then knocks a box off a stool.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS280
SOMEONE bats a hanging lamp and storms off. Now in the daytime, SOMEONE hosts a dinner. Reverend Bryce sits at the head of the table.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS281
SOMEONE shoots the reverend a look, then shakes her head.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS283
She pulls her hand back.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS284
SOMEONE giggles and SOMEONE shoots her a look.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS285
SOMEONE stares at them as they take their seats.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS286
SOMEONE leans in to SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS287
The reverend scrutinizes SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS288
Reverend Bryce looks at SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS289
As Tune Ann chomps on a carrot, her mother shoots her a furious look. SOMEONE draws a deep breath.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS290
Holding her daughter's gaze, SOMEONE shakes her head.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS291
SOMEONE lowers her eyes.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS293
He glances at the others.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS294
SOMEONE meets her daughter's gaze.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS295
Sister wipes tears from her cheeks.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS296
SOMEONE glances down.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS297
SOMEONE shakes her head.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS298
Sister and SOMEONE head for the door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS299
Sister shares a gaze with SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS300
She glances at the others, then walks out.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS301
SOMEONE leaves her seat.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS302
As SOMEONE follows Sister upstairs, SOMEONE touches her temple.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS303
Now SOMEONE watches Sister pack her jewelry into a box.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS304
Sister closes the buckles on her hard case black and white print suitcase, and grabs a second one on her way out.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS305
SOMEONE slowly approaches.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS306
SOMEONE eyes dart between her two sisters.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS307
SOMEONE smiles.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS308
Sister hugs her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS309
SOMEONE buries her chin in Sister's shoulder. Sister faces SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS310
They hug.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS311
Holding back tears, SOMEONE separates from Sister.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS312
With a soft smile, she touches SOMEONE's cheek and grabs her suitcases.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS313
They watch Sister wind halfway down the wooden staircase with a confident strut.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS314
She glances up at them with a reassuring look, and continues to the bottom.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS315
Waiting near the front door with a huge smile, SOMEONE holds her white fur coat.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS316
She hands him a suitcase and they continue out the front door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS317
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from the second floor, as SOMEONE steps into the foyer.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS318
She stares out for a moment toward her oldest daughter, then gently closes the front door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS319
Turning around, she gazes up at her two remaining daughters, who glare down and promptly retreat into the bedroom.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS320
Now at night, SOMEONE mounts SOMEONE's motorcycle, holding him tight.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS321
SOMEONE nods, turns on the headlight and drives away from her house.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS322
Now the young couple cruises through the night.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS323
With her eyes closed, SOMEONE rests her cheek against his brown leather jacket.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS324
Now at a flat roof mansion, identical glass paneled doors line a lengthy balcony.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS325
Sister emerges from inside and approaches SOMEONE in a white baby doll nightie.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS326
As he reads a book in a burgundy robe, she serves him coffee and caresses his shoulders.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS327
She sits on his lap.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS328
He prepares cocaine.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS329
Sister eyes the drugs, then smiles.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS330
SOMEONE licks his fingers. Sister kisses him tenderly. As their embrace intensifies, they passionately kiss each other's necks.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS331
The seductive beauty sinks further into his lap.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS332
He rubs his hand up her body.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS333
Now inside SOMEONE's mansion, Sister rubs her nose while smoking a cigarette. A thick head band supports her disheveled hair.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS334
She steps in front of SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS336
SOMEONE pours a drink.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS337
SOMEONE holds in a giggle.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS338
Her smile fades.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS339
Sister leads the girls out.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS340
As SOMEONE glares at them, SOMEONE cowers, but SOMEONE looks him in the eye.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS341
Now in a dressing room, the girls get ready as Sister arrives.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS342
Sister removes her hat, revealing a black eye.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS343
As SOMEONE leaves, Sister opens her compact and lines cocaine on the mirror.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS344
As Sister leans down, SOMEONE's mouth hangs open and her brow furrows.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS345
The compact's mirror reflects Sister bruised eye.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS346
Now on the dark stage, Sister lets a wrap with a voluminous high collar, drop to her feet.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS347
Her sisters remain silhouetted by backdrops of large lit squares.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS348
The trio moves forward, provocatively swaying their hips with each snap.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS349
At home in front of the TV, SOMEONE snores on the couch holding a teacup.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS350
She wears a blue nightgown with a hair scarf tied around the curlers in her hair.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS351
She awakes to her daughters performing, and leans closer.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS352
On the color TV, a close-up shows SOMEONE’s seductive gaze.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS354
The ladies pump their fists at their rocking hips.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS355
SOMEONE winks to SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS356
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE beckon him suggestively.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS357
Off stage, SOMEONE touches a cut on his forehead.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS358
Sister bends at the knees, sensually rubbing her hands down her thighs.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS359
A white band of sheer fabric down her sides, accentuates her curves.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS360
SOMEONE and SOMEONE shimmy backwards, silhouetted on either side of Sister as she walks with her back to the audience.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS361
She gives one more enticing look to the crowd.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS362
A blue glow consumes her face and her smile fades.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS363
In the dressing room.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS364
He points at Sister.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS365
Sister turns her bruised face away.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS366
SOMEONE enters with SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS367
SOMEONE leans to SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS368
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE leave with a big smile that fades as she faces SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS369
SOMEONE blocks SOMEONE and SOMEONE joins her. They glare at the abusive man.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS370
Sister stays seated and looks toward them.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS371
SOMEONE sneers at SOMEONE, who holds her ground.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS372
He slowly turns away, keeping his menacing eyes locked on hers.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS373
As he and SOMEONE leave the dressing room, Sister faces the opposite way and fiddles with her purse.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS374
Sister looks away.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS375
SOMEONE gently takes her hand.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS376
Tilting her head.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS377
Sister sighs and stands up.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS378
SOMEONE grabs Sister's white fur coat, and some makeup cases.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS379
SOMEONE takes Sister by the hand and leads her out of the room.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS380
In the hallway, audience members mingle backstage. Sister glances across the room to SOMEONE, who initiates applause.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS381
Sister takes the fur coat from SOMEONE and turns toward the party with a glowing smile. Her sisters watch her amble up a few stairs in her black mini-dress.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS382
SOMEONE takes her picture as she hurries into his arms.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS383
SOMEONE glances across the room at SOMEONE and SOMEONE, as Sister leads him out of sight.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS384
The two sisters stare with disappointed gazes, then continue on their way out.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS385
Now at home, a pile of suitcases sit at the foot of the stairs.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS386
SOMEONE sets her makeup case on top.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS387
In the living room, SOMEONE sits on the couch with her hands in her lap, staring straight ahead.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS388
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk timidly toward her in their black overcoats.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS389
SOMEONE keeps her gaze on the floor.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS390
SOMEONE leans forward.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS391
She pulls out SOMEONE's red song journal.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS392
She rises from the couch.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS393
SOMEONE stomps to a waste basket in the foyer and tosses it in. SOMEONE fishes it out.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS394
SOMEONE gives a little nod.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS395
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE, then marches up the stairs.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS396
SOMEONE holds her journal at her side, with one trembling black gloved hand.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS397
SOMEONE puts a steadying hand on it.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS398
SOMEONE nods tearfully.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS399
Now on SOMEONE's balcony, Sister wearing a white feather-trimmed robe, holds a drink as she reads a magazine.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS400
SOMEONE comes out smoking a cigarette.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS401
He snaps a picture of her, then saunters over in his burgundy robe and kisses her on the cheek.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS402
He sits down at the table and shows her a notebook.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS403
She flips through notebook.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS404
She rises.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS405
She straddles him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS406
Putting her arms around him. She kisses him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS408
She flexes one long stocking clad leg and gets up.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS409
She takes the notebook with her into the house.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS410
She turns around.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS412
In the packed nightclub, Sister laughs in a booth with SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS414
The heckler sits in a booth with his arm around a sexy woman. It's SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS415
SOMEONE cranes his neck to look at him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS416
SOMEONE takes a puff on his cigarette. Sister scowls.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS417
SOMEONE moves toward SOMEONE's table.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS418
Sister blinks heavily and lets out a breath. SOMEONE looks from SOMEONE to SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS419
SOMEONE throws down his cigarette.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS420
SOMEONE lunges, but a man at SOMEONE's table blocks him. SOMEONE holds him back.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS421
SOMEONE makes a scissor gesture.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS422
She blows smoke in his direction, then leaves.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS423
Outside in slow motion, SOMEONE struggles to hold back a hopping mad SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS424
SOMEONE finally calms down. Straightens his jacket and throws one last punch in the direction of the club.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS425
He gets into a sleek silver sports car, parked under the baker's flashing marquee. It reads, "Presenting SOMEONE Struthers, 8:00 PM. "
SPARKLE_2012_DVS426
Sister scrambles to the passenger side.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS427
Pulling her fur stole around her, and tossing her cigarette butt.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS428
She exhales one last long stream of smoke.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS429
As SOMEONE holds the door open for her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS430
As the car pulls away, SOMEONE watches it go.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS431
Now in slow motion beyond the windows of SOMEONE's mansion, SOMEONE chases Sister.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS432
In her stocking feet, she slips on the floor and falls.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS434
He tries to pin her arms behind her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS435
She wriggles free, and dashes into another room, where she falls face down on a banquette.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS436
Behind her, SOMEONE raises his belt and brings it down hard on her back.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS437
He beats her again and again.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS438
Now in a cool blue reception area, SOMEONE paces in front of a sign emblazoned with a Colombia logo.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS439
In slow motion, the elevator doors part, and SOMEONE steps out in a mod purple mini-dress. Her hair styled in a close-cropped Afro.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS440
A white businessman does a double take as she passes.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS441
Another white man stares at her, and she glares back as she strides past him and down the hall.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS442
SOMEONE takes her in as she walks up to him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS443
SOMEONE catches SOMEONE staring.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS444
In a utility closet, Sister smooth's down her dress and looks at her battered reflection in a metal paper towel dispenser.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS445
She fiddles with her tangled hair.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS446
SOMEONE enters, followed by SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS447
She looks at needle marks in Sister's arm.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS448
In their struggle, a glass vile breaks on the floor. Outside the door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS449
SOMEONE raps on the door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS450
His blonde receptionist unlocks the door. In the closet on the floor, SOMEONE and SOMEONE huddle around Sister, who shakes back her tangled hair.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS451
SOMEONE looks up to find SOMEONE gone.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS452
SOMEONE leans against the door jam and hangs his head.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS453
SOMEONE casts her eyes down.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS454
Now rain falls as SOMEONE raises her bedroom window and props it open with a red book.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS455
Outside, SOMEONE motions for her to join him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS456
She rises from the window.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS457
SOMEONE, his cap and jacket soaked
SPARKLE_2012_DVS458
walks around the house, and waits by the backdoor.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS459
SOMEONE clutches a thin SOMEONEy robe around her and steps outside to join him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS460
They huddle in the doorway.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS461
He nods his head several times.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS462
She looks down and shakes her head.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS463
He turns and walks down her driveway in the rain.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS464
SOMEONE hesitates,
SPARKLE_2012_DVS465
then turns back and enters the house. She slowly walks up the stairs.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS466
Now at SOMEONE's, SOMEONE lugs a suitcase while sister sits on the banquette twirling her hair in a daze.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS467
SOMEONE in a bright yellow turtleneck, shouts up to SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS468
SOMEONE takes her drink.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS469
As Sister swings at her, SOMEONE yanks her off the banquette.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS470
SOMEONE rushes in.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS471
SOMEONE approaches, a suitcase in each hand. The sisters separate.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS472
He puts down his luggage and gives Sister a little smile.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS473
She walks over to the banquette and sits down.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS474
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS476
He points his finger at her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS477
Sister gets up and lunges at him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS478
SOMEONE attacks him. With one hand, he shoves Sister to the
SPARKLE_2012_DVS479
Banquette, then wrestles SOMEONE off of him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS480
SOMEONE leaps on his back. SOMEONE grabs a poker from the fireplace. He throws SOMEONE to the ground and looms over her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS481
From behind, SOMEONE swings the poker at his head.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS482
He falls face down on the carpet.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS483
With his mouth open, he exhales a long breath and a short gasp.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS484
SOMEONE stands over him, gripping the poker in both hands.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS485
Sister stares in shock.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS486
SOMEONE's mouth hangs open.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS487
Sister looks from SOMEONE to SOMEONE. Then gets up and goes to her side.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS488
She takes the poker in her hands.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS489
SOMEONE kneels over SOMEONE and rolls him face up.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS490
She starts CPR.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS491
She wipes her nose. Sister lays down the poker.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS492
SOMEONE blows air into SOMEONE's mouth.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS493
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE try to revive him.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS494
Sister approaches and kneels beside SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS495
SOMEONE gets to her feet, then pulls SOMEONE off the floor.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS496
SOMEONE pushes her out of the room. Sister sobs and beats on the dead man's chest.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS498
She caresses his lifeless face.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS499
We fade to a black and white snapshot of Sister she holds in her hands.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS500
Now at night, she smokes on the banquette.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS501
Outside, two uniformed men carry a body-bag from the house, past policemen and parked patrol cars with flashing blue lights.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS502
A heavy-set man with glasses leads Sister from the house in a long black coat.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS503
Hands cuffed behind her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS504
She glances at the body-bag, as he guides her into the backseat of a patrol car and closes the door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS505
SOMEONE rests her head across her arm, as she lies face down on her bed.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS506
SOMEONE comes and lies beside her sister, looking into her face.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS507
She wipes a tear running down the bridge of SOMEONE's nose.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS508
Then turns and rests her head on her own crossed arms.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS509
As Sister poses for mugshots, a newspaper headline reads.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS510
"Negro comedian slain. Fiancé pleads self-defense. Bail denied pending trial. "
SPARKLE_2012_DVS511
SOMEONE sings, smiling through tears.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS512
SOMEONE sits in a church pew.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS513
SOMEONE opens her arms before the packed church.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS515
SOMEONE sits at the kitchen table. Luggage rests at the bottom of the stairs. SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive home, and SOMEONE rises to meet them.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS516
SOMEONE hugs her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS517
As SOMEONE steps away, SOMEONE eyes the luggage.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS518
SOMEONE's jaw drops.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS520
SOMEONE blinks back tears.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS521
They hug.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS522
Now SOMEONE watches from her bedroom window, as SOMEONE walks to a waiting taxi, and hands her bags to the driver.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS523
She gets in the backseat and closes the door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS524
As the cab pulls away.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS525
SOMEONE looks back at the house.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS526
SOMEONE waves, then rests her head on the window pane.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS527
Now in prison, SOMEONE looks at Sister through a pane of glass.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS528
Each of them holding a phone receiver.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS529
SOMEONE blinks and looks down.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS530
Tears come to Sister's eyes.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS531
She shakes her head.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS532
Sister stares into SOMEONE's eyes. Then hangs up the phone.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS533
Sister keeps walking and disappears behind a door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS534
SOMEONE sighs and hangs up the phone.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS535
Now her hair in pigtails, Nancy Sinatra sings on a sound stage.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS536
At home, SOMEONE watches TV. In a housecoat and curlers, SOMEONE turns off the set.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS537
SOMEONE walks away. SOMEONE sighs.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS539
SOMEONE looks over an empty apartment, as a white man stands at the open door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS540
She crosses to a window and looks outside.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS541
At night with the room fully furnished, SOMEONE unpacks.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS542
Sitting on her bed by an open cardboard box, she flips through the pages of her song journal.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS543
She smiles to herself and turns the page, stopping.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS544
An underlying song title at the top of a page reads, One Wing.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS545
At night alone at home, SOMEONE smokes a cigarette on her couch. At her apartment, SOMEONE writes in her songbook.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS546
In the daytime, SOMEONE enters a marbled floor lobby through a set of revolving doors. She speaks with a guard sitting within a circular counter.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS547
She nods and heads down a hall.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS548
Now on another floor, she exits the elevator.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS549
Arriving at Columbia Records, she crosses to the desk of the blonde haired receptionist.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS550
The receptionist watches SOMEONE take a seat on a long bench across the reception area.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS551
The patient young woman holds her purse over her lap, wearing a leather jacket.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS552
On another day, now wearing a pink dress, SOMEONE watches a businessman head off for a meeting.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS553
Now wearing a checkered outfit, she notices another businessman on his way out.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS554
Wearing an outfit with yellow sleeves, she eats a sandwich, kicking her leg out of boredom.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS555
In a striped dress, she sleeps clutching a magazine.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS556
A receptionist wakes her and she smiles. Leaving the magazine behind, she follows the receptionist through a door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS557
The receptionist leads SOMEONE down a hall and into SOMEONE's office. The goateed executive talks on the phone, sitting at his desk before a wall of tall windows overlooking a river.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS558
As SOMEONE takes a look around, the door swings shut behind her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS559
She approaches the desk, and the busy executive glances at her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS560
He hangs up the phone.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS561
She takes a seat.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS562
SOMEONE holds her gaze.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS563
Later with her arms folded, SOMEONE paces in the lobby of an apartment building. SOMEONE comes downstairs, and a cigar smoking building manager directs his attention to the visitor.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS564
SOMEONE crosses the lobby and faces SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS565
SOMEONE cracks a smile.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS566
She smiles and they hug.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS567
Now at night, SOMEONE knocks on her mother's front door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS568
Through the paned panel, she can see SOMEONE approach.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS569
SOMEONE opens the door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS570
Averting her cold gaze, SOMEONE gives a careless gesture and steps away from the open door.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS571
SOMEONE enters timidly, and follows her mother into the living room.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS572
Mrs. SOMEONE sits on the couch with SOMEONE, who focuses on a TV show.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS573
The plump woman removes her glasses.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS574
SOMEONE's smile fades, as she notices her mother's haughty gaze fixed stubbornly on the TV.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS575
She takes it out of her purse, unfolds it and shows it to the women.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS576
SOMEONE ignores it.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS577
SOMEONE sets it down before her on a coffee table. And Mrs. SOMEONE leans over it.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS578
SOMEONE shifts her gaze, then looks to her mother.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS579
Ignoring her, SOMEONE points mirthfully at the TV.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS580
SOMEONE shifts on her feet.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS581
Mrs. SOMEONE glares reproachfully at SOMEONE, who stares ahead with an uncaring expression as her daughter leaves the house.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS582
Now on a concert hall stage, SOMEONE oversees three backup singers.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS583
Seated at a grand piano, SOMEONE glances over, then turns her attention to her song journal.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS584
SOMEONE ambles across the stage toward her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS585
She shuts her song journal.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS586
SOMEONE sits beside her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS587
SOMEONE tilts his head tenderly.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS588
She folds her arms across her chest and sullenly obeys.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS589
SOMEONE regards her.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS590
Keeping them shut, she plays the piano.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS591
She smiles at SOMEONE.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS592
SOMEONE steps away.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS593
As she plays on with her eyes closed.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS594
SOMEONE steps out from the wings with a plate.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS595
It bears a single serving cake with white frosting, lit with one candle.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS596
SOMEONE takes a nervous breath, then blows out the candle and smiles.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS597
SOMEONE presents her with a candy ring set in a tasteful jewelry box.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS598
He beams and holds it out.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS599
SOMEONE accepts the candy ring, and grins down at it.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS600
He scoots in closer on the piano bench.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS601
As SOMEONE faces SOMEONE. He beckons her closer.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS602
He cradles her face in his hands, and tenderly kisses her lips.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS604
Pulling back, he gazes solemnly into her eyes.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS605
SOMEONE takes a deep breath, then relaxes and leans closer.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS606
She gives SOMEONE a hug.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS607
Then rests her cheek against his shoulder.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS608
Now in prison, a female guard escorts Sister into a visiting area.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS609
Clad in a pale pink jumpsuit, she wears her un-styled curly hair in a low ponytail.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS610
And moves with a weary shuffling gait.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS611
On the other side of a glass barrier.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS612
SOMEONE sits wearing oversized sunglasses.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS613
Sister takes the seat facing hers and slumps.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS614
SOMEONE removes her sunglasses and faces her daughter with puffy eyes.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS616
Tilting her head, she gives a gentle gaze.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS617
Her daughter regards her gravely, then picks up the telephone handset on her side of the glass.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS618
SOMEONE does the same, and waits patiently.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS619
The mother shuts her eyes, lifts her brow, and gives a sad smile.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS620
Leaning close to the glass, Sister smiles softly.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS621
Her eyes glisten, and she gives an appreciative nod.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS622
In a dressing room, SOMEONE wears a blue gown.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS623
Her backup singers beam.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS624
Tune Ann brings SOMEONE a tissue for her nosebleed.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS625
SOMEONE arrives with a dress.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS626
The backup singers leave the room.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS627
As SOMEONE stares, her mother cocks her head and lifts her brow.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS629
In the dressing room, SOMEONE wears a slinky crimson gown with a plunging neckline.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS630
SOMEONE gently taps her on the chin, and turns away.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS631
Beaming, her mother leaves.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS632
SOMEONE lays her hands over her heart, then faces a full-length mirror and takes in her own striking reflection.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS635
Now on stage, she adjusts her microphone and faces the house.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS636
Turning, she looks to SOMEONE in the wings.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS637
He gives her a confident nod.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS638
SOMEONE's hands falter over the piano keys.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS639
Facing the house, she finds her mother giving an encouraging smile.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS640
An orchestra plays in a pit below the stage.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS641
Lights come up on her backup singers.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS642
A partition rises, revealing a gospel choir of singers dressed in white robes.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS643
In the wings, SOMEONE shifts his weight beside SOMEONE, who watches with crossed arms.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS644
SOMEONE rises from the piano.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS645
She stands at a microphone.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS646
The audience gives her a standing ovation.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS649
On stage, SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE. He blows her a kiss.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS650
Beaming joyfully, the young singer songwriter faces the cheering audience.
SPARKLE_2012_DVS651
SOMEONE leans her head back, spreads her arms and drinks in the applause.