Her square-jawed husband stares grimly at her over his reading glasses.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS20
Breaking off his stare, he answers his cell.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS21
Now, photos of his comatose wife fill a scrapbook.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS24
At a posh house.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS25
SOMEONE sees SOMEONE hurl lawn chairs into a pool.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS26
SOMEONE briefly lowers the phone and glowers at it.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS27
Now, in windy, overcast weather, a silver sedan drives through a middle class neighborhood.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS28
As it passes, we glimpse SOMEONE riding shotgun.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS29
The car arrives at a house. Now a round-faced woman with long, black hair opens its door.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS30
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE in.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS31
The mother leads them into a sprawling cluttered living room where a chubby pre-teen girl watches TV.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS32
Sharing her mother's round face and sullen pout, she faces her visitors. Her mother looks to them indignantly, hands on her hips.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS33
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE's angry mother.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS34
His daughter nods.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS35
She nods emphatically.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS36
SOMEONE gives a shrug of the hand.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS37
The mother faces her daughter inquiringly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS38
SOMEONE nods. Now the woman follows the visitors out to her porch.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS39
She nods plainly. SOMEONE wears a nonplussed smile, then walks his daughter to their car.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS40
In a home office.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS41
Later, he searches stacks of documents.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS42
SOMEONE views two portraits on a wall. One shows a Polynesian woman, the other a bearded Caucasian man.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS43
SOMEONE rubs his eyes. Now, he works in a metropolitan office.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS44
A secretary looks in.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS45
SOMEONE covers a half-eaten salad. In a meeting room, he greets seven people in Hawaiian shirts.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS46
As his cousins debate, SOMEONE sits at the head of the conference table, his chin perched thoughtfully on his hand.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS47
His gaze grows distant and his hand droops.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS48
Later, he enters the hospital through sliding glass doors.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS49
We peer down a square spiral stairwell.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS50
SOMEONE climbs flight after flight.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS51
A balding doctor faces SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS52
Hunched forward, SOMEONE drops his hollow gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS53
His eyes glisten and he hangs his head.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS54
SOMEONE nods faintly, then screws his jaw to one side.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS55
SOMEONE leans back in his seat.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS56
The doctor unhappily faces him.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS57
At the end of a hallway, a door's window frames a view of SOMEONE shambling closer, his arms hanging at his sides.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS58
He pulls the door open and passes through with a thunderstruck expression on his face.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS59
His gait is listless and steady as he makes his way past a few recovery rooms.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS60
He passes behind a staffer on the phone at a nurse's station.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS61
A distant doorway shows a nurse making a bed.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS62
SOMEONE's expression grows woeful as he nears the far end of the ward.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS63
He halts at a door to a private room and takes it in.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS64
Entering, SOMEONE finds an attractive dark-haired woman putting makeup on his gaunt wife.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS65
A fit, pleasant-faced man sits nearby.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS66
SOMEONE mocks an optimistic smile, then looks pointedly in SOMEONE's direction.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS67
Later, his car travels past a park.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS68
SOMEONE rides shotgun as he makes a right turn into a parking lot.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS69
They pass a sign that reads "Ocean Outrigger Club".
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS71
Now in a baggy T-shirt and shorts, SOMEONE sits on the sunny beach, gazing at the surf.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS72
SOMEONE plays in shallow water near the shore.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS73
Wearing a yellow swim mask, she undulates face down in the water.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS74
Her long, brown hair clings like seaweed at her shoulders as she pops up for air.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS75
SOMEONE squints in the sunlight as he watches.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS76
He looks away briefly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS78
As SOMEONE does a handstand, her legs wobble at unsteady angles.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS80
Now in a club restaurant, SOMEONE watches her fondly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS81
As she eats an ice cream sundae, SOMEONE wipes ice cream from her mouth with a napkin.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS82
SOMEONE looks down and gives a noncommittal shrug.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS83
Lifting his gaze, he notices someone in the distance.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS84
His expression darkens.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS85
Behind his daughter, a muscular, blond man arrives at the bar with some friends.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS86
He notices SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS87
He approaches the table.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS88
Troy shifts his wounded gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS89
Eating her sundae, SOMEONE squints up at Troy.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS90
He glances at her, starts to go, but hesitates.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS91
SOMEONE runs out. SOMEONE glares at Troy.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS92
He hurries after his daughter.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS93
SOMEONE leads his daughter back.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS94
They pass the bar where Troy drinks beer with his friends.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS95
The child flips him the bird.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS96
Troy responds with a resigned nod. Now a plane soars into the sky. On a map, a dotted line traces a path from Oahu to the island of Hawaii.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS97
On the plane, SOMEONE and SOMEONE peer through a window at a verdant coastline.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS98
At dusk, a red car passes terrain decorated with names spelled out in white stones.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS100
At the wheel, SOMEONE glances over at SOMEONE, who sleeps with her head leaned against the window.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS101
Later in the night, the car's headlights cut through the darkness.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS102
It turns up a driveway,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS103
passing a sign that reads "Hawaii Pacific Institute".
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS104
Indoors, three figures step into view in a long corridor.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS105
Overhead fluorescents flicker on.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS106
A woman leads SOMEONE and SOMEONE forward.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS107
SOMEONE hurries ahead and knocks eagerly on a door.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS108
It opens, revealing a sleepy, disheveled teen.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS109
The supervisor wearily leads the visitors down the hall to another door.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS110
A partition slides down, revealing a groggy teen girl putting on glasses.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS111
Now, in the darkness, the dorm supervisor uses a flashlight to lead
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS112
SOMEONE and SOMEONE down a long stairway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS113
They pass through a chain link gate to a driving range.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS114
Two teens flee, one falls.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS115
The girls stagger gripping golf clubs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS116
SOMEONE grins drunkenly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS117
Grinning, SOMEONE points at her father with her golf club.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS118
She turns away and flings it.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS119
Now, SOMEONE and his daughters arrive at home.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS120
SOMEONE obeys.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS121
SOMEONE carries a passed out SOMEONE down a hallway upstairs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS122
Her arms hug him around the neck and her head rests against his shoulder.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS123
SOMEONE brings her into a bedroom and lays her down.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS124
The teen stirs sleepily.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS125
SOMEONE guides her raised knees down and covers her with a quilt.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS126
Heading out, he pauses at the door and glances solemnly back at her.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS127
His expression growing resigned, he leaves and shuts the door. In the morning, SOMEONE transfers scrambled eggs from a pan onto a plate with toast.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS128
He sets the meal on a table for SOMEONE. She balks.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS129
She pushes the plate away.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS130
As SOMEONE takes the plate from the table, SOMEONE shuffles in.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS131
Without meeting his gaze, the teen takes a cola from the refrigerator, sits at the table, and slurps sullenly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS132
SOMEONE regards her with a disapproving smirk.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS133
SOMEONE tilts his head sheepishly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS134
SOMEONE brings her the untouched breakfast. SOMEONE glares at him, glances at the plate, and leaves with an indignant sneer.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS135
SOMEONE follows her outside and finds her on her cellphone,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS136
seated at the edge of an in-ground pool littered with leaves.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS137
SOMEONE steps away, picks up a skimmer, and scoops some of the leaves out.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS138
Clad in a bikini, the teen ends her call.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS139
SOMEONE wags her bottom.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS140
Pouting, SOMEONE flips her father the bird and goes inside.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS141
SOMEONE gets in the pool.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS142
Treading water, SOMEONE stares at her father.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS143
She looks away, stricken.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS144
Blinking back tears, SOMEONE meets his imploring gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS145
Surrounding by dead floating leaves, the teen looks away.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS146
She sinks down beneath the water and holds her head in her hands.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS147
Large air bubbles escape her gaping mouth as her body shakes with sobs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS148
Her features contort fiercely and she swims through the water.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS149
SOMEONE walks alongside her as her head emerges.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS150
She climbs out and buries her face in a colorful towel.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS151
Her father approaches with a compassionate frown.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS152
Wheeling around, SOMEONE finds him with his arms spread open to her.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS153
She leaves him.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS154
Her father watches her go with a heavy gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS156
fully dressed and curled up on a sofa, SOMEONE faces its back and rests her chin on her folded arms. SOMEONE walks in.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS158
The girl blinks thoughtfully
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS159
as her father takes a seat opposite her,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS160
She curls her neck to look at him.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS161
SOMEONE sits up, then scoots around to face him fully. SOMEONE blinks quizzically.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS162
He cocks his head.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS164
SOMEONE wears a confounded gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS165
He shifts in his chair.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS166
Looking away, SOMEONE shakes his head.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS167
He springs to his feet and paces.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS168
The betrayed husband halts.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS169
His back to SOMEONE, then turns.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS170
SOMEONE's chest rises and
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS172
He registers a hint of a nod.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS173
He has helpless shrug.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS174
He has hands on his hips.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS175
SOMEONE turns away and paces restlessly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS177
His hands curl into fists then release.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS178
Facing SOMEONE, he rubs his chin and nose.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS179
He goes out onto the porch and steps into a pair of soft-soled shoes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS180
He hops and hobbles as he pulls them over his heels one at a time.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS181
Clambering down to his driveway,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS182
SOMEONE breaks into a run.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS183
The family man races out of a cul-de-sac and reaches a narrow, rain-soaked road.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS184
He follows it at a sprint, his brow furrowed and his arms pumping furiously.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS185
Running at a stilted, awkward gait,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS186
he reaches a hairpin curve and follows it onto a street canopied with lush trees.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS187
It leads him to a neighborhood nestled by verdant foothills.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS189
Arriving at a two-story house, he passes a little brown goat on his way up the driveway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS190
Through a window in a cluttered kitchen, we watch him arrive at a door where he lets himself in.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS191
He ventures further into his friend's house.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS192
SOMEONE emerges on an upstairs landing.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS193
They join SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS194
SOMEONE stares wide-eyed at SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS195
SOMEONE looks away regretfully.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS196
SOMEONE heaves a breath.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS197
SOMEONE fidgets with his wedding ring.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS198
SOMEONE takes a seat and nods.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS199
SOMEONE screws his jaw to one side and faces SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS200
As SOMEONE sinks down in a chair, SOMEONE's gaze softened.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS201
He shrugs a hand helplessly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS202
SOMEONE doubles over, burying her face in her hands as her husband looks on sympathetically.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS203
SOMEONE pulls a chair out from a nearby table and sits facing his friends.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS204
He leans forward, his elbows on his knees.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS205
His gaze fixes on SOMEONE, then drops morosely.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS206
SOMEONE's eyes glisten and he gives a shaky nod.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS207
He swallows hard and blinks back tears.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS208
With a resigned smirk, his gaze toggles between SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS209
SOMEONE leaves.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS210
As SOMEONE rocks herself, her arms folded, SOMEONE gazes remorsefully after his friend.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS213
SOMEONE heads down the sun-dappled driveway past the goat.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS214
SOMEONE catches up to him.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS215
SOMEONE gives a small nod and goes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS216
SOMEONE heads back toward his house.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS218
Now, on a bridge stretching over a sparkling stream, SOMEONE weeps into his hand.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS219
He wipes his face.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS220
Keeping his head down, he wipes his eyes and continues across the bridge.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS221
Now he hikes wearily across a healthy lawn bordered by a stone wall.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS223
The stone one meets a second wall of painted cinder block, that's stained along the top with mold.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS224
SOMEONE arrives at the cul-de-sac leading to his driveway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS226
He heads toward his home, passing lush flowering shrubs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS227
SOMEONE turns. He approaches the pool area where his daughters share a lounge chair.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS228
A teen boy reclines in a chair beside them.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS229
SOMEONE extends a hand. SOMEONE bounds up and clasps it.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS230
He throws an arm around SOMEONE in a brotherly hug.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS231
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS232
SOMEONE eyes the teen boy with a skeptical frown.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS233
SOMEONE grins and shrugs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS234
Now, a man's aging hands hold a document headed "Advance Healthcare Directive". The reader, a man with a grey buzz cut, scowls.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS235
SOMEONE tosses it down bitterly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS236
SOMEONE subdues a glare.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS237
SOMEONE's chin quivers.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS238
Getting to his feet, the older man steps away from the table in his beige knee socks and sandals.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS239
Wearing a white tee tucked into his khaki shorts, he keeps his back to SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE, who watch him halt on the grass.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS240
SOMEONE's mouth twists in a repressed sob and he rubs his lips back into a stoic line.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS241
His chest rises and falls and he bows his head.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS242
Creasing his lips, he lifts his mournful gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS243
Later, inside, SOMEONE gently leads a silver-haired woman by the hand.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS244
She wears a vacant, confused expression as he takes her down a hallway
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS245
to a living room where the three visitors wait.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS246
SOMEONE remains seated at the far end of the room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS247
SOMEONE and SOMEONE respectfully get to their feet.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS248
He kisses her cheek.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS249
Now standing, SOMEONE smiles and waves.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS250
SOMEONE eyes him, then faces his wife.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS251
SOMEONE storms over to SOMEONE, who takes a step back.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS252
SOMEONE punches him.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS253
Now, in SOMEONE's car, SOMEONE holds frozen peas over his eye.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS254
SOMEONE shows his black eye.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS255
SOMEONE touches him gently.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS256
SOMEONE pulls over.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS257
He wheels around, pointing a finger harshly at SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS258
Glaring, SOMEONE withdraws his hand and faces SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS259
SOMEONE contritely lowers his gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS260
SOMEONE turns away from the teen and slumps forward morosely.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS261
SOMEONE observes her father with a concerned gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS262
Unfastening her seat belt, she leans forward and hugs his seat.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS263
SOMEONE raises an eyebrow and blinks at his daughter.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS264
She climbs up.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS265
Now, the car travels along a road overlooking the ocean.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS266
SOMEONE the stops the car across from a pleasant mid-century home with a copper turtle on the gate post.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS267
SOMEONE and SOMEONE duck down in their seats and discreetly cover their faces. A pickup truck passes by. SOMEONE hunches down as well.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS268
All three straighten.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS269
Working his jaw, SOMEONE briefly returns his vulnerable gaze to the stranger's house, then droops his head forward.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS270
Seen from a distance,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS271
his car's break lights blink on and he pulls away.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS272
The sedan follows the winding residential road downhill.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS274
traveling through another neighborhood, the car passes a large, beautifully landscaped house on a corner.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS275
The car backs up.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS276
A real estate sign stands posted outside the home's fence of rainbow-shaped rails.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS277
The real estate sign lists the name SOMEONE Speer and shows a happy photo of a beady-eyed man with a toothy grin.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS279
At home, trophies, medals, and beaded lace fill a set of shelves.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS280
A central photo shows a smiling SOMEONE wearing a race number on her shirt.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS283
SOMEONE uses the phone.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS284
Sitting in a day bed with a bottle of Jameson Irish Whisky at his side, SOMEONE takes a steadying breath and ends the call.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS286
As he turns off a lamp on a stand, the scene cuts to black.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS288
Now, clouds drift fast across the sky as dawn breaks at a sped up pace.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS289
Two mountains frame a distant view of fast motion traffic on a highway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS290
Just off a coast dotted with high-rises,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS291
teams of rowers paddle canoes along the rippling turquoise water.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS292
Under a now bright sky, light traffic dots a multi-lane road.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS294
In the city, an American flag and a Hawaiian state flag hang posted on either side of a building's entrance.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS296
In the hospital, a pair of windowed doors show SOMEONE arriving with his daughters in tow. He opens one door for them.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS298
They lead the way into the ward.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS299
His daughters gaze after him as he enters SOMEONE's room alone.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS300
SOMEONE shuts the door behind him, then draws a curtain covering the windows to the ward floor.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS301
He faces his wife.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS302
He glares down at his comatose wife and circles the bed.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS303
His wife lies slack-jawed and motionless.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS304
Leaning close, SOMEONE holds an anguished stare.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS305
He straightens, picking up a teddy bear from the bed.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS306
SOMEONE starts to gesture with it, then hurls it across the room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS307
Catching his breath, he smooths his graying hair and steps away.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS308
SOMEONE draws himself up and leaves the room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS309
A regal chipped frame displays a photo of a little girl with golden hair.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS310
On a windowsill, a varsity letter P stands propped against a diploma.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS311
Another photo shows a radiantly smiling SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS312
SOMEONE ambles into the hospital room, her eyes fixed on her mother.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS313
Reaching the foot of the bed, she glances at SOMEONE, then takes another step closer.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS314
Her comatose mother's chest rises and falls under her tracheostomy tube.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS315
He spanks her.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS316
He hustles SOMEONE out of the room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS317
SOMEONE's glistening eyes glance between her father and mother.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS318
She turns to face to bed.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS320
Later, SOMEONE sits next to SOMEONE, while SOMEONE reads in a chair facing the foot of the bed.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS321
SOMEONE leads a taller girl into the room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS322
SOMEONE gives a halfhearted wave.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS323
SOMEONE glances around, then joins her friend at SOMEONE's bedside.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS324
SOMEONE nods.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS325
SOMEONE exits.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS326
SOMEONE eyes her sister.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS327
SOMEONE points to SOMEONE, who guiltily averts her gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS328
SOMEONE grabs his cellphone from a counter,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS329
then leans forward heavily.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS330
The display indicates an incoming call from Gold Coast Real Estate.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS331
SOMEONE shows the cellphone to SOMEONE and her eyes widen.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS332
She grabs it from him and crosses the room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS333
She hangs up.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS334
Nodding softly, SOMEONE shifts his thoughtful gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS335
Now, over a dozen cars fill the King's driveway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS336
Inside, using chopsticks, people fill their plates with crabs and sushi.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS337
SOMEONE and SOMEONE peruse the buffet table while other guests convene in the next room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS338
A woman with short, grey hair chats with some friends.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS339
In the kitchen, SOMEONE gazes off sullenly. He takes a sip of scotch.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS340
A teenage boy enters the room and approaches him from behind.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS341
He takes another sip of his drink.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS343
SOMEONE shakes his head, struggling to retain his composure.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS344
He chuckles to himself but quickly succumbs to sobs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS345
The others look on mournfully.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS346
He wipes his nose.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS347
That evening, he crosses the driveway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS348
He waves to the last departing car as he watches it drive off.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS349
A breeze blows through the bushes flanking the end of the driveway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS350
Heading back for the house, SOMEONE shuffles across the lawn.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS351
He drops to his hands and knees, hanging his head low to the ground.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS352
Sitting back on his ankles, the weary husband rests his hands on his thighs and gazes off pensively.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS353
Now, he sits in his office over a load of paperwork.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS354
They notice the recorder in his hand.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS355
SOMEONE lowers her gaze and bites her bottom lip.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS356
Now, as a Hawaiian Airlines jet takes off, the image dissolves to the map of Hawaii with a dashed line leading from Oahu to Kauai.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS357
On the flight, SOMEONE chats with SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS358
SOMEONE listens to music.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS359
Across the aisle, SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE's black eye.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS361
He turns his wry gaze away and awkwardly finds himself face to face with the large goateed passenger to his left.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS362
SOMEONE abruptly faces forward. Later, outside an airport,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS363
a friendly-faced guy comes hurrying over.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS364
Now, a hula girl doll bobbles on the dashboard of a moving vehicle.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS365
The white open-top jeep cruises down a beachside road.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS366
The kids ride in back with the wind in their hair. SOMEONE and his cousin sit up front.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS367
The white jeep makes a left turn off the coastal highway onto a side street,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS368
then heads down a dirt road bordered by a wooden fence.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS369
A distant mountain range spans the horizon.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS370
Later, SOMEONE chains a metal gate to a wooden post and returns to the jeep, beyond which a herd of cows grazes in a field.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS372
A few cows stand in their way.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS373
Later, the jeep travels a winding dirt path wide enough for only one vehicle.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS374
Our view pulls back to encompass the landscape, which includes lush trees and rolling hills.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS376
Heading uphill, the jeep jostles its passengers.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS377
It reaches the summit of the tree-lined road and rolls to a stop.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS378
SOMEONE steps out.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS379
The others climb out as well.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS380
SOMEONE shuts his passenger door.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS382
As the group continues up the dirt road, our view turns to follow them.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS383
SOMEONE runs out on a grassy ridge past the corner of an old stone foundation.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS384
They all stop on the scenic overlook.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS385
Below lies a majestic cove of wild undeveloped land.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS386
The tide rolls in gently on the distant beach.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS387
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE with a faint smile, then sighs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS390
Hovering over the group, our view turns away from the grassy ridge, for a final glimpse of the vast cove and its pristine surroundings.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS393
Now, we pull back from a faux Italian statue of Neptune towering over the center of a fountain, with scalloped ridges evocative of an oyster shell.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS395
The jeep drives by, following a bend in the road.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS396
We drive past a sign for Sandpiper Village, another for Paniolo, then a golf course abutting a housing community.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS398
Riding in the passenger seat, SOMEONE holds his forehead as he absently gazes out his window.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS399
The jeep arrives at a hotel, driving past a fountain near the entrance.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS400
Later, at the front desk, SOMEONE folds up his wallet.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS401
A clerk looks up the name on his computer.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS403
Now, at the beach, he ambles over to a blanket where Alexandra suns her back and SOMEONE lies with her head on SOMEONE's shoulder.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS404
Her bikini top filled with lumps of sand,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS405
SOMEONE wanders over to the water to shake out the sand.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS406
SOMEONE reaches behind her back and fastens her own top as her father takes a seat.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS407
Later, strolling the beach, SOMEONE shows SOMEONE a photo of SOMEONE Speer from a real estate ad.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS408
SOMEONE and SOMEONE trail behind SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they make their way down the wet sand.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS410
We draw back to take in a wide stretch of the shoreline and the misty mountain peaks beyond.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS411
A wide, low-limbed tree shades our view.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS412
The sun sets behind the watery horizon as the foursome continues along the shore toward a distant resort,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS413
the low waves lapping gently at their ankles.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS414
Now, an adults only menu pops up on a TV screen.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS415
SOMEONE mans the remote control as her family finishes dinner in their hotel suite.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS417
SOMEONE snatches the remote.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS418
Flailing her arms, SOMEONE prances out of the room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS419
The frustrated father glances aside, then meets SOMEONE's steady gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS421
SOMEONE steps out from a bathroom and shuts off the light.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS422
He plops down on his unmade bed and sits alone in the dark.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS423
Now, SOMEONE opens a door and steps into the suite's dark living room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS424
Shuffling through the shadows, he pauses by a sofa and juts his head forward.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS426
Lying under a blanket on a fold out bed, SOMEONE rolls his head to look up at SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS428
SOMEONE stares at him, then shifts his frustrated gaze and nods.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS429
He switches on a lamp near SOMEONE's pillow.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS430
The teen shuts his eyes, frowning against the light.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS431
SOMEONE shakes his head.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS432
He shuffles around the fold out bed, shrugs, and takes a seat.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS435
SOMEONE nods thoughtfully.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS436
SOMEONE lifts his chin.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS439
SOMEONE settles into his pillows.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS440
SOMEONE gives a thoughtful nod and regards the teen.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS441
SOMEONE offers a kind smile.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS442
SOMEONE glances down ponderously, nods again, and trains a warm gaze on the boy.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS444
SOMEONE takes a deep breath.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS445
SOMEONE hunkers down and pulls his blanket up to his chin.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS446
The lamp blinks off and the scene cuts to black.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS447
Now, on a misty morning, the waves crawl up on the sandy beach beneath an overcast sky.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS448
In a faded black t-shirt, SOMEONE jogs along the shoreline. He moves with a rhythmic, purposeful gait, glancing occasionally over the slate-hued water.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS449
Some distance ahead, another jogger approaches.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS450
SOMEONE notices dismissively.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS452
As the lanky figure draws near, we recognize SOMEONE's face.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS453
The real estate agent gives a sportsmanlike wave as he passes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS454
SOMEONE returns the gesture, then halts and stares back at him.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS455
His brow knits and he takes off after SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS456
He quickens his pace, struggling to catch up to his wife's lover.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS457
But SOMEONE's long-legged stride keeps him several yards ahead.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS458
SOMEONE works his way up to a sprint, staring at SOMEONE through wild eyes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS459
The real estate agent turns and trots up the beach toward a row of hedges.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS460
SOMEONE pauses, watching him run toward a gate-like gap in the greenery.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS461
As SOMEONE passes out of sight, the wronged husband dashes toward the hedge line.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS462
Glancing over his shoulder, he slows, then quickens his pace to a reckless scramble.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS463
He arrives at the hedge and ducks behind it near the gap.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS464
Seen from inside, the gap shows SOMEONE darting across to take cover behind the opposite hedge.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS465
He peeks up over the top and finds SOMEONE climbing steps
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS466
to a one-story home with a broad roof, a full-length porch, and a sprawling lawn.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS467
SOMEONE stares, only the top half of his face visible,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS468
as SOMEONE kicks off his running shoes and goes inside.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS469
Staying put, SOMEONE narrows his eyes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS470
SOMEONE comes back out, guzzling water from a bottle.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS471
He descends halfway down the porch steps, then leans back against a supporting pillar.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS473
A pretty woman with strawberry blond hair comes out, trailed by two boys.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS474
They bring plates and cups to a table on the lawn.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS475
SOMEONE's arched eyebrows knit and his eyes narrow.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS477
He slowly sinks out of view.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS478
Now, sitting on a blanket on the beach, SOMEONE leans back on his hands.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS479
Beside him, SOMEONE lies down and chats with a reclining Sid.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS481
Several yards ahead, SOMEONE's form bobs in and out of view as she plays in the ocean.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS482
As SOMEONE watches her, he shoots frequent glances over his shoulder toward SOMEONE's rental.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS483
Behind him, the strawberry blond emerges with her young boys.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS484
SOMEONE notices, as the boys race to the water.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS485
The woman slows to a walk. Wearing a sun hat and a long-sleeved shirt of sky blue,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS487
she drops a large, fashionable tote in the sand, walks to the water's edge, and cups her hands around her mouth.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS488
The boys splash each other rambunctiously.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS489
SOMEONE leans toward SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS490
SOMEONE rolls over and sits up.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS491
She glances toward SOMEONE, then gazes after her father curiously.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS494
SOMEONE meanders down to the water's edge and stops a few feet from the woman.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS495
In her sweater and black bikini bottoms, she watches her boys at play.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS496
The woman grins good-naturedly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS497
SOMEONE bites back a comment and faces the water.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS498
The woman offers a sincere concerned frown.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS499
SOMEONE musters a smile.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS500
The mother faces the water.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS501
Watching her, SOMEONE adopts a breezy demeanor.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS502
SOMEONE twitches himself out of a statue-like hold.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS503
SOMEONE marches from the water.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS504
As SOMEONE joins SOMEONE, Mrs. SOMEONE's smile fades and she watches him with a furrowed brow.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS505
Now, shafts of sunlight beam through gaps in the clouds, lighting up patches of the ocean.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS507
In a forest, a rusted metal bridge spans a green brook.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS509
Raindrops plop into the placid water, dotting it with tiny percolations.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS510
Now, SOMEONE, his daughters, and SOMEONE walk toward an inviting ragtag bungalow with a porch and white-fenced yard.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS511
A sign out front reads "Tahiti Nui Restaurant Cocktail Lounge".
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS512
SOMEONE leads the way up to the porch, then through the doorway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS513
The family pauses near the threshold, taking in the thriving casual hot spot.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS514
On a small stage, three male singers perform on stools as they strum a guitar, a ukulele, and a bass.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS515
Scanning the restaurant, SOMEONE spots a man with grey, shoulder-length hair at the bar.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS516
SOMEONE sidles down the narrow gap between the bar and a wall, then rounds a corner to the other side and joins SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS517
SOMEONE stares confusedly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS518
SOMEONE lowers his thunderstruck gaze, then faces the stage.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS519
SOMEONE adopts a nonchalant air. SOMEONE's easygoing smile fades.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS520
SOMEONE regards his cousin with a flinty stare. Looking away, he puts on a smile.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS521
With a worried frown, SOMEONE bridles, and blinks at his cousin.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS522
SOMEONE gets up.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS523
The cousins hug and SOMEONE sends SOMEONE off with an affectionate rub of the head.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS524
The shell shocked man lumbers across the dining area.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS525
Reaching his table, he collapses into a chair and leans back heavily.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS526
He stares off with glistening eyes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS527
SOMEONE lifts his brow and blinks back his tears.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS529
Taking a breath, he shakes himself out of his thoughts.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS530
SOMEONE, who is seated between his daughters, faces us as though we're in SOMEONE's position.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS531
SOMEONE bobs to the music.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS532
SOMEONE looks at us.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS533
SOMEONE's looking at us as he replies. His gaze wilts. He glances at the band, then rubs his face.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS534
His weary profile shows against the backdrop of the lively performers. He idly surveys the bar, then peers over his shoulder,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS535
giving us a view of his distracted face head on.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS536
Now, under a dusky sky, SOMEONE, his daughters, and SOMEONE walk alongside a fence that borders a green field.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS537
Mountains loom in the distance. SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk a few paces ahead.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS538
SOMEONE bites her lip.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS539
At night, SOMEONE addresses SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS540
He leaves with SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS541
SOMEONE and SOMEONE make their way across the narrow road.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS542
Walking side by side, they advance on the large cottage occupied by the Speers.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS543
Moving around the house, they find Mrs. Speer coming out onto the back porch.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS544
SOMEONE's wife turns.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS545
SOMEONE mouths "Howdy".
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS546
SOMEONE comes out.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS547
SOMEONE's grin falters.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS548
SOMEONE goes inside.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS549
SOMEONE conjures his toothy grin.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS550
His smile vanishes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS551
SOMEONE responds with a hangdog stare.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS552
Behind SOMEONE, indoors, SOMEONE gets drinks.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS553
SOMEONE returns.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS554
Holding his wife close, SOMEONE forces a carefree grin. SOMEONE smiles pleasantly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS555
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's side.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS556
As SOMEONE stares after them, SOMEONE steps into his line of sight with a firm glare.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS557
The real estate agent obediently opens the screen door. The two men go in.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS558
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE anxiously.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS559
SOMEONE leans on a counter.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS560
SOMEONE's lips form a tearful pout.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS562
SOMEONE looks away and licks his lips.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS563
Straightening, he faces SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS564
SOMEONE draws his dumbfounded mouth shut and nods.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS565
SOMEONE's gaze grows melancholy.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS566
SOMEONE looks down shamefully.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS567
SOMEONE responds with a bitter sneer and shakes his head.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS568
SOMEONE lowers his remorseful gaze and his lips pucker.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS569
SOMEONE bristles.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS570
His jaw tightens and he holds SOMEONE in a weary, disdainful stare.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS572
He exits the cottage.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS573
As she leans in to hug him, SOMEONE tilts his head and gives her a full kiss on the lips instead.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS574
With an intense stare, he heads off, leaving SOMEONE confused.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS575
Now, on the flight back, SOMEONE stares off pensively.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS576
Sitting behind him, SOMEONE scoots forward in her seat and claps a hand on his shoulder.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS577
SOMEONE nods faintly. Her father turns away and hangs his head.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS578
In the window seat beside her big sister, SOMEONE sleeps with
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS579
a pillow between her head and the wall.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS580
As she stirs a little, getting comfortable, the image dissolves to a corridor in the hospital.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS581
SOMEONE, his daughters, and SOMEONE trudge in from around a corner.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS584
As the girls approach SOMEONE's bed, SOMEONE wraps her arm around her sister's shoulders. They gaze at their unresponsive mother.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS585
She lies with each hand curled around a rolled up towel and her mouth hanging slack.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS586
Now, a kind-faced woman addresses SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS587
SOMEONE, Dr. SOMEONE, and SOMEONE look on from in front of SOMEONE's bed.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS588
The grief counselor's lips form a sympathetic line.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS589
SOMEONE's eyes fill with tears and she turns to her father.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS590
Seeing his woeful look, she lowers her gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS591
The kind-faced counselor strokes SOMEONE's arm.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS592
Her lips trembling, the girl turns back to face her.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS593
As the counselor continues speaking, SOMEONE's face crumples in anguish.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS594
The bereaved little girl watches the woman leave with Dr. SOMEONE,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS596
then embraces her father, burying her face in his chest.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS597
He kisses the top of her head.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS598
He caresses her hair, then tilts her face up to meet his gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS599
SOMEONE gently slides her hands down her sister's ponytail.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS600
Cradling SOMEONE's head,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS601
SOMEONE lifts his eyes to his older daughter.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS602
SOMEONE pushes out a breath and shifts her attention to her mother.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS603
Later, our view shifts from SOMEONE's bed
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS604
to SOMEONE doing paperwork and SOMEONE and SOMEONE reading books.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS605
From the corridor, SOMEONE peers into the room, then enters with his wife and son behind him.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS606
SOMEONE sets aside his work.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS607
He and SOMEONE hug SOMEONE and his frail mother.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS608
As SOMEONE leads her uncle and grandmother to SOMEONE's bedside, SOMEONE shifts his gaze to SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS609
The boy gives him a sullen look, then turns away.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS610
SOMEONE scowls at his father-in-law, then stares off bitterly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS611
Closing his eyes, he lets his head droop.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS612
A faint smile briefly plays on SOMEONE's face as he gives the teens a surprised look.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS613
SOMEONE shrugs his lips, then joins his family at SOMEONE's bedside.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS614
SOMEONE gestures to SOMEONE and SOMEONE and they follow him into the corridor.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS615
He pulls the door closed.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS616
Opening the door a crack, SOMEONE peeks back into the room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS617
SOMEONE and SOMEONE move in close to him and they all spy on standing at his daughter's bedside.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS620
The grief-stricken man gives a helpless shrug,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS621
then leans over SOMEONE and strokes her hair.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS622
The three outside watch sympathetically.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS623
Resting his hand on his daughter's head, SOMEONE bends down and gives her a light kiss on the cheek.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS624
The onlookers watch him whisper "I love you".
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS625
He continues caressing his daughter's hair.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS626
Tightening his lips defeatedly, he withdraws his hand.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS627
He lifts his gaze from his dying daughter and glances, unfocused, toward the doorway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS628
In the morning, sunlight peeks through a blanket of clouds
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS629
and shines down on a lush mountain ridge.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS630
At home, SOMEONE sleeps with his face resting on his cluttered desk.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS631
One of his fingers twitches and he awakes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS632
With a frown, he sits up.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS633
Blinking groggily, he looks at his watch, then leans forward on his elbows and shifts his thoughtful eyes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS634
He pushes his chair back from the desk and rises.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS635
He exits past the portraits of his great great grandparents.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS636
The image dissolves to a sprawling wind-blown property.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS637
SOMEONEs car glides toward a fork in a long driveway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS638
To one side lies a large ranch style house and a tennis court.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS639
On the other, grazing ducks scatter as SOMEONE pulls over onto a well-manicured lawn and parks.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS641
Now, he enters the large house, allowing sunlight to filter through the screen door into the unlit living room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS643
As he pushes open the curtains on the front windows,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS644
more daylight washes over a wall decorated with framed photos.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS645
He strolls past it,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS648
then stops and gazes at the black and white images of his ancestors.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS649
A mustached man gives a serious look. Another shows a frizzy-haired woman.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS650
In a third photo, four men in suits stand on a building's front steps.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS652
Behind the glass of a large frame, wooden block letters spell out "Kikila". Above an antique photo of a man with a mutton chop beard, a plaque beside it reads "Cecil Kikila King. the namesake of this beautiful place. He was a prominent attorney, banker, and socialite in old Hawaii. ".
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS658
SOMEONE eyes more photos of family members throughout the years. two men and two women in 1920s era garb.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS664
Leaving the photos, SOMEONE steps out onto the lawn.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS665
A group of about 40 suddenly fades into view -
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS666
some at picnic tables, others standing around chatting.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS667
One of the King cousins breaks off from the socializing to place a folded slip of paper in a large wooden bowl,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS668
then sets down a pen.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS669
SOMEONE laughs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS670
Wink smokes a cigar.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS671
SOMEONE talks with SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS672
Dogs laze about in the grass at their owner's feet.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS673
Two more cousins drop off folded slips of paper into the wooden bowl.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS674
Now, SOMEONE stares off with doleful eyes as he sits at a table.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS675
SOMEONE unfolds a ballot and reads it.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS676
He hands SOMEONE paperwork.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS677
He offers a pen.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS678
Frowning, SOMEONE takes it, then flips through the paperwork.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS679
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch with encouraging smiles.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS680
SOMEONE thoughtfully hovers his pen over the blank signature line.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS681
He gazes at the documents.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS682
SOMEONE furrows his bushy eyebrows.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS683
SOMEONE glances at his two cousins, then looks back at the contract and shakes his head.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS684
SOMEONE and SOMEONE give him shocked looks.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS685
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, then shakes his head with a frustrated smile.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS686
Tossing the documents aside, he gives his cousins a resolute look.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS687
SOMEONE lifts his brow and shares a thoughtful glance with SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS688
The long-haired, heavyset cousin smirks disapprovingly at SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS689
He rubs his nose then stands.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS690
The crowd looks over.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS691
He slaps SOMEONE's shoulder.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS692
Rising from his chair, SOMEONE faces the group and gives them a nod.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS693
They all watch him expectantly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS694
The scene in front of him fades to SOMEONE's hospital room, where our view edges closer to the back of his head
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS695
as he watches his family.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS696
Now, we travel up the bed quilt to SOMEONE's hands
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS697
still curled loosely around the towel rolls.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS698
Just above the neckline of her hospital gown,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS699
a gauze dressing covers the stoma in her trachea,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS700
its center dampened with a moist circle.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS701
Her mouth hangs open, her lips dry and slightly parched,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS702
while her head lies tilted to one side.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS703
On a couch, SOMEONE lies asleep.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS704
SOMEONE sits lazily in a chair with one leg crooked upward as he somberly does homework.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS705
Slouched in another seat, SOMEONE stares at her dying mother.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS706
Our view drifts closer to her plaintive face as she blinks tears from her eyes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS708
As the door opens, SOMEONE peers over her shoulder and sees a woman entering,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS709
her face obscured by a large bouquet held in front of it.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS710
SOMEONE stares with surprised eyes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS711
Lowering the flowers, SOMEONE Speer glances between him and SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS712
The teen shoots her father a questioning look.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS714
SOMEONE stands.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS715
SOMEONE forces a pained smile.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS716
She puts on her shoes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS717
SOMEONE flashes a polite smile at SOMEONE, who follows SOMEONE and SOMEONE out.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS718
SOMEONE opens his mouth as if to speak, then shrugs his hands.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS719
He and SOMEONE turn toward SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS720
She gives him a pointed look
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS721
and he nods sadly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS722
SOMEONE glances uncertainly at his wife.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS723
Shifting her tearful eyes to SOMEONE, SOMEONE steps to her side.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS724
While SOMEONE watches from the foot of the bed,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS725
SOMEONE's face contorts in anguish as she gazes at the comatose woman.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS726
She stares down at SOMEONE's frozen, slack-jawed expression.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS727
SOMEONE nods empathetically.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS728
SOMEONE gently takes her arm, guides her to the door, then stops and meets her gaze.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS729
With a nod, SOMEONE opens the door for her.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS730
SOMEONE shuts it and sighs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS731
He turns his back to the door and stares across the room at SOMEONE in her bed.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS732
Remaining fixed on her, SOMEONE draws and expels a deep breath,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS733
then ambles across the room and stands at her bedside.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS734
The middle-aged man's weary gaze grows affectionate as he reaches out to her.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS736
Looking over her frail form, he breathes softly.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS737
His fingers caress the pale woman's hair just above her forehead.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS738
With a fond look in his eyes,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS739
he smiles.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS740
He bends down and leans over her, his fingers lingering on her brow.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS741
He gives her a long, gentle kiss on the lips, then remains
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS743
hovering just inches above her.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS744
A tear rolls down his nose.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS747
In a waiting area, SOMEONE sits beside her father with tears in her eyes.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS748
Our view drifts to SOMEONE's weary face as he stares across the room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS749
The door to SOMEONE's room opens.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS750
SOMEONE steps out, her eyes puffy and red.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS751
SOMEONE crosses the hallway toward her family.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS752
SOMEONE rises from his chair and faces her.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS754
SOMEONE hugs her father.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS756
Resting her chin on his shoulder, she gazes upward.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS757
He kisses her temple, then stands aside as she crosses to SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS758
She gives her shaggy-haired friend a hug.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS759
Peering over his shoulder with her arm wrapped around his neck.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS760
SOMEONE faces her younger sister.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS761
Gazing up from her chair, SOMEONE purses her lips.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS762
SOMEONE offers her hands, then guides her sister up from her seat.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS763
She wraps her arm around the girl and they head off together.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS764
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch SOMEONE lead SOMEONE across the hallway
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS765
SOMEONE lead SOMEONE into SOMEONE's room.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS766
Now, a puffy cumulus cloud dominates the lower half of a sky view.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS767
Its vapor edge forms fanciful bulges and dips across the blueness green vegetation blankets a mountain range.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS771
On the yet unsold land, the overlook offers a majestic view of the cove and the meadows and wild groves inland of it.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS773
Beyond a line of breaking waves, vibrant shades of ocean blue extend to the horizon meeting powder blue sky.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS776
The blossoms of a plumeria flutter in a breeze, their petals in shades of yellow and pink.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS778
Now, sitting aboard an outrigger canoe, SOMEONE nods and accepts a container.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS779
She wears a pink and white lei around her neck.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS781
SOMEONE watches his daughter from across the boat, wearing a lei of autumn colors.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS782
They float about a mile from the urban coastline.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS783
SOMEONE draws a scoop of ashes from the container and looks at her father.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS784
He shifts his serene gaze, then gives her a soft nod.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS785
The peaceful young woman looks at the ashes and purses her lips.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS786
Sitting in the middle of the boat,
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS787
SOMEONE watches her sister pour the scoop of ashes into the water.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS788
SOMEONE hands the container to her.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS790
They younger girl tearfully takes hold of the scoop handle, but lets go of it and passes the canister on to SOMEONE.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS791
The middle-aged widower gazes at the gray dust.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS792
A skyward view from the ashes shows a breeze blowing through his grey hair.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS793
The girls watch as he holds the container over the side of the boat
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS794
and pours the rest of SOMEONE's ashes into the sea.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS795
He taps the container against the side of the canoe to empty it completely.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS797
SOMEONE watches the ashes mix with the water, then glances at his daughters.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS798
He takes off his lei and sets it on the water.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS799
SOMEONE and SOMEONE do the same.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS800
They watch their leis floating beside the boat, bobbing on the surface.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS802
Seen from underwater, the leis show in silhouette against the gleaming sunlight.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS803
They take on amoeba-like shapes as they float beside the canoe.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS809
SOMEONE lies on the couch under a blanket.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS811
Beyond the couch, SOMEONE steps out from an arched doorway with two bowls. In shorts and a Hawaiian shirt, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE and hands her one of the bowls.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS812
SOMEONE sits on the couch and rests his feet on an ottoman.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS814
As they eat their ice cream, SOMEONE enters the distant dining room and digs through a bag on the table.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS815
SOMEONE adjusts the end of SOMEONE's blanket and covers his legs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS816
SOMEONE notices them from the dining room and strides observantly through an archway.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS817
Arms folded, she halts behind the ice cream eating pair.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS819
SOMEONE drops her arms to her sides, then steps around the couch and takes a seat
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS821
beside her father, forcing him more into the middle as she takes a corner of the blanket.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS823
As they remain focused on their movie, SOMEONE helps SOMEONE lay the blanket over her legs.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS824
He hands her his bowl of ice cream and she rests it on her lap.
THE_DESCENDANTS_DVS825
As the trio watch the movie together,