SOMEONE jogs after the hurrying stilt-walker.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS25
Still in his Uncle SOMEONE jacket and beard, the young man races across a building's roof. He halts at its edge and eyes a police van below.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS26
At ground level, SOMEONE sprints past the burning parade float. On the roof the young man scampers one way then races back the other way with SOMEONE on his tail. The rugged man chases his target to the roof's edge where the young man leaps off. SOMEONE follows. They land on the police van, then hit the ground hard. Police surround them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS27
SOMEONE hands an officer his badge and ID.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS28
SOMEONE gingerly gets to his feet.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS29
SOMEONE grabs the young man and cuffs him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS30
The officer cuffs SOMEONE. Now, SOMEONE steps off an elevator - phone in hand - and strides past a reception desk. Golden letters behind it read, Daily News.  She passes a colleague.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS31
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE's rear.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS32
SOMEONE enters a newsroom. As she heads to her desk, a mustached man watches her shapely bottom. SOMEONE finds a print-out of her mugshot taped to her computer.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS33
A sticky-note reads, Don't forget court tomorrow. Mr. Ed.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS34
The mustached man sits by her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS35
Meanwhile, police officers mingle at a bar. The bartender answers the phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS36
SOMEONE jots on a coaster.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS37
In a stall, SOMEONE hangs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS38
She claps her feet together.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS39
As she bursts out of the stall, SOMEONE exits a different one.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS40
She leaves. SOMEONE grins at the mirror.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS41
He plucks a tissue from a box. Later, SOMEONE strolls across the roof of an apartment building.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS42
Reaching a corner, she leans on a railing and peers over the edge. She shakes her head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS43
She takes her phone from her bag and answers it as she returns to the roof's corner.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS44
At a spa, SOMEONE talks on phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS46
Nighttime at a police station, a man in a sport coat approaches a jail cell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS47
He shows a badge on his belt. An officer releases SOMEONE from the cell. Now, SOMEONE and his police friend eat at a diner.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS48
As SOMEONE chomps into a taco doused with hot sauce, his friend swigs a coke.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS49
SOMEONE drops his taco on his plate.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS50
Now at a courthouse, a man uses his phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS51
A cab pulls up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS52
She answers her phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS53
He hangs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS55
the judge follows SOMEONE's gaze to the closed double-doors.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS56
Meanwhile, in the parking lot of a Dunkin' Donuts and a Baskin Robbins plaza,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS57
SOMEONE sits in his car, nervously tapping his steering wheel. He glances over his shoulder and blows out an impatient breath.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS58
A man smashes his window with a crowbar.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS60
He pulls SOMEONE out of his car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS61
He shoves him into an SUV.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS62
As he slams the door, a cab pulls into the parking lot. SOMEONE climbs out and sees the chiseled stranger speeding away in his black SUV.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS63
She frowns. Now, in another neighborhood a portly man exits the front door of a house with an adjoining storefront.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS64
He opens a gate. As he follows the sidewalk, he roots around in the pocket of his cargo shorts and pulls out a set of keys. Stopping at the storefront's glass door, he unlocks it and heads inside. A sign on the window reads, Sid's Bail Bonds. The portly man flips on the lights and finds SOMEONE asleep, sprawled across a leather loveseat.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS65
SOMEONE groggily opens his eyes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS66
SOMEONE sits up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS67
Later, SOMEONE packs his station wagon.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS68
He reaches for his pocket.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS69
He hands SOMEONE a folded piece of paper. The bounty hunter opens it and finds SOMEONE's mugshot.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS70
He meets SOMEONE's gaze.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS71
SOMEONE grins.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS72
SOMEONE does a dance.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS73
He hugs SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS74
He kisses him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS75
SOMEONE takes the check from SOMEONE's red-headed assistant and gives her a long, deep kiss.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS76
SOMEONE takes it from his mouth and puts it in hers.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS77
Now at his place, a freshly showered SOMEONE grins at his reflection in a bathroom mirror as he brushes his teeth. Later, he packs a Taser and two guns into a bag. He heads outside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS78
Now, he rings SOMEONE's bell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS79
He jiggles the locked door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS80
SOMEONE scales a wall and lands in a muddy flowerbed. Tracking footprints, he enters SOMEONE's apartment through a back door and eyes her tasteful decor.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS81
As he strolls into the spacious living room, SOMEONE notices his muddy footprints on a light rug. With a grin, he steps to the side dragging his foot and tracking a long smear. In the bathroom, he drops SOMEONE's toothbrush in the toilet, then places it back in its holder. In the bedroom, he lounges on SOMEONE's bed - his muddy shoes on her duvet. He snacks on a pile of nacho cheese Doritos, spilled conveniently within reach.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS82
SOMEONE deletes saved episodes of Weeds and 30 Rock from SOMEONE's TiVo. Meanwhile, SOMEONE keys into a clean white front door. As she enters, SOMEONE freezes on the bed and glances toward the hall. Chewing Doritos, he tosses down the remote and wipes his mouth and hands on a pillow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS83
SOMEONE searches a small pink-tiled bathroom. SOMEONE draws his gun and creeps into the hall.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS84
SOMEONE peers around a corner.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS85
SOMEONE skulks down the stairs.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS86
SOMEONE defensively grabs a picture frame and presses her back to a wall by a white-trim doorway.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS87
As she turns the corner, SOMEONE reaches the white door frame at the bottom of the stairs. They both turn the corner.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS88
SOMEONE scares a cat.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS89
SOMEONE aims his gun at SOMEONE. SOMEONE's at a completely different address.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS90
Back at her place,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS91
SOMEONE aims at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS92
SOMEONE cocks his head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS94
the cat hides under a chair.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS95
SOMEONE frowns.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS97
he swigs juice from a carton.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS98
SOMEONE smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS99
SOMEONE's grin vanishes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS100
SOMEONE grabs the phone and hits redial.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS101
He hits the disconnect button.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS102
Now, in SOMEONE's pink-tiled bathroom, SOMEONE searches a vanity then picks through dirty laundry strewn around the tub. She finds a bar coaster in a pair of jeans. A note on the back reads, Audit Evidence Depository. Missing shit.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS103
Now, on her cell, she crosses the Verrazano-Narrows Bridge.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS104
SOMEONE exits an evidence locker while on his cell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS105
Now, SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE's building. As he gets into his car, SOMEONE creeps outside and scurries over to a red MINI Cooper.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS106
Now, a bird's-eye view shows SOMEONE's car exiting a tunnel and approaching a toll plaza. Later, the baby blue ragtop crosses the bridge.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS107
Later still, it drives beneath an overpass sign reading, Welcome to Atlantic City. A billboard, featuring SOMEONE's mother, reads, Kitty Borgata.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS108
Now, we glimpse lavish buildings housing Atlantic City's hotel casinos. In a lounge, Kitty stands in the spotlight on a stage.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS109
SOMEONE enters and smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS110
Shading her eyes, Kitty peers out at him, he waves.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS111
She slaps him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS112
Kitty gives him a big hug.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS113
she slips off her pumps.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS114
SOMEONE brightens.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS115
At a racetrack, people crowd the stands. An older woman rubs sunblock on her bare arms. A young woman in a flowered hat eyes her tickets. Jockeys ride their horses toward the starting gate. The race begins and the animals burst onto the track. Two young women cheer. Sitting alone on a long bench, SOMEONE thoughtfully pieces through her collective notes, which include the coaster.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS116
She digs her cell from her purse and answers.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS117
Standing near a corral, SOMEONE grins.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS118
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE sharing her bench.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS119
He affects a nonchalant shake of the head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS120
SOMEONE's brow nits distrustfully.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS121
SOMEONE looks away, shifting her wary gaze then frowns at him again. He smirks.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS122
Standing, he steps before her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS123
SOMEONE smiles and shakes her head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS124
She starts to go. His leg blocks her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS126
A race starts and SOMEONE runs too.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS127
She hurries up an aisle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS128
The horses race down the track.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS129
SOMEONE rubs his hands together, inhales through them, and dashes off.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS130
As SOMEONE trots through a picnic area, SOMEONE sprints through a lobby. Emerging outside, SOMEONE finds him blocking her path.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS131
She runs off the other way. We glimpse the racing horses' legs, SOMEONE's high heels, and SOMEONE's sneakered feet. At a concession stand, he cuts SOMEONE off and offers popcorn.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS132
She bats it away and flees. On a patio, SOMEONE intercepts her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS133
She passes him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS134
SOMEONE's four-inch stiletto heels carry her out to a drop-off area.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS135
She approaches two rows of waiting cabs parked along a curb. SOMEONE's convertible arrives, blocking them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS136
SOMEONE gets out, steps in her path, and draws a gun.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS137
She brushes past him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS138
As SOMEONE swaggers over, she tensely faces him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS139
He steps in close.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS140
Finding herself head to head with her ex, SOMEONE backs up a pace.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS141
He hefts her over his shoulder.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS142
She slaps at his back as he carries her to his car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS143
He pops the trunk and dumps her in.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS144
SOMEONE hurries toward him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS145
In the trunk,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS146
she smacks the lid. Her ex-husband backs the car up then pulls away. SOMEONE watches helplessly.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS147
He rushes off. Now, a storefront sign reads, Blue Ink Tattoos.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS148
Inside, SOMEONE's captor readies a needle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS149
Duct tape holds SOMEONE's head in place.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS150
His captor waves the needle in his face.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS151
The chiseled thug blinks.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS152
At Sid's Bail Bonds, Teresa chews gum as she strolls to the phone and answers it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS153
SOMEONE checks his cell display.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS154
SOMEONE takes the incoming call.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS155
The thug holds him at gunpoint.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS156
She hits her head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS157
The thug flips SOMEONE's phone shut.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS158
Outside, the thug makes a call.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS159
Reaching his SUV, he ends the call and gets in. He sets down a newspaper article featuring SOMEONE's name and photo as the credited writer.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS160
In his car, SOMEONE notices smoke wafting from the back.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS161
Later, he pops the trunk. SOMEONE throws the flare aside and punches SOMEONE in the crotch. He chases her down the shoulder then tackles her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS162
Now, In Atlantic City, a storefront sign reads, Souvenirs, SOMEONE's Gifts. The hulking goateed guy, SOMEONE, arrives sporting two black eyes and a gash across his nose He heads inside and lumbers to the rear.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS163
He enters a dingy backroom where bookies work at stations along a table. As he arrives at a desk, an aging blonde swivels to face him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS164
SOMEONE shifts his sheepish gaze.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS165
At night at a gas station, SOMEONE sits handcuffed to SOMEONE's passenger door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS166
SOMEONE washes the windshield.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS167
She gives a resigned shrug.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS168
SOMEONE imagines Teresa chewing her gum and popping a bubble.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS169
He replaces the gas nozzle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS170
He leans on his open window.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS171
Later, Atlantic City's hotel casinos gleam in the night air. SOMEONE works his jaw driving his blue convertible past them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS172
She offers him a wad of cash.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS173
She studies him skeptically.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS174
She smells the cash.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS175
SOMEONE pouts then licks his lips.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS176
Later, he unlocks her handcuffs and lets her out of the car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS177
Now, from his MINI Cooper, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE's car arrive at the Taj Mahal Casino.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS178
With SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS179
SOMEONE checks his phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS180
He hits a button
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS181
In the casino.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS182
Now, SOMEONE drives into the Taj Mahal parking lot.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS183
Out of his car, he creeps up alongside SOMEONE's Delta '88.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS184
He knocks on the trunk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS185
He presses an ear to the trunk and listens.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS186
He opens the driver side door and pops the trunk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS187
He finds it empty.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS188
SOMEONE looks on.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS189
He points at the car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS190
SOMEONE slams SOMEONE's head against the trunk. SOMEONE crumbles. Now, at a craps table,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS191
he shows her the dice.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS192
SOMEONE frowns. SOMEONE quirks his brow at her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS193
She reluctantly purses her lips and blows on the dice.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS194
He rolls a seven.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS195
A croupier's hand nudges a tall stack of chips toward SOMEONE. Later, SOMEONE blows on the dice again.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS196
She gawks and SOMEONE points excitedly. The stickman returns the dice to him, a croupier adds two more stacks of chips to his winnings, and SOMEONE and SOMEONE both blow on the dice.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS197
The bounty hunter rolls a seven.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS198
SOMEONE fans herself nervously.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS199
The croupier awards SOMEONE two more stacks. Now, SOMEONE blows on the dice repeatedly.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS200
SOMEONE cheers throwing her hands in the air.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS201
She starts off.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS202
He grabs her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS203
He shows the dice but she keeps her lips together.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS204
The stickman eyes SOMEONE, who throws the dice.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS205
He rolls.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS206
Later, in a hallway.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS207
Now, they enter a spacious and eclectic suite.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS208
SOMEONE weaves past boldly upholstered furniture.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS209
She admires the chic lamps and mod accessories.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS210
He cuffs her to the headboard, plops down their bags, and heads out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS211
As he stalks out, she flings a vase after him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS212
Trapped by the handcuffs, she plops onto the bed. SOMEONE struts out of the room and presses an elevator call button. He rubs his hands together then primps in a mirror.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS213
He boards the elevator, presses a button, and snaps open the check from Teresa.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS214
He kisses it and the elevator closes. Later, it opens revealing a disheveled SOMEONE clutching a drink. His shirt half untucked and his collar sticking up, he staggers out and drains the glass.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS215
Now he stumbles down the hall, leaning against a wall for support. The drunken man takes a rest then hobbles forward and bends over his door lock. He disappears inside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS216
In the bedroom, SOMEONE lies asleep. Her handcuffed arm leaning vertically against the headboard. SOMEONE eyes her, swaying, then sets his gun on the nightstand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS217
Later, on his side, he turns off the light.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS218
He flops onto his back fully dressed and in his shoes and scooches around getting comfy.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS219
Later, SOMEONE's eyes spring open.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS220
Raising her brow, she looks around thoughtfully, then sits up and peeks over at SOMEONE. Just past him, she spots his gun on the nightstand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS221
SOMEONE lies on her back then rolls toward him,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS222
sliding the handcuff along the top rail of the headboard.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS223
She props herself up on her hands and knees then inches closer and reaches for the gun with her free hand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS224
Her fingers fall short. She tips off balance but catches herself before landing on top of SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS225
SOMEONE braces herself on the headboard, digs her feet into the comforter, and makes her downward facing body as stiff as a board.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS226
She carefully straddles SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS227
He drowsily opens his eyes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS228
She musters a smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS229
She playfully smacks the headboard.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS230
She cranes her lips close to his.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS231
He raises his gun in front of her face.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS232
She rears back.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS233
She climbs off.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS234
She turns her back to him and punches her pillow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS235
He eyes her, smiling.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS236
Daytime. A mural on a slim, brick building bears SOMEONE's name. SOMEONE enters the back room with a pizza.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS237
SOMEONE raises a golf club to let Ray pass.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS238
He leads SOMEONE into a grungy bathroom where SOMEONE sits handcuffed to a pipe.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS239
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the golf club.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS240
SOMEONE hits him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS241
Now, in the suite.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS242
SOMEONE finds herself alone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS243
A maid enters.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS244
She peeks into the bedroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS245
SOMEONE glances at the handcuff.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS246
In the bathroom, SOMEONE steps out of the shower, tucking a towel around his waist.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS247
In the bedroom, SOMEONE zips up SOMEONE's satchel. She tugs at the handcuff then hunkers down and winds up swinging the bag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS248
She flings it across the room.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS249
It misses the ottoman and lands on the floor.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS250
In the bathroom, SOMEONE looks up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS251
As he opens the door, SOMEONE lies down and mimes a yawn.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS252
She sits up and looks around.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS253
She points at the handcuff.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS254
He unlocks her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS255
Massaging her wrist, SOMEONE strides to the bathroom. She sees SOMEONE following her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS256
He glances at her low-cut top then ogles her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS257
She shrugs theatrically and enters the bathroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS258
He steps up to the doors.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS259
In the bathroom, SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's Taser from under her skirt.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS260
She turns it on.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS262
She tasers him in the neck. SOMEONE convulses and crumples. SOMEONE skips over him and grabs her bag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS263
Later, at the elevators, she presses the call button.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS264
One opens behind her and she hurries aboard, shoes in hand. Another elevator opens and the chiseled thug strides out. He glimpses SOMEONE as her elevator closes. He quickly presses the call button.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS266
as the thug searches for her a pedicab pulls up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS267
SOMEONE hops into the shaded seat.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS268
They ride away.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS269
SOMEONE looks in her bag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS270
The driver checks her out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS271
SOMEONE looks off and gives a half-wince, half-smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS272
Later, SOMEONE pedals the stolen pedicab by herself.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS273
The teenager chases her on foot. She rides down a ramp. Now, in the hotel suite's bathroom, SOMEONE awakens on the floor. Holding his head, he sits up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS274
Later, an aerial view shows his baby-blue Delta driving away from the Taj Mahal. Behind the wheel, SOMEONE eyes the two-inch red SOMEONE on his neck in the rear-view mirror then touches it and winces.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS275
Now, SOMEONE struggles to pedal down a highway. Cringing, she leans wearily over the handlebars.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS276
SOMEONE spots the pedicab from a block behind and gives a vengeful smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS277
SOMEONE spots him and scowls. She pedals faster.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS278
He drives up and taps the back of the pedicab with his bumper.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS279
SOMEONE gapes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS280
SOMEONE accelerates and taps her again. Several other vehicles speed past them. SOMEONE drives up close behind her then backs off. SOMEONE pedals exhaustedly then halts, slumping. SOMEONE stops inches behind her then scoots forward and bumps the pedicab again.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS281
SOMEONE sneers. A sedan passes them and she climbs off the bike.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS282
She grabs up her purse and glares at him, then stalks around to the passenger door and reaches for the handle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS283
SOMEONE backs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS284
He shifts into park and raises both hands innocently. SOMEONE glances around. She treads back to the door, her eyes locked on SOMEONE's.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS285
As she reaches for the handle, the car lurches forward.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS286
SOMEONE winces, stifling tears, then stares off. SOMEONE eyes her churlishly.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS287
Her lips tighten and she shakes her head, looking skyward.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS288
She claps a hand to her mouth.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS289
SOMEONE glances away.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS290
SOMEONE brushes her hair out of her face then sobs into her hand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS291
He shifts the car into park, gets out, and faces his ex-wife.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS292
She stays put. Her posture wounded and childlike.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS293
He knits his brow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS294
SOMEONE tugs on the door handle, which sticks, then gives.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS295
She climbs into the seat and slams the door shut.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS296
SOMEONE looks over his shoulder and spots a billboard in a field.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS297
It reads, Cupid's Cabin and shows a picture of a bed and breakfast in a Victorian style mansion.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS298
The bounty hunter purses his lips.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS299
He shuffles back alongside the car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS300
In the passenger seat, SOMEONE wipes her eyes then rests her forehead on the back of her hand, hiding her face.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS301
SOMEONE sheepishly opens his door and takes his seat at the wheel.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS302
He glances at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS303
He backs the car away from the pedicab, steers around it, and drives off.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS304
Now, SOMEONE leads an elderly man with fuzzy hair into the grungy bathroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS305
SOMEONE rests his leg on the toilet.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS306
The man takes out a giant syringe.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS307
The vet jabs the needle into SOMEONE's neck.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS308
Now, in SOMEONE's car, SOMEONE rides with one wrist cuffed to the door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS309
SOMEONE spots a luxury pick-up in her side mirror then eyes it over her shoulder.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS310
SOMEONE aims the rear-view mirror at it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS311
The pick-up pulls up beside them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS312
As the chiseled thug aims a gun at them from behind the wheel, SOMEONE jams her foot on the gas pedal. SOMEONE veers onto the shoulder, then into oncoming traffic on a one-way street. The thug shoots at them from the parallel two-way road.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS313
Drawing his gun, SOMEONE returns fire. SOMEONE cowers. The pick-up swerves onto the one-way street and jams itself alongside the Delta, mangling the convertible's headlight and SOMEONE. The vehicles separate. SOMEONE bashes the pick-up and takes aim.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS314
As they speed forward, shoving against each other, SOMEONE spots an SUV headed straight for the thug's vehicle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS315
Swerving, the chiseled man bursts through construction barricades then ramps up a stack of barricades and launches into mid-air. The pick-up lands on its roof and skids across the two-lane road. Reaching a grassy field, it tumbles onto its side. SOMEONE pulls over.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS316
She wrenches her cuffed arm.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS317
He gets out and surveys the damage.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS318
As SOMEONE jogs toward the luxury pick-up, the thug wriggles out through a window on the other side. Nearing he vehicle, SOMEONE slows and aims his gun.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS319
His assailant gets to his feet, using the pick-up as cover.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS320
The bounty hunter ventures toward the vehicles tail-end and the thug edges around its front. SOMEONE arrives on the other side and finds no sign of the gunman.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS321
Turning back, he finds himself aiming at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS322
She clutches her door's broken-off inner panel.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS324
On the one way street, the thug yanks a woman from her mini-van, gets in, and speeds off.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS325
SOMEONE gawks.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS326
Later, they search the pick-up together.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS327
He opens the covered bed.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS328
He finds a golf bag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS329
She hurls the cup at him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS330
SOMEONE climbs out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS331
SOMEONE notices a tag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS332
SOMEONE glares then yields a smile. Now, SOMEONE's ragtop follows a winding road toward a mansion perched atop an immaculately landscaped hill. At the mansions entrance, they surrender the car to a valet.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS333
Inside, a pristinely quaffed woman works a reception desk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS334
Her red painted lips primly stifle an excited smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS335
They follow her through the lobby.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS336
The woman frowns.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS337
The woman scowls suspiciously.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS338
SOMEONE smiles tightly and SOMEONE shakes his head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS339
The couple steps out back and wanders through a festive picnic.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS340
He walks her to the party's edge.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS341
They find some caddies.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS342
One rumples his lips then flees.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS343
He scurries down some steps.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS344
SOMEONE gives chase.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS345
The caddy leads him down a hill and across a grassy driving range. The bounty hunter frantically dodges golf balls as they whiz toward him. He leaps over one then ducks another. One ball buzzes low over his head and a fourth whips past his nose. As he leaves the range and runs onto a green, SOMEONE drives up in a golf cart.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS346
Elsewhere, the caddy peeks out from a sunken sand trap.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS347
The caddy crawls out from hiding.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS348
As he holds the flag for putting golfers, SOMEONE spies him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS349
SOMEONE steers the cart in the caddy's direction. The young man spots them and his polite smile fades.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS350
Dropping the flag, he dashes over a hill.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS351
Cresting the rise, the cart speeds toward a pond.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS352
SOMEONE leaps out, tackles the caddy, and tumbles with him into the water.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS353
The out of control cart plunges in beside them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS354
SOMEONE dunks him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS355
SOMEONE dunks him again.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS356
He shows his tattooed chest.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS357
SOMEONE swaps looks with SOMEONE then releases the caddy.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS358
Now, at the tattoo parlor.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS360
she pulls her hair back.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS361
He plucks it from her neck.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS362
SOMEONE digs out his cell and holds it up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS363
He answers it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS364
SOMEONE frowns uneasily at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS365
He ends the call.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS366
In the convertible
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS367
at a turnoff, they pass a sign reading, Cupid's Cabin.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS368
Later, they face a three-story Victorian style house with a wrap-around porch.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS369
A curly-haired woman answers the door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS370
A chubby man arrives.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS371
SOMEONE smiles sadly at SOMEONE, who gives a nostalgic nod.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS372
SOMEONE and SOMEONE muster smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS373
SOMEONE stares, her features frozen in a thoughtful gape.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS374
The older woman gawks.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS375
Nighttime. In frumpy clothes, SOMEONE and SOMEONE dine on a patio.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS376
He eyes the adjoining building.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS377
They share a warm smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS378
SOMEONE drops her gaze, fiddling with her silky honey-brown hair.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS379
She shrugs a hand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS380
SOMEONE lifts his brow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS381
Looking away, she shrugs again.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS382
SOMEONE blinks at her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS383
SOMEONE regards him thoughtfully.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS384
He gives a boyish half-smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS385
She raises her champagne glass.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS386
SOMEONE follows suit.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS387
They tap glasses. SOMEONE sips his sparkling wine with a knitted brow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS388
SOMEONE's smile fades to a tight smirk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS389
SOMEONE gives a sad shrug.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS390
Resting her cheek against her hand, SOMEONE shakes her head and gazes skyward.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS391
SOMEONE looks away then faces him defenselessly.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS392
SOMEONE tearfully tightens her lips.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS393
Now, the two stroll down a hallway lit cheerily with glass-shaded lamps.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS394
SOMEONE pauses to eye an inscription on one of the doors.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS395
Reaching another door, they find a lavender heart-shaped sign that reads, Bliss in rosy cursive letters.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS396
SOMEONE and SOMEONE chuckle at the frilly placard then share a warm lingering gaze.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS397
SOMEONE starts to open her mouth, then shakes her head and smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS398
Staring at her intently, he nods.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS400
As he unlocks the door, he steps in close and leans his face toward hers.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS401
SOMEONE opens the door, revealing a narrow four-post bed on a lavender carpet.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS402
Table lamps cast their soft glow against the rosy wall.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS403
SOMEONE gestures her inside and SOMEONE precedes him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS404
At the Borgata lounge, Kitty takes a phone call.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS406
SOMEONE drops by.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS407
SOMEONE accepts a tray.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS408
Checking SOMEONE's wallet, he finds their wedding photo.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS409
It shows SOMEONE and him beaming as bride and groom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS410
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE, who waits in the hall.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS411
He shuts the door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS412
SOMEONE moves from the door, his eyes fixed on the photo, and his lips parted.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS414
she slugs back an entire cocktail and gives a bracing twitch of the brow.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS415
SOMEONE and Teresa talk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS416
SOMEONE enters with his kids.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS417
SOMEONE picks up the phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS418
SOMEONE smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS419
SOMEONE hangs up then stares at her reflection in the mirror.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS422
SOMEONE lights candles around the room and pops a CD into a player.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS423
SOMEONE peeks out from the bathroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS424
His back to SOMEONE, SOMEONE hangs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS425
His ex-wife returns to the bathroom unnoticed. Now, she steps out wrapped tightly in a bathrobe.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS426
She avoids SOMEONE's gaze.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS427
Marching to the bed, she blows out a candle on a bedside table, turns off the CD player, and hurls some pillows to the floor.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS428
She throws down more pillows until only a few remain.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS429
She blows out another candle and climbs under the covers.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS430
Lying on her back, SOMEONE closes her eyes then sneakily peeks one open. She watches as SOMEONE blows out more candles. He snuffs the last one with his hand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS431
He pops a candy into his mouth and climbs into bed fully clothed. He scoots up against SOMEONE and folds his arms.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS432
SOMEONE eyes him as he chews. He glances over and she looks away.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS433
He closes his eyes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS434
She climbs out of bed and grabs a blanket then swipes the pillow out from behind SOMEONE's head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS435
He bumps the headboard.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS436
As he winces, SOMEONE throws the pillow at his face. She settles onto a window bench.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS437
Closing his eyes, SOMEONE folds his hands behind his head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS438
From the bench, SOMEONE turns and glares at him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS439
Later, she wears her own clothes as she slams the suite's door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS440
SOMEONE stirs. He finds himself cuffed to the bed.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS441
SOMEONE jingles the handcuff keys.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS442
She leaves.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS443
SOMEONE yanks on his cuff secured tightly to the headboard.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS444
As SOMEONE races out the door, SOMEONE frantically yanks on the headboard. He breaks off the top and falls back onto the bed.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS445
Now, as he rushes outside, SOMEONE pulls his car out of the drive.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS446
Still attached to the headboard, he chases after her. The convertible speeds away.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS447
He watches as it disappears around a corner.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS448
Meanwhile, at a gas station, SOMEONE opens his trunk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS449
He plucks a SOMEONE from the garbage bag full of cash and heads toward a convenient store.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS450
SOMEONE halts, gives Ray the finger, and steps into the store. Ray spots SOMEONE's car as it rides by.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS452
At cupid's cabin, as SOMEONE stands on the front stoop, SOMEONE shuts the door.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS453
SOMEONE watches as a black luxury sedan pulls up to the porch steps. A young couple climbs out and he approaches the driver.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS454
As the couple heads up the front steps, SOMEONE climbs into the car and peels out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS455
Meanwhile, SOMEONE drives SOMEONE's car. She spots a storefront with a Pink awning. Its psychedelic sign reads, Blue Ink Tattoos. Now, inside the tattoo parlor, SOMEONE strolls to the counter where a woman with a Mohawk and multiple piercings works.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS456
The woman glances at her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS457
SOMEONE frowns.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS458
A bald tattoo artist eyes SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS459
She struts toward him, hand on her hip.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS460
She grabs her breasts.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS461
She frames her pelvis with her hands.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS462
She runs a hand down her thigh then pats it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS463
The tattoo artist eyes SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS464
SOMEONE turns to the tatted clerk.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS465
Now, SOMEONE sits in a chair in a small room papered in tattoo designs.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS466
He draws a curtain.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS467
SOMEONE sits.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS468
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS469
Sitting beside her, SOMEONE leans back and smiles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS470
With a wave, SOMEONE hurries through the parlor.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS471
Brushing her hair out of her face, she peers over her shoulder then casually heads to the bathroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS472
She opens the door, steps inside, and waits briefly. Glancing around, she creeps out of the bathroom and makes her way up some stairs. Now, she opens a door to a wood-paneled entry way. She cautiously checks over her shoulder then tiptoes inside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS473
Seen through another doorway, an office chair sits at a desk with a giant mural of a snarling tiger behind it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS474
A red and black bowling shirt hangs on the back of the chair.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS475
SOMEONE scurries into the office.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS476
She sifts through a stack of paperwork then sits at the desk and rifles through files and drawers.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS477
Swiveling in the chair, she spots a framed photo of a bowling team. In it, SOMEONE and SOMEONE pose with two teammates.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS478
A caption reads, Police Bowling League.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS479
SOMEONE looks around then sets the photo back on a trophy shelf.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS480
Scanning the office, she follows the sound around a corner and finds a louvered door locked by a deadbolt. She undoes the lock, opens the door, and finds SOMEONE inside. His mouth and wrists duct taped.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS481
Downstairs, SOMEONE enters.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS482
Upstairs, SOMEONE cuts tape binding SOMEONE's wrists.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS483
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE out a side door then rushes back in, grabs the bowling photo, and hurries out. SOMEONE enters through the front door, spots the open closet, and draws his gun. Looking inside, he finds it empty.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS485
They race down the street. Meanwhile, SOMEONE makes a call.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS487
they get in SOMEONE's car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS488
SOMEONE's thugs sit in back.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS489
They brandish their guns.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS490
SOMEONE shrugs at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS491
As SOMEONE scrambles out, SOMEONE gawks. With a parting glance, SOMEONE sprints away.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS492
SOMEONE frowns at Ray. SOMEONE lets his head lull back. Now, SOMEONE spies his car in a nearby parking lot. He pulls in. A mural of two widespread female legs flanks the hot-pink back door of a strip club named, Double D's. SOMEONE climbs out of the borrowed car, satchel in hand.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS493
He checks his phone and flips it open.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS494
SOMEONE approaches a purple and white muscle car.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS495
Inside the strip club, SOMEONE eyes his phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS496
Outside, SOMEONE shoots the lock of SOMEONE's trunk and opens it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS497
He finds the garbage bag of cash inside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS498
He answers his phone and casually leans on the open trunk lid.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS499
He slings the garbage bag over his shoulder.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS500
SOMEONE enters the club.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS501
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the cell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS502
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE with her captors and hangs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS503
SOMEONE watches as the two thugs escort his ex-wife through the strip club.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS504
They stop at a neon restroom sign and she heads inside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS505
In the bathroom, SOMEONE's shoulders sag.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS506
Across the club, SOMEONE watches the thugs unnoticed. He answers his phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS508
Outside the restroom, SOMEONE tosses cash at some patrons.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS509
SOMEONE hurls cash at the dancers onstage.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS510
As SOMEONE tosses bills to patrons and employees, the thugs try to grab the cash from their hands. SOMEONE empties the garbage bag on a pool table then runs onstage with more money.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS511
SOMEONE pushes people from the pool table.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS512
He punches a guy. SOMEONE finds SOMEONE in the restroom.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS513
A brawl breaks out in the club.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS515
Back in the bathroom, SOMEONE stares wistfully.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS516
He leads her through the chaos. At the pool table a formidable pole dancer piggy-backs SOMEONE. As Ray shoves her off, she grabs a bottle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS517
The woman smashes it on SOMEONE's head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS518
He falls. Ray faces the dancer.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS519
She knocks him out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS520
Now, in the police department.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS521
In the ragtop, SOMEONE ends the call and glances at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS522
The convertible speeds down a street and through an intersection. Now, in the depository building, SOMEONE packs evidence baggies filled with white powder into a brown paper bag then rolls the top down.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS523
Outside, the Delta '88 sits parked across the street.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS524
A dark sedan drives around the corner of the depository and pulls into a parking spot.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS525
SOMEONE's at the wheel.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS526
SOMEONE slumps.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS527
They lock gazes then watch SOMEONE enter the depository.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS528
Inside, SOMEONE exits a freight elevator.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS529
SOMEONE shifts his confused stare.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS530
Downstairs, SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter through a main door. A clerk behind a cage-wire barrier addresses them.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS532
SOMEONE sets the paper bag down.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS533
The men shoot at each other. SOMEONE grabs the clerk through a window.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS534
The clerk hits a button on his desk. SOMEONE opens a nearby gate.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS535
SOMEONE releases the clerk, who grabs a phone. Now, SOMEONE creeps up a stairwell, his gun drawn. SOMEONE follows. Later, they exit the stairwell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS536
SOMEONE fearfully trots up and hides behind SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS537
He glares toward her feet and she mouths, Sorry.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS538
As SOMEONE surveys their surroundings, SOMEONE takes cover behind a pillar.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS539
He irritably waves her over.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS540
A view through tall shelving units crammed with evidence shows the couple prowl forward.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS541
As they sneak, SOMEONE taps SOMEONE's shoulder and he wheels around with his gun.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS542
Blood stains the freight elevator and they glimpse a fallen man's feet. As SOMEONE skulks off, SOMEONE and SOMEONE slink toward the elevator and find SOMEONE bleeding inside.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS543
They hurry over.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS544
SOMEONE swaps looks with SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS545
SOMEONE stalks off, gun raised. Back in the elevator, SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS546
SOMEONE glares at him.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS547
Out among the industrial shelves, SOMEONE creeps past aisles.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS548
SOMEONE hides at the end of one unit and watches SOMEONE creeping by.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS550
Back in the elevator, SOMEONE points at SOMEONE insistently then creeps out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS551
In the depository, SOMEONE prowls down an aisle.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS552
He aims his gun around a corner and scans the vacant shadows.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS553
SOMEONE minces up to a shelving unit and peeks around it.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS554
Elsewhere, SOMEONE ducks low then skulks forward.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS555
SOMEONE sidles down an aisle, grabs SOMEONE's shoulder, and jabs his gun against the bounty hunter's neck.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS556
Hidden, SOMEONE spots them. SOMEONE drops his gun.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS557
SOMEONE mouths, Oh God and searches the shelves around her.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS558
SOMEONE spots a pair of evidence boxes. One labeled, Gotti, K and the other Gotti, V. A long flat box beneath them reads handle with care. As SOMEONE kneels, SOMEONE finds an outline of a shotgun printed on top.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS559
SOMEONE takes aim.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS560
SOMEONE grins. SOMEONE fumes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS561
She blows a box to pieces.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS562
As SOMEONE turns to shoot, SOMEONE sweeps his legs. SOMEONE misses.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS563
Punched repeatedly, SOMEONE collapses. SOMEONE kicks his weapon away from him then glances at SOMEONE.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS564
Daytime, outside. Dozens of police cruisers surround the depository.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS565
She kisses SOMEONE's cheek.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS566
As she leaves she takes a call from SOMEONE, who limps between a warehouse and an empty lot.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS567
SOMEONE drops.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS568
SOMEONE hangs up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS569
Later, in SOMEONE's ragtop,
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS570
a sly grin spreads across SOMEONE's lips.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS571
She and SOMEONE swap warm smiles. Sunlight bathes her face.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS572
SOMEONE beams. SOMEONE skids around a corner, pulls into a curbside spot, and brakes hard.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS573
She notices the police station across the street.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS574
SOMEONE gets out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS576
In the station, SOMEONE wears handcuffs.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS577
A female officer leads SOMEONE away as she glares at SOMEONE. The bounty hunter signs a form and the cop at the desk shakes his head incredulously.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS578
Pursing his mouth regretfully, SOMEONE waves goodbye to the cop and ambles out.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS579
Now, SOMEONE strolls outside passing an officer and handcuffed teen on their way in. As the bounty hunter descends the stoop, the arresting officer from the parade swaggers up.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS580
SOMEONE eyes him with a half-smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS581
SOMEONE punches him. Inside, SOMEONE uses a phone.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS582
Gelman shoves a cuffed SOMEONE toward a holding cell.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS583
The officers place the couple in side-by-side cells. SOMEONE shrugs and faces his ex-wife through the bars. SOMEONE beams at him and shakes her head.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS584
They share a smile.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS585
They step up to the bars. SOMEONE reaches through them and wraps her arms around SOMEONE's neck.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS586
They kiss passionately.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS587
SOMEONE strokes her ex-husband's hair then cups the back of his head in both her hands.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS588
Separating, they gaze into each other's eyes.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS589
Grinning, SOMEONE massages his neck then wraps her arms around him once again.
THE_BOUNTY_HUNTER_DVS590
They embrace and share a deep kiss.