She enters an office.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS29
SOMEONE calmly brings a whistle to her lips.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS30
Now in a control room.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS31
The team shoots a cooking segment.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS32
SOMEONE sips an energy drink as she oversees production.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS33
On set, the female anchor tastes the sauce.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS34
The anchorwoman's eyes widen.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS35
A weatherman eats.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS36
Spinning wearily in his chair, the director faces SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS37
A monitor shows Rocco swigging from a wine bottle.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS38
SOMEONE gulps it down. In an office, a balding man switches off the feed.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS39
Now she flosses in a ladies room.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS40
SOMEONE shows a photo.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS41
She indicates her breasts.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS42
Now SOMEONE approaches a restaurant hostess.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS43
Later SOMEONE and her date share a table.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS44
The waiter steps away.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS45
SOMEONE takes the printout from her purse.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS46
Later SOMEONE walks alone through the courtyard leading to her apartment.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS47
A view from her living room window shows her passing outside.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS48
She enters and flips a switch, lighting the cheerily decorated apartment.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS49
A gray tabby cat prances over to her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS50
It rubs against her ankle.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS51
Bending over, SOMEONE pets the cat.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS52
Her smile fades as she straightens.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS53
Now a remote lies on a bed.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS54
The cat steps on it.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS55
SOMEONE enters from the bathroom
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS57
He chucks it in the trash.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS59
SOMEONE eyes books on her nightstand.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS63
He pours gasoline in the trash can.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS66
He lights a match.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS67
He tosses it in.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS89
He grabs a skewered marshmallow and swallows it whole.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS90
With a disgusted gape, SOMEONE makes a phone call.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS136
He hits an alarm.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS143
He disconnects her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS146
The next day.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS148
They enter a conference room.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS151
SOMEONE turns on a TV.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS152
SOMEONE gapes.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS153
She turns it off.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS169
SOMEONE reads.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS179
SOMEONE swaggers into the room and grins.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS181
SOMEONE gapes.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS184
SOMEONE haughtily lifts her chin.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS185
SOMEONE shakes her hand and smirks.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS186
SOMEONE steals a muffin.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS187
Later SOMEONE paces in her office.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS188
SOMEONE knocks on the door, then opens it.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS189
SOMEONE rolls her eyes and storms out. Later in the studio.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS190
He eyes SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS192
Now SOMEONE sits at the news desk.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS193
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit to his left.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS200
In the control room.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS206
SOMEONE sneers at SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS213
SOMEONE looks sharply at SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS215
SOMEONE puts his arm around SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS216
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS217
He shrugs.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS218
SOMEONE wheels SOMEONE's chair toward SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS219
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE passionately.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS220
SOMEONE laughs as SOMEONE heaves his wife over his shoulder and carries her away.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS222
SOMEONE discovers SOMEONE curled up on the floor in a closet.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS223
SOMEONE sits up and frowns.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS224
SOMEONE reads.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS225
With a thumbs-up, SOMEONE strides out.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS226
SOMEONE smiles uncertainly.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS227
SOMEONE closes the closet door, shutting herself in.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS228
Now a girl rides her bicycle past a modest suburban home.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS229
In a guest house, SOMEONE tosses a bag to the floor, swigs from a can of Pepsi, and listens to an answering machine.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS230
SOMEONE closes his eyes and crosses himself, then takes off his jacket.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS231
A boy enters.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS232
SOMEONE fumbles with the machine.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS234
He yanks the machine from the wall.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS235
SOMEONE follows the boy outside.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS236
They enter the main house.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS237
A woman enters.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS238
She sits between them.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS239
She flips open the lid of a pastry box and kisses his cheek.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS240
Now in her bathroom, SOMEONE faces a mirror.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS241
She takes out a hair clip and fluffs her shoulder-length hair with both hands.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS243
Her cat sits by a broken fish bowl.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS244
She chases him down the stair
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS245
SOMEONE jumps out the living room window. He scales a tree and perches on a high branch.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS246
SOMEONE stands below, hands on her hips.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS247
She climbs the tree in a hoodie and slip.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS248
She stretches out her hands.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS249
The cat moves farther away. SOMEONE catches him.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS250
She holds him close and looks down.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS251
She shifts on a branch.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS252
She spots a well-built man through a pair of open balcony doors as he exits a shower.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS253
She claps a hand over her cat's mouth, then continues to ogle her neighbor.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS254
She clutches a branch for balance as he steps outside, flossing.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS255
She beams. The branch under her feet snaps and she hangs upside-down.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS256
The bottom hem of her slip dangles around her neck, revealing her panties.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS257
The well-built neighbor runs out, clutching a towel around his waist.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS258
SOMEONE accidentally rips off his towel. She covers her eyes.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS260
He bandages her ankle.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS261
Now clothed, her neighbor smiles.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS262
SOMEONE rubs up against the doctor's leg.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS263
He picks up SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS264
SOMEONE's jaw drops into a gleeful grin.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS265
Her neighbor strokes SOMEONE and gives a friendly smile.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS266
She lustfully eyes him up and down. He arches a brow and points to the door.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS267
She heads over and opens it with a toothy grin.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS268
She leaves without SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS269
The doctor opens his door and finds her dancing on his porch.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS270
He hands her SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS271
Daytime, at the studio.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS272
SOMEONE spots SOMEONE flirting with the makeup artist and holds up a finger.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS273
She marches over to him as the artist brushes makeup on his face. The woman's flirty smile fades.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS274
SOMEONE glares at her as she leaves.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS275
She leans closer to SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS276
SOMEONE shoves an earpiece into the cocky host's ear.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS277
She rips off his makeup bib.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS278
Now SOMEONE watches from the control room.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS279
He walks to a set.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS280
He leaves the set.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS281
He strolls outside the studio.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS282
Two women in bikinis grapple in red liquid.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS283
SOMEONE holds four phones.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS284
The two women seize SOMEONE, yank him into the pool, and tear open his shirt.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS285
In the control room.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS286
SOMEONE talks into a mic.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS287
SOMEONE touches his earpiece.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS288
She watches on the monitors as SOMEONE grabs one of the women's hands and sucks on her finger.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS289
The woman tosses her head ecstatically. He faces the camera.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS290
At the news desk, SOMEONE gapes.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS291
Later, SOMEONE sits in a chair and summons a calming breath. SOMEONE swaggers in with his arms around the bikini-clad women.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS292
As he halts in front of SOMEONE, the women head off.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS293
He gives SOMEONE a proud grin and raises his brow.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS294
SOMEONE storms off.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS295
In a dream, SOMEONE stands naked with cartoon clouds covering her chest and hips.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS297
A cartoony cowboy with SOMEONE's face rides a thrusting hot dog behind her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS298
A cartoon sun peaks out of her cloud mini skirt.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS299
Now she sits up in bed.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS300
She flops back down.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS301
Daytime, in the studio break area.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS302
The coworker hands each of them a page and SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a look.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS303
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE at the coffee maker.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS304
He eyes her curiously.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS305
SOMEONE looks on.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS306
As SOMEONE heads off, SOMEONE follows. They enter the producer's office.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS307
SOMEONE glares. She grabs SOMEONE's business card, puts the phone to her ear and dials.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS308
She ignores SOMEONE. He snatches the card from her hand.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS309
SOMEONE grabs a cordless and listens in.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS310
SOMEONE holds up a shushing finger.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS311
SOMEONE signs a report.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS312
He stands, using a nurse station phone.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS313
SOMEONE tries to get SOMEONE's attention, but she waves him off.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS314
SOMEONE bats her hand away.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS315
SOMEONE disconnects the call. SOMEONE eyes his phone.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS316
She reaches for the phone. SOMEONE sits on it.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS317
SOMEONE returns to his chair.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS318
SOMEONE blocks her reach.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS319
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lower their phones.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS320
SOMEONE shrugs and grins.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS321
SOMEONE puts SOMEONE on hold.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS322
He glances off, then eyes her frankly.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS323
SOMEONE nods and glances at the phone.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS324
The digital display counts past 37 seconds.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS325
At the doctor's office, SOMEONE waits. SOMEONE glares across her desk at SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS326
SOMEONE hangs up.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS327
SOMEONE gets up.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS328
She joins him.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS329
Now at a coffee shop.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS330
She sips from her coffee mug.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS331
Now they browse dresses in a SOMEONE boutique.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS332
At his snap, a red-haired saleswoman smiles.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS333
He eyes a black SOMEONE bra.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS334
Later they hold a cocktail dress up to SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS336
He slaps her butt. Outside.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS337
Nighttime at SOMEONE's apartment.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS338
SOMEONE sits on a chair, where he finds SOMEONE's knitting.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS339
He drops it aside with a smirk, then glances up toward the
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS340
stairs. SOMEONE descends in black stiletto heels and a flattering black cocktail dress that pushes up her cleavage. Her blonde hair is longer and styled with wavy feathering.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS341
He stands.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS342
She slaps his butt.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS343
She leans in coyly and caresses his chest.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS344
Her lips hover inches from his.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS345
SOMEONE hops behind the couch.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS346
He slaps her butt again.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS347
As she answers the door, he ducks down.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS348
SOMEONE checks her out.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS349
He notices SOMEONE peeking over the couch.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS350
She shuts the door.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS351
SOMEONE points and beams at SOMEONE, who gives her a thumbs-up.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS352
He watches as she breaks into a goofy giddy dance. Now at the baseball game, a pitcher winds up and throws the ball.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS353
A batter swings and hits, and the crowd rises.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS354
SOMEONE, who eats popcorn, enters with SOMEONE. He carries drinks.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS355
She nods. SOMEONE sits a few rows up.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS356
SOMEONE sits.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS357
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS358
With a mouthful of popcorn and a semi-nod, SOMEONE gives a sneering grin.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS359
He grins. Now a runner rounds second base and an outfielder goes for the ball.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS360
In the stands, SOMEONE rises with the rest of the crowd.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS361
SOMEONE turns to a vendor.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS362
Nearby, a woman recognizes SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS363
She hugs him. Her date intervenes.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS364
Sitting back in his seat, SOMEONE covers his mouth.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS365
A fat female vendor.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS366
SOMEONE accepts two dogs.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS367
She nods and raises the hot dog.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS368
She spills her soda on SOMEONE's lap.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS369
She fastidiously wipes at his pants.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS370
SOMEONE winces a little as she works his loins. Spectators stare and the camera man approaches.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS371
Over the score board, a big screen's kiss cam shows SOMEONE reclining for SOMEONE's bowed head and jerking arm motions. SOMEONE stands. Ball players on the field notice. SOMEONE keeps wiping.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS372
Onscreen, SOMEONE glances up, then at the camera.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS373
At night, SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk the courtyard between their apartments. SOMEONE hides behind a bush.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS374
He notices her chest.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS375
As SOMEONE watches from the bush, SOMEONE turns away, but SOMEONE grabs her arm and kisses her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS376
SOMEONE's jaw drops.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS377
They end their kiss and SOMEONE smiles.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS378
As they each head back to their own doors, they share another glance.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS379
As SOMEONE heads inside, SOMEONE hurries over to SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS380
He steps out with a grin and she gives him a big hug.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS381
She still beams.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS382
She prances off.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS383
SOMEONE takes his earpiece out and doffs his ball cap.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS384
Walking off, he glances back toward SOMEONE's door.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS385
Now at the studio, a camera's viewfinder shows SOMEONE in a gorilla suit.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS386
Video footage of humping monkeys plays behind SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS387
As SOMEONE crosses off items on a list, SOMEONE spies SOMEONE's nephew.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS388
SOMEONE hustles after the boy.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS389
The anchors take notes.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS390
As SOMEONE spots his nephew, SOMEONE looks on.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS391
SOMEONE grins.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS392
He rubs the boy's head.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS393
As the boy leaves, SOMEONE passes SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS394
SOMEONE turns the back of his neck to her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS395
SOMEONE undoes his gorilla suit.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS396
She does her goofy bouncy dance.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS397
They sit.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS398
An assistant pulls off the rest of his costume.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS399
They cross the set to a coffee station.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS400
SOMEONE joins them.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS401
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a look.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS402
She walks with him.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS403
Now SOMEONE finds a blank gift bag, stuffed with purple tissue paper, on her welcome mat.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS404
She picks up the gift and peeks around.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS405
Finding the card, she steps back inside.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS407
SOMEONE opens the card.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS408
It reads: This present isn't for you. It's for your bean. SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS409
SOMEONE finds a purple box in the gift bag.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS410
She opens an information flap on the box.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS411
Later SOMEONE puts on lipstick at a mirror. She wears a white v-neck dress. A loose bun of her blonde curls rests at the back of her neck.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS412
The producer caps her lipstick and picks up her cell phone. A text message reads: SOMEONE Anderson running late.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS413
Irritably pursing her lips, she picks up a glass of white wine and takes a seat.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS414
SOMEONE sips from her glass and idly smoothes her hair, then notices the gift on the coffee table.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS415
She thoughtfully rumples her mouth,
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS416
shrugs, and sets down her wine.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS417
Reaching up underneath her flowing ramp dress, she slips off her white panties.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS418
D'Artagnan comes downstairs. SOMEONE picks up the SOMEONE, black, vibrating panties and carefully works them over her black high heels.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS419
Reaching underneath her dress once again, she shimmies them up to her waist.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS420
The producer adjusts her skirt, then picks up a remote control.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS421
D'Artagnan peeks at her curiously.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS422
SOMEONE hides her white panties in the gift box, then rushes to the front door with her purse.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS423
Stowing the remote inside, she opens up and finds SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS424
SOMEONE grins sardonically. SOMEONE smirks back.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS425
Later they ride in a car with SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS426
Now in an upscale eatery, the jello girls join them.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS427
SOMEONE swaggers off, arms around both.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS428
They all meet the corporate execs at the bar.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS429
SOMEONE pats SOMEONE on the back.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS430
Later at their table, a waiter pours wine.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS431
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE and squeezes his arm.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS432
SOMEONE drums the table.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS433
SOMEONE kicks him under the table, upsetting her purse.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS434
The remote rolls out.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS435
A stocky pre-teen boy pick it up, quizzically rumpling his lips, and returns to his table.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS436
The boy fiddles with the controls.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS437
He shakes the remote, then hits a button.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS438
A gauge goes up.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS439
SOMEONE leans under the table.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS440
As SOMEONE joins her, SOMEONE checks his cell phone.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS441
Under the table.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS442
SOMEONE cringes. Nearby, the boy shakes the remote.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS443
SOMEONE nods, then sits up.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS444
SOMEONE gives a wide grin. Under the table, SOMEONE crosses her legs.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS445
The boy fusses with the remote.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS446
SOMEONE musters a broad grin and calmly retakes her seat.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS447
SOMEONE spots the boy.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS448
SOMEONE struggles to sit still.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS449
She glares at him, cringing.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS450
SOMEONE winks at her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS451
SOMEONE fidgets with her silverware and writhes.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS452
SOMEONE gawks at her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS453
The remote gauge reads: Ecstasy Level.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS455
SOMEONE smiles and mops his brow.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS456
SOMEONE grins and SOMEONE shrugs his brows. SOMEONE lolls.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS457
SOMEONE takes the remote from the boy.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS458
SOMEONE spots him and seizes it.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS460
SOMEONE rolls her eyes, then looks back at their table.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS461
SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand, then follows SOMEONE out. As SOMEONE gazes after them, SOMEONE approaches.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS462
Daytime. SOMEONE rides in SOMEONE's convertible.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS463
Smiling and chatting, they speed down a narrow sun-dappled road in the woods. SOMEONE's long hair whips in the wind.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS464
Later they round a curve on a mountainside, then drive across a towering bridge.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS465
An aerial view shows the road winding over rolling wooded hills. Later in a sunny forest, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on boulders at the edge of a creek.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS466
They tap wine glasses and drink.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS467
As SOMEONE beams at their surroundings, SOMEONE raises a cracker.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS468
SOMEONE reaches for it, but SOMEONE retracts it and feeds it to her himself. He turns away and SOMEONE spits it out.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS469
She winces disgustedly and wipes her mouth.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS470
SOMEONE faces her with a smile and she grins.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS471
Later they hike barefoot across stones in the creek. SOMEONE helps SOMEONE onto a boulder and they share a tender kiss. Sunlight gleams on SOMEONE's golden hair.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS472
Now in a coffee shop, SOMEONE hands SOMEONE and SOMEONE two drinks.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS473
As he turns away to pay the barista, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE and bounces girlishly. SOMEONE mimes grabbing SOMEONE's waist, repeatedly thrusts her hips, then holds her heart.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS474
Now on a kitchen set at the studio, SOMEONE cooks with a shapely model.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS475
On the studio floor, the delivery guy brings SOMEONE a massive bouquet.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS476
SOMEONE and SOMEONE read the card.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS477
SOMEONE notices them jumping up and down as he feeds the model a spoonful of chocolate.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS478
He obliviously smears it all over the woman's face.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS479
She irritably shakes her head.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS480
Distracted by SOMEONE, SOMEONE absent-
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS481
mindedly wipes the model off. Now in the SF Saloon and Grill, SOMEONE uses her cell. SOMEONE sits across from her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS483
He munches a snack, then leans forward.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS484
SOMEONE ogles a busty woman standing at the bar behind SOMEONE. The producer follows his gaze and sneers.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS485
SOMEONE smiles to herself.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS486
SOMEONE shyly sips her white wine.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS487
SOMEONE leans back.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS488
The producer smiles and raises her glass.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS489
She drinks. SOMEONE frowns thoughtfully. Now she watches him on a control room monitor.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS490
Later in the studio.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS491
On the set, SOMEONE and SOMEONE canoodle. A techie ushers a short boyish guy to SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS492
They hug. SOMEONE approaches them.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS493
They notice her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS494
In the background, SOMEONE and SOMEONE duck under the news desk.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS495
Later in his office, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE wave as she passes his window. He beckons her in.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS496
SOMEONE shakes her head, slack-jawed. Now an aerial view shows the LA skyline.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS497
Outside the Century Plaza Hotel, a sprawling fountain spouts water in dozens of jets. A taxi arrives.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS499
As a valet opens the door, SOMEONE pays the driver.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS500
She gets out.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS501
Later SOMEONE spots her in the lobby.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS502
SOMEONE strolls after her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS503
Later in a limo.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS504
SOMEONE stammers.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS505
SOMEONE fumes.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS506
At The Late Late Show.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS507
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE by the shoulders.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS508
SOMEONE smiles and claps as he goes on stage.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS509
They share a manly hug.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS510
SOMEONE waves at the crowd.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS511
He sits in chair.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS512
With a smile, SOMEONE walks to a monitor to watch the show.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS513
SOMEONE looks toward the stage. She shifts her eyes back to the monitor and watches as SOMEONE forces a smile.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS514
Later SOMEONE strolls into a restaurant and approaches the hostess.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS515
The hostess leads him away.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS516
A disco ball hangs from the high-arched ceiling, twinkling with light.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS517
Directly below, patrons twirl on a large dance floor.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS518
SOMEONE sits in a booth, talking on the phone.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS519
SOMEONE arrives.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS520
He sits across from her with a big grin.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS521
He sips SOMEONE's drink.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS522
A waitress stops at their table.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS523
SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS524
A smile spreads across her face.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS525
SOMEONE gazes out at the dance floor, then turns to SOMEONE.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS526
He leads her to the dance floor and flings off his jacket.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS527
SOMEONE takes her hand and spins her away, then twirls underneath their joined hands, and pulls her into a tight embrace. He grins at her surprised smile.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS528
SOMEONE spins SOMEONE again.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS529
Holding both of her hands, he pushes her away, then pulls her in with her back against him.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS530
Leaning against his chest, SOMEONE slinks up and down.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS531
SOMEONE moves with her, his face buried in her hair.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS532
He twirls her away, then brings her in, wrapping one arm around her waist. With their faces a few inches apart, they spin in tight circles.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS533
SOMEONE dances backward and SOMEONE draws her back in by both hands. He dips her. She straightens with a wide grin and touches her forehead to his as they dance in a circle.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS534
He raises her arms above her head.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS535
She shimmies sexily as he runs his hands down her body.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS536
She twirls away, then moves back into his arms.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS537
SOMEONE spins her away, then pivots gracefully underneath their arms.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS538
Sending her into a twirl, he lets go of one hand and catches her by the other.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS539
She leaps back to him, wrapping her arms around his neck.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS540
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a sultry look as they embrace. Their faces draw close together.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS541
SOMEONE blinks and shrinks back slightly.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS542
SOMEONE meets her gaze for a moment, then turns away and gives a disappointed nod.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS543
As SOMEONE follows her off the dance floor, SOMEONE brushes a strand of hair away from her face. Her smile fades. Now SOMEONE's black pumps dangle from her fingers as she and SOMEONE walk to the elevators. He presses the call button,
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS544
then leans against the wall with his hands in his pockets. SOMEONE shifts nervously.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS545
She hurries into the elevator.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS546
SOMEONE strolls in behind her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS547
She gives him a sidelong glance as she slides her shoes back on.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS548
SOMEONE presses two buttons on the control panel.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS549
They share a look. SOMEONE shifts her eyes to the floor. SOMEONE tilts his head toward the ceiling.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS550
The elevator doors slide open and he grins awkwardly.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS551
They hug tightly.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS552
The doors start to slide shut. SOMEONE stops them.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS553
They hug again and kiss each other on the cheek.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS554
The doors start to close again and SOMEONE pushes them open.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS555
He and SOMEONE grab each other in a passionate embrace and kiss hungrily. She leans against the door frame as they heatedly make out.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS556
SOMEONE glances into the hallway. SOMEONE steps back into the elevator.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS557
He waves at her through the closing doors.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS558
As SOMEONE turns his back to the elevator, his jaw drops and his wide eyes shift disbelievingly.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS559
He heads down the hall.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS560
Now SOMEONE opens the door to her room. She sets down her belongings and sits heavily on a love seat.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS561
Her brow furrowed thoughtfully,
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS562
she gazes around the room, then removes her shoes and casually tosses them aside.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS563
SOMEONE stands hastily.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS564
She smoothes out her dress, fluffs her hair, and hurries to the door.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS565
She opens it to find SOMEONE standing outside. Her face falls.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS566
He steps inside and kisses her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS567
He sits.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS568
SOMEONE sits beside him on the love seat.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS569
She looks away.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS570
Champagne springs from the bottle in SOMEONE's hand.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS571
As SOMEONE rushes away, SOMEONE stands and removes his shirt, exposing his well-toned chest. He grins.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS572
Meanwhile, SOMEONE walks down a hallway.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS573
He stops, turns the other way, then turns back again.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS574
He rubs his nose nervously.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS575
He strides determinedly to SOMEONE's door and raises his fist.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS576
SOMEONE answers, shirtless.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS577
They shake hands.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS578
SOMEONE appears.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS579
SOMEONE watches regretfully as he shuffles away.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS580
She closes the door.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS581
As SOMEONE heads down the hall, the door reopens, and SOMEONE hurries after him.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS582
His smile fades as he meets her gaze.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS583
SOMEONE sucks in a breath and steps closer, her eyes fixed on his face.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS584
She gives him a pleading look.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS585
SOMEONE forces a casual smile.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS586
SOMEONE nods disappointedly and tilts her head.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS587
She gives a bitter smile.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS588
As it fades, she lifts her eyes to his.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS589
SOMEONE turns his back to her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS590
SOMEONE watches sadly as he strolls down the hallway with his hands in his pockets.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS591
She takes a breath and heads back to her room.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS592
The yellow hallway lights glow harshly above SOMEONE as he hangs his head for a moment.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS593
SOMEONE enters her room.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS594
She glances around the spacious suite and finds SOMEONE sitting at the edge of the bed, wearing a clean unbuttoned dress shirt.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS595
He hands her a glass of champagne.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS596
SOMEONE chugs hers.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS597
She cringes as she finishes the entire glass.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS598
He raises his brow.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS599
SOMEONE pours herself another glass.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS600
She turns away with the bottle.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS601
She sips her champagne and leans against the back of a chair.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS602
SOMEONE shifts uncomfortably.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS603
He glances down at his exposed chest and pulls his shirt closed.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS604
SOMEONE sets her glass on the table and steps closer to him.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS605
She shakes her head.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS606
SOMEONE stares at her confusedly.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS607
SOMEONE frowns and reaches to her head.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS608
She released two hidden clips at the back of her hair,
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS609
then two more on the sides.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS610
SOMEONE knits his brow as he watches.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS611
SOMEONE removes a hair extension to reveal her shorter natural length.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS612
She self-consciously brushes her bangs out of her eyes.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS613
Now at the office.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS614
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE waiting for her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS615
Co-workers stare.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS616
SOMEONE points at each.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS617
At the CBS affiliate.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS618
SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand, then pats his shoulder.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS619
A glittery shaft of sunlight on a river overtakes the image.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS620
A dozen colorful hot air balloons hover in the sky at different altitudes. An assistant feeds a cable out from a news van, as a cameraman paces toward SOMEONE, who stands by a grounded balloon.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS621
A blandly handsome man inside the basket fires up the burner, startling her.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS622
SOMEONE shakes her head.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS623
He points his finger like a gun and blows on the tip.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS624
At the station.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS626
SOMEONE glances inside his news van.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS627
SOMEONE yanks him out of the balloon.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS628
She takes SOMEONE's place in the basket.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS629
SOMEONE rises from his makeup chair.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS631
He takes the mic.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS632
She mimes jerking off.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS633
The pilot fires up the burner.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS634
The balloon rises.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS635
He climbs over the edge. He sees the cameraman far below.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS636
The control room monitor shows SOMEONE and SOMEONE in the basket.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS637
SOMEONE smacks his shoulder. They both fold their arms and pout.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS638
SOMEONE pick up a phone.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS639
In the basket, SOMEONE gazes out at the dozens of balloons hovering over a tranquil harbor.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS640
SOMEONE peeks down at the verdant ground far below.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS641
The balloon pilot produces a bottle and glasses.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS642
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sulk.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS643
SOMEONE loosens his collar. In the balloon.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS644
SOMEONE's family watches.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS645
SOMEONE beams.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS646
SOMEONE lowers her petulant gaze.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS647
SOMEONE looks away, shakes his head, and takes a few deep breaths.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS648
SOMEONE stares at him out of the corners of her narrowed eyes, then faces him.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS649
SOMEONE soberly meets her gaze.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS650
SOMEONE stares into his eyes.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS651
He looks away, shaking his head.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS652
Flinging herself at him, SOMEONE seizes his face and plants a passionate kiss on his lips. SOMEONE wraps his arms around her 	and they sway in their embrace.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS653
As SOMEONE leans her against the basket's edge, the pilot looks on anxiously.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS654
Keeping his lips locked on SOMEONE's, SOMEONE dismisses him with a wave.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS655
The pilot turns away and the balloon floats off.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS657
Light filters into SOMEONE's darkened bedroom through the drawn curtains, offering a shadowy view of the couple in bed.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS658
SOMEONE rolls off of her and flips on a lamp.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS659
Sitting up, SOMEONE grins.
UGLY_TRUTH_DVS660
SOMEONE pounces on him and switches off the lamp.