Now adult SOMEONE sits in a therapist office.
BLINDDATING_DVS11
She drops her skirt by her feet revealing SOMEONE thigh highs.
BLINDDATING_DVS12
The therapist shakes her hands out and covers up with her skirt.
BLINDDATING_DVS13
She holds her blouse closed over her chest.
BLINDDATING_DVS15
Now outside, They watch him as he goes, finishing an apple.
BLINDDATING_DVS16
SOMEONE's mother gravely leads them into the living room, and sits on her red sofa by the arm chair. A fire crackles in the brick hearth. SOMEONE stands in front of it, facing his parents.
BLINDDATING_DVS17
Longhaired teen girl enters.
BLINDDATING_DVS18
A dark haired man in a suit enters.
BLINDDATING_DVS19
SOMEONE heads for the door.
BLINDDATING_DVS20
SOMEONE tensely nods and shrugs.
BLINDDATING_DVS21
SOMEONE smiles boyishly.
BLINDDATING_DVS22
and shines on the town. In his room, SOMEONE plays a guitar.
BLINDDATING_DVS23
Outside, an athletic young man bounces a basketball. SOMEONE opens his window.
BLINDDATING_DVS24
SOMEONE comes out of the house on the second floor, wearing a hooded sweatshirt.
BLINDDATING_DVS25
The top of the high steps, SOMEONE perches on the railing.
BLINDDATING_DVS26
They hand SOMEONE the ball.
BLINDDATING_DVS27
SOMEONE shoots and misses the basket. The other guys smirk.
BLINDDATING_DVS28
SOMEONE calmly nods.
BLINDDATING_DVS29
One of the guys tosses it over.
BLINDDATING_DVS30
leads SOMEONE past reflective windows.
BLINDDATING_DVS31
Ace slaps SOMEONE's hand and leaves. SOMEONE enters. As another boy struggle to separate them.
BLINDDATING_DVS32
In the lobby, SOMEONE finds a glass door and enters.
BLINDDATING_DVS34
He steps on a wheel toy and falls flat on his back.
BLINDDATING_DVS35
A little girl pulls papers off the reception desk.
BLINDDATING_DVS36
A woman races to the desk.
BLINDDATING_DVS37
She cleans up the papers.
BLINDDATING_DVS38
Her dark eyes widen.
BLINDDATING_DVS39
She fixes a scrutinizing gaze on him.
BLINDDATING_DVS40
She sneers at SOMEONE and shakes her head.
BLINDDATING_DVS41
Now, in an office, a model human head wears sunglasses with a camera on one lens.
BLINDDATING_DVS42
Answers a desk phone.
BLINDDATING_DVS43
Beckoned by Dr. SOMEONE, SOMEONE's therapist enters. She fiddles with her top button.
BLINDDATING_DVS44
Dr. SOMEONE shifts his wide-eyed gaze.
BLINDDATING_DVS45
SOMEONE shifts in his seat.
BLINDDATING_DVS47
Now, in the hall. SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE faces Dr. SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS48
SOMEONE's therapist steps away. Outside, SOMEONE stands at a corner. SOMEONE walks past him.
BLINDDATING_DVS49
She pauses, yielding a smile.
BLINDDATING_DVS50
Her lips curl up. On the bus, SOMEONE takes a seat. Gazing out the window, she sees SOMEONE raising his hand in a perfectly timed wave.
BLINDDATING_DVS53
SOMEONE Heads for the seated group. At the table, a dashing man smile at her.
BLINDDATING_DVS54
SOMEONE's parents share a concerned look. Now, at a college campus, SOMEONE folds up his cane in a hallway. Entering a small lecture hall, he carefully feels his way down carpeted steps to the front of the room. He trips over a student's knees, knocking a laptop over as he falls.
BLINDDATING_DVS55
Now, SOMEONE rides in the limo's front seat. SOMEONE drives.
BLINDDATING_DVS56
SOMEONE turns an ear toward the screened off backseat.
BLINDDATING_DVS57
Now, at a corner cafe, the brothers eat at a counter.
BLINDDATING_DVS58
He wipes ketchup off SOMEONE's chin.
BLINDDATING_DVS59
He shoves SOMEONE's hand away. SOMEONE eyes him worriedly.
BLINDDATING_DVS60
Outside, a buxom woman in a tight gold mini-dress gets out of the limo with her client. They enter the cafe.
BLINDDATING_DVS61
The SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a camera.
BLINDDATING_DVS62
SOMEONE nods at the digital display.
BLINDDATING_DVS63
Bowing profusely, SOMEONE leaves.
BLINDDATING_DVS64
SOMEONE with platinum hair and faces SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS65
She hands SOMEONE cash. As he pockets.
BLINDDATING_DVS66
SOMEONE watches her leave with a lascivious look in his eye.
BLINDDATING_DVS67
He picks up the check.
BLINDDATING_DVS68
SOMEONE eyes him. SOMEONE shakes his head.
BLINDDATING_DVS69
SOMEONE climbs into the limo. Now, SOMEONE sits behind the wheel.
BLINDDATING_DVS70
Later, the limo turns a corner.
BLINDDATING_DVS71
Now at home, SOMEONE spikes SOMEONE's hair.
BLINDDATING_DVS72
On SOMEONE's shirt, citrus-colored flowers swirl around lavender blossoms on a blood red background. SOMEONE enters.
BLINDDATING_DVS73
SOMEONE points sternly at SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS74
As SOMEONE storms out, SOMEONE searches the closet.
BLINDDATING_DVS75
Shirt with a subtle pattern.
BLINDDATING_DVS76
Now, SOMEONE wears a dark suit. SOMEONE ties a black tie for him.
BLINDDATING_DVS77
SOMEONE pulls away.
BLINDDATING_DVS78
He grabs a pocket knife on a desk.
BLINDDATING_DVS79
SOMEONE snatches the knife, pries out the blade and runs the blunt side across his palm.
BLINDDATING_DVS80
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a quick glare.
BLINDDATING_DVS81
Now, outside an apartment building, SOMEONE smooths his hair and suit. SOMEONE escorts a petite redhead down the building's front steps toward his brother and the limo.
BLINDDATING_DVS82
SOMEONE feels around for the door of the Limo.
BLINDDATING_DVS83
He finds the limo's door. Then opens it.
BLINDDATING_DVS84
Her mouth falls open.
BLINDDATING_DVS86
grabs the scruff of his jacket and drags him back. With a grim expression, SOMEONE climbs in the car. There he closes the door and turns away with a frown. Now, as the limo heads down the street, SOMEONE dabs her nose with a tissue.
BLINDDATING_DVS87
SOMEONE grins at her. As he faces forward, the grin fades and his eyes widen tensely. He forces another smile.
BLINDDATING_DVS88
Raises his eyebrows. Now, in a restaurant.
BLINDDATING_DVS89
SOMEONE stuffs his mouth with lettuce. A goateed waiter offered.
BLINDDATING_DVS90
Plucks out several tissues.
BLINDDATING_DVS91
SOMEONE nods encouragingly.
BLINDDATING_DVS92
SOMEONE grins. SOMEONE claps a hand to her mouth. SOMEONE's brow creases uncertainly.
BLINDDATING_DVS93
Outside, SOMEONE, dressed as a valet, helps SOMEONE in to a taxi.
BLINDDATING_DVS95
Mad woman with a mullet steps out.
BLINDDATING_DVS96
She sets them down.
BLINDDATING_DVS97
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS98
As the woman walks through the open door.
BLINDDATING_DVS99
Later, the woman raises a beer.
BLINDDATING_DVS100
SOMEONE purses his lips.
BLINDDATING_DVS101
Seated across from SOMEONE, the woman sips her beer. SOMEONE pats his plate and finds a salad fork. With a self-satisfied smile, the woman moves next to him.
BLINDDATING_DVS102
She wrenches the fork from his fingers, and spears some lettuce.
BLINDDATING_DVS103
SOMEONE raise the fork to his mouth. SOMEONE pushes it away.
BLINDDATING_DVS104
His date knocks back a shot.
BLINDDATING_DVS105
Right in front of him, he finds her breasts. She yanks his body against hers.
BLINDDATING_DVS106
Now, in a restroom, SOMEONE locks himself in.
BLINDDATING_DVS107
The waiter enters.
BLINDDATING_DVS108
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
BLINDDATING_DVS109
The raised partition blocks them.
BLINDDATING_DVS110
SOMEONE leans toward her.
BLINDDATING_DVS111
As she gazes at him, her shoulders relax.
BLINDDATING_DVS112
Later, SOMEONE kneads his jacket in his lap.
BLINDDATING_DVS113
Dr. SOMEONE looks to Dr. SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS114
She gives SOMEONE a steady nod. Later, Dr. SOMEONE escorts SOMEONE into a waiting room.
BLINDDATING_DVS115
SOMEONE draws a breath. Outside.
BLINDDATING_DVS116
SOMEONE hesitates and turns toward her.
BLINDDATING_DVS117
SOMEONE nods.
BLINDDATING_DVS118
As SOMEONE races to her bus SOMEONE smiles and waves.
BLINDDATING_DVS119
SOMEONE serves SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS120
Nearby, SOMEONE flips through a copy of the Kama Sutra.
BLINDDATING_DVS121
SOMEONE stares at him.
BLINDDATING_DVS122
Behind her back, SOMEONE shows a picture of a sexual pose.
BLINDDATING_DVS123
As SOMEONE glances back, SOMEONE hides the book and waves innocently at her.
BLINDDATING_DVS124
Now, in Dr. SOMEONE office, SOMEONE's doctors hover at his side.
BLINDDATING_DVS125
As SOMEONE exits the clinic, SOMEONE hurries after him.
BLINDDATING_DVS126
SOMEONE smiles.
BLINDDATING_DVS127
They stand with their sandwiches.
BLINDDATING_DVS128
SOMEONE takes another bite of his sandwich and chews it thoughtfully.
BLINDDATING_DVS129
SOMEONE freezes mid chew, then swallows hard.
BLINDDATING_DVS130
SOMEONE's lips curl upward. Now, SOMEONE heads out of the Crimson Elephant.
BLINDDATING_DVS133
SOMEONE gazes at him.
BLINDDATING_DVS134
Later, the goateed waiter pass their table.
BLINDDATING_DVS135
A smile floats across SOMEONE's lips.
BLINDDATING_DVS136
SOMEONE swallows.
BLINDDATING_DVS137
Later, they slow dance.
BLINDDATING_DVS138
SOMEONE smiles mischievously as they continue to dance.
BLINDDATING_DVS139
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk beneath the pergola covered in vines of red blossoms.
BLINDDATING_DVS140
SOMEONE adjusts the strap of her purse. They stop and face each other.
BLINDDATING_DVS141
She tucks her hair behind her ear.
BLINDDATING_DVS142
SOMEONE gently touches her neck and leans his lips toward hers. As SOMEONE accepts the tender kiss
BLINDDATING_DVS143
SOMEONE lifts his other hand to her thick shiny hair, and rubs
BLINDDATING_DVS144
his thumb across her cheek. As they slowly withdraw, SOMEONE opens his eyes and lets down his hands. SOMEONE eyes blink open and her lips remain parted. They walk on.
BLINDDATING_DVS145
SOMEONE with a hopeful smile; SOMEONE with a dumbfounded look.
BLINDDATING_DVS146
In a garage, SOMEONE turns away from a mechanic.
BLINDDATING_DVS147
Comes out from under his limo and faces SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS148
He glances at the limo.
BLINDDATING_DVS149
Now, SOMEONE walks through the park carrying a brown paper lunch bag. She stops in her tracks and grins.
BLINDDATING_DVS150
SOMEONE sits cradling a bouquet of flowers. She crosses the grass to him. Slowing her pace as she draws near.
BLINDDATING_DVS151
SOMEONE smiles.
BLINDDATING_DVS152
He stands and offers her the small bouquet.
BLINDDATING_DVS153
SOMEONE reaches for his folded cane.
BLINDDATING_DVS155
In a dark movie theater, SOMEONE sits with his arm around SOMEONE. He nuzzles her cheek, then kisses her tenderly.
BLINDDATING_DVS156
On a sidewalk bench, they share another kiss.
BLINDDATING_DVS157
They stand staying face to face.
BLINDDATING_DVS158
SOMEONE's wide eyes fix intensely on SOMEONE. He takes a deep breath.
BLINDDATING_DVS159
SOMEONE impulsively puts her lips to his. SOMEONE's fingers cradle her face as he returns the passionate
BLINDDATING_DVS160
As they ease apart, SOMEONE gazes up.
BLINDDATING_DVS162
Tears flood SOMEONE's eyes as she retrieves her bag from the bench.
BLINDDATING_DVS163
Her brow wrinkle as she walks away. SOMEONE stands motionless and his eyelids flutter.
BLINDDATING_DVS165
SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE and their families.
BLINDDATING_DVS166
SOMEONE smiles across the table at SOMEONE who smiles hard. Now, SOMEONE dines with his family.
BLINDDATING_DVS167
Daytime. On a park bench, SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold hands.
BLINDDATING_DVS168
Now, the sun sets behind power lines.
BLINDDATING_DVS169
In the Crimson Elephant, SOMEONE sits with her mother.
BLINDDATING_DVS170
Her mother covers SOMEONE's hands with her own.
BLINDDATING_DVS171
SOMEONE musters a smile. Her mother leans closer and peers in to her daughter's eyes.
BLINDDATING_DVS172
Fighting back tears, SOMEONE nods. Her mother holds her in a gentle embrace.
BLINDDATING_DVS173
Daytime. In the park, she sits near a pond with SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS174
He takes his hand out of hers.
BLINDDATING_DVS175
SOMEONE's lips tremble as he searches for words.
BLINDDATING_DVS176
SOMEONE wets her lips. SOMEONE stands, unfolds his cane and leaves.
BLINDDATING_DVS177
Remains motionless on the bench. Now, SOMEONE drives SOMEONE in the limo.
BLINDDATING_DVS178
Now at the ballpark, SOMEONE pitches a softball.
BLINDDATING_DVS180
Nighttime. SOMEONE and SOMEONE exit the Crimson Elephant.
BLINDDATING_DVS181
SOMEONE glances behind them.
BLINDDATING_DVS182
SOMEONE's mother and another woman help across the street.
BLINDDATING_DVS184
He hobbles down the sidewalk. She follows him.
BLINDDATING_DVS185
SOMEONE watches women spreading their legs in thigh machines.
BLINDDATING_DVS186
Below him, SOMEONE does bench presses.
BLINDDATING_DVS187
muscular guy watches, as SOMEONE sits up.
BLINDDATING_DVS188
The muscular guy grins.
BLINDDATING_DVS189
As SOMEONE stands by, SOMEONE holds the weights over his head.
BLINDDATING_DVS190
SOMEONE racks the weights and sits up.
BLINDDATING_DVS191
SOMEONE shakes his head.
BLINDDATING_DVS192
SOMEONE wryly regards the muscular guy's grin.
BLINDDATING_DVS193
Now at home, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand by his open closet.
BLINDDATING_DVS195
Now, at La Ferrovia, SOMEONE sits across from a brunette with purple streaks in her hair. She smiles, sitting back in her chair. As SOMEONE sips wine, his date slips her foot out of her shoe and slides her toes up his leg. SOMEONE flattens his hands on the table.
BLINDDATING_DVS196
He reaches under him, pushes
BLINDDATING_DVS197
She lifts her cell phone.
BLINDDATING_DVS198
SOMEONE's smile sobers.
BLINDDATING_DVS199
She gives SOMEONE a once over.
BLINDDATING_DVS200
SOMEONE gulps wine and sets down the glass.
BLINDDATING_DVS201
Now, SOMEONE leaves with a hand on SOMEONE's shoulder.
BLINDDATING_DVS202
At the limo, SOMEONE feels for his brother and punches him.
BLINDDATING_DVS204
SOMEONE turns his head away from his brother. Wadded tissues plug SOMEONE's nose.
BLINDDATING_DVS206
SOMEONE hands him a fresh tissue.
BLINDDATING_DVS207
Daytime. Outside La Ferrovia, SOMEONE lets SOMEONE out of the limo.
BLINDDATING_DVS208
He turns sharply and heads toward the table for two.
BLINDDATING_DVS210
SOMEONE pulls out the other chair.
BLINDDATING_DVS211
SOMEONE circles around the table and hands SOMEONE a wine list. SOMEONE holds it up and faces it critically.
BLINDDATING_DVS212
Windows overlook the ballpark.
BLINDDATING_DVS214
He hands him a condom.
BLINDDATING_DVS215
SOMEONE takes it out of the packet.
BLINDDATING_DVS216
SOMEONE has a condom in his hand. A box of condoms sit open.
BLINDDATING_DVS217
SOMEONE talks on phone.
BLINDDATING_DVS218
A female passenger listens.
BLINDDATING_DVS219
He munches corn chips.
BLINDDATING_DVS220
SOMEONE opens the limo door. SOMEONE steps out, followed by a shapely young blonde.
BLINDDATING_DVS222
A new SOMEONE mans the reservations desk.
BLINDDATING_DVS223
A guest hands them some money.
BLINDDATING_DVS224
The blonde smiles up at SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS225
He checks his list.
BLINDDATING_DVS226
SOMEONE follows to the middle of the room, makes a sharp turn and proceeds to the corner table occupied by a Japanese couple.
BLINDDATING_DVS227
He sits with them. The SOMEONE approaches.
BLINDDATING_DVS228
SOMEONE reaches to his right and finds an arm. The Japanese man frowns at him. SOMEONE's jaw drops.
BLINDDATING_DVS229
At the far table, SOMEONE's date applies make up. SOMEONE signals the SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS230
SOMEONE's date mouths flattery to her reflection in her compact.
BLINDDATING_DVS232
SOMEONE sidles behind the SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS234
He sits.
BLINDDATING_DVS235
SOMEONE faces straight ahead, as his date's smile fades, he faces her.
BLINDDATING_DVS236
An elderly server steps to the table.
BLINDDATING_DVS237
SOMEONE takes the wine lists and holds it.
BLINDDATING_DVS239
Later, SOMEONE spoons the melty remnants of an ice cream sundae in to his mouth. His date swipes a cherry from the bowl. She holds its stem delicately in her fingertips and closes her mouth sensuously around the fruit. She eyes SOMEONE's unresponsive face. Spotting chocolate on her date's chin, she points to her chin, then lowers her tongue and points again.
BLINDDATING_DVS240
SOMEONE dabs his chin with his napkin.
BLINDDATING_DVS243
SOMEONE shakes his head.
BLINDDATING_DVS244
SOMEONE smiles.
BLINDDATING_DVS245
She kisses his cheek.
BLINDDATING_DVS248
Finger tips
BLINDDATING_DVS249
She watches the floodlit baseball field through the windows.
BLINDDATING_DVS250
He brings wine glasses. She turned.
BLINDDATING_DVS251
Wine spills down her dress.
BLINDDATING_DVS252
She grips a shelving unit.
BLINDDATING_DVS254
She prowls toward SOMEONE, reaches for his crotch. He recoils.
BLINDDATING_DVS255
SOMEONE smiles vacantly as the vexed woman slaps her butt in reply. SOMEONE glances at the sound. The woman reprises a few pelvic thrusts at the shelves, irritably grabs her dress and clutch and flounces off. The floodlights on the ball field go out. Now, seated in his bedroom at his parents’ house, SOMEONE peels off his dress shirt, he gets up and slams the door shut.
BLINDDATING_DVS256
Daytime. SOMEONE sits on a bench in a spacious and empty train station.
BLINDDATING_DVS257
He sweeps his fingertips across
BLINDDATING_DVS258
Downstairs, SOMEONE returns
BLINDDATING_DVS259
But the wall clock reads 3:25.
BLINDDATING_DVS261
SOMEONE squints at the passing city
BLINDDATING_DVS262
Later, they approach the clinic together.
BLINDDATING_DVS263
SOMEONE gets the door for SOMEONE, who enters alone.
BLINDDATING_DVS264
As he stops just inside, SOMEONE stands up behind the reception desk.
BLINDDATING_DVS265
SOMEONE feels his way to an empty seat. Wide-eyed, SOMEONE eagerly comes around to the front of the desk, but SOMEONE sits with his back to her.
BLINDDATING_DVS266
She makes the call, later.
BLINDDATING_DVS267
Later, crossing to the waiting room doors, SOMEONE stumbles on a toy dump truck. SOMEONE hurries to catch up as he exits.
BLINDDATING_DVS268
She keeps after him.
BLINDDATING_DVS269
SOMEONE watches her jog over.
BLINDDATING_DVS270
SOMEONE stops with SOMEONE at his side. He gives a faint bobble of his head, and they pass just in front of SOMEONE who waits by his limo. He watches SOMEONE lead the way with SOMEONE on his elbow. Now in the park, SOMEONE's cane taps a bench.
BLINDDATING_DVS271
SOMEONE sits first and faces forward. SOMEONE sits to his right, angled toward him. She lays her shoulder bag aside.
BLINDDATING_DVS272
SOMEONE's eyes pooled with tears.
BLINDDATING_DVS273
A tear spills down her smooth cheek.
BLINDDATING_DVS274
SOMEONE flashes a bashful smile.
BLINDDATING_DVS275
And he keeps his head bowed. His gaze stays facing forward.
BLINDDATING_DVS276
SOMEONE's pained gaze lingers on SOMEONE, then she leaves. Now in a visit with SOMEONE, Dr. SOMEONE cleans her eyeglasses as she sits fully dressed.
BLINDDATING_DVS277
Later, at the clinic.
BLINDDATING_DVS278
Now, orderlies wheel SOMEONE along on a gurney and SOMEONE looks on. As he passes, his head rolls to the side in her direction. Later, an OR light illuminates SOMEONE's restful face. In a waiting room, Dr. SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE's parents.
BLINDDATING_DVS279
The therapist takes a seat behind them. Mr. SOMEONE notices his wife staring off. Her lips stiff and tense.
BLINDDATING_DVS280
Mr. SOMEONE puts his arm around her.
BLINDDATING_DVS281
her head on him. In the OR, gloved hands use a trimmer to shave the hair above SOMEONE's right ear. Now, back in the waiting room.
BLINDDATING_DVS282
SOMEONE uses his cell phone.
BLINDDATING_DVS283
Now, SOMEONE's shaved temple lies framed by surgical clothes. And overlaid with iodine-treated film. SOMEONE folds his hands in the waiting room.
BLINDDATING_DVS284
A laser dot crosses an x-ray of SOMEONE's skull and Dr. SOMEONE takes up his scalpel. SOMEONE fidgets in the waiting room. A gloved hand in the OR reaches for a syringe, then a clamp, then discards bloody gauze.
BLINDDATING_DVS285
A microscopic view shows blood flow along a Y-shaped pathway. In the waiting room, Dr. SOMEONE puts on her glasses and exhales. Now, an assistant flips a pump run button and a pressure gauge needle swivels past 40.
BLINDDATING_DVS286
SOMEONE stares off. The surgical team works diligently.
BLINDDATING_DVS287
Later, SOMEONE's limo sits parked outside the neurosurgical center. Inside, Dr. SOMEONE approaches the family.
BLINDDATING_DVS288
Now, in recovery, SOMEONE lies with his eyes closed. A bandage wraps his head, and a tube and wire trail from his hand. His chest rises and falls steadily. SOMEONE arrives outside the glass pane door.
BLINDDATING_DVS289
Wearing a peaceful gaze, she strides eagerly to his bedside, leans in and kisses his cheek. She lets her brow brush his in a brief nuzzle, then straightens.
BLINDDATING_DVS290
SOMEONE takes a few calm breaths then leaves.
BLINDDATING_DVS291
Later, in a dim room, Dr. SOMEONE crouches down beside a conscious SOMEONE as Dr. SOMEONE looks on.
BLINDDATING_DVS292
A monitor shows a transmitter fitted in to SOMEONE's temple.
BLINDDATING_DVS293
Dr. Sato removes a power pack wired with a pair of modified sunglasses.
BLINDDATING_DVS294
The tiny camera sits mounted on the right lens.
BLINDDATING_DVS295
SOMEONE winces.
BLINDDATING_DVS296
A flash shows black and white shapes.
BLINDDATING_DVS297
The doctors follow his gesture.
BLINDDATING_DVS298
It's a hazy window. SOMEONE reaches for it.
BLINDDATING_DVS301
In the evening, they bring SOMEONE home. As SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE watch eagerly, Mr.SOMEONE guides his wife closest to SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS302
SOMEONE winces a little.
BLINDDATING_DVS303
He glimpses a hazy black and white image of SOMEONE in the living room. More flashes reveal Dr. SOMEONE and SOMEONE. As SOMEONE relaxes, his mother briefly fills his view. He bows his head, then lets his touch recognize her face.
BLINDDATING_DVS304
He looks again, sees her tender and emotional gaze and smiles at her.
BLINDDATING_DVS305
They share a tight hug.
BLINDDATING_DVS306
His mom rubs his back and cradles the nape of his neck. As SOMEONE's hand reaches out, his father's curious face cranes in to his view. Both men smile.
BLINDDATING_DVS308
and squeezes him close in his arms. SOMEONE and Dr. SOMEONE tear up. Dr. SOMEONE keeps his eyes respectfully on the reunion.
BLINDDATING_DVS309
Now, father and son separate, and SOMEONE sees SOMEONE step forward with a fond smile. The brothers embrace.
BLINDDATING_DVS310
Their parents beam. Now, Mrs. SOMEONE eagerly reaches for SOMEONE to approach.
BLINDDATING_DVS312
SOMEONE holds him tight.
BLINDDATING_DVS313
And he straightens and looks to his left.
BLINDDATING_DVS314
Faces Dr. SOMEONE, takes in her warm, lovely smile, and gives her a hug.
BLINDDATING_DVS315
SOMEONE comes full circle and pats Dr. SOMEONE's lapels.
BLINDDATING_DVS316
Later, SOMEONE enters
BLINDDATING_DVS317
bedroom and reaches for the remote control. He turns on his TV.
BLINDDATING_DVS318
He touches the screen.
BLINDDATING_DVS319
She joins him.
BLINDDATING_DVS320
As his sister crosses in front of him, he follows. SOMEONE removes two framed baseball pictures from in front of a dresser-top mirror. She smiles at SOMEONE's reflection.
BLINDDATING_DVS321
He touches the glass.
BLINDDATING_DVS322
A hint of a smile crosses his lips. SOMEONE's camera view flares brightly.
BLINDDATING_DVS324
Now, downstairs, Dr. SOMEONE checks his eyes.
BLINDDATING_DVS325
SOMEONE complies. The two doctors swap nods.
BLINDDATING_DVS326
On another night, SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie head to toe on SOMEONE's bed.
BLINDDATING_DVS327
SOMEONE eats popcorn from a bowl on his belly.
BLINDDATING_DVS329
Now, SOMEONE's parents show their daughter a card.
BLINDDATING_DVS330
SOMEONE forces a smile and walks away, leaving her parents perplexed. Morning. SOMEONE and his parents watch a newscast.
BLINDDATING_DVS331
A reporter meets SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS332
Later, SOMEONE overhears.
BLINDDATING_DVS333
Crimson Elephant, SOMEONE notices the TV report.
BLINDDATING_DVS334
her focus on the TV. On screen
BLINDDATING_DVS335
At home, SOMEONE's father enters his son's dark bedroom and turns on the light. SOMEONE lies on top of his bedspread. His hands folded on his chest. His father steps closer.
BLINDDATING_DVS336
Hiking up his pants, his father sits on the bed's edge and leans an arm over SOMEONE's legs.
BLINDDATING_DVS337
A little smile briefly crosses SOMEONE's lips.
BLINDDATING_DVS338
At the Crimson Elephant, SOMEONE and SOMEONE's families toast.
BLINDDATING_DVS339
Mr. SOMEONE sets down his champagne flute and presents a small tray to his son. As SOMEONE stands, he plucks a red ring box from a nest of fresh flowers. Across the table from him, SOMEONE stands, too. SOMEONE opens the box revealing a large diamond ring.
BLINDDATING_DVS340
SOMEONE's mother watches the young Indian man slide the ring on to her daughter's slender finger.
BLINDDATING_DVS341
SOMEONE gives him a tight-lipped smile. Meanwhile, SOMEONE feels around his desktop. He picks up the glasses and the battery pouch. Wearing a determined expression, he turns away. Now, he steps down the driveway, using his cane.
BLINDDATING_DVS342
Reaching the sidewalk, he takes a few steps to his right and pulls out a phone.
BLINDDATING_DVS343
Frowning, SOMEONE pockets the phone and heads off down the sidewalk in the opposite direction. At the Crimson Elephant, SOMEONE hurries to a phone behind a beaded curtain. Holding the receiver to her ear, she gazes at the engagement ring on her finger.
BLINDDATING_DVS347
SOMEONE reluctantly raises her champagne and forces a smile. She has a gloomy expression.
BLINDDATING_DVS349
Meanwhile, the bus arrives at a terminal.
BLINDDATING_DVS350
He puts the glasses back on.
BLINDDATING_DVS351
As Mr. SOMEONE glares, SOMEONE goes to SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS352
He takes off the glasses.
BLINDDATING_DVS353
her face is in his hands.
BLINDDATING_DVS354
SOMEONE and Mr. SOMEONE glare.
BLINDDATING_DVS355
SOMEONE's family watches attentively.
BLINDDATING_DVS356
SOMEONE's big brown eyes brim with tears and she pulls SOMEONE into a passionate kiss. SOMEONE storms out, followed by his father and mother. SOMEONE's father watches the kissing couple with a wistful smile. SOMEONE winces and falls to the floor.
BLINDDATING_DVS357
Now, an ambulance in front of restaurant.
BLINDDATING_DVS358
He gives a comforting pat to SOMEONE's mom then hurries off. SOMEONE's mother pulls SOMEONE close and they step over to a waiting area. SOMEONE's father follows. SOMEONE watches them walk past SOMEONE, who stands alone, still in her sari.
BLINDDATING_DVS359
As he smiles at her, she stares back tearful and
BLINDDATING_DVS360
Her lips tremble, and tears glisten in her eyes. SOMEONE takes a step closer.
BLINDDATING_DVS361
Meeting SOMEONE's sincere gaze, SOMEONE takes a shaky breath.
BLINDDATING_DVS362
SOMEONE gently puts a hand on her shoulder and guides her to the waiting area.
BLINDDATING_DVS363
SOMEONE's mother takes SOMEONE's hand in hers, then pulls her into
BLINDDATING_DVS364
SOMEONE rests one hand on his wife's shoulder and the other on SOMEONE's wrist. Now, SOMEONE sleeps in a hospital bed hooked up to monitors. A bandage covers one side of his head as Dr. SOMEONE watches from the doorway. SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the SOMEONE approach. SOMEONE shifts under the covers.
BLINDDATING_DVS365
They all rush to his bedside.
BLINDDATING_DVS366
SOMEONE leans his face close to SOMEONE's.
BLINDDATING_DVS367
He gently kisses her.
BLINDDATING_DVS368
Now, at the Crimson Elephant, SOMEONE dances with SOMEONE.
BLINDDATING_DVS369
wears a fuchsia pink sari.
BLINDDATING_DVS371
Their lips gently part.
BLINDDATING_DVS372
Now, as a train speeds down a track, SOMEONE laughs