SOMEONE is approaching van.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS11
It shows a statue of a cow.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS12
Now, the van rolls past pedestrians making their way
INSIDE_MAN_DVS13
between the two front seats, SOMEONE gets up.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS15
On marble bank lobby, customers wait in line.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS16
In the alley, the people in coveralls unload a dolly from the van. Back inside, a woman listens to music. A narrow eyed man waits patiently behind her.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS17
As the painters load a flat of one gallon paint cans onto a hand truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS18
a distinguished customer inside an eight-year-old boy standing with him. He uses a handheld video game. A banker in a turban sportingly bumps fist with a hefty co-worker.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS19
The painters ready more supplies.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS20
The painters close up the van.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS21
Now, inside an Asian guy glances at the cell phone user's chest.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS22
She catches him looking. As he looks away, she glares.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS23
Now, the painters wheel their supplies to the curb. One enters the bank carrying two work lights and a white canvas duffel. A potbellied security guard watches him pass. The painter wears a dark cap and sunglasses.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS24
It's SOMEONE. He stops at a bank's lock.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS25
A black guard faces the cell phone user.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS26
She smiles.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS27
SOMEONE aims an unlit work light at the security camera. In a monitoring room, one screen goes dark.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS28
SOMEONE aims a second unlit work light at another camera - incapacitating it.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS29
A customer opens the door for the arriving painters. As they wheel in the hand truck, at street level, the two guards watch the upper lobby from the top of the stairs. Two painters fasten the doors shut.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS30
SOMEONE holds a gun to a guard's side.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS32
A narrow eyed man tries to run.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS33
SOMEONE approaches the standing Hasidic man.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS34
His nose and mouth hidden by cloth.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS35
Outside, pedestrians notice smoke coming from the bank. Two pass a policeman.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS36
The slim policeman approaches the entrance and tries the doors.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS37
Peering inside, he tries another and reaches for his shoulder radio.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS38
As SOMEONE leaves him and re-secures the door, the officer takes out his own gun, then radios in.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS40
He mouths SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS41
Panama hat, he tosses his jacket into an unmarked car. As his partner gets in, Keith takes the wheel.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS42
It shows police cars surrounding the bank.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS44
ESU member is  toting a bunker.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS45
He past the locked down bank doors. Meanwhile, more ESU guys use orange tape to cordon off a perimeter.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS46
SOMEONE waves the vehicle forward.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS47
TV reporter and cameraman hurry from a news van.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS48
Now, a lavish ceiling recessed with octagonal vaults spreads above a spacious study. A brunette woman clad in pastels acknowledges a valet as she crosses toward a lone figure at a full-length window.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS49
The white haired banker sits, his gaze thoughtful and troubled. The light from the window highlights his mustache and drawn weathered face.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS50
The female member of SOMEONE's crew leads down stairs into the basement.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS52
mastermind strides with gun in hand.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS53
The nervous hostages hurry past him.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS54
He points his gun menacingly at the black security guard. SOMEONE approaches the eight-year-old.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS55
His father pushes him behind his back. SOMEONE turns away.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS56
The hostages divide into two groups standing of a wide alcove that opens to the vault.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS58
The hostages comply. The female accomplice.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS59
SOMEONE is collecting keys and cell phones in a sack. As the dark haired executive hands over his keys to the female robber, she stops and raises her arm. She signals to SOMEONE and backs away, hand on her rifle. The leader approaches the executive and turns his ear to the man.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS60
The mastermind puts his arm around him.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS61
He holds his gun to SOMEONE's cheek.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS62
Tears stream down SOMEONE's cheeks. SOMEONE reaches into the sack of employee phones, takes one out and scrolls through its contacts list. He tosses the phone aside, then reaches back into the sack. The hostages watch
INSIDE_MAN_DVS63
One woman hugs her folded hands to her chest. Another closes her eyes.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS64
SOMEONE flips open another phone and pulls up its speed dial numbers. SOMEONE appears at the top of the list. SOMEONE glances at the executive, then presses a button.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS65
The mastermind enters a nearby office and picks up a cell phone from behind the open door.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS66
He gives SOMEONE his cell phone and pats him on the cheek, then returns to the office and shuts the door. A ripple of glass window shows SOMEONE striking a pensive pose. He turns around and teeter-totters his open hands as he weighs options.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS67
SOMEONE storms back out, grabs SOMEONE and drags him into the office.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS68
SOMEONE holds him up, SOMEONE shuts the door.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS70
SOMEONE keeps wailing on him.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS71
SOMEONE stops and opens the door, looking down near his feet.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS72
SOMEONE is stepping over the unconscious executive's legs.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS73
He approaches the turbaned loan officer who holds out a set of keys.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS74
SOMEONE steps over to the eight-year-old boy who offers his handheld video game.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS76
The men and women separate into different groups.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS77
The hostages quickly oblige. Our view passes along the rows of men and women
INSIDE_MAN_DVS78
cutting back and forth, this way, this row.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS79
SOMEONE moves pass the females, some of whom cover their bodies demurely. At the end of the line, a chunky older woman, still clothed, scowls at him. SOMEONE folds his arms behind his back.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS80
He points his gun at her.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS81
SOMEONE's female accomplice grabs hold of the older woman.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS82
The criminals reach into their boxes and toss identical plastic wrapped garments to each of the men and women. The hostages put on dark loose fitting coveralls.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS83
Detectives SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter the command truck and find an officer in a cramped room.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS84
SOMEONE is Putting on bullet proof vests labeled NYPD ESU.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS86
Several hostages lie face down in a break room. The hefty banker trembles in a chair. A masked figure
INSIDE_MAN_DVS87
SOMEONE helps the old man to his feet.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS88
The bank employee staggers over to one of the robbers standing in the doorway. The criminal leads the old man out.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS89
Following them to the doorway, SOMEONE looks back at the other hostages. Now, one of the young criminals exits the bank. Another shoves out an identical looking figure.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS92
Now, the black security guard sits with his back to a concrete wall.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS93
SOMEONE and SOMEONE listen.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS94
In the bank.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS95
Hostages cower on the floor near a bookshelf as one of the criminals throws open a door. He leads his three accomplices through a suite of offices, each containing a number of captives.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS96
The robbers shoot looks at the hostages through their sunglasses. The last one shuts a door behind him. They round a corner out of the offices and walk along a wall of vertical bars. Entering the vault cage, they take a quick look at the stacks of money. SOMEONE turns away and his crew follows. They head to another barred door and glance inside a safe deposit room. Now, darkness.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS97
A door opens. SOMEONE turns on rows of fluorescent lights revealing a storage room. He and the crew step inside and look at the shelves of office supplies. Amid the contents on the back wall, four Dell computer boxes sit stacked on the lowest shelf.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS98
Now, the sun crests a building’s steeply pitched roof. Around the corner from an ornamental statue, a balcony looks in on a spacious penthouse. An amber haired woman brings a date book from a desk to a sunken living room. A swarthy fashionable man in a suit rises from a chair.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS99
The pony-tailed client picks up a metal briefcase and follows the assistant out. Ms. SOMEONE moves to her desk and sets down her date book. Her assistant reappears on her computer monitor.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS100
Mr. SOMEONE hangs up, then rises from his chair with the aid of a cane. Now, in the concrete interrogation room,
INSIDE_MAN_DVS101
It's SOMEONE. His face is cut and bruised.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS102
Now, Captain SOMEONE meets with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS104
the door to the command truck and follows the detectives inside.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS105
Mr. SOMEONE looks out toward the misty harbor. Silhouettes of tall buildings loom on the other side.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS106
In the bank's supply room, a muscular unmasked robber removes boxes from the back wall. An accomplice enters as he slides away an empty shelving
INSIDE_MAN_DVS107
SOMEONE exits. In one bare corner, SOMEONE chips at the floor with a pickax. Now, outside flashing police lights come into focus.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS108
They eye the logo on the criminals' van - perfectly planned painting. We never leave until the job is done.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS109
peels off the decal revealing a different logo underneath.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS110
Later, in the command truck,
INSIDE_MAN_DVS111
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a phone.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS112
Hood lowered, he wears his mask and shades.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS113
sits at the desk, staring at the phone.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS114
In the command truck,
INSIDE_MAN_DVS115
Back in the bank.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS116
SOMEONE sits motionless, one hand on top of the desk.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS117
Back in the command truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS118
An image appears on a screen.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS119
Nine security feeds show the bank. One goes out.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS120
Two more go blank. Rewound footage of the lobby shows SOMEONE at the bank slip kiosk.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS122
In interrogation, the chunky older woman.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS123
Now, two robbers lead another hostage outside.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS125
three cops frisk the released man and pulls off the mask.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS127
Two officers cautiously remove the drawer.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS128
Now, office workers in desks fill an elegant carpeted room. Ms. SOMEONE approaches a balding man.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS129
The mayor smiles.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS130
Nodding, Ms. SOMEONE returns a grin.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS131
As she leaves the room, the mayor looks at a TV. News footage shows an Asian reporter outside the bank.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS132
He holds ice to his brow.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS133
SOMEONE shifts his eyes.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS134
In the bank, SOMEONE dons an earpiece. Meanwhile, SOMEONE reads writing on the drawer.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS135
The policemen stare at Mr. SOMEONE. The elderly chairman scans their sober faces.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS136
SOMEONE shows Mr. SOMEONE out of the command truck, then looks to the others and smirks.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS138
Across from the bank, snipers
INSIDE_MAN_DVS139
Below, officers creep toward the entrance. the door and points a gun
INSIDE_MAN_DVS140
The masked figure holds a piece of paper.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS142
One of the policemen steps forward, takes the paper and passes it back to SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS143
As the Captain walks over to SOMEONE, the robbers in the no hold are re-entering Manhattan trust. SOMEONE looks down at the paper and grins. Back in the command truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS144
In the bank, the hostages sit in an office. A lanky guy removes his hood and mask.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS146
Interrogation. The man's gaze drops.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS147
officers carry boxes.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS148
SOMEONE joins the cops and walks toward the bank
INSIDE_MAN_DVS149
They set the food and water on the ground.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS150
SOMEONE steps out.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS151
SOMEONE smiles at the mastermind.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS152
Robbers collect the food.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS153
SOMEONE backs up into the bank and closes the door. The detective
INSIDE_MAN_DVS154
The criminal fastens the lock and walks
INSIDE_MAN_DVS155
the door with several cops and peers through the glass.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS156
Command truck, the police listen intently to a radio transmission.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS157
As SOMEONE hangs his head, SOMEONE holds his brow wrinkled.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS158
SOMEONE stares off pensively.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS159
SOMEONE leaves.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS160
In the bank, SOMEONE heads down a hallway past an accomplice. She opens an office door and points to a row of
INSIDE_MAN_DVS161
He leads them into the hallway in a line. At the front, she forces the busty woman forward. They reach a second office where another robber stands by just out
INSIDE_MAN_DVS162
just into the room.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS163
She shuts the door. The other robber helps her remove her gun and gloves.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS166
He shoves her inside.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS167
He removes the busty woman.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS168
The criminal leads her around the vault to another office. He looks inside.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS169
hostages comply and lower their heads. He slams the door,
INSIDE_MAN_DVS170
then moves the woman down the hall. He opens the next room.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS171
He turns to the busty woman.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS172
He forces her inside, closes the door and walks onward to another office. In interrogation, the Asian guy looks at a group of instant photos.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS173
SOMEONE's eyes drifts downwards. She cocks her head.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS174
She holds a picture.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS175
Now, in the supply room, SOMEONE kneels over a freshly dug hole with her face unmasked. She moves a tile into a trash bag lined box, gets to her feet and removes a pair of rubber gloves. SOMEONE picks up the box. Now, in the command truck, a stout officer listens to the radio. SOMEONE and the others stare at him.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS177
SOMEONE exits the truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS178
An officer opens the barricade and a construction worker steps forward.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS179
A helmeted worker follows the detective to the truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS180
SOMEONE opens the door.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS181
The worker climbs aboard and joins the rest of SOMEONE's team.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS182
Now, in the bank vault, the young boy sits on a square bale of cash. SOMEONE enters carrying a plate of pizza and a bottle of water. The boy looks up from his video game as the robber approaches.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS183
Putting the game down, the boy accepts the food.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS184
As the young hostage takes the pizza slice in hand, SOMEONE takes another bale of cash off a shelf.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS185
sets it on the floor like a stool and sits across from the boy. While his hostage eats, SOMEONE reaches forward and picks up the handheld video game. On screen, a red convertible heads down a virtual street with graffitied buildings. Wearing a do rag and gold rings, the driver
INSIDE_MAN_DVS186
On screen, the character
INSIDE_MAN_DVS187
The boy spreads his arms toward the cash.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS188
As our view pulls back from the vault, SOMEONE places the handheld device on the floor. He watches the boy.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS189
SOMEONE nods and our view withdraws from the vault.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS190
Now, in the command truck, SOMEONE approaches the construction worker.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS191
Now, inside the vault, we circle SOMEONE as he faces the shelves of money. The mastermind peels back his dark hood, then dons his sunglasses. As we make a second orbit and halt at his face, he tugs the white mask down off his nose and mouth. His green eyes take in the shelves of baled cash.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS192
The circular vault door
INSIDE_MAN_DVS193
his silhouette. Just outside the giant safes, SOMEONE stands with her rifle. SOMEONE turns to face the outer room and leans lazily on the vault doorframe. Now, in the command truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS194
She hands him a glossy bag.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS195
thumbs through dozens of citations.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS196
He eyes SOMEONE, her gaze coyly defiant.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS197
She lights up.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS198
With a sultry smirk, the shapely woman leaves SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE to their investigation.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS199
SOMEONE leafs through the parking tickets.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS200
He tosses the bag to Berk. Now, inside a basement office, an AK 47 leans upright in a locker. Scotch tape holds snapshots to a window and keys hang on a dirty pegboard. A window seal displays bowling trophies and framed images of Jesus hang on a wall. Seated in the key maker’s workshop, SOMEONE eats a pizza. An iPod on the desk plays next to the exposed police bug.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS201
On the far wall of an office, secured with steel bars, SOMEONE unlocks a door and enters
INSIDE_MAN_DVS202
safety deposit box room. As she inserts a key into box 392, SOMEONE joins her. He smokes as she takes a set of picks to a second lock set in the small door. The locks turns. SOMEONE slides out a covered metal drawer painted maroon.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS203
SOMEONE lifts the lid holding a lit cigarette between two of his latex gloved fingers. Finding a black suede envelope, he unfastens its string and button closure and removes a manilla envelope from inside it. We glimpse a black eagle emblem amid the return address and then, the same emblem on the cover page
INSIDE_MAN_DVS204
SOMEONE's blue eyes fix on SOMEONE
INSIDE_MAN_DVS205
SOMEONE focuses on ten black small bags.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS207
A red leather jewelry box sits tucked among them.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS208
SOMEONE leaves the room with the papers. SOMEONE locks the box.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS209
stands in profile to the arriving vehicles. He hikes up
INSIDE_MAN_DVS210
SOMEONE gets in. Ms. SOMEONE and the judge sit pleasantly before him.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS213
Now, as an officer turns a crank,
INSIDE_MAN_DVS214
lights rises vertical and turns on.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS215
Inside the command truck, SOMEONE uses a phone.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS216
He gives a thumbs up to his listening team.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS217
SOMEONE loosens up, rubbing his shaved head. Outside the bank, police stand by in the afternoon sun.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS218
The ESU team members hold their rifles at the ready.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS219
The late day sun washes brightly across the bank's facade.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS220
On the sidewalk, firemen gather for a break outside the corner diner. Two detectives exit the coffee shop. In the window, Ms. SOMEONE sits patiently at a counter, looking out toward the bank.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS221
Seen from inside, she shifts in her seat. In the bank's supply room, one of the robbers digs more at the hole in the corner and scoops dirt into the trash bag lined box. Now, in interrogation.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS222
It's the robber SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS224
One of SOMEONE's staff holds up a note - food.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS225
calmly in the secured office.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS226
Our view drifts to another containing five captives.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS227
Now, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and the lanky guy eye the hole in the floor.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS228
Now, the sky darkens over New York. SOMEONE's girlfriend reclines on a bed in lingerie
INSIDE_MAN_DVS229
He joins Ms. SOMEONE outside the diner. She buttons her designer business coat and follows him.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS230
a cell phone. They stop in front of a We Will Never Forget poster.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS231
He gives the phone to Ms. SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS233
Emergency lights flash on the building. Now SOMEONE walks with Ms. SOMEONE who wears an NYPD cap and jacket.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS235
She strides over to the front doors and knocks on the glass.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS236
Now, inside SOMEONE pats her down, as she lies prone on the marble floor. He taps her shoulder and she gets to her feet.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS237
As Ms. SOMEONE strides forward in her taupe heels, she takes off the NYPD jacket.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS238
The masked SOMEONE faces her through a teller window.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS240
We can see awards line a shelf in his office.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS241
SOMEONE shows her the manilla envelope.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS242
It features a swastika.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS243
Outside, snipers keep their guns trained on the bank. Ms. SOMEONE rejoins SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS244
Ms. SOMEONE leaves him. Now, in interrogation.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS245
SOMEONE studies the instant photos of the hostages. His father rubs the boy's back.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS246
They interrogate the narrow eyed man.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS247
He shrugs and looks down.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS248
They show the Jewish man snapshots of SOMEONE and the lanky guy.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS250
She rolls her eyes, then unzips the coveralls revealing her full chest.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS251
The detectives look at her blankly. Now, in the command truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS252
SOMEONE sits up in his chair and reaches for a phone.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS253
The detective dials and SOMEONE picks up a headset. In Manhattan Trust, SOMEONE exits the supply room, then closes the door.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS254
He walks down the hallway with his face uncovered and his hood back on his shoulders. The mastermind enters the secured office, approaches the desk and picks up the phone.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS255
Our view rotates around SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS256
SOMEONE swaps looks with his partner, then hangs up the receiver. The detective rolls down his sleeve.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS257
Now, at the bank entrance, a robber waves SOMEONE inside. The detective leans over, hands to a wall. As the criminal locks the door, as second masked robber walks downstairs with a pistol pointed at SOMEONE. His accomplice frisks the detective. SOMEONE looks up and stares at the robber with the pistol.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS258
The first robber moves past SOMEONE and climbs the steps ahead of him. With only the police floodlights shining dimly through the windows, the pistol-wielding robber follows behind the detective.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS259
SOMEONE reaches the lobby and follows the first robber past empty desks and chairs. Holding his gun steady, the other robber tails the detective closely. They head through a set of glass doors to another staircase.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS260
As the detective descends, SOMEONE reaches into his pocket and pulls out a pack of gum. He holds it out to SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS261
SOMEONE approaches one of the side offices and turns back to SOMEONE. The mastermind opens the door revealing a group of hooded hostages seated on the floor. As the detective enters, the hostages look at him. Their faces masked only from the nose down. Walking past SOMEONE, SOMEONE heads to an interior door and turns the knob. More hostages sit in the next office.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS262
All dressed in the same baggy coveralls, the men and women line the small office. While SOMEONE looks around, the mastermind opens a third door. The detective continues onward. In the next office, he finds SOMEONE in his original clothing. The unmasked boy sits beside his disguised father. SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS263
SOMEONE approaches another closed door and turns the knob.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS264
Inside, SOMEONE finds half a dozen hostages.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS265
The detective glances at the hostages, then steps out into the hallway. As a robber stands guard behind them, SOMEONE follows SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS266
SOMEONE raises his gun.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS267
SOMEONE walks away from the open vault. The mastermind passes one of his armed accomplices and climbs the stairs after the detective.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS268
SOMEONE stops and faces him.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS269
SOMEONE remains still.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS270
A robber aims a rifle at SOMEONE's head. The detective gets up.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS271
SOMEONE draws his gun.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS272
Holding his hands up, SOMEONE nods and paces to the door. He nervously makes his way past the barrel of the gun and walks out. As SOMEONE fixes his suit, SOMEONE approaches.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS273
In the bank, SOMEONE stares outside, pistol aimed. His armed accomplice backs up the stairs.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS274
The mastermind turns around and climbs the steps to the lobby. In the supply room, unmasked, SOMEONE and the lanky guy join SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS275
Now, in the command truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS277
As SOMEONE picks up the receiver, SOMEONE and SOMEONE lean close.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS278
On top of the truck, our view travels up a pole to a camera. The device rotates. On screen, SOMEONE and five unidentifiable witnesses surround a seventh person masked by a white sack. The mastermind shoots.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS279
SOMEONE exits the white sack and the hostage drops to the floor.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS280
SOMEONE exits the truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS281
Inside, the solemn faced detective glides stiffly past running policemen. Reaching the entrance, SOMEONE pounds on the glass door.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS282
Banging it, they stand inches apart.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS283
The mastermind withdraws into the bank.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS284
SOMEONE lingers outside and stares at SOMEONE. As his nemesis turns away, the detective's breath fogs the glass. Tears shimmer in his stern eyes. Nodding his head slightly, SOMEONE walks off.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS285
Reflected in the glass door, two ESU officers outside back away with their rifles. Now, in the command truck, SOMEONE uses a phone.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS286
SOMEONE looks over and sees his boss leaning against a dark sedan. He heads over
INSIDE_MAN_DVS287
The detective takes a breath and nods. As the captain leaves, SOMEONE turns his head and exhales.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS288
He rubs his palm over his bald head and trudges back toward the others.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS289
the truck, SOMEONE studies blueprints.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS290
He imagines the robber shooting
INSIDE_MAN_DVS292
then hides in the safety deposit vault.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS293
The police officer tosses a smoke bomb.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS294
Back in the truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS296
Officers shoot them down. Approaching the vault, officers spread out. A robber emerges.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS297
collapses on a bale of cash.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS298
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS299
We see bloodstains on box 392. Morning, in the truck.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS300
SOMEONE stares at him gravely.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS301
SOMEONE gets up and walks out of the truck. His partner leans his head against a wall.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS302
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS303
SOMEONE shifts his gaze.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS305
SOMEONE stares unblinking.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS306
Now, in the command truck, SOMEONE stands over the message written on the
INSIDE_MAN_DVS308
he pulls at the inner surface of the drawer and yanks the front panel off.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS309
SOMEONE shakes off his hand.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS310
A mic lies taped inside. He slams
INSIDE_MAN_DVS311
He grabs a radio handset.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS312
In the secured office, SOMEONE looks up. He activates a smoke bomb and rolls it into the hallway. He activates two more and lops them past SOMEONE
INSIDE_MAN_DVS314
As his cohorts gather, SOMEONE pulls up his mask.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS315
on his rifle and ditches his shades.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS316
watches smoke filter from the bank.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS317
Thick clouds of white smoke billow out.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS318
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch the explosion grimly. Officers stand behind a squad car with their rifles aimed at the doors. The masked and hooded figures emerge, waving their arms.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS320
SOMEONE lies on her back, staring meekly at two riflemen over her.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS321
SOMEONE steps among the immobilized suspects. The narrow eyed man scowls, his cheek against the pavement.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS323
The lanky robber now lies on his back, palms up.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS324
Now, two men with bunker shields enter the bank followed by the rest of the police.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS325
They climb the foyer stairs and secure both sides of the lobby.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS326
He beams shine brightly from their riflescopes.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS327
He checks under empty desks.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS328
They methodically search a conference room.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS330
In the lobby, they warily face the teller windows. More ESU officers move in behind the counter.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS331
The ESU squad descends toward the basement.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS332
SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter the bank. With intensely bright lights agleam on their
INSIDE_MAN_DVS333
each office along the alcove.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS334
Officers secure the key maker.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS335
Troopers pass the money vault.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS336
Cross the alcove to the safety deposit room. SOMEONE radios in.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS337
Others halt before the supply room.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS338
lights and check along the shelves. Three trash bags sit in the middle of the floor.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS339
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE descend the dimly lit staircase. Outside the vault cage, they meet up with SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS340
SOMEONE empties a white sack.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS341
SOMEONE one of the robbers rifles.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS343
SOMEONE responds.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS344
SOMEONE strides out into the alcove and turns left before the secured office. He joins SOMEONE and SOMEONE in the ladies' room. SOMEONE lifts a large white hood off the sink. It's spattered with a blood red stain and attached to a hose and hand pump. SOMEONE presses the plungers, squirting red water.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS345
SOMEONE grins.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS346
They file into the supply room and rummage through the three black trash bags in the center of the floor. They dump out loads of men and women's clothing. SOMEONE faces an ESU officer.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS347
Outside, a police transport bus pulls to a stop at one end of the street. As its doors open, officers on the scene hustle handcuffed suspects to their feet.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS349
officers, each guide a separate suspect onto the side.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS351
taking photographs of the busty woman.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS353
He halts the narrow eyed. Now, with the black security.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS354
On one bus, the female robber, SOMEONE, watches more suspects file down the aisle.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS355
guys sit among other hostages. Their faces as dirty and sweaty as their tired neighbors. SOMEONE and the lanky robber take shallow breaths.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS356
Fade to black. Now, in a police station conference room, SOMEONE sits at the long table. His boss enters.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS357
SOMEONE smiles and shakes his hand.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS358
Rolling his tongue in his mouth, SOMEONE eyes his note.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS359
Eyeing the captain. SOMEONE swivels his chair.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS360
He heads off.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS361
SOMEONE leaves. Now, safety deposit box 392 appears. In the squad room, SOMEONE and SOMEONE eye bank files.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS362
statues of sentinels and scholars adorn a massive courthouse. One holds scrolls that read Lex Scripta and Lex Tradita. Inside, SOMEONE shakes a judge's hand.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS363
SOMEONE walks down a marble corridor, rubbing his hands and grinning. Near the elevators, Ms. White sits on a bench.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS364
She meets the doctor SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS366
SOMEONE turns off the recorder.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS367
Ms. White bounces her shapely leg.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS368
SOMEONE's gaze lingers on the woman, then shifts away. He stands and leaves adjusting the jacket of his off-white Panama suit. Now, he descends a half moon spiral staircase, crossing a floor’s elevator lobby to another flight.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS369
Now, at a social club, Ms. White enters a men's room and marches pass the attendant.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS370
She moves past a man in the urinal and continues on to a back room. Mr. Case sits in a chair as a barber sweeps hair off his shoulders.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS372
Mr. Case puts down a newspaper.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS373
He dismisses his aging barber and watches the man go.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS375
Her cool smile evaporates as she leans forward.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS376
He holds out a check.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS377
Smirking, Ms. White collects her purse and gets up. She accepts the check.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS378
Mr. Case's smile wilts a little. Ms. White turns and exits wearing a satisfied smile as she buttons her black jacket. Mr. Case throws his checkbook to the counter. It hits the edge and falls to the floor. Now, in the cinder block cell.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS379
He packs a shoe into a backpack.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS380
He picks up a velvet pouch.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS381
It's full of diamonds.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS383
lanky robber cover a shelving unit.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS384
Now, office supplies sit neatly shelved along the new back wall. In his cell, SOMEONE shuts off two lights.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS385
Back in the supply room, the Dell computer boxes shift. Now, the room's light spills.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS387
As a panel gets removed from the wall, SOMEONE pushes the stack of boxes out of his way.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS388
Then moves a duffel bag into the supply room.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS389
He crawls out through the secret opening,
INSIDE_MAN_DVS390
then fits the panel back on to the fake wall, seaming the cell in darkness.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS391
Now, an American and New York State flag flap in the wind outside the bank. Across the street and around the corner, a black SUV sits parked at the curb.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS392
Passenger side window lowers.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS393
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the lanky robber sit in the back seat.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS394
SOMEONE sits at the wheel. SOMEONE's sedan drives by. In the supply room, SOMEONE wearing a Yankee's cap puts on a pair of stylish sunglasses and slings the backpack over his shoulder. Outside, SOMEONE and SOMEONE exit the sedan. The robbers notice.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS395
SOMEONE dials a cell phone.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS396
Back in the supply room, SOMEONE answers his.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS397
Now, the mastermind slips out into the basement hall. He steps warily past the secured office where a man uses the phone.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS398
As SOMEONE approaches the basement stairs, the man exits the secured office and strides toward the vault. SOMEONE heads up toward the first floor, crossing paths with the woman. She glances back at him.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS399
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter the bank and jog up the main stairs to the lobby. Coming in the other direction, SOMEONE bumps into the middle-aged detective.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS400
The mastermind leaves as SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach a desk.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS401
Outside, SOMEONE walks out through the front door. SOMEONE smiles.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS402
Now, SOMEONE approaches the black SUV. He opens the front passenger door and hands his duffel bag to SOMEONE who passes it SOMEONE.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS403
SOMEONE grips hands with his muscular accomplice, then kisses SOMEONE. SOMEONE checks the duffel bag.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS404
In the safe deposit room, three people enter.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS406
Outside, the black SUV drives off.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS407
SOMEONE slides out the maroon drawer and opens it.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS408
He finds a pack of Juicy Fruit gum.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS409
Next to it, he finds the Cartier box and the huge diamond ring inside it.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS410
He opens up a note and reads.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS411
He bags the note with the other items, then shuts the maroon drawer and slides it back into box 392. Now, a valet holds open a door for Mr. Case as he enters his spacious study. He finds SOMEONE and SOMEONE browsing the room's contents.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS412
SOMEONE shows off the diamond ring placed prominently on his middle finger.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS413
SOMEONE gives the bank chairman a cold look, then follows his partner. Later, the two detectives strut down a sidewalk.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS414
SOMEONE heads up a staircase wearing his Panama hat.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS415
A nicely dressed man approach
INSIDE_MAN_DVS416
He finds the mayor, Ms. SOMEONE, and another man at a table.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS417
He shows the ring.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS418
The other man leaves the table.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS421
He writes it on a business card.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS422
He holds out the pen recorder.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS423
He walks away pocketing the Cartier box. The mayor furrows his brow.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS424
Ms. SOMEONE glances at him. Now, a bare chested young man sleeps on a couch gripping a liquor bottle. A door opens, spilling light into the room. A shadow shows a figure in a brimmed hat. SOMEONE shuts the door, then steps over to the couch.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS425
The detective enters his bedroom.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS426
As he shuts the door, a pair of smooth feminine legs stretches out on the bed.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS427
Wearing sexy lingerie, SOMEONE's girlfriend sits up and kisses him passionately.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS428
Their hands rove up and down each other's backs.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS429
He points her fingers like guns, puts on his hat, and strike a pose.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS430
He puts a framed certificate on his dresser. It reads Awarded to Keith SOMEONE, Detective First Grade. He takes off his pistol, unloads it and places it in a lock box.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS431
He sets his badge and PDA on top. Reaching into his jacket pocket, he feels around, then pauses. He removes a diamond. Pinching it in between his thumb and index finger, he turns it in the light. Its many facets gleam.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS432
SOMEONE stares with a confused look, then faces his reflection in a vanity mirror. He recalls bumping into SOMEONE at the bank.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS433
SOMEONE breaks into a wide grin.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS434
SOMEONE reclines on the bed.
INSIDE_MAN_DVS435
twirls his Panama hat on her toe.