Then they slap at each other.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS22
In a tub, bubbles rise from the little boy's bottom.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS23
His sister lets one loose.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS24
As children, the sister climbs into her brother's bed to snuggle.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS25
Now, the preteen boy in braces shows off sprouting armpit hairs.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS26
His sister passes and shows a bushy patch under her arm.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS27
The boy wilts.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS28
Outside, the teenage boy poses with a prom date.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS29
His sister peeks from behind them.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS30
At school, he waves - clad in a varsity jacket.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS31
His sister runs into him with a French horn.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS32
On a tennis court, the sister bounces a ball on the racket.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS33
As her brother flirts with a girl.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS34
The tennis ball nails the girl in the eye.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS35
The boy walks away from his sister.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS36
Now at a commercial shoot, a dark-haired man sits in the producer's chair, followed by a bespectacled assistant.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS37
A stomach puppet shows up.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS38
SOMEONE grabs a bottle of Pepto.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS39
He chugs some down.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS40
SOMEONE's assistant brings him a soda.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS41
The assistant sips the Pepto.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS42
Now, an alarm clock reads 3:30.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS43
SOMEONE and his wife wake up.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS44
He climbs out of bed.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS45
Later at the airport.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS46
In a deserted baggage claim area, SOMEONE spots a sleeping janitor slumped on the floor.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS47
Then he sees a brunette woman near a dozen suitcases.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS48
The manish woman spots her brother.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS49
On the road.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS50
SOMEONE puts down his window.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS51
The indraft pins the cockatoo against the back of the cage.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS53
The haggard man sulks.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS54
In a pilgrim dress, SOMEONE demonstrates.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS55
SOMEONE kicks and punches, startling SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS56
Now, SOMEONE peeks into a guestroom where his broad-back sister sleeps on her side.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS57
Poopsie perches on the footboard.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS58
SOMEONE climbs out of bed, leaving behind a full body sweat stain on the sheet.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS59
SOMEONE points.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS60
Later, over Thanksgiving dinner.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS61
SOMEONE's mother-in-law shifts nervously.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS62
The girl sits beside a matching doll.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS63
SOMEONE resumes eating.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS64
He looks up.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS65
She smiles at SOMEONE, who shakes his head.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS66
The shirtless boy tapes a drumstick to his belly.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS67
SOMEONE wears a saltshaker taped to his head.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS68
SOMEONE slaps herself.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS69
SOMEONE slaps herself in the face again.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS70
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE off her chair.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS71
She shakes it from SOMEONE's head.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS72
SOMEONE pockets a dinner roll and heads out.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS73
Eating, SOMEONE shakes his head.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS75
SOMEONE falls on her face.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS76
SOMEONE lies among the trees.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS77
On YouTube.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS78
Performing on stage, SOMEONE glares into the audience.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS79
SOMEONE continues his call in the kitchen.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS80
SOMEONE scowls.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS81
A landscaper peeks in from the patio.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS82
He holds his hands out and stops moving.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS83
He smiles at her as he leaves.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS84
He waves affectionately.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS85
She pulls a slip of paper from her bra.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS86
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE exits a shop called My Tiny Me dressed in costumes.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS87
Each holding a doll that matches their outfit.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS88
At a pony rodeo in a park.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS89
The kids ride pass SOMEONE and an employee.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS90
Later, she hoists herself onto a tiny pony.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS91
The horse collapses.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS92
Its legs are completely splayed.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS93
At home, SOMEONE rides a bike with a hamster taped to his back.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS94
Now, wrapped presents lie on a table as six candles burn on a menorah.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS95
SOMEONE awakes on the sofa and notices a lady's meaty fingers caressing his arm.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS96
He turns around to find SOMEONE snuggled up against him, watching him with a big creepy smile.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS97
He falls to the floor.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS98
At a TV taping.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS99
Spinning the big wheel, SOMEONE knocks herself unconscious.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS100
In a truck, overfilled with prizes.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS101
At home, SOMEONE watches Scarface on his computer.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS102
He looks outside to find SOMEONE riding her newly won jet ski in the backyard swimming pool.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS103
She submerges then shoots 20 feet out of the water and crashes down on the patio table.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS104
With a grin plastered on his face, SOMEONE turns back to his movie.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS105
Later, the family watches a movie together at a theater.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS106
SOMEONE and SOMEONE both stuff popcorn into their slack-jawed mouths.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS107
Sitting between them, SOMEONE notices their identical mannerisms.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS108
The twins each clear their throats.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS109
They pry straight popcorn kernels out of their mouths, then eat them.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS111
Watching the movie, the twins crack up.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS112
SOMEONE self-consciously stops laughing and glances over at his sister.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS113
He sets aside his popcorn to change his posture from matching hers.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS114
He gruffly folds his arms.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS115
SOMEONE looks over at him and gives a friendly wave.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS116
They both rest their cheeks against theirs fists and scratch their groins.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS117
Then look around furtively.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS118
In unison, they both casually wave the smell away from themselves.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS119
SOMEONE digs her phone out of her bra.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS120
She tearfully grabs her purse and gets up.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS121
The rest of the family follows her off.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS122
He deliberately spills his popcorn on the smart aleck.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS124
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie asleep.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS125
They wake up.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS126
SOMEONE goes to the window and sees SOMEONE on a riding lawn mower.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS127
The cut grass blows at SOMEONE as he chases her.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS128
At breakfast.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS129
SOMEONE overhears.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS131
She grooves.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS132
She touches the screen.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS133
SOMEONE clicks the mouse.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS134
SOMEONE points to SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS135
She laughs to the kids.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS136
The photo shows SOMEONE about the chow down on a greasy sandwich.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS137
Now, an ad shows Shaquille O'Neal wearing a long gray wig.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS138
He flaunts championship rings.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS139
He gnaws on the packaged SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS140
Shaq cuddles with the SOMEONE then licks it.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS141
SOMEONE sheepishly excuses himself.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS142
That evening, SOMEONE arrives home in his silver Cadillac Escalade.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS143
He peeks in the guest room.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS144
Her mascara smeared, SOMEONE lies asleep cuddling Poopsie among a pile of used tissues covering the bed.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS145
The kids approached SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS146
He takes another look at his sister who sleeps soundly atop the covers, fully clothed.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS147
Later, SOMEONE works at his Sony VAIO computer.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS148
He types a few keystrokes.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS150
SOMEONE climbs off her sweat-stained bed.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS151
SOMEONE gets out of the shower and finds his sister sitting on the toilet.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS152
She massages SOMEONE with a choke cold.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS153
SOMEONE knocks herself out on the Prize is Right.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS154
SOMEONE stands behind him.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS155
The boy runs off with Poopsie taped to his back.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS157
SOMEONE does a Raise the Roof dance.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS158
SOMEONE finds his son staring at him.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS160
SOMEONE opens the door to a dower, clean cut man.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS161
SOMEONE grabs him.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS162
SOMEONE comes downstairs in slow motion.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS163
Wearing a shimmery teal outfit.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS164
With a fuzzy shawl and cap, and a ruffled skirt.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS165
A slack-jawed SOMEONE shakes his head admiringly. His sister beams.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS166
SOMEONE holds a doll that looks exactly like SOMEONE dressed in a matching outfit.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS167
A horrified SOMEONE grimaces painfully at his date.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS168
Later at a restaurant.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS169
She flaps her jaw.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS170
SOMEONE scoots out of their booth.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS171
Awhile later, SOMEONE sits alone in front of two uneaten salads on the table.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS172
She idly drums her hands.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS173
Now in the men's room.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS174
SOMEONE peeks in.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS175
She tentatively steps inside.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS176
She moves toward a closed stall.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS177
Opening the door, she finds it empty.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS178
She frowns to herself.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS179
Fighting back tears.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS180
She leaves.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS181
On the ceiling above the toilet stall, SOMEONE clings hand and foot to a lighting fixture.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS182
At home, the kids play air hockey.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS183
SOMEONE returns.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS184
She runs up to her room.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS185
Now, SOMEONE and the kids enter the guestroom.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS186
Now at the Staples Center, the Lakers and the Kings warm up.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS187
Walking courtside with her brother, SOMEONE holds a giant stick of cotton candy.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS188
She stops and stares at two players.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS189
Across the court, he taps on SOMEONE's shoulder.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS190
SOMEONE sits down beside SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS191
A jumbo screen on the digital scoreboard shows a celebrity cam image of the two stars.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS192
Johnny Depp waves at the crowd.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS193
Poorly disguised in his fake beard and a Lakers hat.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS194
SOMEONE keeps his gaze downward.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS195
The camera zooms in on his face, and his name flashes below it.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS196
Ignoring him, SOMEONE takes a long sip of his drink through a straw.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS197
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch the game.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS198
Kobe Bryant dunks the ball.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS199
As everyone around her jumps up and cheers, SOMEONE gives an unimpressed look.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS200
She notices SOMEONE watching her from across the court and furrows her brow in a quizzical expression.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS201
The older man lowers his fake beard and gives her a smile.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS202
A vendor leans toward SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS203
He serves her a hotdog.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS204
Mustard spells out call me.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS205
A phone number is written in ketchup.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS206
Later on the drive home.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS207
SOMEONE swerves in shock.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS208
His SUV hits a postal box and does a 360.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS210
She puts on granny panties under her robe.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS211
She pulls a hunk of wax from her ear.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS212
Later, SOMEONE and his family arrive at Morton's Steakhouse.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS214
She gestures to two attractive blondes standing with Jared. Later still.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS215
She spots SOMEONE eavesdropping.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS216
He hurries off with an embarrassed look.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS217
SOMEONE walks past SOMEONE Irvin and finds his assistant.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS218
SOMEONE McEnroe holds up a club.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS219
SOMEONE and SOMEONE egg them on.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS220
Everyone suddenly acts casual as SOMEONE presents a giant cake, ringed with candles.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS221
He bends over the cake and blows.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS222
SOMEONE halfheartedly helps him out.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS223
SOMEONE blows out the final candle.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS224
With an emotional nod, SOMEONE heads off.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS225
SOMEONE notes her crestfallen look.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS226
SOMEONE enters the coatroom.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS227
SOMEONE lounges in a chair.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS228
Later, SOMEONE rides in his car.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS229
He clicks a remote.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS230
Spotlights flash on a mansion.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS232
An award-winning baker stands before an array of fancy cakes.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS233
Later, SOMEONE puts on music.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS234
He takes out a four-foot stick.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS235
He tosses SOMEONE the ball.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS236
He holds SOMEONE from behind, guiding her stance.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS240
SOMEONE pitches.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS241
SOMEONE hits the ball and it shatters Pacino’s Academy Award.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS242
He walks his hands up the stick toward SOMEONE's.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS244
The next morning at SOMEONE's house, SOMEONE tinkers with an electrical box in the garden.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS245
He furrows his brows, stands up, and gazes toward the woods.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS246
He heads over.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS247
Poopsie flies off, waking SOMEONE on an inflatable mattress.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS248
SOMEONE holds the bird inside a hoagie roll.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS249
Now, a large crowd picnics in the park.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS250
SOMEONE brings SOMEONE to a table.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS251
They all gaze skyward.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS252
Now, he feeds SOMEONE different Mexican dishes.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS253
SOMEONE's crazy-eyed grandma watches.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS254
SOMEONE nudges a relative, who nudges her back.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS255
She shoulders him right off the bench.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS256
She forks up a chili pepper.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS257
His grandma double-fists chili peppers into her mouth.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS258
Playing soccer, SOMEONE tries to kick the ball but her foot misses and she falls onto her back.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS259
SOMEONE's grandma cackles, displaying her one tooth.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS260
Now, a crowd surrounds a break dancing boy.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS261
He does a head spin.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS262
With a bashful smile, SOMEONE walks onto the makeshift dance floor of flattened cardboard boxes.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS263
She does an awkward dance, patting her elbows then shimmies her ample bosom.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS264
Grandma watches her eyes wide and round behind her glasses.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS265
SOMEONE squats down and folds her arms in front of her.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS266
She does a Cossack dance, kicking out one foot at a time.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS267
Then leaps up from her squat and poses.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS268
The crowd cheers and an old man pinches her butt.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS269
SOMEONE's grandma sits forward and glares, baring her one tooth.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS270
Back in the soccer game.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS271
As she kicks, her shoe flies off. It hits SOMEONE's grandma, knocking her out.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS272
Her family feeds her peppers, rousing her.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS274
Blindfolded, SOMEONE takes the stick from SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS275
She swings at a pinata, but misses and smacks his grandma in the face.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS276
The family brings grandma some peppers.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS277
She eats two at a time.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS278
In the soccer game.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS279
SOMEONE now plays barefoot.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS280
She holds the ball between her feet and jumps. Lifting it over an opposing player.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS281
With the ball in midair, she swings her leg around and side volleys it into the net.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS282
Two relatives lift SOMEONE onto their shoulders, and she gives the crowd high fives.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS283
A guy peeks up her skirt, then turns to his friend.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS285
He hands over money.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS286
At SOMEONE's house.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS287
He uses the intercom.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS288
SOMEONE bursts in with a bouquet.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS289
He enters the guestroom.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS290
They find sweat stains on the bed.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS291
He fondles SOMEONE's stain.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS292
SOMEONE lowers himself on top of the Jill-shape stain.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS293
SOMEONE cringes.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS294
SOMEONE obeys.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS295
He soulfully rests his hand on SOMEONE's shoulder.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS296
SOMEONE drives SOMEONE home.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS297
They both glance at her stomach.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS298
SOMEONE barges through the front door.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS299
She hurries upstairs.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS300
SOMEONE eyes a spoonful of refried beans, then puts down her bowl.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS301
Later outside the bathroom.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS302
Fixing her belt, SOMEONE steps out of the bathroom.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS303
SOMEONE cringes.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS304
He looks around then opens a door for some air.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS305
He swings another door, fanning the air.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS306
He lights a candle and fans the air with his hand.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS307
In the doorway, the cheering kids hold their noses.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS308
The cockatoo holds his beak.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS309
Now, a massive cruise ship sails past the Coastal Resort.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS310
We drift over the luxurious vessel.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS311
Two men ascend a climbing wall.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS312
Another surfs a wave rider.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS313
Children ride a merry-go-round.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS314
Now, on deck.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS315
SOMEONE takes his feet off SOMEONE's desk.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS316
Hangs up and looks heavenward.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS317
Now at a dessert buffet, Poopsie bathes in a chocolate fountain.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS318
SOMEONE wears a lobster taped to his back. Now in the theater.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS319
SOMEONE looks over the audience.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS320
The light up display of SOMEONE's own Smartphone glows through his kingly robe.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS321
He takes the call.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS322
SOMEONE waves for the audience to wait.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS323
An audience member records him.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS324
SOMEONE cups the phone and returns it to his ear.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS325
SOMEONE's understudy steps out.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS326
The track star stands in a costume.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS327
A nervous SOMEONE hangs up.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS328
SOMEONE finishes up a text.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS329
Now onboard the ship.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS330
As two cruise employees turn a jump rope, SOMEONE, in the middle, stumbles.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS332
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE jump double Dutch, side by side, a crowd gathers.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS333
The twins kick their feet backward then point their fingers posing with every jump.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS334
They hold their arms out like mummies.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS335
In a series of intricate steps, they tap their ankles, turn around, then stop, posing shoulder to shoulder.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS336
Two girls playing miniature golf cheer along.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS337
SOMEONE and SOMEONE high five.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS338
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run over.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS339
Chugging SOMEONE's, Poopsie tips over. At night, in SOMEONE's closet, SOMEONE checks her dresses.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS340
He pulls a dress off its hanger then takes a pair of shoes, a purse, and jewelry.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS341
Poopsie watches from his cage.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS342
SOMEONE hurries out.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS343
Now he enters a public restroom and faces an attendant who bows politely.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS344
Crossing the room, SOMEONE looks again at the balding man twice.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS345
The valet bows in kind each time.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS346
SOMEONE enters the stall and the attendant turns to a counter of toiletries.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS347
In the stall, SOMEONE drops the bag on the toilet.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS348
He puts on lipstick and press on nails.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS349
He lathers his chest with shaving cream then shaves it. Rinses his razor in the toilet water and shaves his legs.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS350
He stuffs two melons in his bra. Then sprays himself with perfume.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS351
Padding his rear end with a life vest, he dawns the floral dress and a long wig.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS352
Now dressed as SOMEONE, SOMEONE exits the stall. Looks at himself in the mirror and notices the attendant waiting with the towel draped over his forearm.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS353
The balding man sternly gestures for SOMEONE to approach.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS354
SOMEONE opens his arms inquisitively.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS355
Then shuffles over.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS356
The attendant holds eye contact then grabs and shifts SOMEONE's melons.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS357
The old valet gives his own fingers a kiss of approval.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS358
SOMEONE smiles bashfully.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS359
Later, he climbs a staircase to the empty deck and looks around.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS360
As he paces, wind buffets his 60s style floral dress.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS361
A rope ladder hits him on the head.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS362
In a helicopter, SOMEONE points to a cheesecake in the shape of his own head.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS363
SOMEONE climbs onto the rope ladder.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS364
The copter carries him off.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS365
Later, we circle a medieval castle.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS366
Its exquisite stone dining room features a vaulted ceiling and candlelit chandeliers of iron.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS367
SOMEONE addresses a mustached servant, who struggles to understand him.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS368
The servant presents a liquor bottle.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS369
They do shots.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS370
As SOMEONE holds up his arms,
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS371
SOMEONE tickles away.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS372
SOMEONE squirms.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS373
He grabs a bowl from the table and shatters it.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS374
SOMEONE backs off and SOMEONE brightens.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS375
SOMEONE grabs the liquor bottle from the servant and chugs.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS376
Now in the gym, SOMEONE rides an exercise bike beside two body builders.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS377
She pumps major iron.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS378
The body builders watch SOMEONE easily curl what they struggled with.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS379
She works the heavier weight even faster.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS380
SOMEONE sets down the bar.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS381
One body builder strains to curl the heavy bar.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS382
Now, a record plays on a turntable.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS383
In the Spanish castle, SOMEONE swigs from the bottle as he dances with SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS384
The servant bops to the music.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS385
SOMEONE and SOMEONE bumped rears.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS386
SOMEONE calls from the ship.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS387
Crying, SOMEONE lowers her cellphone and hangs her head.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS388
The balding valet steps out from the restroom and spots her.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS389
SOMEONE notices him and straightens demurely.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS390
The attendant gestures for her to approach.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS391
And the manish woman points inquisitively to herself.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS392
The valet nods.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS393
And she ambles over.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS394
The balding man grabs and shifts her breasts.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS395
She glances at them, then eyes the valet.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS396
He grins.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS397
SOMEONE delivers a right hook that knocks him clear through a door onto the floor of the adjacent restroom.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS398
SOMEONE slaps him hard. SOMEONE staggers back from his chair.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS399
SOMEONE breaks a bottle.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS400
SOMEONE charges.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS401
SOMEONE sidesteps and breaks the chair over his back.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS402
Getting up, SOMEONE finds his melon boobs pushed at his shoulders.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS403
He furtively puts them back in place.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS404
The nearby butler nods.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS405
His brow furrowed, SOMEONE lowers his remorseful gaze.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS406
His chef accompanies him on the piano.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS407
SOMEONE makes a call.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS408
Back on the ship, SOMEONE uses his cell.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS409
Half in costume, he knocks on a door.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS410
His wife and kids come out of the next room.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS411
He eyes his dress.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS412
SOMEONE sad face becomes SOMEONE's.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS413
She wears a winter coat and hat, and carries a grocery bag crammed with junk food.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS414
In her leg warmers.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS415
She makes her way toward a modest house in a working class neighborhood.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS416
An aboveground pool stands among the shrubs, in the snowy yard.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS417
Now, a window edged with frost frames SOMEONE as she stands at a table inside, unpacking her groceries.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS418
Now, a car pulls up across the street from a neighborhood restaurant.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS419
A banner out front reads.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS420
New Year's Eve.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS421
At the wheel, SOMEONE wears a tiara and subtle make up.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS422
She demurely powders her nose.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS423
Then reaches in her bag and takes out
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS424
A framed photo of a silver-haired woman.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS425
She gets out of the car, hugging the photo close in one arm.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS426
Now, in a booth.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS427
A masculine blonde woman wearing a bouffant and a flashy navel revealing dress sits among other gaudy friends.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS428
SOMEONE emerges from the crowd and sits alone at a table by a pillar.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS429
SOMEONE sets out the photo.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS430
With the kids, SOMEONE gives a perplexed smile.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS431
The catty, man-faced blonde glares.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS432
Her date stares cross-eyed.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS433
They kiss.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS434
They hug.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS435
SOMEONE mouths thank you to SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS436
She nods.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS437
The catty blonde struts over and thumbs Erin’s shoulder.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS438
SOMEONE turns, her eyes wide.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS439
She grabs SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS440
SOMEONE holds SOMEONE in the headlock and flings her around.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS441
SOMEONE attacks SOMEONE, who releases SOMEONE.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS442
She flings SOMEONE into a wall.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS443
A spear pops a balloon and SOMEONE arrives as SOMEONE Quixote.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS444
SOMEONE's cross-eyed date stares.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS445
SOMEONE sneaks up with a bottle.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS446
Without turning, SOMEONE punches her out.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS447
SOMEONE spears the ceiling fan.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS448
SOMEONE and her family arrive at the house.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS449
SOMEONE and his kids finished shoveling the yard. Now green and done up in topiary hearts.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS450
She leaps into SOMEONE's arms and he falls back.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS451
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the kids rush over as SOMEONE's kids pile on to the new lovebirds.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS453
A commercial, SOMEONE struts into a Dunkin' Donuts.
JACK_AND_JILL_DVS454
The cut pauses on the TV in SOMEONE's office.