Moving to the door, she looks at the head coach and grins.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS32
She steps out to meet SOMEONE in the hall.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS33
The bitter assistant coach shares a warm hug with her player.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS34
Now as we rove over a river toward a city, words appear.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS35
Arlington, Virginia a few days later.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS36
At a softball practice.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS37
Teammates throw balls to SOMEONE who drops them in a bucket beside third base.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS38
A cellphone rings inside an open duffel bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS39
As SOMEONE looks over, a ball hits her in the face.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS40
Her mouth bloodied, she answers the phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS41
A woman in a skirt suit barges into SOMEONE's office with a letter.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS42
He accepts the letter.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS43
In the office, the boyish businessman opens his letter to find a subpoena for a wire fraud case which reads, United States of America v. SOMEONE Madison.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS44
Now SOMEONE eats with a friend.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS45
Now in a classroom.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS46
The professor steps out to find the businessman texting in the hallway.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS47
In her office.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS49
SOMEONE exits the club with a blond man who stops to sign autographs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS50
His date continues walking down the alley.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS51
She turns back.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS52
He points her around a corner, then runs after her grinning.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS53
SOMEONE rounds the corner, grabs Lisa, and lifts her off of her feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS54
He backs away from her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS55
She nods.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS56
The gray haired doorman glances at SOMEONE, then takes three steps back to patiently stand beside him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS57
SOMEONE glances at each of them, then throws up her arms and starts inside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS58
She punches his stomach.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS59
The next morning, in a well-furnished bedroom with an adjoining balcony, SOMEONE lies alone in bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS60
She sits up and peers across the room, then grabs her slip from a nightstand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS61
He sets two frothy, white blender drinks on a ledge, opens a window, and shakes his head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS62
He hops on the bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS63
He hands SOMEONE one of the drinks. She eyes its garnishment of fruit and a blue plastic star, then takes a sip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS64
She sets it down.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS65
She grabs her dress and steps out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS66
SOMEONE looks around the huge bathroom, which leads to a massive walk-in closet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS67
She opens the drawer and finds it filled with unopened toothbrushes of every color and pattern.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS68
SOMEONE enters.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS69
SOMEONE takes a brush, then puts her bright red dress on over her matching slip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS70
He opens a cabinet filled with women's pink sweat suits.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS71
Size stickers SOMEONE a stack of sweatshirts.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS72
She heads out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS73
He watches her head out the front door. She starts to pull it shut behind her, then stops and reenters the apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS74
She storms back down the hallway and returns to the bedroom where SOMEONE sits on his bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS75
He beams.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS76
With a smile, she leans in.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS77
Now SOMEONE strolls down a sidewalk in her rumpled red dress, passing another pedestrian.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS78
A breeze rustles the green leaves of a bush nearby.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS79
SOMEONE crosses a street, then reaches into her purse as she approaches the front door of a columned apartment building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS80
Later inside, she sits at a laptop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS81
A USA softball website reads, Announcement of 2011 Team USA.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS82
SOMEONE clicks on the link and a notice appears, Selection of next year's team delayed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS83
SOMEONE deflates, then leaves the laptop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS84
Now pedestrians walk past an office building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS85
Inside, SOMEONE finds a bespectacled man drying his hands in a men's room.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS86
He hands him the subpoena.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS87
The bespectacled man finishes drying a hand, then reads.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS88
The man's eyes widen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS89
He braces himself and takes a breath.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS90
In SOMEONE's office.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS91
A bespectacled man with thinning gray hair kisses him on the cheek.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS92
SOMEONE hands him the subpoena.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS93
The lawyer peers closely over his shoulder to read along.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS94
SOMEONE picks up his phone receiver and dials.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS95
A pregnant, auburn haired woman enters.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS97
SOMEONE furiously leaps up to punch him from behind, but SOMEONE stops her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS98
Ron sits with SOMEONE and dictates to her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS99
As SOMEONE exits the office, SOMEONE notes his dejected expression. Outside, SOMEONE crosses the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS100
He stops and presses a hand to his forehead.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS102
Glancing out a window, Ron spots SOMEONE sulking across the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS103
Rising from the table, he faces the window and takes out his cell. He makes a call.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS104
Outside, SOMEONE fishes his phone from his pocket and answers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS105
SOMEONE stares up at the fourth floor office window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS106
Ron hangs up, leaving SOMEONE staring up at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS107
Later in an apartment, SOMEONE makes a call.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS108
His girlfriend eyes him from behind a desk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS109
He hangs up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS111
She rises. She moves to SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS112
She moves to SOMEONE and squats in front of him, resting her hands on his knees.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS113
She briefly rubs his legs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS114
Gaping, SOMEONE leaves.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS115
Later, he grills a steak on a patio balcony, his tie discarded and his shirt untucked.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS116
He sprinkles seasoning on the meat, his hand jerking the container more and more aggressively as he loses composure.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS117
Stabbing a fork into the steak, he flips it repeatedly, then suddenly hurls it off the balcony.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS118
Now inside, he pours vodka into a shot glass and eyeballs it.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS119
He pours half of the glass back into the bottle, then empties the remainder into a cocktail shaker.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS120
He adds a spoonful of horseradish, some Worcestershire sauce and tomato juice, then shakes it all up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS121
With a celery stalk, he stirs his glass of Bloody Mary, then takes a sip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS122
Later, SOMEONE fills his empty glass with more Bloody SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS123
The image dissolves to him clumsily refilling the glass with straight vodka.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS124
Now he points a remote control.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS125
He sings into a lamp like a microphone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS126
He grabs another drink.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS127
Now in the bathroom, SOMEONE urinates. He grabs his phone with his free hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS128
SOMEONE muffles his phone inside a towel.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS129
Holding it away from the toilet, he flushes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS130
He rinses his hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS131
She lifts her shirt and pats her enormous belly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS132
Heading down a staircase, SOMEONE trips and slides to the bottom on his back.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS133
With a grin, he rises, unharmed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS134
Hanging her head, SOMEONE squeezes her eyes shut.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS135
They tear up as she opens them.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS136
With a furrowed brow, SOMEONE hangs up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS137
He briefly presses his fingers to his forehead, then leans back in his chair.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS138
Rising, he straightens his T-shirt as he trudges out of his living room.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS139
He pauses, opens his phone, and makes a call.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS140
Meanwhile, SOMEONE rides on a bus.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS141
She pulls her phone from her bag and answers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS142
SOMEONE frowns uncertainly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS143
SOMEONE leans on a wall and slips.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS144
He lowers his phone and folds it shut.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS145
The next morning, two women stroll across the street in front of SOMEONE's apartment building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS146
Inside, she lies asleep in bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS147
She bolts awake and glances around.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS148
As she throws back her covers, her legs get tangled in the sheets and she wrestles them off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS149
She strides to a table and grabs her phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS150
Its display reads, Missed call Coach SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS151
Frowning, SOMEONE runs a hand through her mussed hair.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS152
She turns to her computer, which displays the softball team website, and clicks on the link for the announcement of the 2011 team.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS153
A window appears.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS154
Click to see next year's lineup.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS155
SOMEONE shifts her gaze to her phone, then picks it up and reads a text message from Riva, I'm coming over.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS156
Setting the phone back down, she sits at her laptop and types frantically.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS157
She scrolls through the team lineup, but doesn't find her name.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS158
A blue asterisk blinks on the roster, indicating a new player.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS159
The position reads, Cam Austin, second base.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS160
SOMEONE drops her head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS161
Pressing her lips together, she closes her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS162
She lifts her gaze back to the laptop and stares at it.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS163
Her chest heaving then closes her eyes again.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS164
She reopens them and stares at the blue asterisk, blinking beside her replacement's name.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS167
Now in her bathroom. SOMEONE grabs her electric toothbrush. The mirror is covered in inspirational quotes written on sticky notes, including, Obstacles are what you see when you lose sight of your goal.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS168
Blinking rapidly, SOMEONE starts to brush her teeth.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS169
As her gaze scans the brightly colored notes, she stops brushing and closes her lips around her toothbrush.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS170
With sad eyes, she resumes brushing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS171
She closes her eyes and tears slide down her cheeks.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS172
As her face crumples, she lowers her toothbrush from her mouth.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS173
Her hand dropping heavily on the counter.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS174
Her mouth trembles.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS175
A froth of toothpaste clinging to her lower lip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS176
She reads two quotes; Courage is mastery of fear, not absence of fear.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS177
Don't judge anybody before you check yourself out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS178
You're lucky when it's your fault, because you can correct the situation.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS180
Her expression hardens.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS181
She leans over the sink. Eyeing her reflection, she wipes her mouth, then heads off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS182
Now SOMEONE leaves his building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS183
SOMEONE sprints away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS184
In his suit and dress shoes. SOMEONE blinks and stares.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS185
Now SOMEONE dons a skirt as her teammates visit.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS186
She heads for the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS187
Now SOMEONE marches down a city street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS188
Pausing at a corner, she wipes a tear, ruefully checks her fingers for runny makeup and rolls her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS189
Now at an elegant restaurant, she approaches a well-dressed Maître d'.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS190
The Maître d' leads her onto a balcony and gestures down toward a solitary figure at a table.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS191
SOMEONE sits slumped, his head in his hands.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS192
The grinning Maître d' leads on.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS193
He obligingly excuses himself.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS194
Heading along the balcony, SOMEONE regards her date uncertainly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS195
Now she arrives at his table.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS196
He looks up pitiably.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS197
He springs to his feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS198
SOMEONE slips into the high-backed booth.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS199
SOMEONE shrugs her brow and frowns.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS200
SOMEONE's eyes narrow.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS201
SOMEONE picks up her menu and SOMEONE nods.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS202
SOMEONE rolls her eyes, then studies her menu.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS203
SOMEONE stares helplessly at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS204
Smiling, SOMEONE stares at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS205
His eyes twinkle and he gives a stunned shake of the head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS206
He amiably shuts his mouth and faces his menu.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS207
SOMEONE fidgets her fingers, allows a small half-smile, and nods.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS208
Later, they dine on spaghetti and meatballs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS209
SOMEONE cuts a chunk of tomato and eats it.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS210
SOMEONE sneaks glances at her as he chews.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS211
His date shifts her worried gaze, occasionally eyeing him impassively.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS212
Her features contorting in a pensive frown.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS213
SOMEONE stops eating and leans back in her seat.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS214
Her lips part and her stubborn chin juts forward.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS215
SOMEONE studies her intently.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS216
His brow lifts and he stops chewing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS217
Catching him staring, SOMEONE gives a nervous half-smile and looks down.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS219
SOMEONE's lips curl into a dreamy-eyed smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS221
He opens the restaurant door for SOMEONE and follows her out with a goofy grin.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS222
He shrugs and beams at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS223
SOMEONE creases her lips, sizing him up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS224
SOMEONE watches her go with his boyish grin.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS225
Now SOMEONE uses his cellphone as he leaves his building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS226
In a bar, SOMEONE talks on the phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS227
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE, the doorman.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS228
The doorman chuckles, points, and steps away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS229
Now SOMEONE plods up a flight of stairs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS230
Entering her apartment, she finds a bouquet of flowers with an attached construction paper card, reading, We love you, Smalls. Dozens of other notes surround the gift, and SOMEONE sits behind the display.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS231
Now in SOMEONE's apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS232
He crosses to the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS233
SOMEONE sulks into the living room. She halts abruptly and looks around.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS234
He leads her to a couch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS235
As she sits, he lies down and puts his head in her lap.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS236
SOMEONE squirms an arm out from under his shoulder and sets her bag on the floor.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS237
Daytime. SOMEONE ushers SOMEONE through a dignified office building's thriving lobby.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS238
Reaching a reception desk, they peer at a vast wall mounted directory.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS239
SOMEONE brushes off his son's suit jacket as he guides him along.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS240
Now they sit side-by-side on a waiting room couch, both resting their hands on their parted knees and drumming their fingers. Later, SOMEONE faces a bearded man.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS241
SOMEONE's head droops forward and he bites his upper lip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS242
Now SOMEONE arrives in a tasteful office where a man with a closely trimmed beard waits at a desk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS243
He gestures to a SOMEONE to sit on chair or ottoman.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS245
SOMEONE perches on the ottoman.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS246
As he takes a seat facing her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS247
The kind-faced man crosses his legs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS248
The psychiatrist patiently lifts his chin.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS249
Narrowing her eyes, SOMEONE gives an appreciative nod and starts to leave.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS250
She halts in the doorway and turns around.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS251
SOMEONE leaves then reappears in his doorway.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS253
As rain pours, party guests in summery clothes crowd a home.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS254
SOMEONE gets food at a buffet while SOMEONE waits on a covered terrace.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS255
Seeing her through a window he notices her watching the man beside him fondling a woman's breast.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS256
SOMEONE pulls the man's hand down and directs their attention to SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS257
The woman scowls and puts her date's hand back on her breast.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS258
SOMEONE brings SOMEONE food.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS259
SOMEONE glances toward the partiers inside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS260
SOMEONE shifts in his seat and gives a sheepishly obliging shrug.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS261
SOMEONE gives a meek, pleased smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS262
Now a bird's eye view shows an umbrella only half sheltering SOMEONE's plate of BBQ.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS263
He and SOMEONE share the umbrella.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS264
SOMEONE sadly throws the plate in a trash bin.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS265
Later at his place.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS266
He grins and SOMEONE gives him an irritated look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS267
Standing behind her he wraps his arms around her waist.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS268
SOMEONE nods.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS269
He pours Cheerios.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS270
He adds Life cereal to their bowls
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS271
SOMEONE gives him a nod. SOMEONE pours blueberries over their cereal.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS272
SOMEONE gives her a bowl.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS273
With a mouthful of cereal, SOMEONE shifts her thoughtful eyes. She gives SOMEONE an expectant look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS274
SOMEONE shakes his head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS275
He slaps her shoulder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS276
As he starts to eat his cereal, SOMEONE gives him an appreciative look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS277
SOMEONE stops eating and looks over with wide eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS278
He gives a disturbed look and she playfully punches his arm.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS279
Now our view tilts up from the lobby doors past the engraved entablature just below the second story.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS280
Bowlen building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS281
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie with their heads at the foot of his bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS282
SOMEONE claps and the lights turn on.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS283
She points at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS284
As he leans over her, she punches his shoulder twice. The lights turn off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS285
On another day, SOMEONE sits on the bench in the National's bullpen smiling to himself.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS286
He stares off dreamily.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS287
He blinks himself out of his reverie.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS288
An opposing player rounds third toward home plate.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS289
A National's outfielder makes an amazing catch, right over the wall of the bullpen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS290
His teammates swivel their heads toward him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS291
Shrugging his hands a ball player rises.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS292
Starting his warm-up he catches a ball.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS293
SOMEONE catches the ball again, then leans toward him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS294
SOMEONE's shoulders heave.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS295
Later in the National's training room, SOMEONE holds his phone to his ear as he runs in a pool treadmill.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS296
In her apartment, SOMEONE removes the bag from the trashcan.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS297
She lets the can fall as she goes to the phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS298
SOMEONE's jaw drops.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS299
Hanging up, SOMEONE glances around, then returns her attention to the trash bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS300
Grinning she flips open her phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS301
A trainer brings him ice.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS302
SOMEONE's mouth lifts into a crooked SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS303
SOMEONE shifts her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS304
With a thoughtful look, SOMEONE hangs up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS305
Now she packs a duffel bag in her room.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS306
SOMEONE shakes her head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS307
The assistant coach rises from the arm of a sofa and hugs her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS308
SOMEONE answers his front door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS309
She indicates a large stack of bags and suitcases.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS310
In his closet, SOMEONE opens a drawer that's only one third empty.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS311
She nods and they share a smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS312
Glancing back at the drawer she shrugs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS313
Now at an apartment above a bakery.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS314
SOMEONE rises from a desk at a bay window. Boxes and other packed items line his small living room and hallway.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS315
He opens the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS316
SOMEONE carries in a grocery bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS317
SOMEONE loads the fridge.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS318
SOMEONE waddles to an armchair and sinks down in it.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS319
She stands.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS320
Standing in front of him, SOMEONE bites her lip and eyes him skeptically.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS321
She takes a few steps away and gives him a sidelong look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS322
With her thoughtful gaze still locked on his face
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS323
she cocks her heads and studies him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS324
She sets her hands on her hips.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS325
She juts out her jaw, then curls her lips together.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS326
SOMEONE stands ready to exit his apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS327
She heads to the kitchen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS329
SOMEONE approaches the Bowlen Building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS330
Meanwhile, SOMEONE makes a call from the desk in his study.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS331
SOMEONE stops in the lobby.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS332
SOMEONE closes his eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS333
He shuts his phone then letting his upper body go limp, slams his head onto a decorative table and holds it there.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS334
The doorman and a concierge stare at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS335
Now SOMEONE trudges into an elevator.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS336
As he rubs his forehead SOMEONE rushes through the open doors.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS337
With a bag of groceries slung over her shoulder, she stands beside him as he rubs his face.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS338
His hand descends to his mouth, pulling down his lower lip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS339
SOMEONE glances over.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS340
He looks at her, then quickly releases his lip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS341
Later, SOMEONE follows SOMEONE into SOMEONE's apartment, carrying the bag of groceries.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS342
She takes it into the kitchen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS343
SOMEONE looks around.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS344
He hurries over.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS345
Entering, SOMEONE frowns at seeing SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS346
SOMEONE gives a comprehending nod, then smiles at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS347
SOMEONE wears a disgruntled look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS348
Smiling tightly, she jerks her to the side, then moves off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS349
SOMEONE follows with a long sigh.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS350
SOMEONE peers after them as they enter another room.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS351
SOMEONE stares with disbelieving eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS352
She blinks up at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS353
Following her into the hall, he glances at George, who looks away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS354
Now SOMEONE packs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS355
SOMEONE opens the front door and SOMEONE stalks to the elevator with her bags and suitcases in tow.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS356
She steps inside and hits a button. As the doors slide shut, SOMEONE shakes his head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS357
He pats SOMEONE's shoulder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS358
Now SOMEONE races down the stairwell, jumping onto each landing as he rounds the next flight.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS359
In the lobby, the doorman rushes to keep ahead of SOMEONE and opens the door for her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS360
She marches outside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS361
SOMEONE dashes out the main door. Spotting SOMEONE he skids to a stop and puts on a casual expression. He pretends to gaze down the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS362
He grins.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS363
He takes a bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS364
He tips the doorman.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS365
He and SOMEONE start off down the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS367
As they head to a bus stop, the doorman answers an intercom phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS368
He sets down the phone receiver and jogs toward George, who waits behind SOMEONE a short distance away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS369
As the doorman opens his mouth to call him
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS370
he notices SOMEONE shaking his head giddily then looking skyward with a grateful smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS371
Grinning sympathetically, SOMEONE returns to the intercom.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS372
He watches as SOMEONE follows SOMEONE on to a bus, hauling up her roller bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS373
Later at his downsized apartment, SOMEONE helps SOMEONE carry in her luggage. She sets down her bags, then takes out her cellphone and charger.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS374
She notes SOMEONE's boxes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS375
His fridge is packed with food from SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS376
He checks his cell and ignores a call from dad.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS377
He enters the kitchen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS378
She opens his fridge, finding the vast array of neatly labeled homemade items.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS379
As SOMEONE sets his jacket down she joins him at the counter and grabs a fork.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS380
SOMEONE leaves the galley kitchen and unplugs her cellphone from its charger. She steps aside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS381
He peeks at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS382
Rolling up his sleeves, he smirks. She faces him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS383
She tosses down her phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS384
SOMEONE considers the idea.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS385
She frowns.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS386
He crosses to the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS387
SOMEONE deflates.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS388
Left alone in the cluttered second floor apartment she glances around and wanders over to a bay window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS389
Peering outside she spots SOMEONE who holds up a six-pack of Guinness on his way back across the
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS390
He runs in front of an oncoming car.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS391
He barely avoids getting hit.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS392
SOMEONE shakes her head and leaves the window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS393
Now on the phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS394
SOMEONE slides open his cellphone and aims it at his sad face.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS395
He checks the pic, then sets up a second shot.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS396
He tilts his head and milks the pout a little more.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS397
Now SOMEONE adds three dashes of bitters to highball glass, drops in a single sugar cube and measures some Maker's SOMEONE in a metal shot cup.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS398
In the living room, SOMEONE grabs her near-empty glass of Guinness and takes a sip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS399
SOMEONE squints as he stirs his creation, then smiles.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS400
He shakes the drink.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS401
SOMEONE hears him singing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS402
She turns to eye him and he stares back, then enters the living room with two cocktails.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS403
SOMEONE downs the last of her Guinness.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS404
She accepts the cloudy, peach tinted beverage.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS405
SOMEONE sits across from her on the floor.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS406
He raises his glass.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS407
He taps her, then taps her again.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS408
She sets her drink aside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS409
He stands. SOMEONE straightens her posture.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS411
She sits up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS412
SOMEONE sits beside her on the couch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS413
She squints distantly then gestures with her sleeve-covered hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS414
SOMEONE lowers her tearful gaze, then notes SOMEONE beside her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS415
She self-consciously stands up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS416
She tugs the hem of her shirt and rubs her nose.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS417
SOMEONE watches her pace across the room and take a seat on a cushioned chair.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS418
SOMEONE glances at her host.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS419
SOMEONE brightens.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS420
Laughing uncontrollably, SOMEONE hunches forward.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS421
She leaves her seat and crosses to her phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS422
SOMEONE nods softly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS423
She unplugs her cellphone and
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS424
flips it open to check the caller ID.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS425
He finds a scrap of paper.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS426
His note reads, I went nuts when you left, I broke a lamp.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS427
A shade and exposed light bulb dangle crookedly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS428
With his back to her, SOMEONE purses his lips and sighs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS429
He regards her affably.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS430
She eyes him awkwardly as he stands.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS431
Later on the street. SOMEONE raises his arm for a taxi.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS432
He smiles warmly, then resumes trying for a cab.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS433
Unseen by her, SOMEONE makes a fist and grimaces.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS434
He lowers his arm, then turns and faces SOMEONE squarely.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS435
A taxi stops.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS436
SOMEONE smiles, meeting his eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS437
They share a pleasant nod.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS438
SOMEONE taps on the rear of the parked taxi.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS439
He opens the trunk, then helps SOMEONE load in her luggage.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS440
He stows the largest first, then she helps with the two smaller bags.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS441
He smiles and shuts the trunk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS442
He nods and follows her to the passenger door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS443
SOMEONE smiles softly, with a touch of sadness, then gets in the cab.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS444
SOMEONE shuts the door, then impulsively leans close to her open window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS445
They share a warm smile, then he leaves the window and the cab drives away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS446
SOMEONE watches her go, tightens his lips, then plods back toward his apartment across the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS448
Pedestrians enjoy a sunny day by a lofty stone fountain.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS449
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on a bench.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS450
SOMEONE glances at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS451
He buries his face in his hand and she wraps her arm around him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS452
Nighttime at the Bowlen Building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS453
Now SOMEONE stands tensely in an elevator.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS454
Now with his father.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS455
SOMEONE sits on a velvet couch facing his father.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS456
It's SOMEONE plainly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS457
SOMEONE paces.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS458
Arms akimbo the bespectacled older man glances at his son and nods.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS459
He shuffles back to his chair and retakes his seat.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS460
SOMEONE gesticulates.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS461
A devastated SOMEONE covers his moth.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS462
SOMEONE gawks at his dad.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS463
Stands over SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS464
In SOMEONE's apartment
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS465
sitting alone he text messages.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS466
She enters the room to find him texting.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS467
He sheepishly pockets his cell.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS468
He kisses her cheek.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS469
He picks up his bags.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS470
Leads SOMEONE to the couch and sits on the coffee table.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS471
SOMEONE gets up.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS472
Barefoot she marches to the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS473
She crosses the outer hall.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS474
She presses the elevator button.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS475
She grabs his bags.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS476
She puts them on the elevator.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS477
SOMEONE notes her flushed complexion.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS478
He kisses her cheek.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS479
She walks away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS480
The elevator door shut.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS481
SOMEONE shuts the apartment doors, then turns and rubs her face.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS482
Back with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS483
SOMEONE sits on the couch between SOMEONE and a pillow decorated with a sand crab.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS484
SOMEONE gives a sympathetic pout then screws up his mouth.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS485
He rubs his father’s shoulder,
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS486
startling him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS487
He eyes SOMEONE's hand on his shoulder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS488
SOMEONE looks away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS489
His lips press tightly together, SOMEONE looks up sheepishly at his glaring son.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS490
Taking a breath he draws himself up and rubs his legs.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS491
SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS492
His gaze hardening, he purses his lips.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS493
SOMEONE gives a small, remorseful shrug.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS494
His son shifts on his feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS495
He rubs his face with both hands.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS496
SOMEONE hurries out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS497
Now at a softball game.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS498
SOMEONE applauds from the sidelines.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS499
Fans behind her hold homemade signs and wear American flag patterned clothing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS500
On the field, her former coaches and teammates congratulate each other.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS501
SOMEONE's smile fades.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS502
The American players line up facing their opponents from Australia and they exchange sporting high fives.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS503
SOMEONE's brow knits and her chest heaves.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS504
She walks away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS505
Later, she rides a commuter train, woefully biting her thumbnail and fidgeting her fingers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS506
Now words type out on a computer screen.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS511
Facing his laptop SOMEONE pauses and reads his letter over.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS512
He picks up his cell phone from a stack of papers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS513
He eyes his cell.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS514
It's Lisa, down on the sidewalk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS515
She faces away from him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS516
He stares down at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS517
She turns, he ducks.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS518
Facing the street, SOMEONE pouts.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS519
SOMEONE yields a comforted nod.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS520
SOMEONE grins down at her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS521
Unnoticing, SOMEONE shifts on her feet nervously.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS522
Ending the call, SOMEONE smiles down at her again.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS523
He springs from his seat.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS524
Rushing around his living room, he gathers up laundry and stacks books on a coffee table.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS525
Downstairs SOMEONE paces before the Cafe/Bakery under his apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS526
Later she leans against a display window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS527
Stepping forward
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS528
she cranes her neck to look up at SOMEONE's window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS529
Now in his apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS530
The door opens to reveal a smiling SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS531
She turns away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS532
She pauses on the landing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS533
SOMEONE stares off with an embarrassed frown.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS534
She marches up, enters the apartment, and pauses to face SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS535
As he covers her mouse she cocks a fist.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS536
Releasing her he backs off, open hands raised.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS537
SOMEONE frowns, gives a small nod and turns away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS538
SOMEONE looks back and forth between her and his cell.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS539
As she sits he answers the phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS540
He glances at SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS541
SOMEONE faces Lisa, his green eyes sparkling.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS542
SOMEONE gets to her feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS543
Heading out she halts.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS544
Now an older couple coos over SOMEONE and a newborn in a blue cap and blanket.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS545
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive in the doorway.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS546
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE questioningly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS547
He kisses her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS548
His parents leave.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS549
As SOMEONE to SOMEONE's side, the new mom regards SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS550
SOMEONE ventures to the bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS551
SOMEONE points at the newborn.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS552
SOMEONE gawks enchanted.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS553
She answers a phone by her bed.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS554
The baby's cap slides off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS555
SOMEONE gently slips it back on.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS556
SOMEONE cues SOMEONE for a discreet exit.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS557
SOMEONE's gaze darkens as SOMEONE walks in with two presents.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS558
Behind him, a tall burly man walks in with flowers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS559
The newcomer hands the flowers to SOMEONE. SOMEONE gives a relieved smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS560
He shakes SOMEONE's hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS561
SOMEONE shows the gifts.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS562
He offers a blue present, then sets the pink one down too.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS563
SOMEONE faces his son cautiously.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS564
He turns away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS565
Eating ice chips with a spoon, SOMEONE looks back and forth between the father and son.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS566
SOMEONE strolls over to SOMEONE and greets her with a smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS567
looks to SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS568
He faces George, who gives a smirk and broad shrug.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS569
He faces SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS570
He leaves with a tense smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS571
SOMEONE leans on her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS572
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a camcorder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS573
He pulls the chair up to SOMEONE and his brand new son.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS574
They share a tearful loving embrace, their newborn between them.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS575
SOMEONE smiles wistfully. SOMEONE beams holding the aimed camera.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS576
SOMEONE's smile vanishes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS577
SOMEONE sits.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS578
SOMEONE giddily bites her lip.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS579
Smiling SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE and finds him beaming tenderly at her, camcorder in hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS580
SOMEONE gives her fiancée an affectionate slug on the shoulder and they share a laugh.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS581
SOMEONE flashes a bashful smile, and shuts the camcorder's display window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS583
He and SOMEONE stroll outside through the hospital's revolving door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS584
They walk close together, their hands swinging gently at their sides.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS586
The twosome approaches a bus stop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS587
SOMEONE stands before SOMEONE as she sits on a bench.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS588
A wistful smile plays on her pixie-like features.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS589
He beams fondly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS590
A city bus turns into view and nears the stop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS591
SOMEONE gets to her feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS592
Shifts his desperate gaze as the bus doors open.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS593
SOMEONE steps on.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS594
SOMEONE storms off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS595
As he marches alongside the bus
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS596
SOMEONE watches him through a window.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS597
His arms give an angry flail.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS598
Wearing a confused frown SOMEONE blinks at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS599
As the bus pulls away she averts her thoughtful gaze.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS600
Her eyes widen and she pulls the stop cord.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS601
The bus lurches to a halt at the curb.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS602
SOMEONE hurries off and moves around the front of the bus.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS603
Spreading her arms in a bewildered shrug, she strides briskly toward her friend.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS604
Step face to face.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS605
Another bus arrives.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS606
SOMEONE's mirthful grin fades.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS607
SOMEONE faces the bus, and her wistful smile returns.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS608
She jerks her thumb at the hospital and shakes her head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS609
SOMEONE watches her climb aboard the bus.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS610
SOMEONE gives a small hopeful smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS611
Beaming tenderly, SOMEONE shakes his head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS612
SOMEONE faces the stout driver and sweeps her bus pass over a scanner.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS613
Now at home.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS614
SOMEONE eyes a list in two columns. The first headed, reasons against reads, I don't want to go to jail, I'm scared.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS615
The reason for column lists I don't want my father to spend the rest of his life in jail. He's scared.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS616
SOMEONE crumples the page and takes out his cell.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS617
He puts the phone to his ear and sits.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS618
In his study, SOMEONE pauses at some paperwork and answers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS619
He ends the call excitedly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS620
Back in her own apartment, SOMEONE munches a cracker as she lounges, facing her TV.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS626
In a well-tailored dark gray suit, SOMEONE arrives at his father's building. At the entrance, sexy model types in slinky clothes line up at a table.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS627
Later he arrives at a door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS628
A legal team files out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS629
SOMEONE leads his son into his study and sits behind his cluttered desk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS630
He gestures to a chair.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS631
SOMEONE totes a brown paper bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS632
SOMEONE averts his gaze, his lips creasing emotionally.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS633
SOMEONE stifles his jaw from dropping.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS634
Grinning SOMEONE hurries out.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS635
SOMEONE gives a half-hearted wave.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS636
On SOMEONE's vast penthouse patio, elegant place settings line tables.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS637
Two vendors wheeling bushels of live lobsters.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS638
SOMEONE and SOMEONE chat in the walk-in closet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS639
He pulls out a chair.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS640
He hands her a box.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS641
He bends slightly and bobs his shoulder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS642
He sits.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS643
He unwraps it for her and hands it back.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS645
Inside, SOMEONE finds a diamond encrusted wristwatch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS646
As SOMEONE beams, SOMEONE's lips stutter.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS647
She puts it on.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS648
SOMEONE's shoulder.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS649
He leaves the adjoining bathroom.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS650
In the hall they pass some guests.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS651
As a teammate leads SOMEONE away, SOMEONE snags SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS652
They walk out onto the vacant patio, and SOMEONE pulls out a chair for her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS653
He sits kitty corner from her and sets down the small paper bag.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS654
She uncurls the bag's crumpled top and reaches inside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS655
SOMEONE watches as she fishes out a present.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS656
Wrapped in polka dot paper, like a hard candy,
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS657
it bears a cheerful red ribbon tied on each end.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS658
SOMEONE gives him a smile, then carefully unties one of the bows.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS659
SOMEONE shifts his anxious eyes between her and the present.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS660
SOMEONE very patiently slides the ribbon off the end of the tube shaped gift.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS661
As she moves on to the other bow, she pauses.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS662
Her eyes flicker over SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS663
He lifts his brow.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS665
With a smile, he watches SOMEONE slide off the second bow.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS667
Unwrapping the gift, she finds a child's tub of Play-Doh.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS669
As she examines it, her diamond watch glitters on her wrist.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS670
He gives her a nod.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS671
He takes the Play-Doh from her and eyes it.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS672
He stares into her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS673
She holds his gaze for a moment, then looks down with a touched expression.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS675
A hint of tears glistens in her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS676
She returns her gaze to him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS677
SOMEONE nods, her eyes glistening.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS678
Her gaze remains locked on him
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS679
and he gives her a tender smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS680
She glances at the Play-Doh.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS681
SOMEONE nods, his eyes misty as well.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS682
She shakes her head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS683
She sets the Play-Doh back inside the paper bag and crumples down the top.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS684
Avoiding SOMEONE's gaze, she stands and he follows suit.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS685
She walks back into the apartment, leaving him staring after her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS686
Inside, SOMEONE strolls past three chatting women.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS687
She shows them.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS688
As the three women chat, SOMEONE lifts her gaze from the watch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS689
On the patio, SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand, then hurries along.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS691
He pulls SOMEONE aside.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS692
He winces. SOMEONE waves at him.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS693
He heads off.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS694
SOMEONE watches with a curious look as SOMEONE opens the door and turns to her again.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS695
He opens his mouth to speak.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS696
Brightly shrugs an arm and lets his fist open up in a self-deprecating flourish.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS697
He leaves.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS698
And SOMEONE's amused
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS699
smile fades.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS700
SOMEONE joins her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS701
They head away from their party guests.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS702
Outside by the bus stop a couple strolls by SOMEONE as he paces, his shoulders sagging.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS703
The headlights of passing cars cast their warm glow on the wet pavement.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS704
Inside the apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS705
SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter the vacant bedroom.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS706
SOMEONE closes the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS707
He watches as she removes the diamond watch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS708
SOMEONE shifts her eyes.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS709
She turns to the door.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS710
He nods, his eyes saddened.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS711
His lips fumble.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS712
SOMEONE rushes over and hugs him. He holds her tightly.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS713
His shoulders heave.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS715
SOMEONE touches her lips to his neck.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS717
SOMEONE continues to trudge back and forth by the bus stop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS719
On a balcony above, SOMEONE talks on a phone.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS720
He hangs up then pockets his cell.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS721
Looking down he sees his son on the sidewalk.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS722
The lofty view shows SOMEONE fold his arms, bow his head, and stamp his feet.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS723
With a concerned look, he thrusts his hand on the balcony railing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS724
A lawyer behind him checks his watch.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS725
Down below, SOMEONE exits the building.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS727
She stops just outside the door as she sees SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS728
He gives her a relieved grin. SOMEONE takes a few steps toward him then pauses.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS731
Shaking his head, SOMEONE shrugs his hands and smiles.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS733
SOMEONE quirks a smile and replies in kind.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS734
SOMEONE beams.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS735
As SOMEONE walks over
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS736
SOMEONE watches from the balcony.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS737
His lips spreading into a grin.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS739
His mouth suddenly drops into a knowing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS740
He heads back into his apartment.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS741
By the bus stop SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS742
As she starts for the bus stop, SOMEONE grabs her by the shoulders and presses his lips to hers. Her brow lifts as he kisses her.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS743
Then her shoulders relax and she wraps her arms around him, pulling him close.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS748
With her eyes closed, SOMEONE rests her face against his shoulder. SOMEONE leans his head against hers. His eyes close too.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS750
His smile fades and his eyes pop open.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS752
SOMEONE opens her eyes. She rolls them, then slides out of SOMEONE's embrace.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS753
She gives him an amused look.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS755
She holds his gaze for a moment, Then walks to the bus stop.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS756
SOMEONE smiles, then follows.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS757
He sits beside her on the bench inside the glass shelter.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS758
Facing her he squares his shoulders.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS759
He smiles.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS760
SOMEONE blinks, then looks away, her brow furrowing.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS761
As she returns her gaze to his,
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS762
the corner of her mouth lifts into an
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS763
astonished smile.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS764
She eyes him for a moment, then turns away.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS767
Reaching over, she places her hand on top of his hand.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS768
SOMEONE closes his fingers around hers.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS769
With a tender expression, SOMEONE watches as she shakes her head.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS772
She meets his gaze with a smile. SOMEONE grins.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS774
As they sit side by side holding hands,
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS775
he leans forward and looks up the street.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS776
He turns to SOMEONE and gives her a nod.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS777
Still holding her hand, he rises.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS778
The bus arrives, eclipsing them from view.
HOW_DO_YOU_KNOW_DVS779
The bus pulls away, leaving the bench inside the quaint shelter empty.