As he and his dark-haired colleague exit onto a college campus, a title appears.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS18
The Ides of March
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS19
A painted barn declares, "Ohio for Morris."
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS20
A roadside sign reads, "Pullman, America's Future Begins March 15."
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS21
Supporters wave homemade posters, including "Gimme More Morris" and "Don't Pull For Pullman."
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS22
A homeless man's sign states, "Will vote for food."
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS23
A headline reads, "Ohio Primary Too Close To Call". The young blonde woman deliver coffees.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS24
The dark-haired campaign staffer drinks a coffee as he watches the debate on TV. In the auditorium, SOMEONE, a handsome gray-haired man, shakes hands with his balding opponent.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS25
The two candidates wave at the audience.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS26
Standing in a wing, a bearded man with sagging features looks across the stage and forces a terse smile.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS27
In the opposite wing, a paunchy, fair-haired man returns the gesture.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS28
The clean cut man joins him.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS29
SOMEONE gives them an inquiring glance.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS30
The two campaign staffers head backstage where the bearded man pours himself coffee.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS31
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS32
Munching on a doughnut, he smirks as he heads off.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS33
Clenching his jaw, SOMEONE shakes his head then strides away, leaving SOMEONE alone with a tense look.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS34
Still onstage, SOMEONE and SOMEONE continue to wave at the audience.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS36
Now, a suited man with a trim mustache plays piano and sings at a bar.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS37
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit at a table with a dark-haired woman in glasses. She scrutinizes the fair-haired campaign manager.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS38
A guy brings drinks.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS39
SOMEONE's grin fades.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS40
He slaps the table.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS41
He leaves SOMEONE alone with SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS42
She gives SOMEONE a pitying look.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS43
Gazing back at her with confident eyes, he shakes his head.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS45
The singer croons into his microphone. Now holding a briefcase, SOMEONE exits the bar with SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS46
He lights a cigarette.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS47
The next day at SOMEONE's campaign headquarters,
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS48
SOMEONE shakes a box.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS49
Entering an office with tall windows that look out into the bullpen, SOMEONE sits at a desk.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS50
The young blonde woman walks in holding a folder.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS51
Barely looking at her, he opens the folder and starts reading.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS52
He returns the folder to her.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS53
She gives a mocking grin.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS54
He jots a note then looks at her.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS55
He smiles to himself as she leaves.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS56
He gives an embarrassed nod, then sits back in his chair and gazes after her.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS57
In a stately home,
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS58
SOMEONE leans closer to Senator SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS59
A woman in a gray blazer and ribbed sweater sets two glasses of whisky on a table between them.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS60
He keeps his sharp-eyed gaze locked on SOMEONE at SOMEONE's headquarters,
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS61
then holds out a laptop.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS62
As SOMEONE reads the documents, SOMEONE waits with a bemused smile.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS63
His lips screw to one side impatiently.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS64
Seated facing him, SOMEONE interlaces his hands on a conference table.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS65
The other staffers swap uneasy looks.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS66
SOMEONE brings SOMEONE a printout of the op-ed piece.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS67
As SOMEONE smirks, the governor cracks a smile.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS68
The young adviser flashes a cocky grin.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS69
SOMEONE goes to his office and picks up the phone.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS70
He shuts his door.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS71
Leaning against a reflective window, SOMEONE knits his brow and takes a breath.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS72
SOMEONE ends the call in his dimly lit office. On the other end, SOMEONE slowly twirls the phone in his hand as he hangs it up.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS73
Through the window, he gazes out at SOMEONE and his diligent campaign staff as he makes a call on his cell.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS74
He hangs up. Now, a neon sign reading "Head First" hangs in a window flanked by shutters painted with the words "Who Dey."
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS75
SOMEONE sits in his car, staring at the bar. Later inside,
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS76
SOMEONE regards SOMEONE with a cool, amused gaze.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS77
SOMEONE scrutinizes his rival's earnest face.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS78
His eyes gleaming in the dim light, SOMEONE abruptly gets to his feet and heads for the door.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS79
Now SOMEONE talks on his cell as he steps into the daylight.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS80
Silhouetted against the sunny day, he faces the bar's door frame and leans his head against it.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS81
Now in a hotel suite, a woman applies makeup to SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS82
In the next room, SOMEONE brings SOMEONE a file and sits by him.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS83
Now with SOMEONE SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS84
SOMEONE has drinks with SOMEONE in a bar.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS85
His brow raised, SOMEONE manages a nod.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS86
She gives him an alluring smirk. SOMEONE looks the young woman up and down.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS87
He stares at her rosy lips.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS88
She returns a cool, enticing smirk. SOMEONE's heavy-lidded eyes remain fixed on her face.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS89
He nods, suppressing a grin.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS90
SOMEONE rubs her lips together, then gives a wicked grin.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS91
Now, the bus sits haphazardly parked outside SOMEONE's hotel.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS92
SOMEONE leaves his bed.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS93
SOMEONE gets dressed as he talks.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS94
She fastens her jeans.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS95
She gives a cool shrug.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS96
She knots his tie.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS97
She kisses him and turns away. Now at an airport, SOMEONE uses his cell.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS98
Beneath an overcast sky, SOMEONE halts and turns on his heel.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS99
Ending the call, he crosses a tarmac to a private jet.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS100
Later in flight, he works beside SOMEONE who sits facing SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS101
Turbulence jostles the aircraft causing SOMEONE to look up from his work.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS102
He braces himself and shuts his eyes.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS103
With a wry smile, SOMEONE glances out his window.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS104
SOMEONE tenses as the plane jostles again.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS105
Delivering his speech, SOMEONE glances at a woman and child off stage.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS106
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stands silhouetted against an American flag.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS107
SOMEONE delivers his speech on the other side of the flag.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS108
SOMEONE bows his head and massages his brow.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS109
Backstage, SOMEONE shakes his head.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS110
SOMEONE strides away.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS111
Standing silhouetted against the backwards side of the American flag with his arms folded across his chest, SOMEONE hangs his head.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS112
Now SOMEONE climbs a set of stairs in the filled auditorium.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS113
She exits into a corridor where a bearded campaign staffer hands her some papers.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS114
Taking them, she skims the top page as she heads down the hallway past a "Morris for President" banner along the wall.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS115
She jogs up a stairwell to a pair of closed doors where SOMEONE and his Secret Service agents stand guard.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS116
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the papers.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS117
In the middle of an empty rehearsal room, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE sit with their chairs huddled together.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS118
As his campaign manager talks, the governor glances down and shoots a look at his young press secretary.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS119
SOMEONE nods, his arms folded.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS120
Pursing his lips into a resolute line, SOMEONE pats his own leg.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS122
SOMEONE talks on the phone.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS123
At night, the campaign bus drives down the highway. We follow it from an SUV.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS124
Resting her head on his shoulder, his wife smiles.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS125
SOMEONE lifts his eyes for a moment.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS126
She shakes her head.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS127
He kisses her forehead.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS128
Closing her eyes, she nuzzles into his shoulder.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS129
Setting his lips in a firm line, he glances at his wife.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS130
She lifts her face to meet his gaze.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS132
Now at a town hall meeting, SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a phone and returns to the meeting.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS133
Later that night, the campaign bus cruises down a highway.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS134
On board, SOMEONE squints at a laptop screen from behind a pair of glasses.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS135
An instant message from SOMEONE pops up.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS136
Do you need me to clean your room tonight? xoxo - The Cleaning Lady
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS137
A smile spreads across SOMEONE's face and he removes his glasses.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS138
Looking over his shoulder, he spots SOMEONE a few seats back.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS139
She meets his gaze with a mischievous smile, then lowers her head and shakes it coyly.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS140
Turning forward again, SOMEONE slides on his glasses and resumes working.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS141
Later at his hotel, pale light edges his bare back as he and SOMEONE have sex.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS142
SOMEONE glances at the town hall meeting on TV.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS143
SOMEONE kisses him.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS144
He buries his face against her neck. Later, she sleeps beside him as he sits in bed working on his laptop.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS145
His gaze sweeps over the covers.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS146
He wrungs his hands over the comforter, then searches inside its folds.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS147
Finding his cellphone, he answers.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS148
He pulls it away from his ear and frowns at it.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS149
With a puzzled look, he turns to a bedside table and spots his own phone sitting on top.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS150
He takes off his glasses and rubs his eyes, then wakes SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS151
He hits redial.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS152
With the cell to his ears, SOMEONE's playful expression fades as he listens.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS153
Noting his reaction, SOMEONE sucks in a quick breath then averts her ashamed gaze.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS154
SOMEONE lowers the phone and stares at it.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS155
Hanging up, he shifts his eyes to SOMEONE who continues to look down.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS156
She reluctantly meets his gaze, her eyes glistening with tears.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS157
SOMEONE stares at her with wide eyes.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS158
He lowers his gaze.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS159
SOMEONE shifts nervously as he paces in front of the bed.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS160
SOMEONE stares at her, his lips parted slightly in a stunned look.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS161
A tear slides down SOMEONE's face and she swallows hard.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS162
Turning away, he gives a tiny shake of his head.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS163
The next day, SOMEONE strides down a sidewalk with his hands in the pockets of his dark trench coat, and his jaw set tight in a resolute expression.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS164
Reaching campaign headquarters, he glances at an idealized poster of SOMEONE in a window, then swings open the door to the bullpen and steps inside.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS165
Sitting behind a desk near the front of the room, SOMEONE glances up at him.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS166
SOMEONE shoots her a brief look as he moves past the desks of the busy staffer.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS167
With his lips set in a troubled line, he enters his office, takes a seat at his desk, and stares out through the windows of the bustling bullpen.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS168
His gaze sweeps from some people examining writing on a whiteboard to the desks of other campaigners making phone calls and typing on laptops.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS169
He stares at the back of SOMEONE's head as she works.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS170
Pushing his chair away from his desk, he gets up and raps his knuckles on a side window which shows SOMEONE working next door.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS171
SOMEONE glances over. Moving from the window, SOMEONE slides off his coat and drops it in a chair.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS172
He rests a hand on the open door as SOMEONE enters. SOMEONE closes the door behind him, then sits on the edge of his desk and folds his arm.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS173
He opens the door for SOMEONE to exit.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS175
The staffers in the bullpen pause and look over. He heads back into his office.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS176
SOMEONE anxiously gets up from her work and follows him.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS177
As SOMEONE enters the office, he continues writing, then shoots the bullpen a cautious look as he hands her the slip of paper.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS179
On SOMEONE' campaign stationary, it reads, "Meet me in the stairwell at noon."
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS181
SOMEONE's shoulders rise with a relieved breath.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS182
She returns the note to him and he rips it up.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS183
He avoids her gaze. With a dejected nod, she leaves.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS184
Later, SOMEONE removes his wallet from his coat pocket as he approaches the entrance to the Stock Yards Bank and Trust.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS185
At a counter, he waits as a teller tallies a handful of bills and sets them in front of him.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS186
He tucks the cash in his wallet.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS187
Now, he takes a call as he exits the bank.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS188
SOMEONE stops in his tracks, his brow furrows.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS190
She strides off. Now, SOMEONE uses a payphone.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS191
A man photographs a woman nearby with his camera pointed in SOMEONE's direction.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS192
A news van sits parked at the curb.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS193
He hangs up and hurries out of Fountain Square.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS194
Now pale, hazy light hangs low behind the Cincinnati skyline.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS195
At SOMEONE's campaign headquarters, SOMEONE enters a dark stairwell and climbs up past the first landing.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS196
She stops halfway to the second one and looks around.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS197
SOMEONE emerges from the shadows.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS198
She continues up the stairs and joins him on the second landing.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS199
SOMEONE gives him a tearful, dejected look.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS200
Now, in SOMEONE's hotel room, SOMEONE gets a text from SOMEONE, "noon tomorrow.”
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS203
He eyes his cellphone. It reads SOMEONE calling.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS204
SOMEONE pockets the phone and tightens his jaw.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS206
SOMEONE waits in a car outside a motel with the campaign bus parked nearby. SOMEONE comes out. He watches her approach.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS207
His gaze softens as it returns to SOMEONE who carries a coat draped over her arm.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS208
She gets in beside him and they share a brief look. Now we peer up at the Roebling Suspension Bridge. SOMEONE drives SOMEONE across.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS209
Leaning back against her headrest, she swallows and lifts her chin, then briefly closes her dark-lashed eyes.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS210
She looks to SOMEONE with a vulnerable pout. He keeps his inscrutable gaze fixed on the road.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS211
SOMEONE turns away sadly and stares ahead.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS213
Later, the car turns onto a city street.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS214
As it pulls into a parking lot, it passes a sign reading, "Oakley Women's Clinic of Cincinnati.” Now SOMEONE fills out paperwork at a reception desk while SOMEONE waits beside her.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS215
She turns in the forms to a nurse who hands SOMEONE a pink printout.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS217
He folds it in half as the woman speaks to him. Nodding, he replies, "Okay."
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS219
He and SOMEONE sit down in the otherwise empty waiting room.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS220
Neither of them looks the other in the eye.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS221
As he faces SOMEONE, she returns a stunned expression. She looks away, her lips trembling.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS223
She glares at SOMEONE with tears in her eyes.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS224
He gets to his feet.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS225
He kisses her forehead, and goes.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS226
She tearfully works her jaw as she looks away. Now SOMEONE lies on his rumpled bed in his hotel suite, talking on his cellphone.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS227
He gets up.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS228
He answers the door.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS229
SOMEONE swigs from a bottle of water.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS230
Working on a laptop nearby, SOMEONE looks back and forth between them.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS231
SOMEONE reclines in his chair.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS232
His hands on his hips, he shuffles closer to the campaign manager.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS233
He sinks down in a chair, leans forward, and interlaces his hand.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS234
SOMEONE stares at him with a lifted brow.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS235
He averts his gaze and shuts his laptop.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS236
He takes it out of the room.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS237
SOMEONE's brow knits in a bewildered frown and he opens his hands.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS238
His arms folded, the campaign manager calmly regards him without a trace of remorse.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS239
SOMEONE lowers his mouth to his upraised hand and shakes his head. SOMEONE takes out his cigarettes.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS241
He gets to his feet and paces.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS242
His eyes wide, SOMEONE nods, then looks away.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS243
At the women's clinic, SOMEONE slumps back in a waiting room chair, her hands over her lower abdomen. A nurse hands her a prescription pill bottle.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS245
SOMEONE eyes the label and nods receptively as she listens. The nurse then hands her another bottle of pills.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS247
SOMEONE nods again with a grave frown.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS248
Her eyes drift back and forth from the nurse to the bottles in her slender, graceful hands.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS249
SOMEONE meets the woman's gaze with wide eyes and gives a final nod.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS250
As the nurse steps away, the young abortion patient briefly musters a smile for her. Now, SOMEONE loosens his tie and sighs tensely as he drives down a city street.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS252
At the clinic, a lamp softly illuminates the dusky waiting room as SOMEONE clutches her medicine in a bag between her knees. She shifts pensively in her chair.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS253
On the road, SOMEONE stares ahead with a sullen gaze.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS255
Outside the clinic, SOMEONE clutches her coat around her as she leaves on foot.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS256
She glances at traffic on the road beside her, and then approaches a cafe.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS257
Later, she sits inside in a booth by a window.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS258
As the sky grows darker outside, she peers out in the clinic's direction, then checks her watch.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS259
Lifting her gaze, she stares off grimly.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS260
As SOMEONE drives on, we glimpse the sunset outside.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS261
At night, he finally arrives outside the clinic.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS262
Finding it closed, he drives on.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS263
Outside her motel, SOMEONE exits a taxicab.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS264
She lets SOMEONE into her room.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS265
SOMEONE's eyes glisten.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS266
Her jaw drops open in a horrified expression.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS267
Leaning forward, she brings a hand to her mouth and shifts her hopeless, tearful gaze.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS268
Now SOMEONE marches purposefully down a sidewalk, his jaw set tight.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS269
He arrives at a storefront with a banner over the entrance reading, "Pullman for President", and goes in.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS270
He holds his wrathful gaze fixed straight ahead.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS271
At the far end of the campaign headquarters, SOMEONE meets with colleagues in a dimly lit office.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS272
He spots SOMEONE and gives a grim smirk.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS273
Later, they enter another small office together.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS274
SOMEONE glances back at the departing staffer, and then faces SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS275
SOMEONE steps in closer, his face half-obscured in shadow. He gives a nod.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS276
SOMEONE abruptly turns away and leaves the room.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS277
SOMEONE lingers, gazing after him with gleaming eyes.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS278
Now we view him from behind as he drives. With a slow, steady rhythm, his wiper sweep rain from his windshield as the city lights twinkle outside.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS279
Later at SOMEONE's motel, he exits the car.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS280
Indoors, we peer down through a narrow gap at a stairwell banister and glimpsed SOMEONE climbing up.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS281
Arriving in a hallway, he spots a man using a walkie-talkie as he hurries from a room.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS282
SOMEONE continues coolly down the hall.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS283
Arriving at the door to SOMEONE's room, he tenses as he finds it ajar.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS284
He gives it a knock, then pushes it open.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS285
A shadowy figure sits on the bed with his back to us.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS286
SOMEONE makes his way over with a furrowed brow.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS287
He halts and stares down with glistening eyes. Her face out of view behind the bed, SOMEONE lies motionless on the floor, her legs and left arm splayed awkwardly.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS288
Fighting tears, Stephens steps a little closer.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS289
Holding the room's phone to his ear, the man on the bed regards him sympathetically.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS290
SOMEONE sees the pill bottles on a bedside table.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS291
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE's cell peeking out from under her coat on the bed. With his back turned to him, the man on the bed sits in silhouette against the room's soft lamp light.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS293
Later, SOMEONE steps back out into the rainy night.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS294
Moving with a stiff gait, he marches across the parking lot to his car. As he gets in, rain patters heavily against his windshield.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS296
The wipers move in a slow rhythm against the downpour.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS297
The water cast modeled shadows against SOMEONE's face as he steers off forlornly.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS298
He sets SOMEONE's phone down, and takes out his own, and scrolls through the menu to check his messages.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS299
His eyes welled with tears.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS300
The next day at campaign headquarters, SOMEONE and the others watch a news report.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS301
Now, as a figure sits on a bench facing the Ohio River,
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS302
SOMEONE's lanky frame steps into view.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS303
He walks up to the bench and takes a seat.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS304
Both men stare out over the river's slate gray water towards Cincinnati on the other side.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS305
As traffic moves across the nearby Roebling Bridge, Senator SOMEONE narrows his eyes and wets his lips.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS306
SOMEONE regards him with a sober frown and nods.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS307
SOMEONE faces him with a furrowed brow and glances warily past his shoulder.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS308
The young man stares at the senator through narrowed eyes, his lips pressed tightly shut.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS309
SOMEONE reaches out hesitantly, then gives his leg a brisk pat and leaves.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS310
Now at a press conference, Paul, Ben, and the other staffers flank SOMEONE as he gives a statement.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS311
He looks to SOMEONE and moves up to the podium. SOMEONE steps aside and checks his cell.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS312
The phone display reads, "Molly calling.”
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS313
SOMEONE scans the room and his gaze falls on two police officers.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS314
Noting their casual expressions, he looks past them to other attendee.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS315
He finds SOMEONE holding SOMEONE's cellphone to his ear.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS316
A flashbulb pops on the governor's wide-eyed stare.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS317
SOMEONE lowers the phone with a cold expression.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS318
SOMEONE clenches his jaw.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS319
Nighttime. Seen from behind, SOMEONE leads us down a sidewalk, following the wall of a shadowy brick building.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS320
Two black SUVs wait outside the closed establishment.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS321
SOMEONE stops and peers in through a window with open blinds on the inside.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS322
He enters a front vestibule and steps into the dim establishment.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS323
As he peers across the room, all but the lower quadrant of his face remains cast in shadow.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS324
At the end of a long empty bar, a man stands in silhouette in the dark.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS325
SOMEONE crosses the darkened room, passing a dozen unoccupied barstools.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS326
He steps past the motionless Secret Service agent and heads through an illuminated doorway to a kitchen.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS327
He crosses a well-lit section on his way to another darkened area.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS328
Beyond stock shelves on a center counter, light shine under an industrial range hood.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS329
SOMEONE shifts his gaze.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS330
He ambles around the counter and finds the governor.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS331
SOMEONE turns away.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS332
He abruptly returns his gaze to the former staffer and the two maintain eye contact.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS333
Shadow conceals all but a lower quarter of the governor's face.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS334
SOMEONE draws a tense breath. SOMEONE remains still.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS335
SOMEONE steps from the shadows, his right eye becoming glaringly visible in the dim light.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS336
SOMEONE swallows his smirk. His expression hardens.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS337
SOMEONE remains poker-faced.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS338
SOMEONE maintains eye contact with SOMEONE who glowers and swallows.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS340
In a barbershop, a seated a bibbed SOMEONE gets a haircut by a barber standing behind him.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS341
Our view slowly roves around the side of the paunchy, middle-aged campaign manager
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS342
who gazes flatly from under his wrinkled brow.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS343
Later, SOMEONE steps outside wearing his thick-rimmed glasses.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS344
Beyond him, a black SUV idles just footsteps away.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS345
Poking out of a nearby alley, another sits parked by the curb.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS346
The campaign manager lights a cigarette then notices the SUV.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS347
Taking a few drags, he heads down the sidewalk and approaches the vehicle in the alleyway.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS348
A backseat window rolls down revealing SOMEONE inside.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS349
The tinted window rolls up and SOMEONE manages a final pull on his cigarette.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS350
He stubs it out on a wall and climbs into the SUV.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS351
A head-on view of the black car gradually drifts toward the grill.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS352
Its front tires rest in a buildup of icy gray slush on the alley apron.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS353
To the left, exhaust blooms from the tailpipe of the second SUV.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS354
The view keeps inching toward the nose of SOMEONE' vehicle until most of the second SUV falls out of view.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS355
The forward moving trip ceases halfway across the street.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS356
The backdoor opens.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS357
SOMEONE steps out and shuts it behind him.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS358
The SUV pulls out of the alley and drives off, followed by its twin.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS359
With his hands in his coat pockets, SOMEONE peers after them.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS360
He shifts his wry and resigned gaze.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS361
Now on a hotel room, SOMEONE watches TV while shaving.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS362
Now, a hearse and three black cars wait outside a cathedral.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS363
Inside, a dark wood coffin topped by an arrangement of white flowers lies at the front of a packed sanctuary.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS364
SOMEONE Stearns stands at a podium.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS365
The bereaved father swallows, then glances upward.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS366
Among the attendees, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE who sits across the aisle a few rows up.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS367
He returns his attention to the chairman who wipes his nose.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS368
The distraught father nods, then lowers his gaze and hangs his head.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS369
Later as SOMEONE exit the cathedral, SOMEONE smokes a cigarette as he ambles across a wintry lawn of dead grass.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS370
He approaches SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS371
He heads off.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS372
SOMEONE gets into his car. Now, SOMEONE stands at a podium with SOMEONE and his wife beside him.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS373
The crowd of excited supporters wave American flags and hold signs. SOMEONE stands motionless toward the back.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS374
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap grins. SOMEONE whispers in his endorser's ears. They shake hands. Outside, a brunette young woman carries two trays of coffees.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS375
The intern strides briskly with the delivery.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS376
She marches past an information booth, enters the crowded hall, and brings SOMEONE one of the coffees.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS377
SOMEONE nods.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS378
SOMEONE gazes absently.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS379
Now, the new campaign manager leads the way down a hall into a room marked "Morris Event Staff Only.”
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS380
Staff members sit at laptops facing three flat screens.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS381
SOMEONE accepts his jacket from a colleague and puts it on.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS383
As SOMEONE leaves, a TV shows an interview with SOMEONE.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS384
The brunette intern faces SOMEONE. Outside, SOMEONE marches across a walkway and heads up the front steps of the campus building.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS385
Later, he heads down an empty stairwell.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS387
SOMEONE waits in a corridor. She follows SOMEONE down the hall toward a pair of imposing guards.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS388
He dons his ID.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS389
They share a knowing gaze, then SOMEONE files past one of the security guards.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS390
Walking in our direction, he crosses a darkened corridor, his face cast in shadow.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS391
An overhead light briefly reveals the young campaign manager's emotionless gaze.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS392
As he continues his stride, another overhead offers a second glimpse of his plain look.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS393
In a dim gymnasium, an empty canvass and wood director's chair awaits.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS394
Beyond it, the lone campaign manager emerges as a blurry form from the corridor.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS395
SOMEONE arrives at the makeshift set and takes a seat under a spotlight, illuminating a patch of the otherwise darkened gym floor.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS396
A soundman outfits him with an earpiece while a makeup artist touches up his face.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS398
The makeup artist leaves. As the soundman preps him for the interview, our view gradually orbits around the side of SOMEONE's face.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS399
SOMEONE nods, gazing straight ahead with a deadpan expression.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS400
As our view finally settles facing the young campaign manager, SOMEONE looks to his left.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS401
He notices the blonde-haired makeup artist admiring him, then faces the camera and lowers his gaze.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS402
We gradually press in on the campaign manager's handsome face, his eyes downcast.
IDES_OF_MARCH_DVS403
SOMEONE looks directly at us.