They arrive back at the door.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS6
SOMEONE smiles and bites her lip coyly. Stepping close, she plants a tender kiss on the drummer's lips.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS7
They share a warm smile and he regards her fondly.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS8
SOMEONE wears his jacket.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS9
As he goes, SOMEONE smiles after him. Later, she steps off the elevator on her floor.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS10
She strolls tipsily down the hall and enters her darkened dorm room. Crossing toward her bed.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS12
In a tank top and cotton shorts, SOMEONE crosses to the lamp and switches it off. In the hall, SOMEONE steps out of the bathroom with her hand to her head.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS13
Returning to the room, she peers into the darkness through bleary eyes. SOMEONE shuts the door and crosses toward her bed. Pausing, she faces her new roommate.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS14
The pretty blonde lies under a comforter with her eyes closed. SOMEONE crosses to her bed, lies down on top of the covers, and huddles under the drummer's jacket. Daytime. Intersecting paths on the bustling quad make a bold X shape in the grass. In bed, SOMEONE rolls over beneath her comforter and groggily wakes. Across the room, SOMEONE hangs up drawings. Turning, she offers her roommate a smile.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS15
The brunette stares with a sleepy pout.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS16
She gives SOMEONE pills and water.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS17
The hungover freshman pops the white pills in her mouth and uncaps the bottle of water.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS18
SOMEONE resumes hanging drawings.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS19
Admiring them, SOMEONE sips her water.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS20
Looks up to find SOMEONE checking her cell display. It reads - SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS21
She ends the call and joins SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS22
Stylish clothes fill SOMEONE's closet.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS23
SOMEONE's fashion design portfolio.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS24
SOMEONE flips through its pages.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS25
SOMEONE crosses to her sketchpad.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS26
Now sprinkler activate on a campus lawn.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS27
In a dining hall.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS29
He notices SOMEONE and stares piercingly.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS31
She smiles and starts to leave.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS32
Pausing, she turns back.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS33
The professor holds a handout for the form. SOMEONE returns and he signs it.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS34
SOMEONE grins broadly. Professor SOMEONE returns the form, and she smiles gratefully.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS35
SOMEONE crosses back to her own bed. Flopping down with a slight pout, she puts in ear buds
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS37
and picks on her stalls.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS38
Outside the bar, SOMEONE heads down an alley past a few club goers huddled in pairs. Reaching an adjacent sidewalk, she stops and looks around. In the dorm, SOMEONE lies in bed, her gaze forlorn. She sits up and grabs her cellphone from a nightstand.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS39
Now in a diner, SOMEONE stirs a cup of coffee, sitting alone at a booth.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS40
She cranes her neck as a car arrives. Outside, SOMEONE shuts the door of her red convertible. She enters the restaurant and joins her roommate at the booth.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS41
SOMEONE gives a tight-lipped smile.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS42
at a museum.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS43
SOMEONE nervously watches SOMEONE check her cellphone.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS44
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS45
The roommates approach a large oil painting in another section.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS46
It shows a blurry nurse peering over a surgical mask.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS47
SOMEONE furrows her brow.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS48
A dark red splotch at the nurse's neck gives the impression of a slit throat. SOMEONE looks back at her friend.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS49
She returns her attention to the unsettling painting. Outside,
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS50
SOMEONE takes out a camera and SOMEONE poses.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS51
They pose together in front of the graffitied wall. SOMEONE looks at the digital photo, then spots a tattoo shop.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS52
She reveals the name SOMEONE over her heart.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS53
Now in their dorm, beyond the photo of SOMEONE and her sister, SOMEONE sits at a laptop.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS54
SOMEONE joins her by the computer.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS56
SOMEONE hangs out the devil high heel.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS57
SOMEONE jogs outside.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS58
SOMEONE turns away from a window.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS59
She casually walks.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS60
She takes a necklace hanged on a photo frame on an end table.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS61
She tries the necklace in the mirror.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS63
As she discovers a black and white kitten drinking from a run off pipe. She gently scoops it up.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS64
SOMEONE looks up as SOMEONE enters their room. They share a smile, then SOMEONE notices the poster over her roommate's bed.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS65
SOMEONE sits on her bed. Something moves underneath her grey hooded sweatshirt.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS66
Wincing, she reveals the kitten.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS67
SOMEONE joins her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS68
She pets the tiny kitten.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS69
SOMEONE notices the necklace around SOMEONE's neck.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS70
SOMEONE quickly takes it off.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS71
SOMEONE sits beside her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS72
Daytime. SOMEONE works at a coffee shop.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS73
She leaves two customers, clears the table, then steps behind a busy counter where a co-worker reads a magazine.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS75
The drummer leans on the counter.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS76
They share a smile.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS77
SOMEONE exits the elevator and passes SOMEONE in a common room.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS78
As SOMEONE stops, SOMEONE leaves the restroom and eavesdrops.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS79
SOMEONE gets up from a couch and faces her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS80
SOMEONE hugs her. SOMEONE steps out from behind a partition, and locks eyes with the suntanned blonde as she passes.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS82
SOMEONE sits on her bed. SOMEONE grabs the necklace near the two tickets on her desk.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS83
The closet. SOMEONE parts the hanging clothes and takes out a jacket.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS84
Crosses the room to retrieve something from a drawer, then returns to SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS85
She places it in her hand.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS86
As SOMEONE leaves, SOMEONE opens her hand to find a set of large drop earrings with yellow toned stones. She looks at herself in the mirror.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS87
Tucking her hair back behind one ear, she studies the unpierced lobe.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS88
SOMEONE flashes a little smile at her reflection, and takes a step closer to the mirror.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS89
She raises an earring to her lobe, and winces as she begins to drive it through.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS90
The post pops through the back of the lobe.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS91
She adjusts the backing, then lowers her hand to find a drop of blood on her thumb. She licks it off.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS92
As the young woman gazes wide eyed at her reflection, a smile spreads across her lips.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS93
Later, SOMEONE sends a text message to Stephen, Sorry, next time. She and SOMEONE wander off through the gallery.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS94
Nighttime. At the dorm, our view slowly moves down the dimly lit hallway.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS96
In her room, SOMEONE sits up in bed and rubs her brow.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS97
She groggily gets up and crosses the dim room.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS98
At the foot of her roommate's bed, she kneels before a mini fridge.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS99
The roommate stirs in her sleep.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS100
SOMEONE opens the door and takes out a near empty plastic water bottle.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS101
She closes the refrigerator.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS102
She goes to the door. Opening it, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE sitting in the hallway.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS103
Glaring, the pale blonde stands.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS104
SOMEONE strides closer to Tracy, who leans back a touch and eyes her nervously. SOMEONE looks her up and down. SOMEONE gapes at the intimidating young woman.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS105
With a look of disgust, SOMEONE walks away.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS106
SOMEONE watches her go, then lowers her frightened gaze.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS107
Daytime. SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk across the campus.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS108
SOMEONE catches up with SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS109
A frustrated SOMEONE watches SOMEONE walk away, then notices SOMEONE spying on her from behind a low brick wall.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS110
Wide eyed, SOMEONE leaves. Now in Professor SOMEONE's class,
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS111
He receives a text from SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS112
5th and Spring, be there now.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS113
SOMEONE smirks.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS114
Now SOMEONE steps outside to find SOMEONE with a coffee.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS116
She crosses a sidewalk. Inside, she ascends a spiral staircase.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS117
She enters designers room.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS120
Now in a library, SOMEONE studies alone at a table.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS121
SOMEONE sets down her bag and takes a seat beside him.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS122
Now at the dorm.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS124
Passing a row of toilet stalls, we glimpse the bottoms of the porcelain bowls under the partition doors.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS125
Our view lifts to the bathroom door where the handle begins to turn.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS126
In her shower stall, SOMEONE runs a hand down her soaked hair. Glistening trails of water glide down her smooth back. She soaps her hands, then washes her stomach. A belly ring shimmers on her navel. As she rubs suds on her wet abdomen, the lights in the bathroom suddenly turn off. She pulls back the shower curtain.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS133
She stares at its drawn curtain, then steps toward it.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS134
SOMEONE reaches in and turns off the shower.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS135
She looks around, her eyes wide. Her body trembles slightly as she gazes out at the seemingly empty bathroom.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS136
With cautious steps, she moves to the adjacent shower stall and peers at its drawn curtain.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS137
Stepping up to it, she lifts a hand to the opaque plastic.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS138
Pulling back the curtain, she finds another vacant stall.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS139
Water streams from the shower head onto the tile floor.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS140
SOMEONE turns away from the stall, her hands still clutching its curtain.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS141
Doffing her towel, she steps back into her shower.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS142
As she washes her hair, a hooded man tears down the curtain and pushes her to the floor.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS144
Later, in room 316, drops of water fall from the sleeve of SOMEONE's sweatshirt as it hangs from the back of her chair. She sits on her bed, petting Cuddles.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS145
Hurriedly turning of her bedside lamp, she huddles under her covers. She watches as shadows pass by beneath the door, then sits back up.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS146
She grabs her phone off her bedside table and hits speed dial.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS147
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold hands as they step out of the dorm's elevator.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS148
She smiles as he leans in and kisses her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS149
Breaking off the kiss, SOMEONE sees her roommate.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS150
As she storms off, SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS151
They watch as SOMEONE returns to the room.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS152
Standing in the elevator, SOMEONE stops the closing door, leans out, and gives her one last kiss. As the door slides shut, SOMEONE
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS153
The roommates walk through the campus, both staring straight ahead.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS154
SOMEONE stops her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS155
As SOMEONE turns away, SOMEONE gently grabs her again.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS156
Now she opens SOMEONE's profile on a social networking site. A photo is captioned - My best friend SOMEONE and me.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS157
SOMEONE gives her a good-humored look. Through a plate glass window across the way, we watch the couple at their library table. As SOMEONE stands, our view shifts to show SOMEONE staring at them through the glass. SOMEONE kisses Stephen, then leaves him at the table. Now SOMEONE creeps between two stacks in the library. On the other side of one, SOMEONE searches through books. As he makes his way down the stack, SOMEONE parallels him on the other side, eyeing him through the gaps between the shelves.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS158
SOMEONE runs his finger along a row of books, examining their spines. SOMEONE stalks him closely.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS159
Stopping, SOMEONE pulls out a book from a shelf to reveal her watchful eye. Not noticing her, he heads to the end of the aisle, and SOMEONE moves with him, concealed by the bookshelves. Lowering his gaze to his book, SOMEONE obliviously walks past her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS160
He pauses and turns back, but finds no one there.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS161
Now SOMEONE catches up to SOMEONE on a campus walkway.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS162
SOMEONE hurries toward them.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS163
SOMEONE strides away.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS164
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare at a grand view of downtown.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS165
She rests her chin on his shoulder.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS166
SOMEONE glances at her, then smiles.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS167
Now they hang from a set of monkey bars, their legs bent away from the ground.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS168
He eyes her bare midriff.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS169
Grinning, she turns away.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS170
Later, they kiss heatedly.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS172
He open the door.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS174
glances at the door. A clock reads 12:55. SOMEONE stands, grabs her phone, and eyes its display. She throws it onto her bed.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS175
Turning to SOMEONE's side of the room, she eyes her roommate's bedside table.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS176
Opening its drawer, she finds SOMEONE's cellphone inside. The caller ID reads - SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS177
SOMEONE removes the phone and answers. She lifts it to her ear.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS178
Meanwhile, SOMEONE removes SOMEONE's shirt.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS179
In the dorm room, SOMEONE twitches a smile, then sits on SOMEONE's bed.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS180
In the frat house, SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS181
We flash between SOMEONE's room and the dorm. As the couple makes out, SOMEONE lies back on SOMEONE's bed with her eyes closed.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS182
Holding the phone to her ear, she stares off with a distant look.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS183
On SOMEONE's bed, her jacket removed and her lover lowers himself on top of her. Meanwhile, SOMEONE's chest heaves.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS184
She eyes the framed photo of SOMEONE and SOMEONE on the bedside table.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS185
Her eyes close as she touches herself.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS186
He presses his lips to Sarah's, then grazes his nose against her cheek. SOMEONE's brow creases in ecstasy, her lips.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS187
SOMEONE closes her eyes as SOMEONE kisses her neck.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS190
SOMEONE's lips spread into a sultry expression as she speaks.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS192
He kisses her neck.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS193
She smile. SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS194
SOMEONE stares off with vacant eyes.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS195
She hangs up.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS196
SOMEONE returns to the dorm room.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS197
Cuddles scurries out to the hall. SOMEONE runs after her. The RA picks up the kitten.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS198
Taking her, SOMEONE heads away.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS199
She walks back into her room. Nighttime.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS200
She brings out another armful of clothes.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS201
SOMEONE sets down the clothes. SOMEONE eyes her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS202
Later, SOMEONE scrolls through an online profile, looking at photos of SOMEONE with beautiful women.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS203
SOMEONE puts away her new clothes.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS204
She sits beside SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS205
Staring at Sarah, she clamps her mouth shut, then averts her gaze.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS206
SOMEONE returns to the closet.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS207
SOMEONE sulks.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS208
At work, SOMEONE uses her phone.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS209
Only a few patrons sit inside the calm coffee house. SOMEONE sets her phone on the counter and lowers her gaze. In the dorm room, SOMEONE carries Cuddles to a laundry basket and sets her on top of some clothes.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS210
She brings the basket with the kitten into a laundry room.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS211
Picking up Cuddles, she carries her to a dryer and opens the door.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS212
She sets her inside.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS213
As she closes the door, the kitten presses its paw to the glass.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS214
She feeds coins into the machine. Later, SOMEONE returns to the room to find her crying.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS215
SOMEONE hugs her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS216
SOMEONE gives her an irritated look.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS217
She leaves. Later, SOMEONE picks at a cup of fruit as she sits across from SOMEONE in the cafeteria.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS218
She gazes intently at her roommate, who glances up from the fruit cup.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS220
In class, the students pack up their belongings and head out.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS221
His eyes drift to SOMEONE's lips. He leans in and kisses her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS222
She recoils, shooting him a disapproving look. He leans back in his seat.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS223
Now SOMEONE marches down an aisle between library bookcases. Reaching a table, she plops down in a seat facing SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS224
SOMEONE lowers her disgusted gaze and purses her lips.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS225
SOMEONE smiles and leans closer to SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS226
SOMEONE lays a hand on hers. SOMEONE stares at it.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS227
A pair of feet in seductive high-heeled shoes stride down a hall bathed in dim red light. SOMEONE arrives in the doorway to professor SOMEONEs's office. Putting on a jacket, he pauses.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS228
SOMEONE enters and shuts the door behind her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS229
As she picks up a photo, SOMEONE tucks off his wedding ring.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS230
The professor moves in close. SOMEONE stares at him, then shuts her eyes and parts her lips. The professor gently kisses her mouth.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS231
He regards her questioningly. SOMEONE puts her fingers to her mouth and gives a Lolita-esque smile.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS232
With a lustful smirk, SOMEONE kisses her more hungrily.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS233
a recording device. As he reaches for it
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS234
SOMEONE kneels down beside the professor.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS235
Feebly lunges for the recorder, but she moves back.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS236
She coldly turns away. Daytime. SOMEONE goes to her design class and finds a middle-aged woman at the front.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS237
SOMEONE turns to a classmate. Later,
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS238
brings dishes to the counter.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS239
She kisses her sweetly. SOMEONE smiles.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS240
She fingers the rosy spot.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS241
Screwing up her doll-like features, she hits herself again.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS242
She repeats the process over and over. Later, our lowering gaze takes in a nasty welt on her arm, then bruises on her outer thigh.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS243
A brief dreamy smile flits across SOMEONE's face. From a jar of art supplies, she takes out a utility knife. Pressing her thumb to a switch on its side, she slides the blade's tip out from its metal handle. SOMEONE lifts up her shirt, revealing her smooth flat abdomen. Her brow furrowed, she puts the knifepoint to the side of her stomach. The troubled young woman closes her eyes, winces, and rips the knifepoint across her flesh.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS244
Now beneath a photo of a statue depicting a screaming man, she lies on her bed.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS245
SOMEONE rocks her injured roommate.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS246
Noticing blood, she gingerly lifts up SOMEONE's shirt.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS247
SOMEONE lies back down with a miserable pout.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS248
Daytime. SOMEONE walks outside with SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS249
They kiss.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS250
SOMEONE hands her a bag. SOMEONE pulls up in her convertible, and SOMEONE gets in. SOMEONE glances at her and she looks away. Later in the speeding car.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS252
security gate with a key code panel. A sprawling mansion peeks out from behind lush trees beyond it.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS253
SOMEONE shifts her uncomfortable gaze. Later, the car passes working gardeners as it travels up a driveway to the gorgeous Greek-style home.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS254
SOMEONE leads her guest into a sunny foyer. A crystal chandelier hangs from the vaulted ceiling.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS255
A tall man with thinning hair arrives with a petite elegant redhead.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS256
He kisses her cheek.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS257
Her father shifts his uneasy gaze.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS258
Her parents face SOMEONE tensely.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS259
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE into a sizable bedroom decorated in shades of gray and periwinkle, and shuts the door.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS260
SOMEONE crawls onto a luxurious bed and rolls over on her back. SOMEONE steps farther in, taking in her surroundings.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS261
SOMEONE notices a collection of drawings on a wall. They all feature the same brunette with almond-shaped eyes.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS263
Now in a dining room, SOMEONE takes a big bite of Thanksgiving turkey, and SOMEONE responds with a warm appreciative smile. Both parents stare at their plates.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS264
SOMEONE sips his wine and glances at Sarah, who musters a tight smile.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS265
SOMEONE beams cheerily. Now in the darkened house, SOMEONE comes downstairs in a t-shirt and sweatpants. He lumbers groggily into the kitchen and opens the refrigerator, its light spilling into the room.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS266
He turns with a start.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS267
She sits glumly at an island counter. Upstairs, SOMEONE sits up in bed. Later, she arrives downstairs in a camisole and knee-length lounge pants. Crossing the foyer, she peers through the partially open kitchen door.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS268
SOMEONE sits by his daughter, staring ahead.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS269
He faces SOMEONE, who stares at the counter.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS270
The troubled young woman sullenly obeys. SOMEONE lingers at the door, listening intently.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS271
SOMEONE's brow knits. SOMEONE stands.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS272
SOMEONE slips out of view. SOMEONE remains at the counter, wearing a morose pout. Daytime. As SOMEONE stands in the foyer, SOMEONE comes in.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS273
SOMEONE blinks at her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS274
Upstairs, SOMEONE steps into view.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS275
SOMEONE leaves as her daughter arrives downstairs.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS276
SOMEONE gazes after her, then follows SOMEONE out. Later, the two girls follow a sidewalk past a brick wall. Her arms folded across her chest, SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS277
A smile spreads across SOMEONE's pale face.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS278
SOMEONE takes a sip.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS279
Three girls halt at the entrance, their smiles fading. Two of them face their brunette friend.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS280
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE's gaze to them. As the brunette waits outside, her two friends come in, glaring at SOMEONE as they pass by.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS281
The troubled blonde glances at the girls as they place their order, then answers her roommate with a cryptic gaze. Looking outside, SOMEONE
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS282
notices the brunette hunched uneasily at a table.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS283
The brunette's friends rejoin her with drinks.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS284
Putting her coffee on the table, she stands and goes outside. The brunette looks up wearily as SOMEONE approaches.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS285
SOMEONE arrives at her roommate's side.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS286
SOMEONE offers a gentle smile.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS287
The three girls huddle uncomfortably, shifting their uneasy gazes. SOMEONE looks up at SOMEONE, who glares resentfully at her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS288
She smiles meekly at Sarah, and they head off.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS289
SOMEONE's brow knits.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS290
The troubled girl pauses and turns back. SOMEONE stands, takes a step closer, and looks her in the eye.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS291
SOMEONE's faint hopeful smile fades. She stares at SOMEONE, who gravely stands her ground.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS292
Her eyes glistening, the troubled blonde musters a smug smile, then follows SOMEONE off.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS293
She speeds down a tree lined street, scattering fallen autumn leaves in its wake. At the wheel, SOMEONE stares ahead with a dull expression. Riding shotgun, SOMEONE maintains a cheery clear-eyed gaze.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS294
SOMEONE watches her roommate flip open her cellphone.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS295
woman scowls resentfully at the phone, then eyes her roommate. Now back at the dorm, SOMEONE takes out her ear buds as she walks down the hall in exercise clothes and running shoes. She arrives at her room, sweat glistening on her face and throat. SOMEONE faces her displayed drawings.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS296
She shoulders her bag and smiles.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS297
With a sunny grin, SOMEONE leaves.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS298
SOMEONE notices her sketchpad lying on her bed. Taking an uneasy breath, she approaches the spiral-bound notebook.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS299
She cheerfully takes it from the bed.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS300
She leaves again, shutting the door behind her. SOMEONE glances at the bed, then creeps to the door. Opening it, she peers down the hallway. She finds no sign of her roommate. Returning inside, SOMEONE yanks open the drawers of SOMEONE's desk, one after another, anxiously searching their contents. She flips through a couple of sketch pads and finds.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS301
a yellow prescription pill bottle.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS302
A hand grabs her shoulder.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS303
SOMEONE hugs her boyfriend.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS304
SOMEONE's red convertible pulls into a gas station. Inside, a worker watching a football game spots her through the window and gets up. Outside, SOMEONE
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS305
She leans to her car's tank.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS306
The toothpick-chewing attendant approaches.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS307
Sidling up to her, he leans against the car.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS308
She forces a smile, then watches him place his hand on her hand.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS309
caresses her cheek, and she squirts his crotch with gasoline.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS310
She drops the nozzle.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS311
She opens a zippo.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS312
She smiles, and he runs away.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS313
She caps the lighter.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS314
Now in the dorm, SOMEONE types Zyprexa into a Wikipedia search field.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS315
she faces a mirror, rubbing a finger over her lips. SOMEONE enters and stands at the next mirror over to fix her hair.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS316
As SOMEONE touches up her lip-gloss, she glances at the younger blonde.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS317
SOMEONE slides in close.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS319
she slowly bring their lips together for a long soft kiss.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS320
woman smiles. SOMEONE grins.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS321
She plays with SOMEONE's hair.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS322
She hands back the lip-gloss and they leave.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS323
Daytime. SOMEONE jogs up to SOMEONE's apartment building. At the entrance, she enters a number into an intercom.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS324
SOMEONE walks out to a curb, then peers up the side of the multi-story building. She glances up and down the street, then adjusts her ear bud and leaves. Now a sideways image shows SOMEONE walking down the dorm hall.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS325
In their room, SOMEONE sits on her bed.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS326
SOMEONE sits on her roommate's bed.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS327
Now the two young women head through a shop selling lots of black clothes and miniskirts. They reach a small tattoo parlor at the back, and face a wall displaying numerous designs.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS328
SOMEONE walks into a back room with a tattoo artist.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS329
Sitting on a couch in a waiting area, SOMEONE picks up a magazine and flips through it.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS330
Later, she drops the magazine and picks up another.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS331
SOMEONE comes out from the back, her hands clasped at her chest.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS332
SOMEONE puts down the magazine and stands.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS333
She faces her smiling friend, who peels back a layer of plastic to reveal a tattoo of the name SOMEONE over her heart. SOMEONE's eyes widen.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS334
SOMEONE steps back a bit.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS335
SOMEONE's smile fades. SOMEONE swallows, her eyes glistening with tears.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS336
He sets down the crate.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS337
From their dorm room, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE load the crate into the back seat of a taxi.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS338
SOMEONE enters to find her sitting on the windowsill.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS339
SOMEONE barely shakes her head no.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS340
He crouches and opens a drawer.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS341
She takes his picture with her camera.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS342
Now at the frat house.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS343
He smells the clothes.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS344
Unpacks the crate. She finds SOMEONE's brown spiral notebook inside.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS345
She finds an unfinished drawing of herself.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS346
Flipping through the subsequent pages, she finds more and more portraits, each more detailed than the last.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS347
Now we drift high over the intersecting pathways on the quad. SOMEONE nervously glances about as she walks alone down a set of steps. Halfway down, she halts and scans the entire area before continuing on.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS348
Nighttime. SOMEONE steps out of the coffee shop, then
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS349
she walks home alone on the dark deserted street. She notices someone walking in her direction.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS350
SOMEONE squints at the slender hooded figure as the person draws near.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS351
She averts her gaze as they pass each other.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS352
As SOMEONE continues on, the hooded figure stops and watches her go. SOMEONE glances back and sees the person walking away.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS353
Now SOMEONE enters the frat house and shuts the door.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS354
She finds a group of frat guys playing video games and allows a smile.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS355
Daytime. In SOMEONE's room, SOMEONE's cellphone vibrates.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS356
She flips it.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS358
SOMEONE glances at her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS359
Outside the dorm building, a guy holds a cellphone to his ear.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS360
Two students step outside, and SOMEONE hurries over to catch the open door before it shuts. In SOMEONE's room, SOMEONE looks up from her books.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS361
At the dorm, SOMEONE follows the hallway.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS362
He stops at room 316 and knocks.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS363
Inside, we drift backward, away from the door.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS364
SOMEONE sits in a plain armchair.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS365
Wearing an anguished frown, she repeatedly stabs the utility knife into the chair's armrest.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS366
SOMEONE looks up at the door.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS367
She concentrates on the handle.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS368
In the hall, SOMEONE jots a note to SOMEONE - I'm here, and I just want to see you. He includes his hotel and room number and signs - Love, SOMEONE. He slips it under the door.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS369
SOMEONE rises from the armchair and picks up the note.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS370
At the library, SOMEONE takes notes as she studies.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS373
Later, she opens SOMEONE's wardrobe, then grabs a bottle of SOMEONE's perfume. Looking at herself in the mirror, she puts on SOMEONE's fedora.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS374
She strokes the SOMEONE tattoo, which peeks over her black SOMEONE bra. Now SOMEONE opens a wide bureau drawer containing only SOMEONE's necklace. She fastens the chain around her neck.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS375
Later still, at the Rosewell Hotel, a chambermaid pushes a supply cart down a hallway. SOMEONE exits the elevator dressed like SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS376
She watches the maid unlock a door down the hall.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS377
As the maid tends to the room, SOMEONE crosses to the cart and steals a key card off of it.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS378
Now outside room 210, SOMEONE inserts the card into the electronic slot on the door.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS379
Inside, SOMEONE sleeps soundly.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS380
SOMEONE slides into the room and shuts the door behind her. As she removes her black sleeveless top, SOMEONE remains asleep on his side, his back to her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS381
SOMEONE slides off her jeans.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS382
She eases into bed behind him and gets under the comforter.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS383
She rubs his shoulder and kisses his back.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS384
He smiles, his eyes still closed.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS385
The bleary-eyed young man glimpses SOMEONE's necklace and familiar tattoo.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS386
She pulls the utility knife from her bra strap and raises it.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS387
SOMEONE opens his eyes, SOMEONE plunges the knife downward. She stabs him again. SOMEONE's head presses to his pillow, then his wide eyes go lifeless.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS388
At the library, SOMEONE packs up her books. She receives a text message from SOMEONE - Urgent, I need you right away.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS389
At SOMEONE's posh apartment building, SOMEONE crosses the lobby.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS390
The door slides open and she steps in the elevator and hits number six.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS391
Her gaze drifts to the digital display as it counts upward. SOMEONE waits with a faint smile.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS392
Now the door slides open, and SOMEONE steps into a hallway. She pauses in front of SOMEONE's apartment as she finds the door ajar. A sign on it reads - Entre des artist. With a puzzled look, SOMEONE peeks inside.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS393
Pushing the door all the way open, she walks into the dark apartment.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS394
As she heads down a hall, she pulls her phone from her bag and checks it.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS395
Sheer curtains at the end of the hall billow in front of an open window.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS396
Turning a corner, SOMEONE narrows her eyes as she heads toward SOMEONE's bedroom. Its door hangs partially open as well. SOMEONE draws closer, and finds the bedside lamp on and the comforter on the bed rumpled.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS397
She opens the door wider and steps into the room.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS398
SOMEONE aims a revolver at her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS399
SOMEONE sits. SOMEONE kneels in front of her. She touches SOMEONE's hair.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS400
she glances at her restrained friend.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS401
Point blank at SOMEONE's head.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS403
SOMEONE smiles tearfully.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS404
She shakes out a plastic bag.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS406
She went out of the room searching for the weapon.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS407
SOMEONE closes and locks SOMEONE's bedroom.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS409
SOMEONE reaches for the fire escape.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS411
He pulled her back through the window.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS412
SOMEONE smiles down at her.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS413
He hauls her up. As they both fell down.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS414
approaching and grabs the gun from SOMEONE's waist.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS415
She smiles and reaches out.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS416
SOMEONE grips the gun with both hands.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS417
She flinches, her smile vanishing. SOMEONE squeezes the trigger again. SOMEONE gives a dejected pout.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS418
SOMEONE stands, with the gun still in her hand.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS420
She resists desperately.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS421
SOMEONE leans over SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS422
She stabs SOMEONE in the back with a utility knife.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS423
SOMEONE drops to her knees.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS424
She reaches backward, her fingers straining for the knife. She topples onto her side.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS425
SOMEONE looks over at SOMEONE. Still bound to the bed, the young woman stares down at the fallen killer. With a wince, SOMEONE sits up partway.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS426
She strains to move herself along on her arms, and fixes her eyes on SOMEONE.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS427
She leans in and reaches a hand toward SOMEONE's necklace, still worn by the motionless psychopath.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS428
Holding her breath, SOMEONE inches her fingers closer, almost touching the necklace.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS429
SOMEONE opens her eyes and grabs SOMEONE's wrist.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS430
her chest heaves.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS431
SOMEONE's eyelids droop, and her eyes roll back in her head. SOMEONE yanks her wrist from the dead woman's grasp.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS432
SOMEONE clutches SOMEONE's necklace in her hand and gives it a tug. The chain gives, and she retrieves it from SOMEONE's neck. With a final look at her ex-roommate, SOMEONE crawls over to SOMEONE. He stirs as she lies down beside him.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS433
Draping an arm across his chest, she rests her head on his shoulder, and he places his hand on her head. Daytime. A clear blue sky sprawls above SOMEONE as she stops in front of her dorm, gazes at it, then heads inside.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS434
SOMEONE enters room 316, its walls now bare and its contents packed in suitcases and boxes. She slides a duffle bag off her shoulder.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS435
Sitting on her bare bed, she scans SOMEONE's former half of the room. With a pained expression, she lowers her gaze.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS436
SOMEONE enters.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS437
He turns to leave.
THE_ROOMMATE_DVS438
Now SOMEONE drags the extra bed out of her room.