SOMEONE turns to her two maids.
TITANIC_1_DVS27
The maids leave. SOMEONE stops SOMEONE as he wanders past.
TITANIC_1_DVS28
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE aside.
TITANIC_1_DVS29
SOMEONE stands nearby.
TITANIC_1_DVS30
SOMEONE leans forward.
TITANIC_1_DVS31
SOMEONE nods and walks off.
TITANIC_1_DVS32
Meanwhile in his office, the Master at Arms handcuffs SOMEONE to a vertical water pipe.
TITANIC_1_DVS33
SOMEONE stands nearby.
TITANIC_1_DVS34
A dark-haired crewman rushes in.
TITANIC_1_DVS35
SOMEONE pulls out a handgun.
TITANIC_1_DVS36
As he leaves with the crewman, the Master at Arms hands SOMEONE the handcuff key.
TITANIC_1_DVS37
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare at each other, as SOMEONE sits in a desk chair. On the bridge, Bride runs up to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS38
Bride leaves. SOMEONE glances around the bridge deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS39
SOMEONE descends to the port side of the boat deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS40
SOMEONE, a man with short light brown hair, and SOMEONE hurry over to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS41
SOMEONE nods.
TITANIC_1_DVS42
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE then rushes to passengers gathered nearby.
TITANIC_1_DVS43
Bandleader SOMEONE leads the band on to the boat deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS44
The band plays.
TITANIC_1_DVS45
In steerage, a SOMEONE hands out life belts to third class passengers.
TITANIC_1_DVS46
SOMEONE follows Tommy, who grabs a life belt and puts it on. They stand behind a crowd of passengers on a stair leading to the main deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS47
At the top of the stairs, a SOMEONE stands behind a locked gate.
TITANIC_1_DVS48
A young brown-haired boy turns to his auburn-haired mother.
TITANIC_1_DVS49
The mother glances at her young daughter, who nods.
TITANIC_1_DVS50
The two stewards exchanged glances.
TITANIC_1_DVS51
SOMEONE directs sailors lowering lifeboats filled with women and children.
TITANIC_1_DVS52
As one of the lifeboats tilts to one side the passengers on board SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS53
The sailors level the boat and lower it toward the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS54
A crewman fires a flare into the night sky.
TITANIC_1_DVS55
The passengers on deck including SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze up.
TITANIC_1_DVS56
A young blonde girl watches the flares and smiles.
TITANIC_1_DVS57
The flare explodes into separate fiery streams that fall and extinguish in the ocean.
TITANIC_1_DVS58
In the Master at Arms office, SOMEONE peers out through a porthole at the water, which almost reaches the middle of the glass.
TITANIC_1_DVS59
Sitting near SOMEONE, SOMEONE places a bullet on a table, watches it roll off then catches it.
TITANIC_1_DVS60
He puts the bullet in a clip then shoves the clip into the handgun.
TITANIC_1_DVS61
SOMEONE stands.
TITANIC_1_DVS62
He punches SOMEONE in the stomach.
TITANIC_1_DVS63
SOMEONE winces. SOMEONE picks up the handcuff key from the table, places it in his breast pocket and leaves.
TITANIC_1_DVS64
SOMEONE Brown helps a brunette woman.
TITANIC_1_DVS65
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS66
SOMEONE watches a tearful woman hug her husband. SOMEONE scans the passengers on the lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS67
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE and smiles.
TITANIC_1_DVS68
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE. SOMEONE stands in a lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS69
SOMEONE helps SOMEONE into the boat.
TITANIC_1_DVS70
SOMEONE's jaw slackens as she stares at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS71
SOMEONE places SOMEONE's life belt in the boat.
TITANIC_1_DVS72
SOMEONE and SOMEONE reached toward SOMEONE. SOMEONE gestures.
TITANIC_1_DVS73
SOMEONE walks away.
TITANIC_1_DVS74
SOMEONE follows and grabs her.
TITANIC_1_DVS75
As she steps away, SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE and spins her toward him.
TITANIC_1_DVS76
SOMEONE spits in SOMEONE's face and runs off.
TITANIC_1_DVS77
The crewmen lower the lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS78
In the Master at Arms office, SOMEONE peers at the water covering the porthole window.
TITANIC_1_DVS79
He bangs his handcuffs against the water pipe.
TITANIC_1_DVS80
Water floods the staircase and streams down a long corridor leading to the office.
TITANIC_1_DVS81
In the first class corridor, SOMEONE searches for SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS82
In another corridor, SOMEONE stops a looks around. SOMEONE closes a door.
TITANIC_1_DVS83
SOMEONE turns to a brunette woman. He touches a blonde maid face.
TITANIC_1_DVS84
SOMEONE checks a passenger cabin.
TITANIC_1_DVS85
SOMEONE runs to him.
TITANIC_1_DVS86
SOMEONE shakes his head.
TITANIC_1_DVS87
In the Master at Arms office, SOMEONE drops his head.
TITANIC_1_DVS88
Water streams in under the door.
TITANIC_1_DVS89
SOMEONE climbs up the water pipe near the ceiling and bangs the handcuffs against the pipe. Elsewhere, SOMEONE bumps into a SOMEONE as she runs to an elevator.
TITANIC_1_DVS90
As she reaches the elevator, an elevator operator with dark blonde hair stops her.
TITANIC_1_DVS91
SOMEONE shoves the operator into the elevator.
TITANIC_1_DVS92
The operator pushes a lever down as SOMEONE closes the door.
TITANIC_1_DVS93
In the office, SOMEONE tries to pull off the handcuffs.
TITANIC_1_DVS94
In the elevator, SOMEONE's chest heaves.
TITANIC_1_DVS95
The elevator descends into rising water which pours into the elevator.
TITANIC_1_DVS96
SOMEONE opens the elevator doors and steps into a flooded corridor.
TITANIC_1_DVS97
The operator pulls the lever up, water empties out of the elevator as it rises. SOMEONE watches the elevator ascend and glances around as she wades through knee-deep water.
TITANIC_1_DVS98
She glances up at a sign over a doorway.
TITANIC_1_DVS99
She walks down a short corridor and turns down a long hallway. In the office, SOMEONE still handcuffed to the pipe, climbs onto a desk as the water rises.
TITANIC_1_DVS100
SOMEONE pauses at a staircase then turns left and walks down another flooded corridor, lit with floating furniture.
TITANIC_1_DVS101
The hall lights flicker on and off.
TITANIC_1_DVS102
SOMEONE turns toward the closed office door.
TITANIC_1_DVS103
SOMEONE turns around.
TITANIC_1_DVS104
SOMEONE hurries to the office door.
TITANIC_1_DVS105
SOMEONE steps into the office.
TITANIC_1_DVS106
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS107
SOMEONE searches through a cabinet filled with keys.
TITANIC_1_DVS108
SOMEONE pulls out a desk drawer.
TITANIC_1_DVS109
She turns to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS110
They exchange smiles.
TITANIC_1_DVS111
SOMEONE searches in the drawer. Meanwhile the bow of the ship sinks. Empty handed, SOMEONE glances around the office.
TITANIC_1_DVS112
SOMEONE pushes the desk chair out of her way as she walks to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS113
She kisses SOMEONE and makes her way out of the office.
TITANIC_1_DVS114
SOMEONE moves down the long dimmed corridor in waist deep water.
TITANIC_1_DVS115
She climbs upstairs to the D-deck and runs down hallways.
TITANIC_1_DVS116
A mustached man runs toward SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS117
The man runs away. SOMEONE gazes down the empty corridor.
TITANIC_1_DVS118
She takes a few steps then stops as the lights go out.
TITANIC_1_DVS119
Her chest heaves as she leans back against the wall.
TITANIC_1_DVS120
The lights turn back on.
TITANIC_1_DVS121
SOMEONE stands.
TITANIC_1_DVS122
A dark-haired SOMEONE rounds the corner.
TITANIC_1_DVS124
She punches him in the face. He stumbles back and touches his bloody nose.
TITANIC_1_DVS125
He hurries away. SOMEONE leans back against the wall, blinks then stares ahead.
TITANIC_1_DVS126
She steps forward, unwraps a fire hose and uses it to break the glass on a case containing an ax.
TITANIC_1_DVS127
She grabs the ax and runs toward the E-deck stairs. On the bridge, SOMEONE leans over the railing and gazes down at the flooding bow and front well deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS128
Meanwhile, SOMEONE descends the E-deck stairs and stops above the water, which has risen above several steps.
TITANIC_1_DVS129
She steps down into the water, grabs an overhead frame and ducks her head out into the hallway.
TITANIC_1_DVS130
She glances both ways down the flooded hallway then steps back and hangs the ax on the frame.
TITANIC_1_DVS131
She takes off her long sweater and drops it.
TITANIC_1_DVS132
She grabs the ax with one hand and wades into the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS133
With her free hand, she grasps along pipe running along the ceiling, propelling herself down the hallway.
TITANIC_1_DVS134
She holds the ax overhead with both hands and walks through the chest deep water into the office.
TITANIC_1_DVS135
She holds out the ax.
TITANIC_1_DVS136
SOMEONE stretches the chain connecting the handcuffs out on the water pipe. SOMEONE lifts the ax.
TITANIC_1_DVS137
SOMEONE walks to the wooden cabinet, swings the ax and strikes the cabinet door.
TITANIC_1_DVS138
SOMEONE swings the ax and hits the cabinet door missing the first SOMEONE by several inches.
TITANIC_1_DVS139
She approaches SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS140
SOMEONE grips the ax handle with both hands.
TITANIC_1_DVS141
She moves her hands apart.
TITANIC_1_DVS142
SOMEONE stretches the chain across the pipe and closes his eyes.
TITANIC_1_DVS143
SOMEONE closes her eyes and swings and cuts the handcuff chain in half.
TITANIC_1_DVS144
SOMEONE lifts his hands and smiles.
TITANIC_1_DVS145
They move into the corridor. SOMEONE points to the flooded stairway.
TITANIC_1_DVS146
SOMEONE pulls her toward the opposite end of the corridor. Outside, passengers paddle two lifeboats away from the Titanic.
TITANIC_1_DVS147
In one lifeboat, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare at the ship, now tilted forward with its bow nearly submerged.
TITANIC_1_DVS148
A flare shoots up from the bridge deck and explodes.
TITANIC_1_DVS149
On the boat deck, passengers crowd around the remaining lifeboats. As SOMEONE seats people in a lifeboat one woman, toting luggage tries to climb aboard.
TITANIC_1_DVS150
SOMEONE pulls a sobbing gray-haired woman away from her husband.
TITANIC_1_DVS151
SOMEONE puts her in the boat.
TITANIC_1_DVS152
An auburn-haired woman cries and kisses a brown-haired man. SOMEONE
TITANIC_1_DVS153
turns toward SOMEONE as he approaches.
TITANIC_1_DVS154
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE, who uses the ax to break through a door and into the corridor. A SOMEONE addresses them.
TITANIC_1_DVS155
The SOMEONE follows SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS156
SOMEONE and SOMEONE glance back.
TITANIC_1_DVS157
The SOMEONE stops in his tracks.
TITANIC_1_DVS158
SOMEONE picks up a woman.
TITANIC_1_DVS159
And places her in a boat.
TITANIC_1_DVS160
SOMEONE rushes over.
TITANIC_1_DVS161
SOMEONE gazes at as several partially filled lifeboats moving away from the Titanic, then motions to waiting passengers.
TITANIC_1_DVS162
Several full lifeboats are lowered to the water. SOMEONE and other passengers pop open the third class gangway door and peer out along the ship.
TITANIC_1_DVS163
Two seamen pull the passengers back and close the door. SOMEONE and others stand at the locked gate at the top of the third class stairwell.
TITANIC_1_DVS164
Two stewards unlock the gate.
TITANIC_1_DVS165
A woman and several men rush through the open gate. The stewards push back the men, punch them, and hit them with ax handles.
TITANIC_1_DVS166
One SOMEONE pulls out a small handgun and points it at the crowd, now contained behind the closed gate.
TITANIC_1_DVS167
SOMEONE and SOMEONE reach the bottom of the third class stairs.
TITANIC_1_DVS168
At top of the stairs SOMEONE grips the gate and glares at the armed SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS169
SOMEONE glowers and points to the SOMEONE then runs downstairs.
TITANIC_1_DVS170
SOMEONE rushes over.
TITANIC_1_DVS171
SOMEONE hugs him.
TITANIC_1_DVS172
In the suite, SOMEONE removes the Heart of the Ocean along with some cash from the safe and puts it in his jacket pocket. He glances at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS173
SOMEONE opens his jacket revealing a handgun in a shoulder holster. SOMEONE closes the safe, locks it, and walks out. Elsewhere, SOMEONE and the others run along a crowded corridor then stop.
TITANIC_1_DVS174
SOMEONE leads them down another corridor. They pass a mustached man flipping through a book and studying a sign on the wall.
TITANIC_1_DVS175
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE and his friends down another corridor and up a stairway to another locked gate.
TITANIC_1_DVS176
At the top, a SOMEONE addresses a small crowd from behind a locked gate.
TITANIC_1_DVS177
SOMEONE grabs the gate and shakes it.
TITANIC_1_DVS178
SOMEONE rushes over and pulls on a wooden bench nailed to the floor.
TITANIC_1_DVS179
SOMEONE and SOMEONE help SOMEONE pull up the bench.
TITANIC_1_DVS180
They charge forward and ram the gate with the bench.
TITANIC_1_DVS181
They ram the gate again. The gate collapses.
TITANIC_1_DVS182
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and other passengers pass the SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS183
SOMEONE punches the SOMEONE. On the boat deck, passengers swarm around the remaining lifeboats. SOMEONE pushes away a group of men.
TITANIC_1_DVS184
A man knocks a woman off the deck. She grabs on to the side of the lifeboat and dangles high above the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS185
A sailor pulls the woman on deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS186
SOMEONE lifts a revolver.
TITANIC_1_DVS187
He waves the gun at the group of men.
TITANIC_1_DVS188
He turns toward a young sailor.
TITANIC_1_DVS189
SOMEONE loads his revolver while Lowe boards the lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS190
On the other side of the ship, SOMEONE and SOMEONE peer down as SOMEONE supervises the lowering of a lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS191
SOMEONE and SOMEONE peered down the side of the ship.
TITANIC_1_DVS192
Below, one lifeboat is lowered on to another lifeboat, sitting on the water but unable to detach. In a lower lifeboat, a man labors to cut the ropes connecting the two boats.
TITANIC_1_DVS193
On the other side of the ship, Lowe stands in a lifeboat as it is lowered. He waves his revolver at men on the decks as they try to jump into the boat.
TITANIC_1_DVS194
SOMEONE and SOMEONE turn as Lowe fires his gun in the air.
TITANIC_1_DVS195
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE toward the bow.
TITANIC_1_DVS196
Meanwhile SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE arrive on the upper deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS197
They run to the side of the ship.
TITANIC_1_DVS198
SOMEONE stands up on the railing and gazes toward the bow. As he steps down, SOMEONE stops the mustached Col. Gracie.
TITANIC_1_DVS199
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the others run toward the bow. Meanwhile as the band plays on deck, a passenger bumps into one of the violinists.
TITANIC_1_DVS200
SOMEONE's brow furrows.
TITANIC_1_DVS201
As the band resumes playing, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE run past.
TITANIC_1_DVS202
Elsewhere, SOMEONE and several seamen load a small boat. SOMEONE glances around then turns to a sailor.
TITANIC_1_DVS203
SOMEONE slips money into SOMEONE's coat pocket.
TITANIC_1_DVS204
SOMEONE glances down at the cash then exchanges looks with SOMEONE and walks off.
TITANIC_1_DVS205
On the port side, SOMEONE loads passengers into a boat.
TITANIC_1_DVS206
Dozens of people surge toward him.
TITANIC_1_DVS207
SOMEONE shoots into the sky.
TITANIC_1_DVS208
In the crowd, SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS209
SOMEONE moves off through the crowd. Meanwhile, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE, who stands beside the small boat called the Collapsible.
TITANIC_1_DVS210
SOMEONE glances away.
TITANIC_1_DVS211
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE and SOMEONE while SOMEONE helps load the Collapsible.
TITANIC_1_DVS212
SOMEONE stares at the Collapsible then blinks.
TITANIC_1_DVS213
SOMEONE turns and walks off. SOMEONE scowls.
TITANIC_1_DVS214
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE, who walks through the bridge.
TITANIC_1_DVS215
SOMEONE and SOMEONE brush past an officer. Meanwhile, SOMEONE stands by the Collapsible.
TITANIC_1_DVS216
SOMEONE glances at a crowd of passengers on the lower side of the bridge then turns back toward the Collapsible.
TITANIC_1_DVS217
While SOMEONE turns away, SOMEONE slips into a seat on the Collapsible.
TITANIC_1_DVS218
SOMEONE faces the collapsible and finds himself staring at SOMEONE, who gazes ahead.
TITANIC_1_DVS219
Motioning downward with both arms, SOMEONE glowers at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS220
The seamen lower the Collapsible.
TITANIC_1_DVS221
As the Collapsible drops below the deck, SOMEONE glances up.
TITANIC_1_DVS222
SOMEONE grabs a young girl then places her in a lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS223
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS224
SOMEONE glances from SOMEONE to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS225
SOMEONE pulls off the blanket SOMEONE is wrapped in and shoves it at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS226
SOMEONE removes his own coat and places it around SOMEONE's shoulders. He starts to caress SOMEONE's hair but she backs away from him. SOMEONE steps up to her.
TITANIC_1_DVS227
A crewman grabs SOMEONE and guides her toward the lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS228
SOMEONE and another crewmember help SOMEONE climb into the boat.
TITANIC_1_DVS229
SOMEONE turns and grasps SOMEONE's outstretched hand.
TITANIC_1_DVS230
The crewman pushes SOMEONE back.
TITANIC_1_DVS231
The lifeboat jerks.
TITANIC_1_DVS232
Standing at the rail, SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze at SOMEONE as the lifeboat lowers toward the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS233
SOMEONE stares back at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS234
SOMEONE looks from SOMEONE to the descending boat.
TITANIC_1_DVS235
SOMEONE looks around herself then up at the ropes running through the pulleys.
TITANIC_1_DVS236
She gazes back at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS238
SOMEONE looks to her right where the young girl waves to her father while her sister cries.
TITANIC_1_DVS240
On deck, another crewmember with both arms raised out at his side yells orders.
TITANIC_1_DVS242
SOMEONE gazes back up at SOMEONE, who still stands next to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS243
In the dark sky above them, another flare shoots then dissipates.
TITANIC_1_DVS244
The light briefly illuminates SOMEONE's face. More streaking flares cascade in the sky above SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS245
Suddenly, SOMEONE steps to the edge of the lifeboat. SOMEONE leaps from the boat and hangs from the ship's rail several decks below SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS246
Two crewmembers pull her on board.
TITANIC_1_DVS247
SOMEONE runs along the deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS248
SOMEONE turns then runs along the main deck pass passengers and crewmembers.
TITANIC_1_DVS249
SOMEONE runs along the lower deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS250
SOMEONE rushes inside then runs down the grand staircase.
TITANIC_1_DVS251
At the bottom of the stairs, SOMEONE runs into his arms. They embrace.
TITANIC_1_DVS252
They kiss.
TITANIC_1_DVS253
They kiss then hug.
TITANIC_1_DVS254
SOMEONE gazes down at them from an upper landing.
TITANIC_1_DVS255
Stepping up to him, SOMEONE glances down then grabs SOMEONE's shoulder and pulls him away.
TITANIC_1_DVS256
As they step away from the railing, SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's gun from its holster then runs toward the stairs.
TITANIC_1_DVS257
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE away.
TITANIC_1_DVS258
SOMEONE and SOMEONE flee. SOMEONE tears down the stairs after them.
TITANIC_1_DVS259
SOMEONE steps on a piece of broken banister and falls. He stands, picks up the gun, and runs after them.
TITANIC_1_DVS260
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run to the bottom of the staircase. SOMEONE aims but doesn't fire. He knocks a man out of his way then shoots again.
TITANIC_1_DVS261
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run down another staircase then jump at the waist high water.
TITANIC_1_DVS263
SOMEONE runs into the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS264
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hurry into the dining room. SOMEONE aims but the gun is empty.
TITANIC_1_DVS265
SOMEONE looks around himself at the rising water.
TITANIC_1_DVS266
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run through the dining room.
TITANIC_1_DVS267
SOMEONE climbs several steps then stops.
TITANIC_1_DVS268
He chuckles to himself as SOMEONE appears.
TITANIC_1_DVS269
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run down a passageway.
TITANIC_1_DVS270
They turn then run down more stairs. Stopping SOMEONE presses his finger to his mouth.
TITANIC_1_DVS271
In the dining room, a glass door swings slowly through the water. Small waves push plates and silverware as rising water covers the tables and chairs.
TITANIC_1_DVS272
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step into another passageway. At the far end, a small boy stands against a wall.
TITANIC_1_DVS273
Water pours down the steps.
TITANIC_1_DVS274
They run toward the boy. Sparks shoot from an overhead pipe. SOMEONE picks up the boy then watches as water shoots in from cracks around the door.
TITANIC_1_DVS275
They turn and run back up the passageway. They stop as water rushes into the passageway ahead of them.
TITANIC_1_DVS276
As they run in the opposite direction, a man - the boy's father - steps into the hall. The man grabs the boy from SOMEONE then knocks SOMEONE against the wall.
TITANIC_1_DVS277
The man runs off with the boy and SOMEONE and SOMEONE run after him.
TITANIC_1_DVS278
The man picks up a suitcase then gapes at the door which bursts. Water rushes in, knocking the man over.
TITANIC_1_DVS279
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run into another passage.
TITANIC_1_DVS280
A huge torrent of water rushes after them as they run down the passageway.
TITANIC_1_DVS281
A wave knocks them over and rushing water carries them away.
TITANIC_1_DVS282
SOMEONE and SOMEONE slam into a locked gate.
TITANIC_1_DVS283
Water pours around them as lights flicker. SOMEONE struggles against the current toward a stairwell.
TITANIC_1_DVS284
They pull themselves along the wall toward the stairwell.
TITANIC_1_DVS285
SOMEONE pulls himself into the stairwell.
TITANIC_1_DVS286
SOMEONE pushes SOMEONE through the shoulder high water toward the railing.
TITANIC_1_DVS287
He shoves her upward. SOMEONE grabs the railings and climbs to another locked gate.
TITANIC_1_DVS288
SOMEONE shakes the gate as the water rises below them.
TITANIC_1_DVS289
The water reaches their feet.
TITANIC_1_DVS290
As SOMEONE runs pass them.
TITANIC_1_DVS291
The SOMEONE returns for them.
TITANIC_1_DVS292
He tries several keys in the lock as water swirls around their feet.
TITANIC_1_DVS293
The water reaches their thighs.
TITANIC_1_DVS294
Sparks shoot nearby. The SOMEONE fumbles with the keys then drops them.
TITANIC_1_DVS296
SOMEONE drops underwater, holding onto the grate with one hand, he reaches for the keys.
TITANIC_1_DVS297
SOMEONE grabs the keys then resurfaces.
TITANIC_1_DVS298
SOMEONE reaches around the grate with the key but misses the lock.
TITANIC_1_DVS299
He slips the key into the lock then turns it.
TITANIC_1_DVS300
He turns the key.
TITANIC_1_DVS301
SOMEONE opens the gate. She swims across the water which nearly reaches the ceiling.
TITANIC_1_DVS302
She stops at the stairs then turns.
TITANIC_1_DVS303
SOMEONE pulls himself onto a pipe.
TITANIC_1_DVS304
She reaches for him. He swims to the stairs and they both climb.
TITANIC_1_DVS305
On deck, people run through knee high water.
TITANIC_1_DVS306
On the top deck, crewmembers try to lift a lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS307
At the head of a crowd, SOMEONE and SOMEONE hop over a barrier. Crewmembers lift the lifeboat onto long oars set up like a ramp.
TITANIC_1_DVS308
The boat crashes to the deck. SOMEONE rushes to a stairwell and stares down at churning water.
TITANIC_1_DVS309
SOMEONE runs through a doorway, a man knocks him into a running crowd.
TITANIC_1_DVS310
SOMEONE turns and runs with the others then stops.
TITANIC_1_DVS311
He climbs a platform and peers over the crowd.
TITANIC_1_DVS312
SOMEONE peers down at a crying young girl then walks away.
TITANIC_1_DVS313
Inside, SOMEONE and SOMEONE run up a staircase.
TITANIC_1_DVS314
A man falls into the water. Another dangles from a rope.
TITANIC_1_DVS315
SOMEONE approaches.
TITANIC_1_DVS316
SOMEONE pulls money from his pocket and flings it at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS317
SOMEONE pushes SOMEONE. A man leaps toward the lifeboat, SOMEONE shoots at him.
TITANIC_1_DVS318
A man pushes SOMEONE forward. SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS319
SOMEONE kneels by SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS320
SOMEONE gazes downward then steps back toward the edge of the ship.
TITANIC_1_DVS321
He looks to his right then at the crowd of passengers. SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS322
SOMEONE stands at attention, salutes then holds the gun to his own head.
TITANIC_1_DVS323
He fires and falls into the ocean.
TITANIC_1_DVS324
SOMEONE turns then runs through the crowd.
TITANIC_1_DVS325
On the other side of the ship, crewmembers tip another lifeboat onto the deck below.
TITANIC_1_DVS326
SOMEONE picks up the crying girl then steps toward the crowded passengers.
TITANIC_1_DVS327
SOMEONE hurries forward.
TITANIC_1_DVS328
SOMEONE hands the girl to a woman, climbs into the lifeboat then sits.
TITANIC_1_DVS329
The woman hands the girl to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS330
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run through the smoking room, SOMEONE stands by the fireplace gazing at a painting.
TITANIC_1_DVS331
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE his life belt.
TITANIC_1_DVS332
She hugs SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS333
SOMEONE hurries through a revolving door. SOMEONE glances back, nods then follows SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS334
Elsewhere, a SOMEONE holding two life belts hurries toward the grand staircase.
TITANIC_1_DVS335
Outside, a sailor rotates a winch as others work to turn over the toppled lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS336
Captain SOMEONE watches then turns as a man wades through shallow water on deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS337
A woman holding a baby approaches the captain.
TITANIC_1_DVS338
Captain SOMEONE stares at her then turns and steps away. A man with a life belt runs up to the captain.
TITANIC_1_DVS339
The captain stops, glances at the life belt, then walks off. Knee deep in water, he steps on to the bridge.
TITANIC_1_DVS340
Captain SOMEONE gazes at a ship's wheel and various instruments then steps into the wheelhouse and shuts the door.
TITANIC_1_DVS341
The string quartet finishes playing.
TITANIC_1_DVS342
Carrying their instruments, three of the quartet members walk away as people run past.
TITANIC_1_DVS343
Hartley, the violin player places his instrument against his neck and resumes playing.
TITANIC_1_DVS344
A viola player glances back then returns and joins in.
TITANIC_1_DVS345
The bass player carries his bass back then stands on the other side of Hartley.
TITANIC_1_DVS346
The cello player also returns.
TITANIC_1_DVS347
Captain SOMEONE steps across the wheelhouse.
TITANIC_1_DVS348
He gazes through a window at the rising water then places one hand on the helm.
TITANIC_1_DVS349
Water pours in beneath the door.
TITANIC_1_DVS350
In the smoking room, SOMEONE checks his pocket watch as a glass slides off the mantle.
TITANIC_1_DVS351
He opens a clock on the mantle and adjusts the time.
TITANIC_1_DVS352
He shuts the clock then leans against the mantle gazing downward.
TITANIC_1_DVS353
An elderly couple lies in bed as water streams beneath them.
TITANIC_1_DVS354
The man kisses the woman. A red-haired woman leans over two young children lying in a bed.
TITANIC_1_DVS355
The children sleep.
TITANIC_1_DVS356
Elsewhere, a Degas painting of a woman wearing a long tutu floats beneath water.
TITANIC_1_DVS357
On deck, people run past the band.
TITANIC_1_DVS358
Water almost completely covers one end of the ship.
TITANIC_1_DVS359
As people scramble about, SOMEONE unties the life belt on SOMEONE's body.
TITANIC_1_DVS360
People rush away from the rising water.
TITANIC_1_DVS361
The young girl in SOMEONE's arm looks around herself wide-eyed.
TITANIC_1_DVS362
People work to right the overturned lifeboat. One sailor slides down a rope.
TITANIC_1_DVS363
SOMEONE puts on the life belt as water surges around him.
TITANIC_1_DVS364
Water rushes over the listing ship causing some people to fall into the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS365
People struggle to free a lifeboat from its falls.
TITANIC_1_DVS366
SOMEONE opens a knife and cuts at a rope.
TITANIC_1_DVS367
SOMEONE hands the girl to a woman.
TITANIC_1_DVS368
People wade toward the stern as the Titanic sinks.
TITANIC_1_DVS369
SOMEONE backs away from the rushing water.
TITANIC_1_DVS370
SOMEONE and others slice at the thick ropes.
TITANIC_1_DVS371
Inside, people slip and fall near the grand staircase.
TITANIC_1_DVS372
Guggenheim wearing a top hat and formal wear sits in a chair watching with wide eyes.
TITANIC_1_DVS373
Outside, people fall into the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS374
Others run up the deck from the approaching water.
TITANIC_1_DVS375
In the wheelhouse, SOMEONE stares wide-eyed as water covers the glass windows.
TITANIC_1_DVS377
Water gushes in and engulfs him.
TITANIC_1_DVS378
Outside on one of the decks, passengers wade through waist deep water to a lifeboat in the middle of the ship.
TITANIC_1_DVS379
SOMEONE slices through the rope with his pocketknife partially freeing the boat, but causing it to tip on to its side.
TITANIC_1_DVS380
SOMEONE climbs on to the high side of the capsizing lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS381
All along the sinking ship, people struggle to hang on to railings or pull themselves onto pieces of floating SOMEONE. Several people run toward the back end of the Titanic, which is now tilted up at a slight angle.
TITANIC_1_DVS382
Some passengers hang from ropes or leap into the icy sea.
TITANIC_1_DVS383
SOMEONE and SOMEONE make their way to a railing near the rear of the ship and peer over the side.
TITANIC_1_DVS384
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's hand and leads her through the crowd. Water swamps the base of the first funnel as it sinks below the ocean's surface. Inside the ship, seawater floods the grand staircase. Passengers and crew grab on to anything they can as the water rises.
TITANIC_1_DVS385
SOMEONE climbs over a railing and helps SOMEONE climb over.
TITANIC_1_DVS386
They drop onto the deck below.
TITANIC_1_DVS387
Meanwhile inside the ship, tables and chairs batters swimming passengers. As the water rises, some are carried up the staircase while others are trapped against the ceiling of the room below.
TITANIC_1_DVS388
The ornately carved wall clock at the top of the staircase sinks beneath the churning water.
TITANIC_1_DVS389
Several windows shutter as seawater pours into the openings, the current sucks fleeing passengers back into the sinking ship.
TITANIC_1_DVS390
Wearing a life vest, SOMEONE swims pass one of the broken windows. The suction slams him against the side of the ship. But he braces himself against the window frame.
TITANIC_1_DVS391
He reaches up for a railing but slips. He turns and swims toward open water.
TITANIC_1_DVS392
Meanwhile, SOMEONE drops on to a lower deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS393
The ship's baker helps her up.
TITANIC_1_DVS394
SOMEONE and SOMEONE reunite in the crowd.
TITANIC_1_DVS395
In one of the lifeboats, SOMEONE beats off paniced passengers with an oar. Several cables holding a funnel snap and flail against the water like whips.
TITANIC_1_DVS396
SOMEONE's eyes widen as the huge funnel tips over. Swimming in the water with several others, SOMEONE looks up as the giant funnel falls on to him.
TITANIC_1_DVS397
The impact creates a wave which washes away several people. A man climbs into SOMEONE's lifeboat but SOMEONE pushes him back into the ocean.
TITANIC_1_DVS398
SOMEONE and SOMEONE continue to fight their way through the crowd which slowly funnels up another staircase.
TITANIC_1_DVS399
Inside, people cling to columns at the top of the grand staircase.
TITANIC_1_DVS400
Water gushes in through the glass skylights, sweeping people across tiled floors, or pinning them against wooden railings.
TITANIC_1_DVS401
Onrushing water surges up an empty corridor, splintering furniture and knocking doors off their hinges.
TITANIC_1_DVS402
Some people in the lifeboat behind the Titanic
TITANIC_1_DVS403
row furiously as the ship's enormous propellers rise out of the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS404
Some passengers leap off the back of the Titanic, which is now tilted up several stories above the ocean surface.
TITANIC_1_DVS405
Gripping SOMEONE's hand, SOMEONE weaves through the crowd.
TITANIC_1_DVS406
They move to a railing and watch as several passengers plunge overboard.
TITANIC_1_DVS407
SOMEONE and SOMEONE continue on, pressing past a group of people kneeling around a priest. A few dozen people tread water near the propellers, which have now risen completely out of the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS408
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE up the poop deck, which is now slanted at about a 45-degree angle. They grab onto the railing at the exact spot they first met. Water streams down the exposed propellers as they continue to tilt upward.
TITANIC_1_DVS409
Several kneeling people grab one of the priest's hand as he holds on to a capstan or rotating shaft with his other hand.
TITANIC_1_DVS410
Beside SOMEONE and SOMEONE, a woman hugs a young boy to her chest.
TITANIC_1_DVS411
Shivering, SOMEONE clings to SOMEONE as she looks down at the sinking ship. His breath smokes in the cold air.
TITANIC_1_DVS412
SOMEONE smiles. SOMEONE hugs her tight and kisses her forehead.
TITANIC_1_DVS413
Inside a submerged portion of the ship, a woman's lifeless body drifts beneath a large chandelier. Her gauzy dress billowing in the currents.
TITANIC_1_DVS414
Elsewhere, stacks of plates slide off their shelves and smash on the floor.
TITANIC_1_DVS416
A lifeboat full of people rows away from the rear of the ship, which rises several stories into the night sky.
TITANIC_1_DVS417
People slide down the slanted deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS418
SOMEONE's eyes widen as he watches people and deck chairs slide down the length of the ship, passing other people hanging on to posts or railings.
TITANIC_1_DVS419
In a cabin, a vanity mirror tilts over and smashes into a bed.
TITANIC_1_DVS420
A brunette woman slips out of a man's grasp and slides down the deck on her stomach.
TITANIC_1_DVS421
All along the Titanic, people dangle from ropes, spill from railings, or slide down into the ocean.
TITANIC_1_DVS422
Several people climb over the railing at the back of the ship.
TITANIC_1_DVS423
One man jumps and free falls into the icy water, where small groups of survivors cling to floating SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS424
Standing at the rear railing, the black-haired baker watches a falling man bounce off of one of the giant propellers and cartwheel into the sea.
TITANIC_1_DVS425
The baker pulls a flask out of his pocket and takes a drink.
TITANIC_1_DVS426
SOMEONE wraps his arms around SOMEONE as she grips on to the railing.
TITANIC_1_DVS427
Sitting beside SOMEONE in a lifeboat, SOMEONE's eyes are glassy as she watches from a distance.
TITANIC_1_DVS428
Also in a lifeboat SOMEONE turns away from the carnage and squeezes his eyes shut.
TITANIC_1_DVS429
In the engine room, a crewman reaches towards a sparking circuit breaker. A shock flings him backward.
TITANIC_1_DVS432
All along the Titanic, electric lights flicker then go out.
TITANIC_1_DVS433
As the rear of the ship continues to tilt upward, the deck boards splinter and snap.
TITANIC_1_DVS434
Blood streaming down his forehead, SOMEONE grips a side railing as it splits apart.
TITANIC_1_DVS435
Inside the ship, a ceiling collapses as several support columns fail.
TITANIC_1_DVS436
A crack opens down the side of the Titanic. Small explosion shoot flames from portholes. A pair of men slides into the widen chasm, opening in the middle of the deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS437
The mighty ship snaps in half, sending the rear of the boat plunging back toward the sea.
TITANIC_1_DVS438
The back of the Titanic slaps down on the ocean surface crushing dozens of people treading in the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS440
The impact causes water to spray up in all directions. The last of the funnels topples over as water rushes into the gap between the two sections, which are still joined at the bottom.
TITANIC_1_DVS441
As the front half of the Titanic rapidly fills with water and sinks, it pulls the back half into the air again.
TITANIC_1_DVS442
People slide and topple down the slanting deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS443
SOMEONE climbs over the railing at the back of the ship as it tips skyward rapidly.
TITANIC_1_DVS444
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE up to him.
TITANIC_1_DVS445
SOMEONE and a few other passengers manage to scramble over the railing as the ship tips completely vertical.
TITANIC_1_DVS446
Sheets of water glimmer in the moonlight as they run down the exposed hull, which rises up from the ocean like a tower.
TITANIC_1_DVS447
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie on their stomachs and stare straight down the deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS448
People dangling from railings, lose their grips and fall.
TITANIC_1_DVS449
One man bounces off a capstan before slamming into other people hanging on below,
TITANIC_1_DVS450
creating a domino effect of falling bodies.
TITANIC_1_DVS451
A blonde maid dangles from the railing near SOMEONE, who looks into the young woman's eyes as she loses her grip and falls.
TITANIC_1_DVS452
Her breath visible in the cold air, SOMEONE turns to the baker who crouches on the railing beside her.
TITANIC_1_DVS453
He returns her silent gaze.
TITANIC_1_DVS454
The entire ship sinks downward again.
TITANIC_1_DVS455
Rising air pressure blows water out of compartments and windows as they become submerged.
TITANIC_1_DVS456
The ocean roils around the ship as it sinks deeper.
TITANIC_1_DVS457
Dozens of passenger still dangle from poles or lie against railings and staircases on the vertical deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS458
SOMEONE keeps one arm wrapped around SOMEONE as they descend toward the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS459
One man slips off a pole and spins as he bounces off a railing.
TITANIC_1_DVS460
Some people behind the ship try to swim clear as the massive propellers sink below the surface.
TITANIC_1_DVS461
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold hands as they kneel beside one another.
TITANIC_1_DVS462
SOMEONE nods as the bubbling water covers the tail rudder and surges up the poop deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS463
Waves swirl around the name Titanic written across the ship in gold lettering.
TITANIC_1_DVS464
SOMEONE and SOMEONE take deep gulps of air as the tail end of the ship sinks beneath the surface.
TITANIC_1_DVS465
Underwater, SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold hands as they tumble in the jostling currents.
TITANIC_1_DVS466
The ship sinks into the murky depths and vanishes.
TITANIC_1_DVS467
SOMEONE grabs on to SOMEONE's life vest but is swept away by the turbulence.
TITANIC_1_DVS468
SOMEONE kicks to the surface and emerges amid other flailing survivors.
TITANIC_1_DVS469
For at least a quarter mile, the ocean churns with panicked swimmers.
TITANIC_1_DVS470
Two men try to grab onto a bobbing barrel which spins out of their grasps.
TITANIC_1_DVS471
SOMEONE swims through the mass of people.
TITANIC_1_DVS472
One man grabs on to SOMEONE and shoves her underwater as he tries to climb on top of her.
TITANIC_1_DVS473
SOMEONE punches the hysterical man in the face until he releases SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS474
SOMEONE tows SOMEONE by her life vest.
TITANIC_1_DVS475
They swim out of the mass of survivors.
TITANIC_1_DVS476
SOMEONE leads her to a flat piece of wood floating on the surface.
TITANIC_1_DVS477
SOMEONE pulls herself on to the elaborately carved panel.
TITANIC_1_DVS479
Tries to pull himself on to the panel as well but it tips under their combined weight.
TITANIC_1_DVS481
SOMEONE holds on to the panel as he floats in the water beside her.
TITANIC_1_DVS482
SOMEONE looks down and blinks and nods to himself.
TITANIC_1_DVS483
Lying on her stomach on the panel, SOMEONE moves toward SOMEONE and leans her forehead against his.
TITANIC_1_DVS484
Their breath is visible in the cold air. He takes her hand.
TITANIC_1_DVS485
Clinging to a nearby piece of debris, a crewman blows into a whistle.
TITANIC_1_DVS486
SOMEONE's blue lips tremble as she smiles weakly.
TITANIC_1_DVS487
Sitting in a lifeboat beside SOMEONE, SOMEONE closes her eyes.
TITANIC_1_DVS488
Furrowing her brow, SOMEONE looks around at the other people in the boat who avert their gaze.
TITANIC_1_DVS489
A young woman sobs.
TITANIC_1_DVS490
SOMEONE glares at the crewman then sits.
TITANIC_1_DVS491
Beside her, SOMEONE presses her hands over her own ears.
TITANIC_1_DVS492
Elsewhere, survivors in four lifeboats work to lash the vessels together.
TITANIC_1_DVS493
A dark-haired crewman supervising the operation glances back toward the side of the wreck.
TITANIC_1_DVS494
Still clinging to wreckage, the crewman with the whistle in his mouth floats motionless with his eyes closed.
TITANIC_1_DVS495
Swimming a few yards away, SOMEONE stares at the man then turns toward SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS496
SOMEONE's lips tremble as she stares at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS497
Ice crystal sparkle in SOMEONE's hair as he takes her hand.
TITANIC_1_DVS498
He kisses the back of her hand.
TITANIC_1_DVS499
SOMEONE smiles, then closes his eyes and winces.
TITANIC_1_DVS500
SOMEONE closes her eyes and leans her head against their entwined hands.
TITANIC_1_DVS501
As one lifeboat returns to the side of the wreck, the dark-haired crewman shines his flashlight over the SOMEONE stream water.
TITANIC_1_DVS502
Frozen bodies float in mid pieces of furniture, barrels, and other wreckage.
TITANIC_1_DVS503
Using an oar, the crewman prods several stiff corpses.
TITANIC_1_DVS504
Leaning over the front of the boat, a sailor pushes bodies out of their path as they row forward slowly.
TITANIC_1_DVS505
The crewman's flashlight beam illuminates a dead woman and infant floating in the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS506
Elsewhere in the SOMEONE field, SOMEONE lies on her back atop the floating wooden panel.
TITANIC_1_DVS507
SOMEONE floats in the sea beside her. His head and arms propped above water.
TITANIC_1_DVS508
SOMEONE sings to herself as she gazes up at the starry night sky.
TITANIC_1_DVS509
Her hair and eyebrows caked with ice,
TITANIC_1_DVS510
SOMEONE turns her head as a distant light illuminates the side of her face.
TITANIC_1_DVS511
The lifeboat passes several yards away from her.
TITANIC_1_DVS512
She shakes SOMEONE's hand.
TITANIC_1_DVS513
Smiling, SOMEONE rubs SOMEONE's arm then sits up.
TITANIC_1_DVS514
He floats motionless with his eyes closed.
TITANIC_1_DVS515
She shakes him harder, then gazes toward the lifeboat.
TITANIC_1_DVS516
Between them, the dead crewman floats with the whistle still in his mouth.
TITANIC_1_DVS517
SOMEONE's smile fades as she stares at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS518
She shakes him again.
TITANIC_1_DVS519
A tear trickles down her nose.
TITANIC_1_DVS520
Furrowing her brow, SOMEONE chokes back tears as she strokes SOMEONE's hand.
TITANIC_1_DVS521
The lifeboat rows farther away.
TITANIC_1_DVS522
SOMEONE trembles as she watches it recede.
TITANIC_1_DVS523
She lays down her head and closes her eyes.
TITANIC_1_DVS524
The light of the rescuers' flashlights grow dimmer as they move on.
TITANIC_1_DVS525
SOMEONE's eyes pop open.
TITANIC_1_DVS527
SOMEONE pries her hand out of SOMEONE's grip.
TITANIC_1_DVS528
She kisses his hand then releases him.
TITANIC_1_DVS529
SOMEONE sinks into the icy water and vanishes in the gloom.
TITANIC_1_DVS530
SOMEONE slides on her stomach to the edge of the platform then rolls into the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS531
Her breath steaming out in cloud, SOMEONE swims to the frozen crewman and pulls the whistle from his lips.
TITANIC_1_DVS532
SOMEONE continues to blow into the whistle as the rescuers shine their lights on her.
TITANIC_1_DVS533
On the research ship, the now older SOMEONE opens her eyes.
TITANIC_1_DVS534
Tears stream down SOMEONE's face.
TITANIC_1_DVS535
As dawn breaks over the ocean.
TITANIC_1_DVS536
SOMEONE sits silently in a lifeboat with other survivors.
TITANIC_1_DVS537
In another boat, a man takes a drink from a flask then passes it to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS538
Elsewhere, SOMEONE huddles against SOMEONE, who stares out to the sea with a blank expression.
TITANIC_1_DVS539
In another lifeboat, SOMEONE lies wrapped in a blanket, her face pale.
TITANIC_1_DVS542
Standing over her, the dark-haired crewman waves a green flare.
TITANIC_1_DVS543
As pink hues tinge the sky along the horizon, lifeboats row toward a waiting ship anchored amid floating icebergs.
TITANIC_1_DVS548
Nestled in her blanket, SOMEONE opens her eyes as they row up alongside the ship Carpathia.
TITANIC_1_DVS551
Later, Titanic survivors, mostly women and children, recover on one of the ship's lower decks, as nurses and crewmen flit amongst them.
TITANIC_1_DVS552
Still dressed in a tuxedo, SOMEONE walks down a staircase onto the lower deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS553
SOMEONE brushes pass the man then walks amid the survivors.
TITANIC_1_DVS555
SOMEONE sits on a bench with the blanket wrapped around her hooding her hair and head.
TITANIC_1_DVS556
She glances up at SOMEONE's back as he surveys the passengers.
TITANIC_1_DVS557
SOMEONE looks away as he turns toward her.
TITANIC_1_DVS558
She closes her eyes as SOMEONE paces behind her.
TITANIC_1_DVS559
SOMEONE peers sideways at SOMEONE as he walks away.
TITANIC_1_DVS560
Her hair wet and stringy, SOMEONE stands in pouring rain on the deck of the ship.
TITANIC_1_DVS561
She stares up at the Statue of Liberty.
TITANIC_1_DVS562
The torch and crown glowing in the night.
TITANIC_1_DVS563
A ship's crewman holding a clipboard steps up to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_1_DVS564
SOMEONE continues to stare up at the giant statue as the crewman moves on.
TITANIC_1_DVS565
SOMEONE smiles.
TITANIC_1_DVS566
On the ocean floor, the two submersible shine their lights on the Titanic's remains.
TITANIC_1_DVS567
The submersibles rise leaving the wreck in darkness.
TITANIC_1_DVS568
At the surface, crewman work to recover the submersibles.
TITANIC_1_DVS569
Standing with SOMEONE on the research ship, Brock sniffs a cigar then throws it into the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS570
Staring at Brock, SOMEONE smiles and shakes her head.
TITANIC_1_DVS571
He turns and watches lights glint off the surface of rolling waves.
TITANIC_1_DVS572
Later that night, wearing only a nightgown,
TITANIC_1_DVS573
SOMEONE walks barefoot across the desolate deck.
TITANIC_1_DVS574
Her lose white hair blows in the wind.
TITANIC_1_DVS575
Clutching her hands over her heart.
TITANIC_1_DVS576
SOMEONE walks to a railing at the back of the ship.
TITANIC_1_DVS577
She grips the railing with one hand.
TITANIC_1_DVS578
And pulls herself up onto the bottom rung.
TITANIC_1_DVS579
Smiling, she stares down into the water.
TITANIC_1_DVS580
She unclasps her left hand, revealing the Heart of the Ocean.
TITANIC_1_DVS581
The large heart-shaped blue diamond glints in the moonlight.
TITANIC_1_DVS582
On the deck of the Carpathia, young SOMEONE stands in the rain and stares at the Statue of Liberty.
TITANIC_1_DVS583
Frowning, she looks down.
TITANIC_1_DVS584
And pulls the Heart of the Ocean out of her jacket pocket.
TITANIC_1_DVS586
Back on the deck of the Keldysh, SOMEONE has the diamond necklace in her hand.
TITANIC_1_DVS587
As the necklace sinks.
TITANIC_1_DVS588
SOMEONE smiles and exhales deeply.