The sub moves forward, stirring up clouds of sediment as the second sub follows close behind.
TITANIC_2_DVS27
The brown-haired man films himself with a camcorder
TITANIC_2_DVS28
as he stares out a window at the wreck.
TITANIC_2_DVS29
The man smiles at a bearded crewmate.
TITANIC_2_DVS30
Both subs glide over the wreck and illuminate twisted metal shapes encrusted with grayish growth.
TITANIC_2_DVS31
They pass alongside upper balconies running down the side of the ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS32
The man sets down his camcorder as the subs descend toward the wreck.
TITANIC_2_DVS33
Their lights illuminate rectangular windows with panes of broken glass.
TITANIC_2_DVS34
A crewman operates a remote control with a joystick.
TITANIC_2_DVS35
Outside, a small robotic vehicle attached to a tether disengages from the sub.
TITANIC_2_DVS36
The remotely operated vehicle named SOMEONE free falls beside the wreck.
TITANIC_2_DVS37
SOMEONE enters a hole in the side of the hull and films a door with an ornate leaded glass window.
TITANIC_2_DVS38
Powered by a small propeller, SOMEONE glides past the door.
TITANIC_2_DVS39
Outside, the other sub releases a second remotely operated vehicle.
TITANIC_2_DVS40
Snoop Dog descends into an open pit in the ship's hull.
TITANIC_2_DVS41
Snoop Dog moves through an opening.
TITANIC_2_DVS42
Its bright lights illuminate a crystal chandelier still dangling from a ceiling.
TITANIC_2_DVS43
Snoop Dog glides up a corridor.
TITANIC_2_DVS44
A partially decayed boot lies on the sediment beside a pair of eyeglasses missing one lens.
TITANIC_2_DVS45
Nearby, a porcelain doll's face juts out of the silt.
TITANIC_2_DVS46
Snoop Dog's lamps shine into a bunkroom.
TITANIC_2_DVS47
A broken door lies on the floor beside a dilapidated bed frame.
TITANIC_2_DVS48
The bearded crewman stares into a visor as he pilots Snoop Dog through a doorway.
TITANIC_2_DVS49
A pale eel slithers through the water as Snoop Dog approaches an elaborately carved fireplace surround and a mantle.
TITANIC_2_DVS50
One of the robotic explorers shines its lights on the rotted remains of a grand piano.
TITANIC_2_DVS51
Snoop Dog glides into a room, the remains of a wooden bed lie collapsed on the floor.
TITANIC_2_DVS52
Another eel swims past a porcelain bathtub.
TITANIC_2_DVS53
Snoop Dog pivots toward a broken door lying in the silt.
TITANIC_2_DVS54
The bearded man grasps the two joysticks as Snoop Dog extends a pair of mechanical claws.
TITANIC_2_DVS55
Snoop Dog moves the door aside and uncovers a square object.
TITANIC_2_DVS56
The brown-haired man squints as he studies a video monitor.
TITANIC_2_DVS57
The silt settles, revealing an unopened safe.
TITANIC_2_DVS58
On the ocean surface, a research vessel outfitted with cranes plucks the submersibles out of the water.
TITANIC_2_DVS59
Men cheer as a winch raises a net holding the safe to the surface.
TITANIC_2_DVS60
The bearded SOMEONE kisses his brown-haired boss, Brock. SOMEONE uncorks a bottle of champagne and sprays everyone as a crewman opens the safe with a cutting wheel.
TITANIC_2_DVS61
A man pulls off the door, unleashing a flood of muddy water. As a cameraman films him, Brock kneels and pulls out wads of sodden papers.
TITANIC_2_DVS62
He removes a muddy ledger which he tosses aside.
TITANIC_2_DVS63
Brow furrowed, he empties the safe.
TITANIC_2_DVS64
Scowling at the safe, Brock stands.
TITANIC_2_DVS65
Later, Brock takes a phone call.
TITANIC_2_DVS66
Nearby, lab techs clean the muddy papers, revealing a sketch of a woman.
TITANIC_2_DVS67
Reclining on a settee, the naked woman wears a large pendant around her neck.
TITANIC_2_DVS68
Brock studies a photograph of a pendant necklace with a heart-shaped gem.
TITANIC_2_DVS69
The same necklace the woman in the drawing is wearing.
TITANIC_2_DVS70
A date at the bottom of the sketch reads April 14th, 1912.
TITANIC_2_DVS71
Elsewhere, in a home, a young, long-haired woman walks past a small dog
TITANIC_2_DVS72
as she carries teacups to a table.
TITANIC_2_DVS73
In an adjoining sunroom, a white-haired woman uses a pottery wheel.
TITANIC_2_DVS74
Leaning on a cane, the older woman steps toward a small television set in a nearby kitchen.
TITANIC_2_DVS75
Brock stands on the research ship's deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS76
Brock uses a satellite phone.
TITANIC_2_DVS77
Holding the small, white dog on her lap, SOMEONE and the young woman ride inside a helicopter as it flies out to the research ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS78
Brock and SOMEONE move to a railing as the helicopter approaches.
TITANIC_2_DVS79
They wait on the perimeter of the landing pad as the helicopter touches down.
TITANIC_2_DVS81
Crewmen unload several suitcases and a large trunk.
TITANIC_2_DVS82
Two men set SOMEONE, who sits in a wheelchair on the deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS83
SOMEONE shakes Brock's hand.
TITANIC_2_DVS84
The longhaired woman smiles and pushes SOMEONE away in her wheelchair. A man aboard the helicopter hands a fish bowl to Brock.
TITANIC_2_DVS85
Later, SOMEONE sets framed photographs beside the fish bowl.
TITANIC_2_DVS86
In the lab, SOMEONE peers down at the clean sketch which rests in a container of clear liquid.
TITANIC_2_DVS87
She closes her eyes.
TITANIC_2_DVS88
A blond man with a few stray locks over his eyes sketches the drawing.
TITANIC_2_DVS89
SOMEONE smiles as she picks up a silver hand mirror.
TITANIC_2_DVS90
SOMEONE turns the mirror in her hands, catching her own reflection in the cracked glass.
TITANIC_2_DVS91
She sets down the mirror and examines other objects.
TITANIC_2_DVS92
She picks up a silver and glass hair comb adorned with an ornamental insect with outstretched wings.
TITANIC_2_DVS93
SOMEONE gulps as she stares at the comb.
TITANIC_2_DVS94
SOMEONE kneels beside her.
TITANIC_2_DVS95
SOMEONE nods.
TITANIC_2_DVS96
Later, a computer animation of the Titanic striking an iceberg.
TITANIC_2_DVS97
SOMEONE stands behind her grandmother as SOMEONE climbs out of her wheelchair.
TITANIC_2_DVS98
The crew watches SOMEONE as she shuffles to a video monitor displaying footage of the Titanic wreck.
TITANIC_2_DVS100
Blinks and inhales sharply as the door with the ornate leaded glass window comes into view.
TITANIC_2_DVS102
two men wearing tuxedos smile and nod as they open a pair of doors with leaded glass windows.
TITANIC_2_DVS103
On the video monitor, grayish growth covers the window's ornate scrollwork.
TITANIC_2_DVS104
SOMEONE places her hands over her mouth.
TITANIC_2_DVS105
SOMEONE turns away from the monitor and returns to her wheelchair.
TITANIC_2_DVS106
SOMEONE switches on a tape recorder as he sits across from SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS107
SOMEONE grins then nods.
TITANIC_2_DVS108
On a video monitor behind SOMEONE, the corroded Titanic wreck transforms into a gleaming ocean liner moored alongside a dock.
TITANIC_2_DVS109
Passengers walk up one of three gangplanks leading into the hull.
TITANIC_2_DVS110
On shore, a truck marked Frances Limited Southampton
TITANIC_2_DVS111
transports burlap sacks through a throng of people.
TITANIC_2_DVS112
Men and women toting suitcases make their way to the Titanic.
TITANIC_2_DVS113
A nearby warehouse bears the name White Star. A crane loads an antique car onto the ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS114
Elsewhere, on the dock, a uniformed official standing beside a sign, Health Officer, directs the crowd.
TITANIC_2_DVS115
Sitting in her father's arms, a young brunette girl watches a fleet of gleaming automobiles arrive.
TITANIC_2_DVS116
A chauffeur wearing a tweed uniform and black leather gloves steps out of the driver's seat and opens the car's back door.
TITANIC_2_DVS117
He takes a woman's gloved hand as she steps out of the car.
TITANIC_2_DVS118
The brown-haired woman who wears a white dress with thin, black stripes and a large brimmed hat
TITANIC_2_DVS119
gazes up at the enormous ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS120
A black-haired man wearing a bowler hat and gray suit steps out behind her.
TITANIC_2_DVS121
The man hands over money.
TITANIC_2_DVS122
The man checks his pocket watch then steps to SOMEONE and her mother.
TITANIC_2_DVS123
SOMEONE follows her fiance, SOMEONE Hockley, through the crowd.
TITANIC_2_DVS124
A health inspector runs a comb through a man's dark hair and beard.
TITANIC_2_DVS125
SOMEONE strides ahead of SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they walk up a gangplank.
TITANIC_2_DVS126
Inside a saloon with a view of the Titanic, men smoke and drink as they play a game of cards.
TITANIC_2_DVS127
A brown-haired card player turns to a man beside him. Subtitles.
TITANIC_2_DVS128
You moron! I can't believe you bet our tickets.
TITANIC_2_DVS129
Blond SOMEONE deals SOMEONE another card then exchanges one of his own for a card from the deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS130
Eyes narrowed, SOMEONE smokes a cigarette as he peers across the table to SOMEONE's partner.
TITANIC_2_DVS131
Several silver coins, a pocket knife, a pocket watch,
TITANIC_2_DVS132
and a pair of third class tickets for the Titanic rest in the middle of the table.
TITANIC_2_DVS133
A black-haired man raps his knuckles on the table.
TITANIC_2_DVS134
SOMEONE lays down his cards.
TITANIC_2_DVS135
SOMEONE snatches the tickets and dances.
TITANIC_2_DVS136
As SOMEONE sweeps up the coins, SOMEONE grabs his collar.
TITANIC_2_DVS137
SOMEONE closes his eyes as SOMEONE makes a fist, but SOMEONE punches SOMEONE instead.
TITANIC_2_DVS138
SOMEONE kisses the tickets and hugs SOMEONE as SOMEONE throttles SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS139
SOMEONE quickly sweeps the winnings into SOMEONE's cap. Later, the two young men run along the dock.
TITANIC_2_DVS140
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run up a gangplank.
TITANIC_2_DVS141
Carrying sacks over their shoulders, SOMEONE and SOMEONE dash into the ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS142
They run onto one of the upper decks and wave to onlookers from a railing.
TITANIC_2_DVS143
Black smoke belches from one of the Titanic's four stacks.
TITANIC_2_DVS144
Hundreds of passengers wave to the people on the dock below as tugboats pull the Titanic away from shore.
TITANIC_2_DVS145
Underwater, massive propellers turn, churning up clouds of silt.
TITANIC_2_DVS146
On the dock, a bearded man turns a crank on a movie camera as the ship glides forward.
TITANIC_2_DVS147
White seagulls appear no larger than insects as they flutter past the Titanic's massive prow.
TITANIC_2_DVS148
Four rows of portholes line the sides of the ocean liner which glides past a small two-man sailboat.
TITANIC_2_DVS149
Inside the Titanic, a brown-haired woman herds a young boy and girl up a corridor.
TITANIC_2_DVS150
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pass in the opposite direction.
TITANIC_2_DVS151
SOMEONE enters a berth.
TITANIC_2_DVS152
SOMEONE's roommates exchange puzzled looks.
TITANIC_2_DVS153
Subtitles: Where's SOMEONE?
TITANIC_2_DVS154
In her cabin, SOMEONE unpacks a painting.
TITANIC_2_DVS155
A porter carries in a pair of suitcases as SOMEONE enters from the adjoining promenade deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS156
As a porter wheels in a safe on a dolly, SOMEONE jams a bottle of champagne into an ice bucket.
TITANIC_2_DVS157
As the Titanic cruises in open water, the white-bearded captain steps up beside the first officer on deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS160
SOMEONE strides into the wheelhouse.
TITANIC_2_DVS161
Moody pulls a telegraph lever to Ahead Full. In the engine room, a needle on an identical machine moves to the same position.
TITANIC_2_DVS163
Men dash along catwalks as turning gears pump huge pistons up and down.
TITANIC_2_DVS164
The mustached foreman turns a wheel connected to several steam gauges.
TITANIC_2_DVS165
In the smoky boiler room, men covered in soot shovel coal into large furnaces.
TITANIC_2_DVS166
A needle rises on a steam pressure gauge.
TITANIC_2_DVS167
Pumping pistons move faster and faster.
TITANIC_2_DVS168
The Titanic's three propellers churn up clouds of bubbles as they spin.
TITANIC_2_DVS169
Water foams white around the ship's prow as it slices through the ocean.
TITANIC_2_DVS170
On deck, SOMEONE and SOMEONE run to the prow and lean against the railing.
TITANIC_2_DVS171
Wind ruffles their hair as they lean forward and stare straight down from the front of the ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS172
Several yards behind them, Captain SOMEONE stands on the uppermost deck outside the pilothouse.
TITANIC_2_DVS173
1st Officer SOMEONE steps up beside him.
TITANIC_2_DVS174
The captain glances at him and grins.
TITANIC_2_DVS175
On the prow, SOMEONE points towards something below.
TITANIC_2_DVS176
A dolphin swims ahead of the ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS177
Other dolphins join the first one.
TITANIC_2_DVS178
The dolphins zoom through the clear water like zigzagging torpedoes.
TITANIC_2_DVS179
One dolphin leaps out of the water.
TITANIC_2_DVS180
SOMEONE smiles as he gazes down at the dolphins. Behind them, a crewmember hands a teacup to Captain SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS181
He sips his drink while gazing out to sea.
TITANIC_2_DVS182
In the boiler room, men dump wheelbarrows of coal beside stokers who shovel the fuel into furnaces.
TITANIC_2_DVS183
An engineer leans over a railing as massive pistons pump on either side of him.
TITANIC_2_DVS184
Grabbing on to a cable, SOMEONE stands on the railing at the ship's prow.
TITANIC_2_DVS185
SOMEONE raises his arms over his head.
TITANIC_2_DVS186
With his arms spread, SOMEONE tilts his head back and closes his eyes as the enormous ship surges across the ocean.
TITANIC_2_DVS187
Meanwhile, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE lunch with several guests, including SOMEONE Brown and a brown-haired man with a mustache.
TITANIC_2_DVS188
SOMEONE stiffens as SOMEONE lights a cigarette in a holder.
TITANIC_2_DVS189
SOMEONE inhales then blows the smoke in her mother's direction.
TITANIC_2_DVS190
SOMEONE snatches the cigarette and stubs it out.
TITANIC_2_DVS191
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS192
SOMEONE stands and leaves the table.
TITANIC_2_DVS193
On deck, the young brunette girl stands on a railing as her father grips her from behind.
TITANIC_2_DVS194
Sitting a few feet away, SOMEONE sketches them with a stick of charcoal.
TITANIC_2_DVS195
Crewmen walk dogs on leashes.
TITANIC_2_DVS196
The brown-haired Irishman extends his hand to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS197
SOMEONE gazes across the ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS198
SOMEONE steps to a railing on an upper deck behind SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS199
SOMEONE turns and glances at her, then grins at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS200
SOMEONE stares up at SOMEONE. She glances in his direction, then looks away.
TITANIC_2_DVS201
She peeks toward him from the corner of her eyes.
TITANIC_2_DVS202
SOMEONE waves his hand in front of SOMEONE's face.
TITANIC_2_DVS203
SOMEONE steps up behind SOMEONE and grabs her arm.
TITANIC_2_DVS204
They exchange words and SOMEONE strides off.
TITANIC_2_DVS205
SOMEONE rolls his eyes and trails after her.
TITANIC_2_DVS207
Wearing a ruby-colored evening gown, SOMEONE shoves past other passengers as she runs down a deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS208
SOMEONE opens a gate, then dashes down a lower deck leading to the rear of the ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS209
Meanwhile, SOMEONE lies on a bench and smokes a cigarette as he gazes up at the starry sky.
TITANIC_2_DVS210
He sits up as SOMEONE runs past.
TITANIC_2_DVS211
Tears streaming down her face, SOMEONE runs onto the poop deck at the rear of the ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS212
She glances over her shoulder, then steps toward the railing.
TITANIC_2_DVS213
She gazes down at the churning waters of the ship's wake.
TITANIC_2_DVS214
Slowly, she places her hands on the railing then climbs onto its first rung.
TITANIC_2_DVS215
Holding on to a flagpole, she swings her feet over the railing one at a time,
TITANIC_2_DVS216
then lowers herself onto the gunwale.
TITANIC_2_DVS217
Gripping the railing for support, SOMEONE turns and faces the water.
TITANIC_2_DVS218
The wind whips her curly, auburn hair around her face.
TITANIC_2_DVS219
She leans forward over the ocean.
TITANIC_2_DVS220
SOMEONE creeps up behind her.
TITANIC_2_DVS221
SOMEONE stops a few paces from her.
TITANIC_2_DVS222
He takes a last puff on his cigarette, then leans forward and tosses it off the ship.
TITANIC_2_DVS223
He places his hands into his pockets and turns to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS224
SOMEONE removes his coat.
TITANIC_2_DVS225
He unlaces his boots and pulls them off.
TITANIC_2_DVS226
SOMEONE stares down at the water, then studies SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS227
He takes off his vest.
TITANIC_2_DVS228
SOMEONE reaches out his hand.
TITANIC_2_DVS229
SOMEONE grabs his hand, then turns around on the narrow ledge
TITANIC_2_DVS231
SOMEONE stares into SOMEONE's eyes.
TITANIC_2_DVS232
SOMEONE steps on the hem of her dress and slips.
TITANIC_2_DVS233
SOMEONE grips her arms with both hands.
TITANIC_2_DVS234
He pulls SOMEONE up. She grabs for the railing but slips again.
TITANIC_2_DVS235
Three nearby sailors turn and run toward SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS236
SOMEONE grips the railing with her free hand as SOMEONE pulls her up.
TITANIC_2_DVS237
The sailors run onto the poop deck as SOMEONE wraps his arms around SOMEONE's torso and lifts her back over the railing.
TITANIC_2_DVS238
SOMEONE falls on top of SOMEONE as she spills onto the deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS239
The sailors run up to them.
TITANIC_2_DVS240
One sailor glances at SOMEONE and then at SOMEONE's torn dress.
TITANIC_2_DVS241
SOMEONE stands and places his hands into his trouser pockets.
TITANIC_2_DVS242
Later, SOMEONE sits wrapped in a blanket as men handcuff SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS243
SOMEONE glances at wide-eyed SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS244
SOMEONE rubs SOMEONE's arms.
TITANIC_2_DVS245
SOMEONE strides back to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS246
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE before leaving with SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS247
SOMEONE motions over SOMEONE's brown-haired manservant.
TITANIC_2_DVS250
He steps up to SOMEONE and holds out a cigarette case.
TITANIC_2_DVS252
SOMEONE takes two cigarettes, placing one in his mouth and other behind his left ear.
TITANIC_2_DVS254
SOMEONE looks down at his unlaced boots.
TITANIC_2_DVS258
SOMEONE looks down as the man walks off.
TITANIC_2_DVS259
In her berth, SOMEONE sits at a vanity table and holds her silver hand mirror.
TITANIC_2_DVS260
She sets down the mirror as SOMEONE opens the door.
TITANIC_2_DVS263
SOMEONE opens a box containing the Heart of the Ocean.
TITANIC_2_DVS266
He fastens the necklace with the blue heart-shaped diamond on SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS267
SOMEONE strokes the necklace as she gazes at her own reflection in the vanity mirror.
TITANIC_2_DVS269
SOMEONE kneels beside SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS270
She stares at him.
TITANIC_2_DVS271
SOMEONE smiles at the blank-faced SOMEONE,
TITANIC_2_DVS272
who blinks then turns and stares at her reflection.
TITANIC_2_DVS273
She places her right hand over the diamond.
TITANIC_2_DVS275
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk along an upper deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS306
SOMEONE hold out her engagement ring.
TITANIC_2_DVS337
SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand up and down.
TITANIC_2_DVS339
She releases his hand and walks away.
TITANIC_2_DVS347
She stares at him with her mouth open.
TITANIC_2_DVS349
She snatches SOMEONE's sketchbook.
TITANIC_2_DVS353
SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE as she flips through his drawings.
TITANIC_2_DVS355
She studies the sketch of a woman breastfeeding an infant.
TITANIC_2_DVS363
She turns to a drawing of a nude woman lying on her side with a cigarette in her mouth.
TITANIC_2_DVS364
Another sketch depicts a nude woman standing against a ballet bar.
TITANIC_2_DVS366
SOMEONE closes the sketchbook as another passenger walks past.
TITANIC_2_DVS370
Smiling, SOMEONE turns to a sketch of a nude dark-haired woman lying with one arm stretched over her head.
TITANIC_2_DVS371
Another drawing of just a pair of hands.
TITANIC_2_DVS377
SOMEONE looks down open-mouthed as SOMEONE flips to another drawing.
TITANIC_2_DVS381
A fully clothed middle-aged woman.
TITANIC_2_DVS392
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS395
Her smile fades.
TITANIC_2_DVS396
In a dining room, SOMEONE sips tea with two other women.
TITANIC_2_DVS397
SOMEONE nods at SOMEONE then strides off.
TITANIC_2_DVS398
Nearby, mustached SOMEONE sits with the captain.
TITANIC_2_DVS399
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's hand.
TITANIC_2_DVS400
He pulls her to a different section of the railing.
TITANIC_2_DVS401
SOMEONE spits.
TITANIC_2_DVS402
SOMEONE leans forward and spits.
TITANIC_2_DVS403
SOMEONE's mother and her friends stroll nearby.
TITANIC_2_DVS404
As SOMEONE steps up, SOMEONE taps SOMEONE's arm. He turns around and swallows.
TITANIC_2_DVS405
SOMEONE steps toward her mother then glances at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS406
Smiling at SOMEONE, SOMEONE points to her own chin.
TITANIC_2_DVS407
SOMEONE quickly wipes saliva off his own chin.
TITANIC_2_DVS408
SOMEONE waves as SOMEONE and her mother walk off.
TITANIC_2_DVS409
SOMEONE lifts his hands and shrugs.
TITANIC_2_DVS410
Elsewhere, SOMEONE helps SOMEONE into a black tuxedo jacket.
TITANIC_2_DVS411
SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze into a full-length mirror.
TITANIC_2_DVS412
At dusk, the Titanic trails black smoke from its four smoke stacks, the funnels, as it sails toward the setting sun.
TITANIC_2_DVS413
Later, a SOMEONE opens a door for SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS414
Wearing a white tie and shirt, SOMEONE smiles at the SOMEONE as he steps inside.
TITANIC_2_DVS415
He pauses, then walks toward an ornate railing and columns beneath the dome skylight.
TITANIC_2_DVS416
SOMEONE steps to the railing and gazes down at a couple descending the ship's grand staircase.
TITANIC_2_DVS417
SOMEONE glances up at the skylight, then walks down the staircase to a landing,
TITANIC_2_DVS418
where he studies a wall clock with an elaborately carved wooden casing.
TITANIC_2_DVS419
SOMEONE descends past a winged statue.
TITANIC_2_DVS420
Couples wearing formal evening wear stroll or stand about chatting.
TITANIC_2_DVS421
SOMEONE leans against a column, then glances at a bearded man standing erect with his left arm behind his back.
TITANIC_2_DVS422
SOMEONE stands up straight and places his own arm behind his back.
TITANIC_2_DVS423
SOMEONE nods to the man as he and a woman stroll past.
TITANIC_2_DVS424
SOMEONE watches the couple, then gazes up the staircase as SOMEONE and SOMEONE descend toward him.
TITANIC_2_DVS425
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE as they step past him.
TITANIC_2_DVS426
From the staircase's landing, SOMEONE gazes down at SOMEONE, who pretends to shake somebody's hand practicing to be a gentleman.
TITANIC_2_DVS427
He turns and looks up at SOMEONE, who wears a floor-length, black lace dress.
TITANIC_2_DVS428
She smiles and descends the stairs toward him.
TITANIC_2_DVS429
SOMEONE stops a few steps above SOMEONE, who takes her white-gloved hand and kisses it.
TITANIC_2_DVS430
SOMEONE holds out his bent right arm for SOMEONE, who takes it.
TITANIC_2_DVS431
She smiles as he tilts back his chin, nose in the air.
TITANIC_2_DVS432
Arm in arm, they stroll up to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS433
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step arm in arm toward the reception room.
TITANIC_2_DVS434
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE as they follow.
TITANIC_2_DVS435
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE descend another wide, curving staircase.
TITANIC_2_DVS436
A dark-haired woman speaking with a white-haired man.
TITANIC_2_DVS437
They gaze toward a group of people.
TITANIC_2_DVS438
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's other arm.
TITANIC_2_DVS439
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE step into the large dining room.
TITANIC_2_DVS440
Mustached Astor turns.
TITANIC_2_DVS441
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stroll through the dining room.
TITANIC_2_DVS442
They stop at their table.
TITANIC_2_DVS443
SOMEONE waves his hand.
TITANIC_2_DVS444
SOMEONE gestures across the table at SOMEONE to put his napkin in his lap. SOMEONE gazes down at an array of silverware placed on both sides of the charger holding his plate.
TITANIC_2_DVS445
The waiter spoons a dollop of black caviar onto SOMEONE's dinner plate.
TITANIC_2_DVS446
SOMEONE smiles.
TITANIC_2_DVS447
SOMEONE grins at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS448
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS449
The waiter refills SOMEONE's glass.
TITANIC_2_DVS450
SOMEONE tosses a box of matches to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS451
SOMEONE raises her glass.
TITANIC_2_DVS452
They all toast.
TITANIC_2_DVS453
SOMEONE raises his glass to SOMEONE. SOMEONE lifts his glass, frowns, and then sips.
TITANIC_2_DVS454
Later, a waiter pushes a cart laden with desserts.
TITANIC_2_DVS455
SOMEONE hands a pen to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS456
SOMEONE lobs the matches back to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS457
He slips them into his pocket, then approaches SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS458
SOMEONE smiles, stares at them.
TITANIC_2_DVS460
Kissing her hand, SOMEONE slips a note to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS461
He turns and walks off, glancing back at her over his shoulder.
TITANIC_2_DVS462
SOMEONE unfolds the note and reads it. Make it count. Meet me at the clock.
TITANIC_2_DVS465
As SOMEONE stares at her daughter, SOMEONE gazes across the room toward the door.
TITANIC_2_DVS466
Beneath the skylight, SOMEONE stands on the landing and faces the clock.
TITANIC_2_DVS467
SOMEONE steps to the bottom of the staircase.
TITANIC_2_DVS468
Lifting her dress slightly, she ascends the stairs.
TITANIC_2_DVS469
SOMEONE turns.
TITANIC_2_DVS470
On a third class deck, a man pounds a drum. Another plays a set of pipes. Two men swing each other around on a platform as couples dance. SOMEONE dances with a blond woman, Helga.
TITANIC_2_DVS471
He places his hand on her back.
TITANIC_2_DVS472
SOMEONE, now with his tie removed and sleeves rolled up, dances with SOMEONE, a little girl with dark hair.
TITANIC_2_DVS473
Some people clap their hands in time to the music.
TITANIC_2_DVS474
SOMEONE sits at a table with blond SOMEONE as SOMEONE sets down several glasses of beer.
TITANIC_2_DVS475
SOMEONE sets a beer in front of SOMEONE, who takes a sip.
TITANIC_2_DVS476
SOMEONE claps her hands as she watches SOMEONE twirl SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS477
Nearby, a man falls to the floor. Two other men help him up while another hands the man his drink.
TITANIC_2_DVS478
SOMEONE spins SOMEONE as SOMEONE and SOMEONE prance back and forth.
TITANIC_2_DVS479
SOMEONE leans toward SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS480
SOMEONE nods.
TITANIC_2_DVS481
He waves SOMEONE over.
TITANIC_2_DVS482
He grabs her hand.
TITANIC_2_DVS483
They stand on the dance floor.
TITANIC_2_DVS484
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE close. SOMEONE stands watching them. SOMEONE turns to her.
TITANIC_2_DVS485
SOMEONE smiles. SOMEONE and SOMEONE dance.
TITANIC_2_DVS486
SOMEONE and SOMEONE dance through the crowd of other dancers.
TITANIC_2_DVS487
SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb onto the platform then dance. SOMEONE and SOMEONE whirl around the room.
TITANIC_2_DVS489
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE onto the platform. He lets go of her hand then performs an intricate dance.
TITANIC_2_DVS490
Watching him, SOMEONE pulls off her shoes, tosses them to a nearby woman, then holds up the hem of her dress as she imitates the dance steps.
TITANIC_2_DVS491
SOMEONE smiles, claps his hands, then continues dancing.
TITANIC_2_DVS492
When he stops, SOMEONE dances.
TITANIC_2_DVS493
They link arms and dance in a circle.
TITANIC_2_DVS494
Other couples dance around them.
TITANIC_2_DVS495
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold hands, then face each other and spin faster and faster.
TITANIC_2_DVS496
In the smoking room, a SOMEONE lights SOMEONE's cigar.
TITANIC_2_DVS497
Others talk or smoke cigars.
TITANIC_2_DVS498
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arm wrestle as others cheer them on.
TITANIC_2_DVS499
SOMEONE steps up to their table, and reaching over SOMEONE, grabs two glasses of beer.
TITANIC_2_DVS500
He hands one glass to SOMEONE, then drinks from his own. SOMEONE watches SOMEONE gulp down most of her beer.
TITANIC_2_DVS501
A bearded man knocks into SOMEONE, who spills his beer on SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS502
SOMEONE slams SOMEONE's fist to the table top.
TITANIC_2_DVS503
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE's cigarette from his mouth.
TITANIC_2_DVS504
SOMEONE puffs on it.
TITANIC_2_DVS505
She blows out smoke, then hands SOMEONE the hem of her skirt.
TITANIC_2_DVS506
As SOMEONE hold on to her dress, SOMEONE slowly lifts her heels and rises onto her toes.
TITANIC_2_DVS507
SOMEONE gazes down as SOMEONE stands on her tiptoes.
TITANIC_2_DVS508
SOMEONE grimaces
TITANIC_2_DVS509
and collapses into SOMEONE's arms.
TITANIC_2_DVS510
SOMEONE's manservant, SOMEONE, descends halfway down a staircase and peers around the room.
TITANIC_2_DVS511
He spies SOMEONE holding SOMEONE in his arms.
TITANIC_2_DVS512
Couples hold hands as they dance in a line through the crowded room. SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's hand and she grabs SOMEONE's.
TITANIC_2_DVS513
The line of dancers snakes through the clapping, drinking crowd.
TITANIC_2_DVS514
The next day, SOMEONE and SOMEONE eat breakfast at a table in the private promenade.
TITANIC_2_DVS515
SOMEONE shakes his head.
TITANIC_2_DVS516
As SOMEONE stirs her coffee, she and SOMEONE exchange glances.
TITANIC_2_DVS517
SOMEONE stands and flips over their dining table.
TITANIC_2_DVS518
SOMEONE walks away.
TITANIC_2_DVS519
As he steps through the doorway, an aproned woman rushes over to SOMEONE, then bends and picks up dishes.
TITANIC_2_DVS520
SOMEONE crouches to help.
TITANIC_2_DVS521
SOMEONE lays her hand on dark-haired SOMEONE's shoulder, then sinks against her chair.
TITANIC_2_DVS522
Later, in SOMEONE's room, SOMEONE laces up the back of SOMEONE's corset.
TITANIC_2_DVS523
Her mother steps in.
TITANIC_2_DVS524
SOMEONE curtsies and steps out.
TITANIC_2_DVS525
SOMEONE walks to SOMEONE and ties the laces of her corset.
TITANIC_2_DVS526
Turning her head, SOMEONE covers her mouth.
TITANIC_2_DVS527
She closes her eyes, exhales, and drops her hand.
TITANIC_2_DVS528
Turns back to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS529
SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE, then reaches out her hands.
TITANIC_2_DVS530
Gently cradling SOMEONE's face, SOMEONE kisses her cheek.
TITANIC_2_DVS532
She turns SOMEONE back around, then continues lacing the corset.
TITANIC_2_DVS533
SOMEONE grimaces as SOMEONE tightens the laces.
TITANIC_2_DVS534
In the dining room, a man plays piano as first class passengers holding sheet music sing.
TITANIC_2_DVS535
SOMEONE stands between SOMEONE and her mother.
TITANIC_2_DVS536
SOMEONE descends the grand staircase.
TITANIC_2_DVS537
One hand in his pocket, SOMEONE strolls toward the dining room where two stewards stand outside its doors.
TITANIC_2_DVS538
One SOMEONE wearing a dark suit steps in front of SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS539
Inside, SOMEONE steps toward the door.
TITANIC_2_DVS540
SOMEONE emerges.
TITANIC_2_DVS541
SOMEONE hands the money to the SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS542
The two stewards escort SOMEONE away.
TITANIC_2_DVS543
On the bridge, a crewman steps up to the captain.
TITANIC_2_DVS544
Captain SOMEONE reads a note, then smiles at SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS545
Outside, SOMEONE climbs a railing, then hops on to a deck where a boy wearing a cap winds a string around a top.
TITANIC_2_DVS546
The boy spins the top on the deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS547
SOMEONE steps toward another railing, pauses, and picks up a black bowler hat and long coat from a chair.
TITANIC_2_DVS548
Donning the hat, SOMEONE wets his fingers and plasters down his hair.
TITANIC_2_DVS549
Wearing the hat and coat, SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's arm. They hurry through a door into a gymnasium.
TITANIC_2_DVS550
SOMEONE places his hand on SOMEONE's cheek.
TITANIC_2_DVS551
SOMEONE places her gloved hand over his.
TITANIC_2_DVS552
She steps outside.
TITANIC_2_DVS553
SOMEONE watches her leave through wavy window glass, then gazes downward.
TITANIC_2_DVS554
Later, in the first class lounge, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, the countess, and another woman drink tea.
TITANIC_2_DVS555
SOMEONE gazes toward another table where a woman pulls a slouching young girl upright.
TITANIC_2_DVS556
SOMEONE watches as the girl places a napkin on her lap with her small, gloved hands.
TITANIC_2_DVS557
As the Titanic cuts through the water, SOMEONE leans on a railing at the bow and stares into the sea.
TITANIC_2_DVS558
Wind ruffles his hair.
TITANIC_2_DVS559
SOMEONE steps across the deck toward him.
TITANIC_2_DVS560
He turns and faces her.
TITANIC_2_DVS561
SOMEONE smiles.
TITANIC_2_DVS562
SOMEONE walks toward him.
TITANIC_2_DVS563
SOMEONE reaches out.
TITANIC_2_DVS564
They hold hands.
TITANIC_2_DVS565
SOMEONE gently pulls her toward himself.
TITANIC_2_DVS566
SOMEONE closes her eyes.
TITANIC_2_DVS567
Grasping her hand, SOMEONE helps SOMEONE onto the bow rail platform.
TITANIC_2_DVS568
They both step onto the lowest rung of the railing.
TITANIC_2_DVS569
Standing behind her, SOMEONE lifts SOMEONE's hands from the railing then holds her arms out like wings.
TITANIC_2_DVS570
Wind blows her shawl back from her outstretched arms.
TITANIC_2_DVS571
He places his hands around her waist as she opens her eyes.
TITANIC_2_DVS572
Black smoke trails from the ship's funnels as SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand at the bow high above the water.
TITANIC_2_DVS573
SOMEONE reaches out and grasps SOMEONE's hands, then leans his face close to hers.
TITANIC_2_DVS574
Their fingers intertwine.
TITANIC_2_DVS575
SOMEONE folds SOMEONE's arms around her waist.
TITANIC_2_DVS576
She turns her face to him.
TITANIC_2_DVS578
SOMEONE places her hand on the back of SOMEONE's neck.
TITANIC_2_DVS579
The sunken Titanic sits on the bottom of the ocean.
TITANIC_2_DVS580
The elderly SOMEONE turns from the monitor and addresses the crew of the salvage vessel.
TITANIC_2_DVS581
SOMEONE gazes back at the monitor which shows the underwater image of the fireplace in her former suite.
TITANIC_2_DVS583
The room transforms into its former state, as young SOMEONE and SOMEONE step inside.
TITANIC_2_DVS584
SOMEONE rushes toward a painting.
TITANIC_2_DVS585
SOMEONE opens the safe.
TITANIC_2_DVS586
SOMEONE hands the Heart of the Ocean necklace to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS587
SOMEONE shakes his head as he examines the faceted blue diamond.
TITANIC_2_DVS588
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS589
Later, SOMEONE removes the butterfly comb from her hair
TITANIC_2_DVS590
and shakes out her hair which falls to her shoulders.
TITANIC_2_DVS591
SOMEONE drags a settee to the center of the room,
TITANIC_2_DVS592
places one pillow atop another.
TITANIC_2_DVS593
Sitting in a chair near the settee.
TITANIC_2_DVS594
SOMEONE opens a canvas bag
TITANIC_2_DVS596
and a thin stick of charcoal which he sharpens.
TITANIC_2_DVS597
SOMEONE looks up as SOMEONE steps into the room.
TITANIC_2_DVS598
Holding a kimono close with one hand, SOMEONE lifts a sash and twirls it.
TITANIC_2_DVS600
SOMEONE smiles.
TITANIC_2_DVS601
SOMEONE steps toward SOMEONE. He sits back.
TITANIC_2_DVS602
She tosses a dime to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS603
SOMEONE steps backward, then slips the kimono from her shoulders.
TITANIC_2_DVS604
The kimono slides to the floor.
TITANIC_2_DVS605
Naked, SOMEONE runs her fingertips over her own thigh.
TITANIC_2_DVS606
SOMEONE points toward the settee.
TITANIC_2_DVS607
SOMEONE steps to the settee.
TITANIC_2_DVS608
Then stretches out on settee, SOMEONE drapes one arm along the back of the settee.
TITANIC_2_DVS609
SOMEONE lays her hand on the pillow behind her head.
TITANIC_2_DVS610
She places her right hand near her temple.
TITANIC_2_DVS611
Smiling, SOMEONE lowers her head.
TITANIC_2_DVS612
SOMEONE licks her lips.
TITANIC_2_DVS613
SOMEONE peers over the top of his sketchpad, then draws a line.
TITANIC_2_DVS614
Looking from the paper to SOMEONE, he sketches.
TITANIC_2_DVS615
SOMEONE grins as he draws.
TITANIC_2_DVS616
He runs his charcoal across the paper, creating faint arcs.
TITANIC_2_DVS618
He jerks his head to toss his hair out of his eyes.
TITANIC_2_DVS619
He adds details as he flushes out the sketch.
TITANIC_2_DVS620
Smiles as he darkens a shadow under SOMEONE's breasts.
TITANIC_2_DVS621
SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE as he draws.
TITANIC_2_DVS623
With his finger, he rubs various parts of the charcoal drawing SOMEONE's hand, forehead, and face.
TITANIC_2_DVS625
SOMEONE stares expressionless.
TITANIC_2_DVS626
Gradually, wrinkles form around her eyes
TITANIC_2_DVS627
and she transforms into her older self.
TITANIC_2_DVS628
The crewmembers and SOMEONE's granddaughter, SOMEONE, stare at her.
TITANIC_2_DVS629
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange smiles.
TITANIC_2_DVS630
SOMEONE signs and dates the drawing, then blows on it.
TITANIC_2_DVS631
He closes his sketchbook and hands it to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS633
Later, SOMEONE writes on a sheet of paper.
TITANIC_2_DVS634
SOMEONE steps up to her.
TITANIC_2_DVS635
She hands him the case holding the Heart of the Ocean.
TITANIC_2_DVS636
SOMEONE walks into the next room and slides the case into the safe.
TITANIC_2_DVS637
In the first class smoking room, SOMEONE approaches Cal, who stands.
TITANIC_2_DVS638
Nighttime. The Titanic moves slowly across dark water.
TITANIC_2_DVS639
On the bridge, the helmsman turns the ship's wheel as the ship's officer steps up to Captain SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS640
Captain SOMEONE looks down as he stirs a slice of lemon in his tea.
TITANIC_2_DVS641
The captain walks off.
TITANIC_2_DVS642
Meanwhile, SOMEONE gazes out on open window along the private promenade.
TITANIC_2_DVS643
Stepping back into SOMEONE's suite, he blows on his hands.
TITANIC_2_DVS644
Wearing an evening dress, SOMEONE joins him.
TITANIC_2_DVS645
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS646
She pulls him through the sitting room toward a door.
TITANIC_2_DVS647
SOMEONE steps into the suite.
TITANIC_2_DVS648
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hurry into SOMEONE's bedroom.
TITANIC_2_DVS649
SOMEONE closes the door.
TITANIC_2_DVS650
SOMEONE strides through the sitting room.
TITANIC_2_DVS651
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step through another door into a corridor.
TITANIC_2_DVS652
SOMEONE bursts into another room.
TITANIC_2_DVS653
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hurry down the corridor.
TITANIC_2_DVS654
SOMEONE opens a door and glimpses SOMEONE and SOMEONE, who walk faster.
TITANIC_2_DVS655
SOMEONE follows them.
TITANIC_2_DVS656
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run to an elevator.
TITANIC_2_DVS657
The dash into the elevator. The operator slides the grate shut.
TITANIC_2_DVS658
SOMEONE runs up to the elevator and slams his hands against the grate.
TITANIC_2_DVS659
As the elevator descends, SOMEONE glares through glass at them.
TITANIC_2_DVS660
SOMEONE raises her middle finger then waves.
TITANIC_2_DVS661
SOMEONE hurries to the staircase.
TITANIC_2_DVS662
The elevator opens and SOMEONE and SOMEONE spill out, almost running into a SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS663
SOMEONE runs down a staircase as SOMEONE and SOMEONE scramble from the bottom of a different staircase.
TITANIC_2_DVS664
SOMEONE bumps into a food cart. He and SOMEONE run through swinging doors into a white corridor, then stop.
TITANIC_2_DVS665
SOMEONE runs up to the elevator, then scans the area around himself.
TITANIC_2_DVS666
SOMEONE peers in a door's round window.
TITANIC_2_DVS667
SOMEONE and SOMEONE rush down the corridor.
TITANIC_2_DVS668
They turn a corner and stop at a closed door.
TITANIC_2_DVS669
SOMEONE opens a different door. They step inside as SOMEONE turns the corner and tries to open the door. Inside, SOMEONE holds her hands to her ears. SOMEONE peers down a ladder at rising smoke.
TITANIC_2_DVS670
In the boiler room, men shovel coal into the furnaces. Near them, SOMEONE helps SOMEONE down the ladder.
TITANIC_2_DVS671
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run through the smoky boiler room past men shoveling coal.
TITANIC_2_DVS672
One man turns to watch them run past. SOMEONE and SOMEONE run through drifting smoke.
TITANIC_2_DVS673
A metal door opens. SOMEONE and SOMEONE step through it and into the cargo hold.
TITANIC_2_DVS674
They look around themselves as they walk past crates and stacks of boxes.
TITANIC_2_DVS675
Leading SOMEONE by the hand, SOMEONE hurries around a stack of crates, then stops at a gleaming black car.
TITANIC_2_DVS676
He lets go of SOMEONE's hand, then peers inside the car.
TITANIC_2_DVS677
SOMEONE steps around SOMEONE to the passenger door.
TITANIC_2_DVS678
He holds out his hand and opens the door.
TITANIC_2_DVS679
SOMEONE takes his hand and steps up into the passenger compartment.
TITANIC_2_DVS680
SOMEONE shuts his door.
TITANIC_2_DVS681
As SOMEONE glances around herself, SOMEONE steps into the open-sided driver seat.
TITANIC_2_DVS683
SOMEONE pulls down a glass partition.
TITANIC_2_DVS684
SOMEONE reaches over SOMEONE's shoulders, then pulls him into the passenger compartment.
TITANIC_2_DVS685
Sitting on the seat, SOMEONE puts his arm around SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS686
They gaze into each other's eyes as they interlock their fingers.
TITANIC_2_DVS687
SOMEONE lays her head on SOMEONE's shoulder, then kisses his fingertips.
TITANIC_2_DVS688
She places SOMEONE's hand on her breast.
TITANIC_2_DVS690
The Titanic leaves a long wake in the dark ocean.
TITANIC_2_DVS691
Two sailors stand in a metal crow's nest attached to a mast high above the deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS692
Murdoch, with his collar up, peers over the railing outside the wheelhouse.
TITANIC_2_DVS693
In the back seat of the car, SOMEONE slaps her hand against the back window,
TITANIC_2_DVS694
her hand against the back window,then slowly slides it downward.
TITANIC_2_DVS696
Naked and his face dripping with sweat, SOMEONE lies on top of SOMEONE. He breathes heavily as they gaze at each other.
TITANIC_2_DVS698
SOMEONE strokes SOMEONE's hair, then kisses his forehead. He lays his head on her chest.
TITANIC_2_DVS700
In the boiler room, two stewards with flashlights step down a short corridor and into the cargo hold.
TITANIC_2_DVS701
SOMEONE opens the safe. He pulls out a note and SOMEONE's portfolio.
TITANIC_2_DVS702
SOMEONE approaches. SOMEONE opens the portfolio and studies the drawing of SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS703
He reads the note.
TITANIC_2_DVS704
Darling, now you can keep us both locked in your safe. SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS705
SOMEONE's forehead tenses as he closes then opens his eyes.
TITANIC_2_DVS706
He glances at the note again.
TITANIC_2_DVS707
In the hold, the two stewards creep toward the car.
TITANIC_2_DVS708
One SOMEONE shines his flashlight in the car's steamed up windows.
TITANIC_2_DVS709
He snaps his fingers and points to the car,
TITANIC_2_DVS710
then yanks open the car door, revealing empty seats.
TITANIC_2_DVS711
Smiling, SOMEONE and SOMEONE run onto the forward well deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS712
SOMEONE places her hand on SOMEONE's lips and gazes at him.
TITANIC_2_DVS714
Standing at the bridge rail, SOMEONE glances down at them, smiles, and walks off.
TITANIC_2_DVS715
Watching from the crow's nest, another man, Fleet, looks down and taps his comrade Lee on the arm.
TITANIC_2_DVS716
They stare down at SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS717
The men turn and gaze past the ship. Their eyes widen as a large iceberg looms straight ahead.
TITANIC_2_DVS718
Fleet rings the lookout bell three times, then grabs a telephone which rings on the bridge.
TITANIC_2_DVS719
The quartermaster at the wheel glances back at the phone.
TITANIC_2_DVS720
Officer Moody steps onto the bridge and answers the phone.
TITANIC_2_DVS721
Moody hangs up and turns to SOMEONE as he runs to the bridge door.
TITANIC_2_DVS722
Quartermaster SOMEONE turns the wheel to the left. SOMEONE rushes over to the engine room telegraph and shifts the handle to full speed astern.
TITANIC_2_DVS723
SOMEONE turns the wheel quickly. In the engine room, the chief engineer spots the telegraph shift and drops a pot of steaming soup.
TITANIC_2_DVS724
SOMEONE turns the wheel until it stops.
TITANIC_2_DVS725
SOMEONE hurries to the bridge rail and peers at the iceberg. In the engine room, an engineer yells.
TITANIC_2_DVS726
Other engineers scurry around.
TITANIC_2_DVS727
A red warning light flashes.
TITANIC_2_DVS728
Engineers slam the furnace dampers shut. The needle on the steam pressure gauge drops.
TITANIC_2_DVS729
Underwater, the ship's main propeller slows.
TITANIC_2_DVS730
The main propeller stops.
TITANIC_2_DVS731
An engineer pulls down a thick lever. All the propellers stop.
TITANIC_2_DVS732
An officer pushes an engineer out of the way and turns a wheel quickly to the right.
TITANIC_2_DVS733
The propellers spin in the opposite direction.
TITANIC_2_DVS734
In the crow's nest, the men stare at the iceberg as the ships heads straight toward it.
TITANIC_2_DVS735
SOMEONE stares at the iceberg.
TITANIC_2_DVS736
Nearing the iceberg, the ship veers slowly to the left.
TITANIC_2_DVS737
The ship's propellers turn in reverse.
TITANIC_2_DVS738
Sweat trickles down SOMEONE's temples.
TITANIC_2_DVS739
The ship's bow shifts to the left of the iceberg. At the bow railing, a man runs toward the bridge.
TITANIC_2_DVS740
The ship's hull scrapes along the side of the iceberg. On the forward well deck, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stop kissing as the ship trembles. On the bridge deck, SOMEONE glances down at his hands resting on the shaking rail. Above, Fleet holds on to the rim of the crow's nest while Lee sits on the floor.
TITANIC_2_DVS741
In the bridge, SOMEONE keeps the wheel turned hard left. Below deck, SOMEONE sits up in his bunk.
TITANIC_2_DVS742
In the cargo hold, water shoots through a long tear in the hull as it rips open. In his cabin, SOMEONE sits at his desk.
TITANIC_2_DVS743
He glances up at the trembling crystal chandelier above.
TITANIC_2_DVS744
In the crow's nest, Fleet and Lee gaze at the iceberg. On the bridge deck, SOMEONE yells to SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS745
SOMEONE turns the wheel to the right. Meanwhile, water floods the cargo hold, knocking down the two stewards. On the front well deck, SOMEONE pushes SOMEONE behind him as the ship breaks up chunks of ice which land on the deck and knock down two men. The ship continues moving alongside the iceberg.
TITANIC_2_DVS746
In the engine room, water pours in as a man scrambles past furnace stokers swept across the floor.
TITANIC_2_DVS747
SOMEONE runs to the starboard railing and watches as the back of the ship moves alongside the iceberg. SOMEONE runs to the bridge and moves a lever which closes the hydraulic watertight doors in the engine room.
TITANIC_2_DVS748
A man motions to the stokers.
TITANIC_2_DVS749
Workers run through the rising water and crawl under the lowering doors.
TITANIC_2_DVS750
He follows the others through one of the doorways. The door closes, leaving several stokers behind. As the others escape past closing doors, the remaining stoker dives under the last closing door and crawls out as its steel hatch slams shut.
TITANIC_2_DVS751
On the bridge, a row of lights blinks on the watertight door indicator panel. SOMEONE stares at the panel, then turns away.
TITANIC_2_DVS752
On the passenger deck, a man and a woman lean over the starboard rail and peer at the iceberg.
TITANIC_2_DVS753
In the crow's nest, Fleet turns to Lee.
TITANIC_2_DVS754
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the two men peer over the railing at the iceberg now behind the ship. On the bridge, SOMEONE addresses Moody.
TITANIC_2_DVS755
Moody glances at a wall clock as he exits. SOMEONE turns to the bridge door as Captain SOMEONE enters.
TITANIC_2_DVS756
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE onto the bridge deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS757
SOMEONE peers down from the bridge deck shelter, then stands at the bridge railing overlooking the front well deck.
TITANIC_2_DVS758
SOMEONE hurries off. In his cabin, SOMEONE jumps down from his bunk into inch-deep water and turns on the overhead light.
TITANIC_2_DVS759
His roommates follow as he opens the door.
TITANIC_2_DVS760
SOMEONE approaches.
TITANIC_2_DVS761
The countess steps out of her stateroom and stops a mustached SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS762
SOMEONE hurries past, carrying blueprints.
TITANIC_2_DVS763
Outside, smoke rises from the ship's huge funnels as people gather on the decks.
TITANIC_2_DVS764
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and others follow running rats down a hallway.
TITANIC_2_DVS765
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step out of the sitting room and stop a dark-haired SOMEONE in the hallway.
TITANIC_2_DVS766
The SOMEONE hurries off. On the upper deck, a dark-haired man tosses a blond man a chunk of ice.
TITANIC_2_DVS767
He tosses the ice back.
TITANIC_2_DVS768
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE pass SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
TITANIC_2_DVS769
The Master at Arms studies SOMEONE's drawings.
TITANIC_2_DVS770
SOMEONE snatches the drawings from him.