Now outside, SOMEONE kicks over a trashcan.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS21
Sitting on a nearby bench, the nerd looks over.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS22
The jock slumps down on a bench on the other side of two columns.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS23
With tearful eyes he notices the awkward teen watching him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS24
Tucking his longhair behind his ear, SOMEONE leaves.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS25
The nerd wipes his own tears and stands.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS26
He gives the trashcan a kick then grabs his aching leg.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS27
Words appear. Seven years later.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS28
His close cropped hair now caramel brown.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS29
The nerd enters the Metropolitan City Police Academy wearing a blue uniform and takes his place in a registration line.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS30
Ahead in line, SOMEONE now sporting a buzz cut spots him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS31
The former nerd musters a courteous nod. Now students spar in a hand-to-hand combat class.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS32
SOMEONE lifts the former nerd.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS33
He slams him down on the mat and raises his fist.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS34
In another class SOMEONE gets an F on a test.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS35
He notices SOMEONE's test which boasts a perfect score.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS36
On an obstacle course, SOMEONE finishes a tire run then roots for SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS37
Now SOMEONE tutors him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS38
Now by SOMEONE's bed, SOMEONE shoots him with a toy gun. Then lifts his mattress, dumping him off.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS39
Later he drags SOMEONE through a jog.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS40
In a training course cutout targets swing out at them and they shoot.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS41
The oddly matched recruits cover each other.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS42
As SOMEONE finishes the tire run
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS43
the teacher gives a thumbs up.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS44
In class, SOMEONE gets a test back and pumps his fist.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS46
He proudly shows his score, a C-.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS47
They bump fists. At graduation.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS48
SOMEONE smirks and SOMEONE beams.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS49
Now partners, they patrol a tranquil public park on bicycles.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS50
With teens at a pond.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS51
SOMEONE fishes it from the water.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS52
He hurls it back.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS53
Later he beats SOMEONE at red-hands. Now they flip their guns.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS54
A boy defiantly holds out torn bread.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS55
SOMEONE stares ahead.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS56
He sees a biker gang.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS57
They pass a joint around.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS58
SOMEONE struts off.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS59
Now the partners furiously pedal their bicycles across a green lawn.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS60
Little red and blue lights twinkle on their handlebars.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS61
Reaching their destination, they climb off their bikes and lower their kickstands.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS62
The rookies approach the biker gang.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS63
SOMEONE smacks the joint from the leader's hand.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS64
The bikers scatter.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS65
SOMEONE gets on his bike.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS66
SOMEONE chases the leader on foot.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS67
A fat bearded biker crosses the bridge.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS68
SOMEONE rides after him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS70
Pulling out in front of the bearded bikers, SOMEONE gets off his bike and draws his gun.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS71
Elsewhere, SOMEONE vaults off a post and tackles the leader.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS73
The biker knocks him over and runs off.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS74
With the gang leader.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS75
Straddling the leader's rear, SOMEONE humps him as he cuffs him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS76
SOMEONE leaps into SOMEONE's arms and the athletic cop swings his partner around. They face the gang leader.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS77
As SOMEONE pretends to hump him SOMEONE kneels by his face.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS78
Nearby young families gawk with horrified expressions.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS79
SOMEONE fires his gun skyward and the families flee.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS80
Later, they strut into a police station passing two hookers.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS82
In an office, The Deputy Chief flicks the cut.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS83
Now outside an abandoned church.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS84
SOMEONE parks a faded hatchback at the curb. Getting out with him, SOMEONE reads a sign at the entrance printed in Korean and English.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS85
He leads his partner through the front gate.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS86
Stickers on its mailbox spell out 21 Jump Street.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS87
Stepping inside.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS88
The uniform cops walk through a storage area and enter a small chapel.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS89
Where youthful looking cops in street clothes lounge in the pews.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS90
A woman with long blonde hair turns. So does an Asian woman with bleached hair.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS91
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in the rear pew.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS92
An older African-American police officer wearing a badge on one hip
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS93
and a gun on the other steps out to the pulpit and scowls at them.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS94
SOMEONE nods meekly.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS95
He spreads his hands in a dramatic shrug.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS96
He points out SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS98
Now in the headquarters make-shift bullpen.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS99
The Captain eyes SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS101
An online video.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS102
He shows drugs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS103
A colorful title card appears on the video. Phase One: The Gigs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS104
The teens laughs uncontrollably.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS105
Another title.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS106
Phase Two: Tripping Major Ballsack.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS107
The teen stares into the camera with a stunned expression.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS108
Phase Three.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS109
Over Falsity of Confidence.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS110
He plays an acoustic guitar while blowing a harmonica attached to a neck rack.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS111
Phase Four: Fuck Yeah, Motherfucker.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS112
The teen dances, rips the clothes from his closet, trashes a piano keyboard and then leans close to the camera.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS113
The Captain glares at SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS114
The Captain slaps the desk.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS115
Later, as SOMEONE walks through the bullpen the lights cut out.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS116
Passing the chapels few remaining pews he approaches the alter
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS117
where a statue depicts Jesus reaching from the cross.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS118
A dove in his outstretched hand.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS119
SOMEONE kneels.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS120
Behind him SOMEONE bites his fist and doubles over with laughter. The Captain opens his office window.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS121
Now outside a home.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS122
SOMEONE eyes a wall of his childhood portraits.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS123
SOMEONE picks up a vase.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS124
She answers the door.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS126
In the morning, SOMEONE and SOMEONE wake to find SOMEONE's father using an elliptical machine at their feet.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS127
Later they shave.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS128
Now the pickup bagged lunches with the names SOMEONE and Doug written in quotes.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS129
SOMEONE eyes his shoulders.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS130
They go outside.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS131
SOMEONE eyes his hatchback.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS132
Now, at a police impound a female officer walks them to a 1970s Camaro.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS133
Now in the driver's seat SOMEONE revs the engine.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS134
He drives toward SOMEONE who nimbly rolls over the hood and lands safely on the ground.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS135
SOMEONE runs back to him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS136
As SOMEONE drives at him, SOMEONE slams up on the hood, then slides to the pavement.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS137
His partner rushes out to him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS138
SOMEONE sprawls, unmoving.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS139
Now, the Camaro pulls into a high school parking lot bustling with teens.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS140
They pull into a handicapped spot.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS141
In slow motion the undercover cops get out and sling their backpacks over one shoulder.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS142
They notice every student around them wearing their backpacks strapped to both shoulders.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS143
One teen sneers.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS144
He eyes black clad teens.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS145
He spots scrawny awkward kids.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS146
He notices teens in Rockabilly clothes.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS147
Other girls wear kooky Harajuku fashions.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS148
Looking head SOMEONE stares. In slow-motion a fresh-faced blonde with a sunny smile rides a bicycle through the quad.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS149
She arrives before a handsome boy.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS150
He kisses her, then sees the newcomers.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS151
SOMEONE punches him in the face.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS152
A crowd gathers.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS153
With the principal.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS154
SOMEONE nods.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS155
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS157
Now in a drama class.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS158
SOMEONE leans toward the pretty blonde.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS159
She directs his gaze to the back of a chair.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS160
Next to a sticker depicting poop with a halo, a hand-scrawled arrow points to a phone number.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS161
He sends a text to the number. Looking for hook-up.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS163
In a chemistry class. The red-haired teacher beams.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS164
The red-haired teacher and other students clap.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS165
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS166
SOMEONE gives a perplexed shake of the head.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS167
Subtitles, French: The Language of Love.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS168
The teacher arrives.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS169
She gives him a quiz and winks flirtatiously.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS170
Her gaze lingers on him as she steps away.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS171
In drama, SOMEONE stands on a small stage facing the class.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS172
He sways nervously and takes a deep breath as a keyboardist struggles to cue him in.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS173
Smirking, SOMEONE tilts her head.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS174
SOMEONE digs for his phone.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS175
A text, meet at yearbook. Five minutes.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS177
Taking the quiz SOMEONE reads a question.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS178
He sees the multiple choice answers as, you're an idiot. No I'm not. Yeah you are dumbass. Fuck you quiz.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS179
He circles the remaining answers at random then steps up behind the teacher to turn in his quiz.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS180
SOMEONE gets a text from SOMEONE reading, hallway now.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS181
She smiles coquettishly.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS182
Now the two cops run down a hall.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS183
Now they enter a darkened classroom with the window blinds drawn.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS184
Stacks of old computers and other equipment fill the room.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS185
Moving further inside the two undercover cops find the handsome, sensitive teen
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS186
working alone at a computer.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS187
A pencil case holds wafers depicting the haloed poop logo.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS188
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE who nods.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS189
They each take a wafer sealed in a baggie.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS190
The click the wafers together as if in a toast then pop them in their mouths.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS191
Now they rush into a toilet stall.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS192
They gag themselves.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS193
They jam their fingers into each other's mouths and gag each other.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS194
An elderly janitor shuffling past pauses and looks on.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS195
As the undercover cops gag each other again, the janitor turns and wearily shuffles away.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS196
In the hall they encounter a coach.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS197
He takes SOMEONE's.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS198
The coach eyes SOMEONE's physique.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS199
SOMEONE raises his hand.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS200
The couch swats at his reaching hand.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS201
SOMEONE laughs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS202
Phase One: The Gigs. SOMEONE and SOMEONE laugh uncontrollably.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS204
SOMEONE gives a spastic nod. Our view rapidly switches between the two giggling cops.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS205
Phase Two: Tripping Major Ballsack.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS206
The cops stare.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS207
The coach's eyebrows crawl down his face and form a mustache.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS208
SOMEONE sees a robotic furry kitty head on the coach's shoulders.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS209
SOMEONE blows on the coach.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS210
The coach's head becomes an ice cream cone.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS211
As the ice cream melts, SOMEONE sticks his tongue out.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS212
SOMEONE curls his tongue.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS213
The coach starts to give the pass back, then pauses.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS214
As the undercover cops shake their heads, a rapid series of explosive and disturbing images fill our view.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS215
In chemistry class. He writes and writes on the board.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS216
board covered with number 4.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS217
He struts off.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS218
Phase Three: Over Falsity of Confidence. Now, SOMEONE bursts into drama. He pushes an auditioning kid off stage.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS219
He signals to the keyboardist then struts and twirls proudly across the small stage.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS220
SOMEONE smiles.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS221
SOMEONE applauds delightedly. The drama teacher approaches SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS222
He extends a hand, but SOMEONE pinches his face.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS223
Phase Four: Fuck Yeah, Motherfucker.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS225
SOMEONE run into a school band practice and trips over free-standing cymbals.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS226
He smacks a cymbal with his hand.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS228
Lined up to start, SOMEONE boogies.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS229
In the band room SOMEONE does Kung Fu moves with a cymbal in each hand.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS230
Well ahead of the others SOMEONE's teammate arrives and hands him the baton.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS231
SOMEONE watches.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS232
SOMEONE gets distracted by the others and slows.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS233
He bats the batons out of their hands.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS234
SOMEONE hurls the baton over the finish line and skips back and forth.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS235
In the band room, SOMEONE spikes a trumpet.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS236
He dives headfirst through a gong's ring stand.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS237
On the tracks, SOMEONE holds the baton to his thrusting hips like a penis. The coach tries to take it away but he keeps his hips
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS240
Now, SOMEONE sleeps in a school fountain.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS241
Phase Five: A Sleepiness
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS243
SOMEONE sprawls across the track.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS244
Now SOMEONE, the dealer, and two friends pass SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS245
As they go, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE delightedly.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS246
Now at headquarters, they show a perp chart.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS247
Now at school, SOMEONE arrives at a classroom door colorfully labeled Science. He tries the handle then pounds on its frosted window.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS248
As the door starts to open he forces his way in.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS249
At the far end of the chemistry classroom SOMEONE sits with two other nerds.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS250
SOMEONE sits down on a stool in front of SOMEONE, who tinkers with several cell phones. The other nerds go back to their game.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS251
SOMEONE winks at him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS252
Grinning, SOMEONE winks and shrugs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS254
Now in his old room, SOMEONE nervously taps a cordless phone against his palm, then makes a call.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS255
In her bedroom, SOMEONE answers her cell.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS256
SOMEONE covers a laugh. SOMEONE grimaces.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS257
SOMEONE's smile freezes.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS258
SOMEONE comes in.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS259
He pounces on SOMEONE playfully.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS260
He sits on his head.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS261
SOMEONE kicks him away.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS262
SOMEONE pounds SOMEONE's crotch with a stuffed giraffe's head.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS263
SOMEONE dry humps SOMEONE with a full duffle bag.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS264
SOMEONE smiles at her phone.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS265
Now in his office, the Captain slowly chews a sandwich in his hands.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS266
Holding SOMEONE and SOMEONE in a disapproving glare he points at them accusingly.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS267
Now, SOMEONE's parents leave the house.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS268
Later, SOMEONE adds a picture to the wall of photos.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS269
They high five. Later they run from a liquor store with carts full of beer and booze. Now they make punch.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS270
At the police station SOMEONE enters an evidence locker while SOMEONE keeps lookout.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS271
Back at home, chips fill a bowl. A hand peels the evidence sticker off the pot.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS272
The cops put a compost sign in a trash can, then set up a keg.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS273
A CD reads, Brads Super Awesome Party Mix. The lights dim and a colorful spinning globe switches on.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS274
They each do a shot. SOMEONE spits his out.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS275
Now SOMEONE and his partner open the door to find the nerds on their stoop.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS276
SOMEONE high fives them as they enter.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS277
Two teens struggle to operate the keg.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS278
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive. One of the nerds uses Ms. SOMEONE's Sedona vase for drinks.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS279
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE an enthusiastic hug.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS280
SOMEONE faces the nerds.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS281
A nerd knocks him into SOMEONE and SOMEONE swipes the dealer's phone.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS282
He passes it off to the nerds and follows.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS284
The nerds dismantle SOMEONE's phones.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS285
SOMEONE chokes on punch.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS286
In the hall, they open the door.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS287
They walk in on a two girls, one guy three-way with one woman thrusting in back.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS288
They go downstairs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS289
Listening, SOMEONE bursts back in on the nerds, hitting SOMEONE with the door.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS290
Downstairs three tough looking teens enter and strut toward SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS291
SOMEONE sneers at him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS292
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS293
SOMEONE dances up in his face.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS294
He takes off his shirt.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS295
SOMEONE punches him in the gut.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS296
SOMEONE rushes downstairs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS297
SOMEONE hits SOMEONE as SOMEONE fights his friends.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS298
As SOMEONE and the two teen thugs trade expert fighting moves, SOMEONE twirls his hand stylistically.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS299
SOMEONE's punch lands on SOMEONE's boob.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS300
She slaps him. SOMEONE tackles SOMEONE onto a couch.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS301
The cop defends himself with a throw pillow.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS302
His flailing foot kicks SOMEONE's groin.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS303
As SOMEONE's fight moves to the kitchen, SOMEONE chases SOMEONE around the living room.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS304
As SOMEONE punches out a thug, SOMEONE backs SOMEONE to the mantel where the Sedona vase rests.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS305
SOMEONE smashes it over SOMEONE's head. The thug collapses on his living room rug.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS306
SOMEONE and the partygoers rally around SOMEONE. The nerds come downstairs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS307
SOMEONE beckons them over, takes the pilfered phone and slips it back in SOMEONE's pocket.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS308
SOMEONE turns, revealing an ornate South-western knife handle sticking out of his back.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS309
SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE cheer with the others. In their mini-van SOMEONE's parents smoke pot.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS310
At home, SOMEONE bites down on a whole lemon.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS311
SOMEONE pulls the bloody blade from SOMEONE's back and SOMEONE pours vodka on the wound.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS312
She duct tapes a bandage on over his shirt.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS313
He swigs vodka from the bottle.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS314
Later, as people dance, SOMEONE chats with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS315
A hot blonde drinks liquor out of SOMEONE's navel while SOMEONE cheers.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS316
One of SOMEONE's friends discreetly passes over an HFS wafer. Another teen passes SOMEONE a joint and he takes a hit.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS317
Now, SOMEONE makes out with a brunette.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS318
SOMEONE and SOMEONE dance holding SOMEONE's naked childhood portrait between their hips.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS319
SOMEONE lifts up SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS320
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap uneasy looks as SOMEONE does a weird humping dance with the nerd.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS322
SOMEONE pinches his own nipples and makes them dance.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS323
SOMEONE holds SOMEONE's embarrassing portrait above the crowd.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS324
SOMEONE and SOMEONE laugh as they dance together.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS325
Outside, his parents pull up.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS326
SOMEONE storms into the house and stares.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS327
The teens from the three-way join the panicked stampede.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS328
SOMEONE and SOMEONE flee with the teens.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS329
She chases them with a stick.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS330
Running down the street with SOMEONE, SOMEONE slows to a halt.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS331
SOMEONE arrives as they bump fists.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS332
As SOMEONE heads off, SOMEONE grins at SOMEONE and pumps his fists.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS333
Later, SOMEONE holds SOMEONE's now defaced childhood portrait.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS334
Now at the police firing range, the two cops shoot at a cutout depicting a gunman using a woman as a human shield.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS335
SOMEONE cocks his head, then turns away.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS337
Now, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in the yearbook room.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS338
SOMEONE sends him off with a paper bag.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS339
Later, HFS wafers dump out on the Captain’s desk.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS340
As SOMEONE stands by glumly, the Captain hands SOMEONE a role of cash then sips his coffee peevishly. SOMEONE takes the cash to SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS341
They move off together revealing a left behind SOMEONE. Now in the chemistry classroom.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS342
SOMEONE and the third nerd, a red-haired kid slap hands then have an imaginary light saber duel.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS343
SOMEONE pretends to slice off his enemies arm.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS344
Outside they pour chemicals into a plastic bottle set on an overturned chair and desk set.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS345
Then run to a safe distance. The bottle explodes.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS346
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE deface a police car. SOMEONE sends SOMEONE a message featuring a woman in a slutty Peter Pan costume. It reads, "My Peter Pan Costume. Too revealing?" SOMEONE responds, "Try something manlier," and includes a photo of a man in green spandex with a giant fake penis. Now in a show store.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS347
SOMEONE spots them.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS348
She waves from across the store.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS349
He goes to meet her.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS350
As SOMEONE and his friends watch, SOMEONE mouths, "This woman's crazy."
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS352
He pinches her lips together.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS353
He shoves SOMEONE into a shoe display.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS354
SOMEONE hustles the teens out of the store. In the school parking lot, SOMEONE waits by the Camaro in the handicapped spot.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS355
A few tickets stick up from the windshield wiper.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS356
He receives a text from SOMEONE. "Don't wait up. Out with Eric".
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS358
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE pass a huge pool on their way to a chic modern home.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS359
SOMEONE comes out with another girl and greets SOMEONE with a big hug.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS360
SOMEONE gives her a kiss but she pulls away and hugs him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS361
Now in a humble house, the three nerds play music as SOMEONE arrives with energy drinks.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS362
On his patio SOMEONE plays guitar.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS363
With the nerds.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS365
In the house a phone lights up.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS367
They listen eagerly. Now SOMEONE wanders into the house with the beer.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS368
He spots a laptop on a desk and opens it.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS369
Bringing up an email account he finds several messages from cooldeets88.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS370
Including one titled, New Supply Just in Bro.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS371
SOMEONE and the nerds listen in on SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS372
SOMEONE sits close to SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS373
SOMEONE whips throwing stars at a Zod poster.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS374
She gazes at him with doe-like eyes. SOMEONE remembers asking out Melody in high school.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS375
SOMEONE smiles warmly.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS376
As she gazes into his eyes, SOMEONE's grin fades.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS377
Her expression tender, SOMEONE leans her lips toward his.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS378
He shakes her hand.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS379
SOMEONE and the others come in and sit around them.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS380
SOMEONE turns it off.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS381
He flings a throwing star into the Zod posters face. Now at his desk in the bullpen SOMEONE laughs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS382
Sitting tensely behind him SOMEONE opens his desk drawer, then slams it.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS383
SOMEONE and her partner come in.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS385
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in the Captain’s office.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS386
SOMEONE and the Captain stare.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS387
Later, SOMEONE follows his partner out of the church.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS388
They reach their car.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS389
Now in a theater dressing room SOMEONE curls her hair into ringlets.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS390
SOMEONE wears his Peter Pan costume.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS391
As he poses playfully, SOMEONE approaches.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS392
She tenderly fastens his collar.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS393
Now, SOMEONE stands before his chemistry classmates.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS394
He wears a decorated hoodies.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS395
He glances nervously at Ms. SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS396
The window behind her shows SOMEONE and his black gay friend furtively carrying a piñata.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS397
In the dressing room.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS398
Outside, SOMEONE and his friend drive off.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS399
SOMEONE slides over the Camaros hood then gets in with his partner. He starts the engine. The revving vintage car starts to backup then lurches to a halt.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS401
It sports a boot.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS402
SOMEONE turns.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS403
They rush to the student Driver's car.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS404
They ignore the instructor and get in behind the twin steering wheels.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS405
Now, SOMEONE's maroon sedan arrives at a highway underpass where the biker gang, the One-Percenter's awaits the young dealer and his friend.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS406
Near a rusted out wreck across the lot
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS407
The Driver's Ed car rolls to a stop.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS408
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch the deal go down.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS409
The dealer's handover the piñata.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS410
The guys duck. SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE's head toward his lap.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS411
One by one the bikers ride off on their choppers.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS412
As the last of the bikers rides off, SOMEONE rises from SOMEONE's lap.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS413
At a stoplight, the gang leader idles at the front of the pack. The Driver's Ed car pulls up behind them.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS414
SOMEONE steps on the brake and the car stops short again.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS415
SOMEONE stomps the accelerator, then hammer fists his groin.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS416
As SOMEONE recoils, the car rams the bearded biker's rear tire. Knocking him onto the hood.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS417
He rips the student driver sign off the roof and bashes it over the hood.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS418
As he jumps up and down on the hood his cohorts get off their bikes and watch. SOMEONE observes an instruction card, before you drive fasten seatbelt, check mirrors, hands on ten and two.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS419
The car peels out dropping the biker and knocking over the motorcycles.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS420
They blow through a red light.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS421
The bikers get back on the motorcycles and speed after them.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS422
The leader weaves through traffic with the piñata strapped to his sissy bar.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS423
The bikers gain on them.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS424
They slap at each other’s hands.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS425
Heading up a clogged freeway onramp they jam the breaks, stopping an inch shy of a station wagon full of kids.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS426
SOMEONE flees.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS427
SOMEONE spots him running away.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS428
SOMEONE catches up with him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS429
He spots a sports car.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS430
SOMEONE head-butts the driver.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS431
SOMEONE pulls him out then gets behind the wheel. A light turns green and he speeds on to the freeway.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS433
A biker pulls out a handgun and takes aim. Using a tennis racket, SOMEONE hits a golf ball into his head. The biker wipes out into a truck, busting open its side gate and spilling flammable propane tanks onto the pavement.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS434
One breaks open, spewing gas.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS435
Back at the school auditorium.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS437
they jump out and run on foot.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS438
SOMEONE gets a text from SOMEONE, "Where the hell are you?"
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS439
SOMEONE replies, "I'll be there fairy soon." Followed by emoticons.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS440
SOMEONE leaps over the top of a stopped car.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS441
He pulls the driver out.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS442
They drive off in her pink Volkswagen Beetle toward a bridge.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS443
As the Beetle rides up alongside a tanker truck, one of the bikers gains on them.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS444
The vehicles reach the center of the bridge over a river.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS445
SOMEONE tosses out a sunshade which wraps around the biker's face.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS446
Firing wildly he shoots holes through the tanker.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS447
He overtakes the rig and falls off his bike.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS448
The truck runs over his legs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS449
The tanker slows to a stop gushing oil and fuel as sparks fly from the tumbling motorcycle.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS450
We dramatically zoom back from the tanker ad glide above the truss bridge.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS451
Yielding a silver revolver, the gang leader pulls up alongside the Beetle and shoots out the driver side window.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS452
SOMEONE swerves into another traffic lane.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS453
SOMEONE finds a four-shot pistol.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS454
He glances at his partner. The gang leader cuts off a sedan and rides up alongside them again.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS455
SOMEONE aims out the driver side window.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS456
The gang leader takes aim. SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's pistol and pulls the trigger himself. The piñata bursts.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS458
As the gang leader swerves, a truck hauling chickens blocks his path.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS459
He wipes out and his bike slides underneath the vehicle.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS460
The truck explodes and chicken feathers fly into the Beetle.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS461
The return to Sagan High and SOMEONE parks crookedly in a space.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS462
SOMEONE runs off.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS463
In the auditorium the audience watches SOMEONE perform with the understudy.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS464
SOMEONE runs on stage.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS465
He takes flying harness ropes off French and hooks them to his own costume.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS466
SOMEONE sneaks past stagehands. As SOMEONE rises off of the stage SOMEONE falls of a fake boulder and grabs on to his dangling partner.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS467
The stagehands struggle with the ropes.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS468
They swing before the crowd.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS469
SOMEONE falls hard on a fake boulder then tumbles on to the stage.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS470
Upside down, SOMEONE swings past SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS471
The stagehands lose control of the ropes and SOMEONE crashes. SOMEONE and SOMEONE get to their feet.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS472
As SOMEONE charges, SOMEONE leaps over him with the aid of the stagehands working the lines. SOMEONE picks up one of the fake boulders and chucks it at his partner.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS473
He leaps straight up then dangles over the stage with SOMEONE clinging to his leg.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS474
He throws glitter in SOMEONE's eyes. The stagehands drop them.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS475
As they wrestle, the principal enters the auditorium with the drama teacher. They hurry on stage and break up the fight.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS476
The coach laughs over a girls shoulder as he munches on Doritos.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS477
SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a disheartened gaze.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS478
In the audience SOMEONE applauds over his head.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS479
As the curtains close SOMEONE paws at SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS482
Jump Street.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS483
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in the Captain's office. The goateed man glares at each of them. His hands folded over a desk full of paperwork.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS484
SOMEONE glances at his partner.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS486
Beside SOMEONE, SOMEONE lowers his sad gaze.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS488
Playing foosball, the others watch the pair clear out their desks.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS489
Outside, SOMEONE and SOMEONE part ways.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS490
Each carrying a cardboard box.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS491
In her bedroom SOMEONE picks up her vibrating cell phone and sees an incoming call from Doug.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS492
In his own room, SOMEONE holds a phone to his ear.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS493
SOMEONE tosses her cell on a dresser ignoring the call.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS495
SOMEONE hangs up, sitting alone on a weightlifting bench.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS497
SOMEONE carries a box to his car’s open hatchback. Inside, SOMEONE sits at a laptop.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS498
His mother looks out the window then shuts the laptop and gives her son a stern look.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS499
Loading the hatchback, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE ambling across the front lawn.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS501
He tosses in a final bag as he ex-partner meets him by the car.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS502
Staring at SOMEONE, SOMEONE shuts the hatchback.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS504
SOMEONE starts to go but turns back.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS505
SOMEONE shifts his frustrated gaze. As SOMEONE turns to leave, SOMEONE arrives in his maroon sedan accompanied by his dark haired friend.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS506
Later, in a rundown alley SOMEONE leads the pair away from his car.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS507
His cohort hangs back.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS508
He hands them each one gun.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS509
SOMEONE and SOMEONE trade a look.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS510
SOMEONE eyes them desperately.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS511
The partners take aim.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS512
With expert precision they shoot up old bottles and cans on the tailgate of a rundown pickup.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS513
SOMEONE joins them, slack jawed.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS515
Now in SOMEONE's room.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS516
They stand over weapons and ammo neatly laid out on the bed.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS517
SOMEONE straps on a white bullet proof vest, then dons a tuxedo shirt and buttons the cuffs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS518
SOMEONE buttons a black satin vest over his shirt.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS519
SOMEONE loads a clip.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS520
SOMEONE pumps a shotgun.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS521
Wearing shoulder holsters, they ready their handguns.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS522
Outside, SOMEONE takes out the trash while SOMEONE mows the front lawn.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS523
Inside, SOMEONE grabs a set of handcuffs. Then tucks a gun behind his back.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS524
SOMEONE prepares shotgun shells.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS525
They conceal weapons strapped to their ankles.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS526
SOMEONE clips the shotgun to the back of his partner's shoulder holster.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS528
each man readies themselves at a mirror.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS529
As SOMEONE struggles with his bowtie SOMEONE notices.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS530
SOMEONE fixes his partner’s bowtie.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS531
He returns to his mirror.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS532
SOMEONE returns to his mirror.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS533
Then notices the hanging shotgun clipped to the back of his partners holster.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS534
He removes the weapon.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS535
SOMEONE watches him set it on the counter.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS536
Each man faces his mirror with a pensive gaze.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS537
SOMEONE regards his partner
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS538
The boyish young man shifts his humbled gaze.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS539
Now, in slow motion the door of a white limousine opens, releasing doves. SOMEONE steps out wearing a white tuxedo with black lapels, vest and tie.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS540
SOMEONE follows in matching attire holding a cardboard box marked Doves. SOMEONE steps out wearing a top hat, followed by SOMEONE and the red-haired nerd.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS541
Cinnamon and her prostitute friends join the geeks.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS542
As the teen strides past two valets, SOMEONE tosses the box in the air.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS543
Inside, a sign adorned with a lit up cactus and sombreros reads, One Night in Tijuana.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS544
SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter a ballroom filled with celebrating students.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS545
A tattooed DJ presides over the dance floor. Ms. SOMEONE ends a chat with a colleague and approaches SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS546
She smacks him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS547
She leaves and he shakes his head.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS548
On the dance floor SOMEONE sways to the music, dancing alone.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS549
SOMEONE joins her.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS550
He covers his face with his hands.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS551
SOMEONE watches them go.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS552
Now SOMEONE leads SOMEONE and SOMEONE out of an elevator and down the hotel hall.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS553
The teenager opens the doors of a suit to reveal Coach SOMEONE who sits with a few piñatas, watching TV and eating Cool Ranch Doritos.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS554
In a bathroom stall.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS555
The hookers help the nerds conduct surveillance.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS556
SOMEONE fake punches SOMEONE's abs.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS557
He lunges tauntingly at SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS558
He opens the door to reveal the One-Percenter's leader the bearded biker and the swarthy Hispanic biker.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS559
As a few others follow, SOMEONE and SOMEONE keep a low profile.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS560
He hands a bag to the bearded thug.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS561
A long-haired biker eats peanut butter from a jar.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS562
The cops reluctantly turn.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS563
The bikers stare at them.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS564
In his eye patch, the leader points at SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS565
SOMEONE gulps fearfully.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS566
Phase Four: Fuck Yeah, Motherfucker.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS567
SOMEONE pistol whips SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS568
The bikers aim guns at SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS569
SOMEONE barges in knocking SOMEONE aside.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS570
SOMEONE grabs her.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS571
SOMEONE goes limp.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS572
The cops obey.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS573
The long-haired thug aims at the guys.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS574
SOMEONE gives a sneering nod.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS575
He turns and aims his gun. He takes off his sunglasses.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS576
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pull off disguises.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS577
SOMEONE eyes the rookies.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS578
SOMEONE drags SOMEONE into a kitchen and hides behind the counter.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS579
A bullet tears through SOMEONE's neck. SOMEONE holds a smoking gun.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS580
As the bikers and DEA agents launch into a gunfight, SOMEONE takes more bullets. SOMEONE dives behind a couch.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS581
SOMEONE starts to follow.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS582
He runs around it. SOMEONE scrambles into the kitchen.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS583
The bikers riddle the DEA agents with bullet holes and they collapse side by side.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS584
In the bathroom stall, the red-haired nerd grabs his headphones.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS585
As the bikers reload, SOMEONE opens fire. SOMEONE peeks out from the kitchen.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS586
He grabs the biker's bag.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS587
He thrusts it at SOMEONE. SOMEONE leans out from behind the couch and shoots expertly.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS588
SOMEONE keeps his eyes squeamishly shut and fires upward.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS590
SOMEONE and SOMEONE bleed out.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS591
SOMEONE listens in. SOMEONE fires then rolls behind the couch and faces his partner.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS592
Behind the couch SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a look.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS593
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie dead on the floor,
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS594
SOMEONE urges SOMEONE to scram and takes SOMEONE with them.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS595
Now, SOMEONE peeks out and SOMEONE fires. His shot shatters a flat screen showing SOMEONE Wen as SOMEONE on the TV show.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS596
Now, SOMEONE notices the money bag gone and SOMEONE leaving.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS597
In slow motion, SOMEONE rises and leaps over the couch.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS598
Piñata confetti flurries around him as he dives sideways, shooting a mohawked biker in the chest.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS599
The thug collapses.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS600
Behind SOMEONE, SOMEONE climbs over the couch.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS601
He falls clumsily out of view.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS602
Getting up, he aims his gun at a departing biker with a topknot braid.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS604
Puckering his lips squeamishly, He throws the gun instead.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS605
It hits the base of the biker's neck and he turns.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS607
As he takes aim at SOMEONE, SOMEONE rises from the floor.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS608
He shoots the biker multiple times in the chest.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS609
The thug lurches back.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS610
His braid twirling as he twists around and falls.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS611
His gaze steely, SOMEONE lowers his gun. The cops step on SOMEONE's discarded fake nose as they races from the sweet.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS612
SOMEONE vomits on him.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS613
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE exit an elevator.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS614
Now a slideshow of snapshots holds the attention of sentimental prom guests.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS615
SOMEONE and SOMEONE start through the crowd.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS616
The coach hauls SOMEONE, slung over his shoulder.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS617
SOMEONE, SOMEONE and the swarthy biker follow.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS618
A photo of SOMEONE and SOMEONE, aka SOMEONE and Doug,
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS619
Pops up as the two cops reach the dancefloor.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS620
SOMEONE notices, then dashes with his partner into the hotel kitchen.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS621
They sprint across the deserted room.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS622
Outside they see SOMEONE speed off in a silver stretch limo.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS623
She's in back with SOMEONE. SOMEONE shoots at the cops then gets in a black stretch limo.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS624
SOMEONE and SOMEONE return fire.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS625
As the gang limo leaves, the undercover cops race into the lot.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS626
SOMEONE slides across a white limo's hood.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS627
As SOMEONE makes a hard right in his limo, SOMEONE lops over.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS628
The bikers black limo follows and the cops white limo brings up the rear.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS629
A drunk brunette wakes in the back.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS630
SOMEONE shoots at his pursuers from the silver limo. SOMEONE weeps.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS631
As SOMEONE peeks through the sunroof, SOMEONE rises through his.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS632
SOMEONE ducks back down.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS634
In the white limo, SOMEONE shoots the champagne bottle in her grip. SOMEONE yanks SOMEONE down.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS635
SOMEONE stands in the sunroof and shoots. SOMEONE fires at him and the silver limo.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS636
SOMEONE bats at SOMEONE who tries to unzip his fly.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS637
As SOMEONE expertly weaves the limo through traffic his partner leans down to face SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS638
SOMEONE resumes the gunfight. The silver and black limos swerve between lane barriers and speed through oncoming traffic.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS639
They veer back into the flow.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS640
Following them into an alley, the white limo stops. SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE out.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS641
SOMEONE wrenches the wheel, taking the limo back to the main road.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS642
He puts gunpowder from the shells and two lithium batteries from SOMEONE's digital camera in a liquor bottle. He stands in the sunroof and makes a perfect quarterback pass. Spiraling, the bottle drops through SOMEONE's sunroof.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS643
Meanwhile SOMEONE sideswipes a parked car. As SOMEONE comes to, a busted hydrant spouts water.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS645
The black limo explodes and rolls into a fuel tank. A second blast flips it like a tiddlywink.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS646
As the white limo halts, SOMEONE gets out of the stalled silver one and grabs SOMEONE by the arm.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS647
The cops leave their car passing a charred corpse.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS648
They aim their guns at the corrupt coach.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS649
As SOMEONE draws, SOMEONE pulls his trigger.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS650
He uses SOMEONE as a human shield.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS651
SOMEONE blithers in the car.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS652
As he drags her off, SOMEONE pleads.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS653
The coach fires at SOMEONE but SOMEONE dives between them taking the hits.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS654
Shoulder bleeding, SOMEONE reveals the other shot mashed into his bullet proof vest. SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS655
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE and steadies his aim.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS656
A helicopter hovers overhead.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS657
SOMEONE remembers being gun-shy in the park.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS658
Then in the Peter Pan car chase.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS659
As SOMEONE elbows SOMEONE in the gut and escapes, SOMEONE recalls his insecure past.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS660
He remembers Korean Jesus.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS661
SOMEONE fires hitting SOMEONE in the groin.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS663
SOMEONE joins him in making the arrest.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS664
The two guys gaze into each other's eyes.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS665
SOMEONE nods tearfully. They jump up and slap palms. SOMEONE clutches his bleeding shoulder. SOMEONE massages his own hand.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS666
It lies in the street.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS667
Handcuffed SOMEONE tries to pick it up with his mouth.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS668
Later, as emergency crews work the scene, a cop takes SOMEONE away. A bandaged SOMEONE shouts after the teen.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS669
SOMEONE sits by SOMEONE.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS670
SOMEONE sits glumly in the back of an ambulance as a SOMEONE checks on her. She perks her head up as SOMEONE comes over.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS671
She cracks a smile. SOMEONE extends a hand.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS672
Shaking it, SOMEONE grins. Then cranes in fast for a kiss.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS673
SOMEONE melts into the lip lock.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS674
Looking on, SOMEONE chuckles approvingly.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS675
The SOMEONE stands by uncomfortably.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS676
He steps away.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS677
Rejoining SOMEONE spread his arms wide in a proud strut.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS678
They head off.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS679
Daytime, they burst into the bullpen.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS680
SOMEONE high fives a cop while SOMEONE dips SOMEONE in a kiss. The Captain smirks tolerantly.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS681
As his two prodigal agents hug him, he shrugs them off.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS682
He presents a framed arrest report.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS683
He deflects a second hug.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS684
As we cut to black, words appear, The End.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS685
Now, as scenes of violence and debauchery play interspersed with clips from the movie, titles appear.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS687
A rolled $20 SOMEONE sucks up a line of coke.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS692
At a desk, a writer types rapidly then pulls the paper from his typewriter.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS709
The front of a sweatshirt unzips revealing glittering skin underneath.
21_JUMP_STREET_DVS711
Two hands clasp in a soul brother shake and we see a compilation of explosions. Korean Jesus looks at us.