He takes out their pizzas.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS16
He starts for his car, then turns back.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS17
He stuffs their cash in his back pocket.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS18
Now the Mustang drives an empty road lined with abandoned warehouses.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS19
The shaggy-haired driver drums on his steering wheel with his thumb.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS20
The Mustang crosses a truss bridge over a river.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS21
That night sitting on a stoop, the shaggy-haired young man opens a bottle of beer, tosses the cap and takes a sip.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS22
He notices a scruffy Indian-American guy alone in the passenger seat of a silver car, then lowers his gaze and sips his beer.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS23
A young girl lifts her head from his lap and picks something from her mouth.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS24
She cradles his dark sideburns and kisses him passionately on the lips.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS25
He sees the delivery guy.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS26
Now a watermelon explodes.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS27
Two guys celebrate in a scrapyard.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS28
SOMEONE holds a crossbow.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS29
He pulls up another watermelon. Now in a home screening room SOMEONE and his friend watch Friday the 13th Part III in 3D.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS30
He pawns the air.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS31
He gets up and thrusts his hips.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS32
His friend joins in.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS33
A stern older man enters.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS34
The lights switch on.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS35
He picks up a plate, but the Major grabs it.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS36
SOMEONE dumps his 3D glasses.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS37
He heads out.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS38
He and SOMEONE exit a mansion. Various vehicles sit in the driveway, including an RV and a boat. SOMEONE spots a truck emblazoned with a bald eagle surrounded by stars and stripes.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS39
SOMEONE spits on it.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS40
At night, the Mustang parks at a curb outside their store.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS41
Inside the uniformed delivery guys carries a pizza through an aisle of colorful vases and decorations.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS42
He gazes at a young Indian-American woman fixing an arrangement of white flowers,
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS43
then notices his own reflection in a metallic balloon.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS44
Using his car key, he pops it.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS45
The young woman flinches.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS46
Now they eat pizza at a display table set for an elegant dinner.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS47
At a strip club, SOMEONE gets a lap dance.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS48
He takes a sip of beer.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS49
She rips off her top baring her breasts.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS50
She pinches her nipples.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS51
She breathes on SOMEONE's crotch.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS52
She scratches his goatee chin.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS53
SOMEONE looks at her supple breasts.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS54
She puts his hand on them.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS55
He nods.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS56
Now in an apartment the shaggy-haired delivery guy grabs a Rolling Rock from a refrigerator, then enters the living room.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS57
He throws the bottle cap at SOMEONE.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS58
SOMEONE grabs a remote and shuts off the TV.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS59
SOMEONE turns off the TV again.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS60
He stands.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS61
They both sit back down.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS62
SOMEONE tackles his friend and they wrestle on the floor.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS63
He briefly gets the upper hand, but SOMEONE throws him off.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS64
He repeatedly punches SOMEONE on the hip.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS65
SOMEONE gets him in a chokehold.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS66
He releases him.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS67
He stumbles to his feet.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS68
He flips the bird and leaves.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS69
SOMEONE and SOMEONE tend to a backyard swimming pool.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS70
SOMEONE flings leaves across the yard, then gathers more in his skimmer.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS72
He sips a takeout soda.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS73
In a garage.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS74
He grabs a component from a cluttered workbench.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS76
On TV the bearded pizza man holds up a slice to his mouth.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS77
At work the delivery guy assembles pizza boxes.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS78
The boss gives him an address.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS79
The delivery guy goes to his car, starts the timer and drives out of the Vito's Pizza parking lot.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS80
He taps his steering wheel with his thumb as he cruises an empty street.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS81
The timer counts down to zero.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS82
The Mustang rounds a darkened corner and stops halfway through the gate of a chain link fence with an address number on a sign.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS83
The delivery guy checks it against his order ticket then pulls the rest of the way through and drives down a long dirt lot.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS84
His car rolls through the junkyard between mounds of scrap metal.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS85
Across a dirt clearing lies a shed with lights on inside.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS86
Parking nearby the delivery guy steps out with the pizza and slams his door.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS87
He marches up to the shed.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS89
The customer steps out in a gorilla mask.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS90
A second guy in a chimpanzee mask waddles out with a lead pipe.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS91
SOMEONE tackles the delivery guy.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS92
His masked assailant covers his nose and mouth with a white rag until he passes out.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS93
SOMEONE approaches with a revolver. He takes off his gorilla mask.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS95
A blurry view shows the masked kidnapper.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS96
Duct tape covers the victim's mouth.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS97
SOMEONE checks his wallet.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS98
SOMEONE sees a wired vest underneath his green army jacket.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS99
SOMEONE tries to get up.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS100
SOMEONE does some clumsy jump kicks.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS101
As he starts a timer on the vest the image briefly freezes.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS102
The teddy bear explodes.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS103
SOMEONE unties SOMEONE.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS104
He shoots the ground around SOMEONE's feet.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS105
SOMEONE stumbles to his car.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS106
SOMEONE takes off his mask.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS107
SOMEONE rips off his mask.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS108
Now a red dot moves around the map.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS109
SOMEONE barges into the classroom.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS110
SOMEONE approaches him.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS111
They step out to the hall.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS112
SOMEONE unzips his jacket to reveal the vest.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS113
Now a sleek black car pulls around the strip club where the brunette dancer waits by a backdoor.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS114
A goateed thug with a shaved head and a tattoo on his neck steps out.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS115
She wraps her arms around his neck and kisses him.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS116
She climbs in his car, giving him a view of her butt.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS117
SOMEONE's sitting on a toilet fully clothed.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS118
He crosses to a window and spots a van outside.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS119
SOMEONE rolls his eyes then sits on SOMEONE's couch.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS120
SOMEONE slaps him.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS122
Now at a store.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS123
They reach an aisle of toy guns.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS124
SOMEONE aims at SOMEONE.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS125
Outside the Family Dollar store SOMEONE and SOMEONE wait in the van.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS126
SOMEONE bops his head to the song, SOMEONE pops out the cassette.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS127
He notices a commercial property for lease in a strip mall.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS128
Meanwhile at a register.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS129
The cashier scans the items.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS130
SOMEONE puts another item on the checkout counter.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS131
Now SOMEONE spray paints a gun black.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS132
The Mustang abruptly skids to a stop.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS133
Pulling back out, SOMEONE almost hits a passing truck.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS134
The Mustang drives off. Later, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE around the side of a garage and tries a door.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS136
They peer through a cracked open window at a maroon Datsun inside.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS137
SOMEONE hands him the shopping bag, then slides the window up and knocks over a few plastic bottles.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS138
He awkwardly climbs through the window and falls over a workbench onto the floor.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS139
SOMEONE peeks inside.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS140
SOMEONE lets him into the garage.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS141
SOMEONE sets down the bag, then checks items dangling from a shelf.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS142
SOMEONE crosses to a counter and peeks inside a green bag.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS143
SOMEONE searches a couple of cluttered desk drawers.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS144
SOMEONE checks inside the car under a visor.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS145
SOMEONE looks up from a cabinet.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS146
SOMEONE peers out a window and spots an older man exiting the house.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS147
He tosses SOMEONE a ski mask.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS148
Just as they SOMEONE their ski masks, Mr. Fisher enters. SOMEONE takes out a toy gun.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS149
SOMEONE fixes his mask.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS151
Mr. Fisher presses a button and the garage door rises.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS152
SOMEONE gets in after SOMEONE. They each wave.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS153
The Datsun speeds across the driveway and bottoms out as it turns onto the street.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS154
SOMEONE peels of his mask. SOMEONE buckles his seatbelt.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS155
SOMEONE shifts gears.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS156
At Vito's the Datsun parks by a dumpster.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS157
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from inside the van as SOMEONE runs past the entrance.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS158
SOMEONE steps out.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS159
Now SOMEONE sprints across a bridge, crossing the river in his buttoned up green army jacket.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS160
As he reaches the other side, SOMEONE arrives at the start of the bridge and stops to catch his breath.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS161
SOMEONE talks on his cell as he runs into the building with the flower store.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS162
SOMEONE staggers up the front steps. Now SOMEONE steps onto the roof. SOMEONE stands on the opposite side.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS163
He hurries past SOMEONE to the door.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS164
In the stairwell, SOMEONE talks on the phone.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS165
As SOMEONE enters SOMEONE casually turns away.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS167
It shows Vito's Pizza place.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS168
Now SOMEONE enters Vito's Pizza and marches up to his boss.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS169
He storms off.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS170
In the Datsun SOMEONE chugs a 5-hour Energy shot while eating a cheeseburger.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS171
SOMEONE returns.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS172
He shakes an empty bottle.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS173
The maroon Datsun drives off and the old beige van follows. Later across the street from the bank.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS174
They pull down their masks and barge inside.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS175
SOMEONE approaches the tellers.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS176
SOMEONE aims at a security guard.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS177
SOMEONE eyes a guy in a green shirt.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS178
The guard slides his gun directly over to a mom.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS179
She flings it away. It slides into a counter and discharges into a fat man's leg.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS180
SOMEONE scurries over to SOMEONE's side.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS181
She nods.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS182
She heads for the vault.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS183
SOMEONE opens a barred gate and enters the vault.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS184
She fills the sack with cash.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS185
SOMEONE gives two sacks to SOMEONE, who tosses one to SOMEONE.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS186
As the fat man reaches into the sack, blue paint explodes in his face.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS187
SOMEONE hands him a garbage bag of cash.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS188
They exit.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS189
A police car cuts them off.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS190
He reveals his vest.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS191
The officer drops his gun and flees.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS192
Now the getaway car pulls out, making a U-turn.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS193
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from the van.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS194
Two police cars chase the Datsun down a main road.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS195
He turns onto another street with the police cars hot on his tail. SOMEONE glances out the back window.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS196
He briefly veers into the opposite lane toward oncoming traffic.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS197
As the Datsun makes a sharp right, pedestrians dodge to a sidewalk.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS198
One of the police cars crashes into a minivan.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS199
SOMEONE shifts gears and races ahead.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS200
Reaching an intersection, he pulls the emergency break.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS201
As the car slides into a turn, he loses control and spins out completely.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS202
A minivan drives by.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS203
The Datsun peels out with the remaining police car on its tail.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS204
SOMEONE speeds through a red light.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS205
The police car follows but gets T-boned by a crossing dump truck.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS206
Another police car T-bones the Datsun, which flips onto its roof and skids toward us.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS207
SOMEONE and SOMEONE unbuckle their seatbelts and land on their heads.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS208
They climb out of the wreck.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS209
Near the police car a stream of water rises four stories high.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS210
They run through an alley.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS211
SOMEONE pulls out the bloody shard.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS212
They reach the end of the narrow alley.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS213
They cross the street.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS214
The bus halts.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS215
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hurry onboard and take a seat.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS216
As the bus pulls out two police officers exit the alley.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS217
SOMEONE and SOMEONE quickly hide their faces from the window.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS218
Meanwhile, at the wrecked Datsun.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS219
SOMEONE approaches a bystander.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS220
Walking a residential street, SOMEONE looks at the cash in the bag.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS221
They cross the street.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS222
SOMEONE kisses his car.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS223
He and SOMEONE get in.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS224
SOMEONE takes out his cell phone.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS225
Now the van parks in front of a Taco Boy restaurant.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS226
SOMEONE steps out.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS227
He answers his cellphone.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS228
SOMEONE hangs up.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS229
SOMEONE makes a call.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS230
Now the Mustang speeds over railroad tracks back at Taco Boy.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS231
He sets his cellphone on the table.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS232
He slides it to SOMEONE.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS233
Left alone, SOMEONE glances at the cell phone.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS234
Now at the railroad bridge.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS235
As SOMEONE's car arrives, SOMEONE grabs the garbage back from atop the Mustang's trunk.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS236
The black car rolls up and parks between an abandoned building and the railroad tracks, about 20 feet away from SOMEONE's car.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS237
SOMEONE climbs out.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS238
He hands over the bag.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS239
He reveals his vest.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS240
He aims a pistol.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS241
SOMEONE sneaks up.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS242
He bashes SOMEONE with a crowbar. SOMEONE jumps on him.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS243
SOMEONE pulls her down and slams her into SOMEONE's car, then grabs the bag.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS244
SOMEONE gives her a weak stomp.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS245
He and SOMEONE climb in the Mustang.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS246
As they drive away she shoots at them with SOMEONE's gun.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS248
In his garage SOMEONE trims SOMEONE's hair.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS249
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a mirror, then answers his cellphone.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS250
SOMEONE hangs up.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS251
The Mustang pulls over and SOMEONE runs a safe distance away.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS252
In the garage, SOMEONE holds his cellphone to his ear. He looks at SOMEONE.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS253
He hangs up and throws the phone.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS254
He pulls off his barber cape and upends the table.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS255
He grabs his phone. He dials.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS257
As SOMEONE attacks, SOMEONE defends himself with the hair trimmer.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS258
SOMEONE whips him with the cord.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS259
SOMEONE punches him in the kidney.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS260
SOMEONE plops on the couch.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS261
SOMEONE inches over and retrieves the cellphone.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS262
He sits across from SOMEONE.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS263
SOMEONE sits up.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS264
SOMEONE picks up the phone.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS265
SOMEONE lowers the cellphone from his ear and looks at it.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS266
SOMEONE shifts his gaze then nods understandingly.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS267
SOMEONE tries to pull the bomb vest up over SOMEONE's head.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS268
He steps aside and makes the call.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS269
Now in a bathroom stall, SOMEONE unravels toilet paper.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS270
Leaning forward she spots men's shoes crossing the checkered floor.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS271
They reached the door of her stall.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS272
SOMEONE nervously holds still.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS273
The door swings open to reveal SOMEONE and SOMEONE in their ape masks.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS274
Now a reality show plays on a flat screen TV.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS275
The Major watches from his bed.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS276
He knits his brow at the sound.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS277
He slips out of bed.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS278
From a desk he grabs a pen with a plunger at its end.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS279
He opens the door with the pen poised in his right hand, then cautiously steps out of the bedroom.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS280
Advancing through a hallway he creeps past a windowed door.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS281
He heads towards a giant framed Michigan Lottery check adorning the wall.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS282
Stepping around the corner he scans the area.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS283
He heads down a set of steps.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS285
SOMEONE aims his pistol at the Major's back.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS286
The Major smirks, then faces him and lowers his pen.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS287
The Major smiles defiantly.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS288
He shoots SOMEONE in the neck with his pen.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS289
He straddles the intruder who fends off his pen gun.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS290
The hit man grabs his own gun and pistol-whips him.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS291
Jumping up SOMEONE stands over the Major.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS292
SOMEONE shoots him in the stomach.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS293
He heads upstairs, leaving the wounded Major on the floor.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS294
In a bathroom, facing a mirror, SOMEONE finds a bottle of rubbing alcohol and twists it open.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS295
He pours the rubbing alcohol on his neck wound, then grimaces and shakes his head.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS296
Fighting tears he holds a towel to his neck and hurries out.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS297
SOMEONE barges into SOMEONE's bedroom and drops the bloody towel.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS298
He searches a workbench, then crosses the room and ransacks a bookshelf.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS299
Noticing a desk with a padlock on one of its drawers he takes aim.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS301
He opens the drawer.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS302
Searching the contents of a folder he finds a hand-drawn schematic showing the scrapyard, the bank and SOMEONE's Tantastic Tan Salon.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS304
He hands SOMEONE the phone.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS305
SOMEONE hangs up.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS306
SOMEONE sits in the passenger seat while SOMEONE grabs the loot and gets behind the wheel.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS307
The Mustang pulls out of the empty lot and drives off past a few warehouses. Now our view rises from one the van's headlights to SOMEONE, who drives with a determined look in his eyes, wearing his chimpanzee mask. SOMEONE repeatedly pokes at SOMEONE's face, which is covered in a Slayer T-shirt.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS308
The van speeds down an industrial road at dusk.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS309
Later that night our view rises from one of the Mustang's headlights to SOMEONE,
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS310
who glances determinedly at his best friend beside him.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS311
SOMEONE glances back. The Mustang parks.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS312
SOMEONE steps out and the Mustang continues on down the dirt road.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS313
SOMEONE runs down a path strewn with garbage.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS314
Now our view rises from a heap of crushed cars to reveal the Mustang arriving in the scrapyard.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS315
Its headlights go dim and SOMEONE steps out.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS316
SOMEONE exits the van in his mask.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS317
SOMEONE drops the bag.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS318
SOMEONE ditches his jacket then picks the bag back up.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS319
SOMEONE enters the code into a keypad on the wired vest.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS320
A buckle adorned with a smiley face sticker releases four straps.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS321
SOMEONE slowly unzips the vest from top to bottom then slides it off.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS322
As SOMEONE sets the vest aside SOMEONE claps his hands overhead.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS323
They make the switch. SOMEONE removes the shirt from SOMEONE's face and she hugs him. SOMEONE eyes the cash.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS324
He aims his gun.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS325
A red dot shines on the forehead of SOMEONE's mask emanating from SOMEONE's laser path.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS326
SOMEONE pulls off his mask.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS327
He yanks off his mask.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS328
SOMEONE pistol-whips SOMEONE, knocking him to the dirt. SOMEONE tries to rouse her friend.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS329
He tosses the bag over. SOMEONE cocks his pistol.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS330
SOMEONE shoots a plume of fire.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS331
A charred SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE in the shoulder.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS332
SOMEONE screams as he watches his partner collapse onto his back. SOMEONE rouses SOMEONE.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS333
He spots the moneybag.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS334
SOMEONE torches SOMEONE again.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS335
He shoots a bullet into the flamethrower tank.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS336
It explodes sending SOMEONE flying off his feet.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS337
SOMEONE runs back with the bag.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS338
SOMEONE sits up and sees them getting into the Mustang.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS339
They shut the car doors.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS340
He glances at his van.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS341
SOMEONE lies face down his back consumed in flames.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS342
As the Mustang drives off, SOMEONE takes off his jacket and whips it at the flaming tank.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS343
Embers rise into the air as he puts out the fire.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS344
He kneels at his friend's side and rolls him over.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS345
He watches SOMEONE hobble off with his gun.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS347
In the mustang, SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE and kisses him as he drives.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS348
The van approaches.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS349
He pulls up alongside the Mustang, SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE through their open windows.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS350
He takes aim.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS351
The unit freezes and a digital timer flashes zero.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS352
A fiery explosion flips the van upside down.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS353
The Mustang gets away as the flaming wreck tumbles to a stop on its side.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS354
A stack of cash sprays blue paint in SOMEONE's face.
30_MINUTES_OR_LESS_DVS355
As the Mustang drives away, the picture cuts to black.