The boy peddles with his mother.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS32
The girl's on a slide.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS35
The boy eats cake messily. The girl grins, holding a candle.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS38
The children smile at the cameras.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS40
The girl feeds some ducks. The boy rides on a miniature railway.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS43
The boy, now older, plays an electric guitar.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS45
The girl does a cartwheel.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS46
She waves to the camera
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS47
She makes an origami paper model.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS49
The boy plays football.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS50
The girl rides a horse.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS53
The girl blows on a dandelion.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS54
The boy plays with bubbles.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS56
One scrolls forwards to 290.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS57
A young girl cycles through the city at night.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS58
The road passes rapidly beneath the bike's wheels.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS59
She chains the bike to a post, and wearing a helmet, strides towards the entrance to an apartment building.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS60
She hurries in.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS61
Two guys open an apartment door.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS62
SOMEONE's in the kitchen, smashing plates on a counter.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS63
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk hand in hand.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS64
They kiss in bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS65
They walk through an Ikea store holding hands.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS66
They hug in the street and grin at a Ringo Starr record in a shop.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS67
A waitress brings two plates.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS68
SOMEONE gets up.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS69
Back to day one.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS70
A poster of a child with mothers.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS71
SOMEONE blinks alluringly.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS72
Day three, and she's at work in a vest top.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS73
SOMEONE goes back to work. Three rolls over to four.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS74
Wearing headphones, SOMEONE enters a lift.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS75
SOMEONE hurries in as well.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS76
SOMEONE, in shirt and cardigan with a loosely knotted tie, studiously ignores the dark haired large-eyed SOMEONE.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS77
SOMEONE stares at her, entranced.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS78
SOMEONE exits, leaving SOMEONE awestruck.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS79
Four advances to eight.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS80
A sign reads, Happy engagement, SOMEONE.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS81
SOMEONE's handing out glasses of bubbly. He spots SOMEONE standing alone.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS82
He hands her a greetings card.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS83
SOMEONE chokes on his bubbles.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS84
He nods and wipes wine off his face.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS85
He stares after her as she walks away through the open plan office.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS86
He studies her as she sits at her desk
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS87
He sits down at his work station.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS88
As he starts a drawing, SOMEONE glances across the office towards him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS89
He's drawing a city skyline in pencil.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS90
There's another drawing of a building in a frame on his desk.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS91
With a look of dissatisfaction,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS92
he rubs out what he's done so far on the new picture.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS93
He glances around the office then screws up his piece of paper into a ball. 8 jumps to 154.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS94
SOMEONE's long-haired friend looks worried.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS95
154 skips back to 11.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS96
SOMEONE beats him at tennis on the Wii. 11 jumps to 22.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS97
She blinks in puzzled inquiry.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS98
His friend and colleague grins as SOMEONE watches SOMEONE walk across the room.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS99
SOMEONE finds the Smiths on his iTunes.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS100
SOMEONE turns the music up as SOMEONE walks across the office to leave work, her handbag over her shoulder.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS101
He stares at her.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS102
But she doesn't even glance in his direction.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS103
22 jumps to 27. In the office, SOMEONE's friend mimes for him to take off his headset.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS104
SOMEONE's eyes flick towards SOMEONE.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS105
Day 27 becomes day 28.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS106
SOMEONE heads for the pub stage.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS107
SOMEONE's friend, Mackenzie, hands him a beer.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS108
SOMEONE smiles as she sings, then grabs another couple of beers and chasers from the bar. SOMEONE's sitting in a booth with Mackenzie.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS109
They study one another.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS110
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE try to think, Mackenzie hits the stage.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS111
He drops the mic and drunkenly downs another shot.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS112
Smiling, she looks him in the eye.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS113
He stares at her.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS114
She smiles back.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS115
She gives a casual salute and heads off.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS116
He remains, staring after her.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS117
Standing on the pavement outside the bar.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS118
SOMEONE turns slowly and walks away.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS119
Day 28 becomes day 31
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS120
SOMEONE's at the photocopier when SOMEONE walks up.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS121
She gets on with some copying of her own
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS122
They work side by side.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS123
Unsure what to say, SOMEONE half turns toward SOMEONE
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS124
who's just getting on with her copying.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS125
She moves away from the copier
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS126
and approaches SOMEONE.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS127
They kiss.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS128
They hold each other close,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS129
kissing with increasing passion.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS130
SOMEONE turns and walks back to her copying.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS131
She picks up her file.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS132
She briefly looks SOMEONE in the eye.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS133
Then She walks away.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS134
SOMEONE's thoroughly confused.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS135
Later, SOMEONE opens his front door to his long-haired friend, SOMEONE.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS136
SOMEONE gasps, realizing SOMEONE's in the apartment.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS137
SOMEONE nods awkwardly and has no idea what to say.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS138
SOMEONE dismisses him with a salute, then turns to SOMEONE.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS139
SOMEONE drops his head in embarrassment.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS140
Day 282 and a tap isn't working.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS141
It's a sink in a showroom.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS142
SOMEONE's standing nearby.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS143
She walks off, unimpressed by his attempt at humor.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS144
282 rewinds to 34.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS145
They're in Ikea.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS146
She grabs a dummy remote from a coffee table and pretends to watch TV.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS147
SOMEONE jumps up from the sofa they've been sitting on and walks off. SOMEONE follows. They arrive at a kitchen display.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS148
He clowns, sitting at a table
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS149
as SOMEONE wanders over to the sink.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS150
He walks through to another display.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS151
She ballets out of the kitchen.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS152
SOMEONE chases her through the huge furniture store.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS153
SOMEONE dives onto a double bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS154
SOMEONE crawls on after her
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS155
and looks deep into her eyes.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS156
They look around, slowly.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS157
A whole Chinese family is indeed staring at them from the on-suite bathroom display.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS158
SOMEONE and SOMEONE smile
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS159
and the family wanders off glumly.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS160
They face each other on the bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS161
She gets up
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS162
and he stays thoughtfully on the bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS165
As they wander through Ikea, SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's hand. There are signs on the store wall,"Ikea Stockholm. We don't make fancy quality, we make true every day quality".
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS171
At night, they tumble, kissing on to the bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS173
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE heads to the bathroom.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS174
SOMEONE comes out of the bathroom and stares. SOMEONE's now naked in his bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS175
SOMEONE switches off the bathroom light and approaches the bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS177
In daylight, he walks out of the apartment building with a broad grin on his face.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS178
SOMEONE struts jauntily down the street and everyone who passes smiles at him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS179
He pauses to check his look in a shop window.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS180
The reflection he sees is Harrison Ford as SOMEONE Solo winking back at him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS181
A large fountain erupts like watery fireworks.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS182
SOMEONE boogies his way past the display and through a park.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS184
He cheerfully greets the people he meets, even kissing one woman's hand.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS185
He daps and slaps with a couple of guys he meets on his sunny walk to work, shakes a lot of hands, and is wreathed in smiles.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS188
He tosses his bag to a woman and starts to dance.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS189
Everyone on the path dances with him and it turns into a routine.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS190
SOMEONE grabs a baseball bat and knocks an imaginary ball out of the park.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS191
He's hoisted shoulder high by his dancing friends.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS192
The large crowd of dancers is joined by a marching band in full colorful military style uniform.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS193
A little cartoon bluebird flits up to SOMEONE and lands on his shoulder.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS194
It hops onto his finger.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS195
He strokes its head and lets it go.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS196
It winks down at him as it flies off.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS197
SOMEONE puts his bag back on.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS198
SOMEONE with a satisfied grin.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS199
He dashes off to work.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS200
He skips happily through the front door and to the lift
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS201
He smirking to himself.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS202
Day 35 rolls forward to day 303, and the lift door opens revealing a despondent, disheveled SOMEONE. He sits hollow-eyed, staring towards the desk where SOMEONE used to sit. His boss has a new assistant with a large afro.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS203
SOMEONE stares gloomily at Mackenzie.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS205
Day 303 rolls back to day 45. Mackenzie sees SOMEONE singing on the phone.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS206
It's day 87 and they're in a DVD and music store. SOMEONE leads Toms through to the adult's only section.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS207
At home, they're on a sofa watching a DVD called Sweet and Shower.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS208
They're fooling around in the shower.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS209
Day 95.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS210
SOMEONE points up at the city's sculpted stone buildings and at the multi-level Eastern Columbia building with a large clock face and the word Eastern in bold white letters.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS211
They sit on the park bench overlooking some of the downtown buildings.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS212
She hands him a pen.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS213
He rolls up her sleeve.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS214
He draws on the inside of her wrist.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS215
He creates a detailed skyline on the inside of her forearm.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS216
Day 109.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS217
It's evening.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS218
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive at SOMEONE's place.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS219
SOMEONE closes the front door and walks slowly into the apartment with patterned wallpaper,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS220
boxes still unpacked,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS221
pictures and books resting on the mantelpiece and on the floor.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS222
Lying on the bed,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS223
SOMEONE studies her.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS224
SOMEONE challenges his friends who can't meet his eye.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS225
Day 118.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS226
SOMEONE's amazed by SOMEONE's stories.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS227
SOMEONE's little sister runs of to join her football team on the pitch.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS228
SOMEONE remains sitting thoughtfully on the bleachers.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS229
SOMEONE and SOMEONE drive through the city in SOMEONE's aging 3 Series BMW.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS230
She nuzzles his arm and he grins.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS232
They smile happily and she studies him as they drive.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS233
They have fun chatting as they drive through the sunny city.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS234
They drive into a tunnel.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS235
Day 259.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS236
They're in a cocktail bar.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS237
A suit makes a beeline for SOMEONE.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS238
She calmly sips her cocktail.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS239
The big guy challenges SOMEONE who eyes him with calm distaste and sips his drink.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS241
The guy wanders off.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS242
SOMEONE floors him with a right hook. The guy responds.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS244
SOMEONE's not happy.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS246
With an ice pack to his cheek, SOMEONE doesn't know what to say.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS247
He turns away from her and heads for the front door.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS249
She sits on the bed and he shrugs, challenging her.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS251
SOMEONE stunned. As SOMEONE stomps downstairs, he meets two women coming up.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS252
He continues down the many flights of wooden stairs.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS254
he lies restlessly in bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS255
SOMEONE lies still in her bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS256
SOMEONE sits up in bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS257
It's still night time and raining outside.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS259
He gets up and puts on a t-shirt.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS260
He wanders slowly to open the front door.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS262
She stares at him expressionlessly,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS263
then rests her head wearily against the door frame.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS264
She moves close to him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS265
She touches his bruised jaw
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS266
She kisses him gently.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS267
She links her arms around SOMEONE's neck and they kiss.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS269
They're lying in bed in their pajamas.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS270
SOMEONE has a large bulge in the crotch of his leather trousers.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS271
She slumps back down on the bed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS273
SOMEONE gently nudges his shoulder with her head.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS274
They're sitting on a blanket in the park.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS275
Day 266 flips back to day 191. SOMEONE and SOMEONE are at an art gallery. There's a picture of two dogs copulating. They're standing in front of huge prints of intertwined tubes.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS276
They stare in bafflement at a coiled poo.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS277
The sign outside the cinema proclaims, part vampire, part giant.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS280
They smile and eat popcorn in the theater
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS281
as others laugh and cringe in equal measure.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS282
Day 191 fast forwards to day 314
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS283
and SOMEONE's sitting alone in the cinema.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS284
The film is black and white and the star is SOMEONE.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS285
Subtitles read, "He is broken, more than broken, he is alone".
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS289
The SOMEONE character's carrying a balloon.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS290
He turns around to face a mime in a top hat
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS291
and hands him the balloon.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS292
The mime smiles happily
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS293
and lets the balloon go.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS294
It floats up into the air.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS295
The mime eyeballs SOMEONE and then slaps him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS301
A crusader SOMEONE plays chess with a little winged angel by a rocky shore.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS303
The child angel moves.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS306
Crusader SOMEONE buries his face in his hands. The word "fin" appears on the black screen.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS307
SOMEONE wakes up in the cinema. Looks around, then gets up.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS308
Day 314 jumps to day 321.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS310
The new assistant approaches SOMEONE's workstation.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS311
SOMEONE's head sags.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS312
Vance shows SOMEONE a selection of greetings cards.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS313
He dismisses SOMEONE with a friendly smile.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS314
SOMEONE picks up the cards and trudges slowly out of the office.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS315
On the assistant's desk he spots a card with "I love us".
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS317
He scowls.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS318
Day 321 rolls back to day 167. SOMEONE strides into the office.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS319
SOMEONE spots SOMEONE across the office.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS320
She smiles at him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS321
Fast forward to day 322.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS322
SOMEONE yells on a bus which lurches to a halt.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS324
SOMEONE remembers the cinema, Ikea, and the record store.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS325
SOMEONE stares at auburn haired SOMEONE, then grins tipsily.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS326
SOMEONE, completely fed up, sits in a booth as SOMEONE lurches through his karaoke performance.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS327
SOMEONE leaves.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS328
Day 402.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS329
SOMEONE, toting a suit carrier, boards a train.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS330
He calls Mackenzie on his mobile.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS331
SOMEONE continues glumly down the train.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS332
He scans left and right looking for a space
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS333
and walks right past SOMEONE.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS334
He chucks his suit carrier into the luggage rack
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS335
and flops down into a seat further down the carriage.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS336
He peers round behind him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS337
SOMEONE spots him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS338
He takes out her earphones.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS339
SOMEONE frantically packs away his headphones and opens a book.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS340
SOMEONE gets up and walks down the carriage.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS341
She spots the book and grins.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS342
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE to the buffet car.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS343
They sit, talking over coffee, with the evening sunlight filtering through the window.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS344
They laugh happily together.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS345
SOMEONE looks into SOMEONE's eyes as he chats away happily.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS346
They get up and leave the buffet car.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS347
It's a sunny day at SOMEONE's wedding.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS348
SOMEONE, wearing his suit, spots SOMEONE wearing a knee-length pale dress.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS349
They wave to one another.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS350
They take their seats for the outdoor ceremony.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS351
SOMEONE leans over to SOMEONE.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS352
SOMEONE and her new husband embrace.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS353
The sun sets in a blaze of orange on a hilly shoreline and the wedding guests dance into the night.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS354
SOMEONE's dancing with a young lad.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS355
SOMEONE leaps up and chases the young lad.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS356
The singer sports a massive afro.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS357
SOMEONE throws her bouquet over her head.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS358
SOMEONE catches it and SOMEONE grins.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS360
SOMEONE and SOMEONE down a shot.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS361
They join the throng of guests for a slow dance, smiling happily at one another.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS362
SOMEONE nods towards the band.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS363
The nighttime dance floor is festooned with bright lights.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS364
SOMEONE's on the train home.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS365
He sits thoughtfully.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS366
SOMEONE asleep on his shoulder.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS367
He glances down at her with a pensive smile.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS368
SOMEONE speaks on camera in black and white.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS370
SOMEONE's next in the frame.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS371
The camera switched off.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS372
SOMEONE and Susan Trainers rings the bell to a building with a wrought iron entrance.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS373
Clutching a present, SOMEONE goes inside.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS374
Expectations appears as a subtitle on a split screen as SOMEONE climbs the stairs.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS375
On the other side of the screen, reality is the caption as he walks down a corridor.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS376
In expectations, SOMEONE opens the door, smiles, and kisses SOMEONE on the lips.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS377
In reality, she opens the door, gives him a friendly hug, and ushers him in.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS378
SOMEONE nods to the gathered guests and gives SOMEONE the gift.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS379
He acknowledgment was in expectations. In reality, she opens the gift in silence.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS380
In expectations, she hugs him in thanks for the architecture of happiness, not in reality.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS381
In reality, they're on opposite sides of a chatting group. In expectations, they're talking together, ignoring everyone else.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS382
Later in reality, SOMEONE sips a beer alone.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS383
In expectations, they're together, flirting.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS385
SOMEONE watches glumly as SOMEONE chats to two guys.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS387
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk indoors together and kiss passionately.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS389
SOMEONE fixes himself another drink.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS392
SOMEONE stares as SOMEONE shows a girlfriend a ring on her left hand.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS393
His jaw sags and his eyes fill with tears as he notices it's a diamond engagement ring.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS394
He puts down his drink and leaves,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS395
He is running down the stairs.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS396
He storms out into the night, striding down the road, fighting back tears as he encounters a couple walking arm in arm.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS397
He walks down the middle of the road.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS398
The city becomes a grey, black and white drawing
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS399
which is then erased,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS400
just leaving SOMEONE as a black silhouette
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS401
standing with his shadow
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS402
in the middle of nothing.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS403
The SOMEONE silhouette fades.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS404
Day 408 jumps forward to day 440.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS405
It's 7:00 AM. SOMEONE slaps off his alarm.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS406
Day 441,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS407
it's 7:00 AM. SOMEONE slaps off his alarm.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS408
SOMEONE stares at the alarm clock with an empty Twinkie packet beside it
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS409
then rolls himself up in his bed clothes.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS410
Day 441 and a half,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS411
SOMEONE buys Blackjack Bourbon, juice, and Twinkies.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS412
He's in his dressing gown.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS413
He gives a "so what" shrug to the concerned shopkeeper.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS414
He wanders out of the shop past another happy couple holding hands.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS415
SOMEONE shuffles off.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS416
Day 442.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS417
There's a pile of empty cake packets and an aspirin bottle next to the alarm clock.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS418
SOMEONE lies, staring at the ceiling.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS420
SOMEONE trudges into the office wearing shades. Mackenzie's on the phone, looks up and notices his friend.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS421
SOMEONE throws the card on the boardroom table.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS422
His colleagues watch in stunned silence as SOMEONE walks out.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS423
Mackenzie stops, realizing he's alone in appreciating SOMEONE's performance.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS424
SOMEONE exits the lift past a sign that reads, Thank you for 75 years,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS425
and walks slowly past the metal sign on the wall which says, "New Hampshire greetings, greeting the world one card at a time".
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS428
Day 450.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS429
SOMEONE in her football kit, studies her brother.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS430
He's drawn a girl holding a dagger dripping blood.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS431
Brother and sister look at one another, then SOMEONE pats SOMEONE on the shoulder and goes back to her teammates.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS433
SOMEONE stares into the middle distance and remembers times with SOMEONE walking down the street.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS435
He remembers her by the photocopiers,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS437
He remembers holding hands in Ikea, laughing in the car.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS439
the punch up in the cocktail bar, SOMEONE coming around in the rain to apologize.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS442
Lying in bed and talking,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS443
and sitting in a restaurant.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS444
They sit, barely looking at one another.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS445
SOMEONE and SOMEONE in her wedding dress, sit in the back of the bus in the last scene from The Graduate, which SOMEONE and SOMEONE are watching in the cinema.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS448
On screen, the characters' excited smiles fade.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS449
SOMEONE stares straight ahead and SOMEONE glances at him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS450
She's crying.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS453
SOMEONE walks off. SOMEONE follows her.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS454
Later they're in the music store.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS455
SOMEONE nods unconvincingly.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS456
SOMEONE finds the Ringo Starr record.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS457
SOMEONE gives a tight smile and walks away from the
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS458
record stand.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS459
SOMEONE reaches out to take her hand
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS460
but she pulls away.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS461
With a disappointed sigh,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS462
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE out of the shop.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS463
SOMEONE purses her lips.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS464
She leans forward and kisses him
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS465
on the cheek.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS466
He processes this for a moment
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS467
then manages a smile.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS469
Day 450 becomes days 456 to 476.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS470
SOMEONE's lying on his bed
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS471
despondently bouncing a tennis ball on the floor.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS472
SOMEONE bounces the ball in time to the banging.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS473
He tears down all the sketches and notes from his bedroom wall.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS474
He stands back examining the clean wall and the piles of paper on the floor.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS475
SOMEONE sits in an easy chair in a coffee lounge reading a book.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS476
There's a pile of books on architecture on the coffee table in front of him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS478
He is wearing a suit
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS479
and carrying a portfolio.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS480
SOMEONE talks to the security guard on the desk who takes the portfolio from him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS481
SOMEONE despondently ends a call on his mobile.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS482
He's chalked architectural firms names on his wall.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS483
There are lines through many of them.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS484
He chalks lines through four more.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS485
Using chalks and a long ruler,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS486
SOMEONE creates a design on the dark bedroom wall.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS487
He carefully rules lines and shades in areas of the design.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS488
He draws in his sketchbook, looking at the city skyline from a rooftop.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS489
At night, the skyline shimmers with lights.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS491
Nighttime traffic is a blur of speeded up light.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS492
SOMEONE copies a city design onto the bedroom drawing. Nighttime traffic continues to blur through the city at super speed.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS493
SOMEONE stands back and appraises the complex skyline
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS494
which is his bedroom artwork.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS495
SOMEONE's being fitted for a wedding dress.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS496
The chiffon veil is lowered over SOMEONE's face.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS497
SOMEONE travels on a bus.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS498
As SOMEONE sits gloomily on the bus,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS499
SOMEONE smiles under her veil.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS500
It's lifted from her face
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS501
and she kisses her new husband.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS502
SOMEONE stares blankly on the bus.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS503
Day 488.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS504
SOMEONE wearing his suit, reaches pavement level on an escalator.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS505
He stares expressionlessly out across a leafy park.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS507
he sits on his favorite bench.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS508
He sits up.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS509
SOMEONE's sitting on a bench a short distance away
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS510
wearing a dark skirt and a raincoat.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS512
she strolls down towards him.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS513
They sit awkwardly, side by side.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS514
Becoming serious, he stares at her.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS516
She smiles and looks away.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS517
Hurt, he looks away from her.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS518
She self-consciously brushes her hair away from her face.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS519
They sit together looking out at the city.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS520
She places her hand on his
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS521
with a pained expression.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS522
He looks down at her diamond ring
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS523
He studies her face.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS524
She gives his hand a squeeze.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS525
She gives him a pat on the back
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS526
She walks off.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS527
She smiles sweetly at him,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS529
She goes.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS530
SOMEONE stands, looking at the skyline
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS531
then sits back down on the bench.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS532
Day 500.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS533
SOMEONE walks on a tiled floor through a large airy old office building
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS535
SOMEONE takes a seat on a balustraded balcony area.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS536
A young woman is on a sofa also, waiting.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS537
She has long dark hair.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS538
They notice each other,
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS539
They don't acknowledge one another.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS540
SOMEONE walks off She smiles to herself.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS542
SOMEONE stares at her.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS543
She looks right at the camera with a twinkle in his eye.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS544
Day 500 becomes day 1.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS545
The sun shines on the line drawing city.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS546
Blossoms bloom on the tree and birds fly in the sky.
500DAYSOFSUMMER_DVS547
Two little birds hop on the ground towards one another.