A young man saunters out of a parked blue van and hides something in the rear tire well. The motorcycle whizzes through an empty parking structure.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS47
The young man uses a payphone.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS48
He hangs up and crosses the street toward a colored blue-lit nightclub.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS49
Now, a shapely brunette gets off the motorcycle and unzips her leather body suit.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS50
Outside the club, the man takes off his jacket.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS51
Now, the brunette enters a large modern apartment and approaches SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS52
Now, a hand raps on a metal door.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS53
A tiny window opens, a chef takes a scrap of paper and lets the young man in.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS54
At waist level, we follow him as he walks past a scantily clad woman and into the kitchen.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS55
Without breaking his stride, he lifts a napkin on the counter and takes a gun hidden beneath it.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS58
Through a curtain, the young man enters the hopping nightclub.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS59
In a booth, a man sits with several young beauties. SOMEONE nuzzles the brunette's hair.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS63
The young man faces the man in the booth.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS64
SOMEONE makes a call.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS68
He raises his gun to the man in the booth.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS71
The young man shoots him in the chest. Someone tackles him and our view cuts to black.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS76
Bullets tear a hole through the backside of a paper target.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS77
The target glides forward to reveal SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS78
Setting his weapon down, the aging bald cop removes his protective glasses.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS79
SOMEONE faces a man with a badge around his neck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS80
Leaning next to the cop, SOMEONE looks at a file in his hand.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS81
SOMEONE gives him a cool sidelong glance.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS82
SOMEONE's stony expression softens as he shifts his gaze.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS83
SOMEONE tilts his head and leans toward his friend.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS84
Now at the airport, SOMEONE sits in the passenger seat of a silver Sedan.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS85
He and SOMEONE share a smile, then look away. She paces.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS86
She looks at SOMEONE as he stares out the windshield.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS87
She starts to speak then swallows.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS88
She hands him a Moscow travel guide. SOMEONE smirks as he takes it.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS89
She raises her eyebrows slightly.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS90
Her father gives her a half smile.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS91
He gets out of the car with a small bag and shuts the door.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS92
SOMEONE walks underneath the sign that reads Aeroflot.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS93
Later a jumbo jet sails above the cloud.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS94
Inside the plane, the name atop a file reads, SOMEONE opens it.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS96
By the dim light above his seat, he peruses the documents written in Russian.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS99
He flips past paperwork and uncovers a mug shot of his son.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS100
Looking it over, the heartened detective inhales deeply.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS101
He lingers on the mug shot.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS102
Later in the dark, he reclines in his seat and shuts his eyes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS103
Now, a man's cuffed hands rest folded on a table.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS104
Another man slaps a file down next to an ashtray.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS105
Wearing a suit and ID card, he sits across in front of the prisoner.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS107
He looks at the file, then takes out a pack of cigarettes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS108
The prisoner, SOMEONE's son, watches him light up.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS111
The man in the suit studies him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS113
He takes a drag off his cigarette.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS118
The men stare at each other.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS119
Now, congested traffic trickles along one side of a massively wide avenue.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS120
SOMEONE sits in the back of a taxi with a tense brow staring at scribbled notes about his son's arrest.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS121
His eyes scan over a Russian detective's phone number and settle on Groginski.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS123
which he outlined in red ink.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS124
Reading from the guidebook, he addresses the driver.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS125
The driver glances back with a quizzical frown.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS126
SOMEONE looks out the windshield.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS127
Grinning, the driver lifts his hand.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS128
SOMEONE exits the cab.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS129
Elsewhere, police vehicles surround a parked prisoner transport truck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS130
Uniformed Russian soldiers along with an armed guard in a ski mask, escort SOMEONE and SOMEONE to the truck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS132
Riding inside, SOMEONE glances at the young criminal, who stares back with a blank piercing
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS134
Elsewhere, three black Sedans move through an alley, barely wide enough for cars. Outside the courthouse, hundreds of protesters gather.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS135
SOMEONE strolls through the chaos.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS136
Elsewhere, SOMEONE walks through a dim arched hallway. The three Sedans travel a street along a river.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS137
Fixing his suit jacket he continues downstairs.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS138
At the courthouse, two police motorcycles lead the heavily guarded motorcade to the front entrance.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS139
SOMEONE stands alone nearby, with protesters marching behind him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS140
As a policeman opens the truck, uniformed soldiers escort the prisoners out.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS142
SOMEONE sneers at the crowd.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS143
The black Sedans continue in an evenly spaced line.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS144
As the soldiers escort the prisoners along the barricaded path, SOMEONE spots his son.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS145
SOMEONE remains still with his brow tense,
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS146
as he watches his son reach the courthouse stairs.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS147
His softening gaze slowly drifts to the ground.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS148
The prisoners continue through two lines of darkly clad armed guards.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS149
Inside, a crowded courtroom erupts as the soldiers escort the man.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS150
Quiet. Order in the courtroom.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS151
The soldiers place SOMEONE and SOMEONE in adjacent thick glass holding cells.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS152
Order in the courtroom. Order.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS153
The judge faces a soldier.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS154
They seal the doors.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS155
Uniformed soldiers seal every exit.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS156
From overhead, the three black Sedans round the corner and continue down a one-way street.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS157
Outside the courthouse, SOMEONE slowly tilts his head.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS158
He watches a large armored truck, reverse behind a building corner at the end of the block.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS159
Shifting his gaze, SOMEONE's eyes linger on its protruding front end.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS160
In the truck, a dark-haired man checks the timer on his watch.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS161
Two masked snipers dressed in all black, survey from the courthouse rooftop,
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS162
as the Sedans arrive at the military checkpoint.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS163
In the courtroom, the prisoners stand attentively in their holding cells.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS164
SOMEONE glances over at SOMEONE's son.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS165
Using a rounded mirror on a pole, a soldier checks the underside of the first Sedan,
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS166
then quickly moves on to the second.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS167
The windshield's glare conceals the driver's face.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS168
The prisoners simultaneously sit in their adjacent glass cells, and SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS169
Slowly turning, SOMEONE connects with his glaring eyes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS170
The old man averts his gaze and faces the courtroom.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS171
At the checkpoint, the soldier finishes searching the third Sedan and waves them through.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS172
SOMEONE steps toward the crowd of protesters.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS174
As the checkpoint bar rises, the black Sedans enter the restricted area beneath the rooftop snipers.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS175
They round a raised curb by a side entrance and park in a line along the courthouse.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS176
The dark-haired man holds out his hand.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS177
His bearded driver glances up.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS179
The man casually chews gum.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS180
The driver reluctantly hands his boss a cellphone detonator with wires and electronics taped on.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS181
The three Sedans remain still as the court session continues inside.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS182
Behind him, armed men in body armor and gas masks fill the truck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS183
The Sedans explode,
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS185
blasting through a courtroom wall. SOMEONE rolls on the ground as frantic civilians scatter through the smoke and SOMEONE. Rounding a corner, the armored truck barrels toward the blast point.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS186
SOMEONE climbs to his feet and jumps through the chaos.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS187
Inside, SOMEONE kicks the grate off his cell and finds SOMEONE hunched next to his.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS188
The armored truck parks beside the charred Sedans,
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS189
and the masked men pour out the back.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS190
SOMEONE helps SOMEONE to his feet, as the men rush inside the building.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS191
A masked man tosses a duffel bag to his dark-haired boss.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS192
SOMEONE leaps a half wall and faces SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS193
Come on, come on, come on now. The masked men charge up the stairs.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS195
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE down a dark corridor.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS196
Sitting up, an injured soldier reaches for his weapon as the masked men enter.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS197
They shoot the soldier without hesitation.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS199
Outside, the view through the smoke-filled air.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS200
SOMEONE emerges through the haze, gripping SOMEONE's handcuffs.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS201
The old man struggles to break free.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS203
SOMEONE grabs a pistol from a deceased officer and pushes SOMEONE forward.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS204
In the courtroom, the masked men scour the SOMEONE, aiming flashlight-mounted rifles.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS205
Their boss finds the glass cells with no one inside.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS206
They continue searching as the masked brunette enters.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS207
A hanging florescent light flickers behind her.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS209
The masked woman mercilessly executes an injured civilian and pieces of ceiling sprinkle down.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS210
She slowly proceeds through the room, stopping beside the dark-haired boss.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS213
A squad car speeds by SOMEONE and SOMEONE. As SOMEONE starts away, SOMEONE pulls him toward the blue van.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS216
the woman follows the dark-haired man outside.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS219
With SOMEONE in the passenger seat, he reverses on to the street.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS221
He tosses SOMEONE a jacket.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS225
SOMEONE blocks the van, and SOMEONE slams on the brakes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS226
His eyes widen.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS227
Elsewhere, SOMEONE hurries down a debris-covered street, as two of his armed men flank him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS228
Moving to the driver's door, SOMEONE pulls on the locked handle.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS229
SOMEONE exits the van and looks about.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS230
Spinning around, SOMEONE spots the van nearby.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS231
SOMEONE sees SOMEONE and his crew.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS234
SOMEONE hops out.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS235
SOMEONE drags SOMEONE back and SOMEONE's
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS236
small thug fires.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS237
We need him alive.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS238
SOMEONE aims at his father's head.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS239
Glaring, SOMEONE shakes his head.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS240
He backs toward the van.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS241
SOMEONE gets inside as the armored truck reaches SOMEONE. He and his men hurry inside. SOMEONE takes off, leaving his father on the street.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS242
The armored truck rumbles toward SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS243
SOMEONE eyes the truck in his rear view mirror as he drives over a cobblestone courtyard. The truck follows, smashing through a cement monument. Returning to the street, it sideswipes a car. SOMEONE gets in a flatbed truck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS244
A man chases him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS245
SOMEONE swarms through traffic. Reaching over, he grabs an earpiece from the glove box and puts it on.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS246
In an Ops room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS247
A drone soars through the sky.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS248
The armored truck sends a parked car flying.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS249
The drone changes course.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS250
Moscow police swarm the massive Garden Ring Avenue.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS251
SOMEONE takes a hard right turn. In the flatbed truck, SOMEONE weaves through traffic.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS252
As SOMEONE speeds through a stop sign, an intersecting car slides sideways and gets hit head-on by another.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS253
The armored truck bulldozes through both cars and smashes into SOMEONE's van.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS254
As the van spins a 180 degrees, SOMEONE's truck pushes a sideway Sedan into his front end.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS255
Face-to-face, the truck forces SOMEONE backwards.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS256
SOMEONE smashes into the armored truck's rear end.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS257
Reversing, SOMEONE whips around and drives off with a determined stare.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS258
The armored truck quickly follows.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS259
Switching gears, SOMEONE releases the clutch and peels out after them.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS260
The chase continues on a narrow street between two rows of cars parked on an angle. SOMEONE barely evades collisions as the armored truck smashes into every single rear end.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS262
SOMEONE's bearded driver narrows his eyes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS263
As SOMEONE follows, his truck rips off the open door of a parked car.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS264
SOMEONE takes an abrupt U-turn on to an onramp for a Riverside Avenue.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS265
As the truck follows, it clips the Sedan and sends it soaring off the ramp onto the street below.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS266
SOMEONE struggles to make the sharp U-turn.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS268
A hundred yards ahead, the armored truck speeds down the street. Further on, SOMEONE leads the way, weaving through oncoming traffic.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS269
He narrowly misses a Sedan.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS270
Dodging a tractor-trailer, SOMEONE's bearded driver smashes into a parked van.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS272
With the armored truck close behind, SOMEONE turns off the street.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS273
He continues down an onramp.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS274
Following, the armored truck hits a car and fishtails around another. SOMEONE keeps his flatbed right on their heels.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS275
SOMEONE's truck rear-ends a hatchback, shoving the innocent civilian forward.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS277
Beneath an overpass, a car evades SOMEONE and hits the wall.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS278
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE in his side mirror.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS279
A man emerges from the roof with an RPG and aims at SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS280
SOMEONE pulls the emergency brake and as he spins, the rocket soars over his flatbed and strikes a garbage truck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS281
Spinning out of control, SOMEONE's truck rams off a motorcycle and barrel rolls over a line of parked cars.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS282
The tail end flips upward and the truck comes down perfectly on its wheels.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS283
Climbing down, SOMEONE lands hard on his back.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS284
The aging man grimaces.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS285
Elsewhere, SOMEONE continues down a highway, shifting his glaring eyes between his mirror and the road.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS286
He speeds in to traffic.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS287
On foot, SOMEONE hurries into a busy street.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS288
As he attempts to stop swerving cars, an SUV hits him head on.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS289
Flying off the hood, SOMEONE rolls on the hard pavement.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS290
A large Russian man exits the SUV, waving his arms.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS291
SOMEONE punches him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS292
SOMEONE rushes in to the man's SUV.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS293
SOMEONE takes off. Meanwhile, SOMEONE speeds down an off-ramp, weaving through cars.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS294
In his mirror, he sees the armored truck right on his tail.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS295
The bearded driver narrows his eyes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS296
He accelerates through the off-ramp's concrete wall, plummeting 15 feet on to a taxi, which launches upward into the overpass.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS297
SOMEONE glances in his side mirror. On another street, SOMEONE zips through traffic, using both sides of the road. He veers on to the overpass. Looking over, he spots SOMEONE's blue van and the armored truck speeding down the highway below. SOMEONE clenches his jaw. Two cars collide as he screeches to a halt.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS298
Quickly reversing, he turns the front end toward SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS299
SOMEONE bursts through the guardrail and down on to a car-hauling tractor-trailer in traffic.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS300
He bumbles along the entire trailer to a lower level and crushes a red sports car.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS301
Ramping off the end, SOMEONE continues on top of more tractor-trailers stuck in standstill traffic.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS302
He drives out of a gravel truck and onto the tops of civilian cars.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS304
Crushing windshields, SOMEONE barrels over several more vehicles, then jumps the center barrier.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS305
Speeds away from the halted traffic and continues the pursuit.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS306
Checking his mirror, SOMEONE takes an off-ramp.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS307
He quickly soars on to another highway, as the armored truck closes in. The truck hits the van's rear.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS308
Struggling, SOMEONE regains control of the wheel.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS309
SOMEONE's truck accelerates beside the van and performs a pit maneuver, spinning SOMEONE out of control.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS310
Clenching his jaw, SOMEONE yanks at the wheel as the van wildly spins.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS311
The truck's front end connects with the van's side and bulldozes it down the highway.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS312
Glancing over, SOMEONE thrusts his middle finger toward SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS313
SOMEONE advances in the SUV.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS314
SOMEONE keeps his eyes on the armored truck ahead, rapidly approaching he collides with the rear end.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS315
He hits the truck again and SOMEONE's van spins away, passing by SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS316
SOMEONE glances back at the van.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS317
SOMEONE accelerates beside the armored truck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS318
He swerves repeatedly into the truck's side, and smoke billows from its front end.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS319
The vehicles separate around a civilian car.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS320
Gaining control, SOMEONE turns the van with traffic and rejoins the chase.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS321
SOMEONE keeps his SUV snug against the truck's side.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS322
SOMEONE forces the truck toward the side of the road.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS323
With his face tense, SOMEONE gives a final bump.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS324
The truck rams off a concrete barrier, flipping the massive vehicle through the air.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS325
The bearded driver screams as they soar off an overpass.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS327
The truck flies through an enormous concrete drainpipe, toppling the tractor-trailer carrying it. On its side, SOMEONE's SUV slides to a stop.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS328
The armored truck topples over.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS329
Meanwhile, SOMEONE drives the van with a weary glare.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS330
Pressing his lips together, he steers the van in a U-turn across the highway. At the overturned SUV, SOMEONE kicks the windshield from its frame. He struggles to pull himself out and on to his feet.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS331
Steam wafts from the engine as he clears the vehicle.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS332
Below, SOMEONE and his men recover from their collision.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS333
On the overpass, SOMEONE hurdles a low barrier and cuts across traffic.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS334
He stays the cars with an outstretched hand. Below, a police cruiser arrives at the crash site.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS335
As the door opens, SOMEONE shoots the officers inside.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS336
SOMEONE fires up at SOMEONE, who ducks behind the metal railings. His son pulls up beside him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS337
SOMEONE obeys.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS338
SOMEONE pulls away, leaving SOMEONE behind and darts through traffic. SOMEONE rides in back, holding on to a pole.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS339
On a walkway, SOMEONE uses a phone.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS354
Now, in a dim ramshackle hallway, standing with SOMEONE and SOMEONE, SOMEONE beckons SOMEONE over.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS355
As he joins the others, his son leads SOMEONE into the safe house.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS356
SOMEONE uses a cellphone.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS357
SOMEONE takes in the setup.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS358
His son picks his handcuffs open.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS359
SOMEONE changes clothes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS360
SOMEONE tucks a fresh shirt into his pants.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS361
Pausing, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE who wears a solemn gaze.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS362
SOMEONE takes passports from a safe.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS363
SOMEONE checks an ammo cartridge in the handle of a small switchblade.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS364
SOMEONE cocks his head. SOMEONE takes a deep breath then faces.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS365
SOMEONE offers a phone, but holds it back.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS366
SOMEONE stows the knife in his boot. SOMEONE taps SOMEONE on the arm, signaling the agent to step away with them.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS367
As they go, SOMEONE dials a number on the borrowed cellphone.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS374
Glancing aside, he pauses and fixes a grave stare.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS375
SOMEONE faces his own reflection in a mirrored cabinet.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS377
A speeding bullet grazes SOMEONE's arm, another tears through SOMEONE's head, killing him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS378
Outside, three masked men break a door open.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS379
SOMEONE sprints across the room and protectively tackles SOMEONE. SOMEONE finds an assault rifle.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS380
He fires on the men, as his son crawls with SOMEONE across the floor. The intruders drop under the gunfire, but more stream in behind them. Scrambling into the next room, SOMEONE hits a button. A blast consumes the entryway landing, taking several men with it.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS381
SOMEONE grabs a portable frame.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS385
As he attaches it to a far wall, we recognize a small detonator at its top.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS386
The frame blasts a large hole in the wall.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS387
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS389
As all three pass through the hole and head through a hall, more gunmen shoot at them.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS390
Now a bird's eye view shows tightly packed buildings in a city neighborhood.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS392
As we drift closer, the three men emerge onto a rooftop.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS393
Wielding a handgun, SOMEONE follows SOMEONE and his son past a scaffold-supported sign.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS394
They descend a caged ladder.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS395
Landing first, SOMEONE urges the two older men onward.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS396
As they arrive in a shadowy market with closed doors, SOMEONE brings SOMEONE to a bench.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS397
SOMEONE rips off SOMEONE's sleeve and makes a tourniquet.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS398
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE his jacket.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS399
SOMEONE hands over his cellphone. SOMEONE drops it on the ground and stomps on it repeatedly, smashing it to pieces.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS400
SOMEONE lifts his brow wryly.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS401
SOMEONE checks the gun's chamber and clip, then holsters it in his waistband.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS402
SOMEONE shifts his exasperated gaze as his son helps SOMEONE to his feet and urges him onward.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS403
Now, a long passenger train breaks on its tracks.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS404
Our view lists to take in the station, in the midst of the city.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS405
Inside, SOMEONE opens a locker and digs through the content.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS406
He hauls out a bag and slams the locker shut.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS407
Beneath an over cast sky, we zoom back from the steeple of the Ukraina Hotel. SOMEONE leads his companions to the edge of a construction site.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS408
Leaning out from hiding and craning his neck, the young agent peers up at the hotel.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS409
With a resentful sneer, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE with SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS410
The two older men lean against a construction truck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS411
SOMEONE turns his head away, his gaze solemn and distant.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS412
His arms folded, SOMEONE gives an understanding nod.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS413
Returning, SOMEONE listens in.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS414
SOMEONE heaves a regretful sigh and shakes his head as SOMEONE eavesdrops unnoticed.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS415
SOMEONE blinks thoughtfully, then rejoins the older men.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS416
The agent retrieves his bag and leads them onward.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS417
SOMEONE keeps an eye on their surroundings.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS418
Now in the hotel laundry, the men hide.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS419
SOMEONE approaches a worker.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS420
SOMEONE pays off the worker and beckons his companion.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS421
Now, he swipes an employee key card in an elevator's control panel.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS422
The open doors frame SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they wait.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS423
As the door slides shut, SOMEONE digs in his bag and retrieves a shotgun with cartridges stored along the barrel. He hands it off to his father, then readies an assault rifle for use.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS424
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE, who lifts his brow sheepishly.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS425
SOMEONE glances at the Russian and shrugs his head.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS426
SOMEONE frowns.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS427
Leaning against the wall, SOMEONE's straightens.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS428
Now, tall windows in a stained glass ceiling allow weak sunlight into a vast deserted ballroom.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS429
Dining chairs stand on tables with champagne hued tablecloth.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS430
Sparkling chandeliers hang from both the ceiling and wooden storage carts on the floor.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS431
At the far end of the room,
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS432
a threshold shows the three men venturing through a pair of tall glass doors.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS433
They cross a brief red-carpeted lobby.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS434
Then reach the threshold and pause.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS435
Taking point, SOMEONE cautiously scans his surroundings with his weapon ready, as he leads the others in.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS438
The tall windows show a fog-enshrouded city outside,as they cross the room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS441
From behind stacked chairs,a shapely figure with long dark hair steps into view. Her feature's out of focus. Our view sharpens to reveal SOMEONE's brunette companion.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS443
She wears a pale blouse and skirt. She hurries toward SOMEONE. With a loving smile, he meets her halfway.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS444
Embracing, they hold each other tight. With a crooked smirk, SOMEONE faces the Russian.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS446
The father and daughter part. He caresses her cheek.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS449
His eyes wide, SOMEONE turns his head to face his father. Staying close to her father, SOMEONE notices SOMEONE with a bewildered vulnerable gaze.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS453
Leaving his daughter, SOMEONE heads toward a window. SOMEONE follows.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS454
SOMEONE hangs back, keeping an eye on SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS455
The young woman watches her father with a breathless
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS457
Keeping his weapon ready, SOMEONE presses his lips together and plants his feet.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS458
SOMEONE faces him distractedly, then nods.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS459
SOMEONE gives a skeptical nod.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS460
At a window, SOMEONE lifts the grated lid from a wooden radiator encasement.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS462
SOMEONE takes a couple of steps closer to the Russian's daughter.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS463
Leaning over the encasement, SOMEONE reaches in up to his shoulder. His fingertips brush a small parcel within.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS464
Gazing out, SOMEONE notices a military grade helicopter parked below. SOMEONE blinks at the older American.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS466
As SOMEONE pulls out the small bundle, SOMEONE drives into view.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS467
SOMEONE pushes SOMEONE behind him. Wielding a rifle, SOMEONE beckons a team of armed thugs out to join him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS468
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sidle back to SOMEONE. Nearby, SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE's men helplessly.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS471
Facing SOMEONE and the Americans, SOMEONE munches a carrot. SOMEONE gives a cool nod.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS473
SOMEONE reaches for SOMEONE. She takes him hostage.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS474
She jams a gun into his cheek.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS475
SOMEONE gestures with a carrot. SOMEONE drops his shotgun and his son reluctantly follows suit.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS476
With a clenched jaw, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE who glares out at him from behind her father's shoulder.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS477
SOMEONE signals to two men.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS478
One zip ties SOMEONE's wrist before him. The other binds SOMEONE's hands behind his back.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS479
The thugs force the Americans to their knees.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS483
The beautiful woman leans her lips close to his ear.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS484
As SOMEONE leaves with SOMEONE, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS485
He swallows a bite of carrot.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS486
Stifling a smirk, SOMEONE nods.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS487
SOMEONE chucks the remaining carrot aside, then launches into a soft shoe dance.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS488
SOMEONE shoots his father a wry look and SOMEONE sighs patiently.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS489
Dancing over to the Americans, SOMEONE kicks SOMEONE's gun away.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS490
He shuffles over to SOMEONE's gun and sweeps it away as well. The Russian gives a shrug.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS491
SOMEONE lowers his smiling gaze.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS493
SOMEONE rests his hands on his knees and leans close to the Americans.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS495
He beats them with his rifle.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS496
The father and son crumple, but the thugs haul them back on to their knees.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS497
SOMEONE stares boldly and SOMEONE spits.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS498
Meanwhile on a rooftop, a bald man escorts SOMEONE and SOMEONE to the military grade chopper.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS500
In the ballroom, SOMEONE falls from SOMEONE's punches. SOMEONE kicks him hard in his side.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS501
He backhands SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS502
SOMEONE surreptitiously reaches for the knife in his boot, as SOMEONE delivers a knee to SOMEONE's face.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS503
His thugs pick up the men from the floor and set them back on their knees.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS504
SOMEONE primps his dark curly hair and chews gum.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS505
SOMEONE sees SOMEONE's knife behind his back.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS506
SOMEONE works to cut his bonds. SOMEONE glances at the knife and smiles.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS507
Gazing at his Dad, SOMEONE laughs too.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS508
As SOMEONE turns to his thugs with a grin, SOMEONE continues sawing at his bond.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS509
SOMEONE shrugs and approaches SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS510
SOMEONE cuts his hands free, as SOMEONE lunges at SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS511
SOMEONE shoots down two thugs with the knife.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS512
SOMEONE pushes SOMEONE into a crystal chandelier.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS513
SOMEONE stabs a blonde haired man in the leg, then takes his weapon and uses him as a human shield.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS514
SOMEONE pummels SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS515
A man fires at SOMEONE, hitting his blonde comrade.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS516
The agent fires back, then drops the blonde man's body and runs to his father.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS517
SOMEONE scoops up a machine gun as he follows.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS518
SOMEONE rises slightly from the floor and takes aim.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS519
The Americans leap behind the bar.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS520
The remaining thugs pelt it with bullets.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS522
They look up at stained glass skylights.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS523
The Americans get on their backs and fire up at them.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS524
The shattered panes send giant glass fragments raining down on the Russians, who cower amid the dust and SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS525
SOMEONE retreats from the ballroom, as SOMEONE and SOMEONE continue their barrage. They pop up from behind the bar and shoot at the two remaining men, who go down in a storm of bullets.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS526
As SOMEONE fires a few more bullets, father and son survey the scene.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS527
Now SOMEONE scurries across the rooftop, to the waiting chopper. The bald man runs up to him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS528
They get into the military helicopter.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS529
Inside the hotel, SOMEONE and SOMEONE jump over the bar and cross the hazy room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS530
SOMEONE inspects the area, then jogs over to the window.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS532
He watches the chopper lift off from the rooftop helipad below.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS533
At an open side of the chopper, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit facing out.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS534
SOMEONE topples a chair as he storms from the window.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS535
Flying low over city rooftops, the helicopter banks to its left.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS536
SOMEONE watches as the helicopter makes a graceful wide turn and heads back in the direction of the hotel.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS537
As it swiftly approaches them, SOMEONE signals to his pacing son.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS538
The heavily armed vessel looms before the building. SOMEONE reaches for SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS539
They duck as the chopper bombards the ballroom with its heavy artillery. The rounds tear into the building and lay waste to the interior. The men huddle behind the wall.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS540
SOMEONE spies scaffolding through a window across the way.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS541
They scramble to their feet and run through the room. Machine gun fire whizzes by, narrowly missing them.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS543
The copter pulls left to follow the fleeing men. SOMEONE and SOMEONE run side-by-side, and SOMEONE drops his gun as they take a flying leap out of the window.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS544
They rip through green netting and crash-land on a wooden platform.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS546
SOMEONE gets on his feet and looks around.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS547
They break through the platform and into a red plastic shoot.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS548
As they slide down, the helicopter gets into position and fires at it.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS549
SOMEONE and SOMEONE plummet through the shoot. Under heavy fire, it falls apart.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS550
The pair emerge from the tube, and break through several more wooden platforms before landing in a large metal dumpster of cardboard and plastic wrapping.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS551
The chopper holds position and hovers overhead.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS555
The chopper makes a hard left turn.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS556
Below, SOMEONE and SOMEONE get to their feet.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS557
SOMEONE holds his son's shoulder as they step into the street.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS558
Dust and SOMEONE drift down over police cars and frightened bystanders.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS559
The Americans walk past a limping woman.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS560
They run across an empty street, as a police cruiser whizzes by.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS561
On the chopper, SOMEONE takes out his phone and makes a call. SOMEONE walks at the head of a large crowd.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS565
In slow motion, SOMEONE hangs up his phone and leads a pack of lawyers and judges in suits and robes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS566
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter a defunct department store, full of mannequins and dusty display cases.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS567
SOMEONE limps slightly and SOMEONE staggers.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS568
He sits on the floor and opens his jacket to look at his side.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS569
A piece of rebar protrudes from his stomach.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS570
SOMEONE plucks a piece of glass from the wound in his knee.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS571
SOMEONE stares thoughtfully ahead, his young face caked with blood.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS572
He slowly tilts his head back, and his father turns to him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS573
He looks at his son with a smirk.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS574
SOMEONE returns his gaze glumly.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS575
He reaches over.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS576
SOMEONE braces himself.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS577
SOMEONE pulls out rebar and examines.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS578
SOMEONE looks at the small metal piece, as SOMEONE chucks it aside.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS580
He helps his son up.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS581
Now outside a nightclub, green laser lights and strobe flashes illuminate the exterior of the building.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS582
Nearby, sleek and shiny luxury cars sit in a dark parking lot.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS583
SOMEONE crouches by the passenger door of a Maserati and attempts to pick the lock.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS584
His father comes up behind him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS585
He shows SOMEONE a set of keys.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS586
Now they pop the trunk of another car.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS587
They find a stockpile of guns.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS588
They shut the trunk.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS589
Now they drive on a rain slicked country road in a Maybach.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS590
SOMEONE glances at his father. SOMEONE looks away, leaning back in his seat.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS591
He turns to the passenger window.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS592
Now, our bird's eye view slowly moves toward the Chernobyl Power Plant.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS593
A few large lights illuminate the exterior of the facility in an otherwise dark landscape.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS594
Inside a flashlight shines on a portrait of Gorbachev.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS595
As our view shifts, the flashlight passes over a high ceilinged open office space.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS596
A wall of small filing drawers stands in disarray and the smattering of papers litters the floor.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS597
Their probing light leads back to a group of figures in black hazmat suits.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS601
Vertical lights flicker on, illuminating a corridor.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS602
The file is in the inner vault.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS603
The group led by SOMEONE heads for the corridor.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS604
They move past the series of tall thin florescent lights in a heavy circular door.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS605
SOMEONE takes the group deeper into the vault, beyond the set of metal bars.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS606
As they inspect the area with their flashlights, he faces a wall of safety deposit boxes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS608
Now, the Maybach coasts slowly along a dirt road, past a graffitied sign, and several dingy dilapidated structures.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS609
The car makes a slight left and rolls to a stop.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS610
As SOMEONE surveys the scene, his son raises a pair of binoculars and focuses them on a group of men in yellow suits outside the plant.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS611
SOMEONE lowers the binoculars.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS612
SOMEONE looks at him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS613
He returns his gaze to the power plant, where men work frantically and dart about the facility.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS615
Now inside the plant, SOMEONE stands behind the tall florescence.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS617
He keeps his gaze and flashlight trained on SOMEONE, who feels along the wall of deposit boxes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS618
SOMEONE eyes her father as he slows his pace and glides his hand over box number 475.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS619
He lightly raps on it then turns to his kidnappers.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS620
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE open the Maybach's trunk, and peruse their stockpile of military grade weaponry.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS621
They strip down to T-shirts.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS622
SOMEONE picks up a black leather jacket and puts it on, as SOMEONE dons a combat vest filled with grenades.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS623
He smiles at SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS624
SOMEONE reaches into the trunk and hands him a sawed-off shotgun.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS625
SOMEONE picks up an assault rifle and puts the strap over his head.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS626
SOMEONE picks up a similar weapon and slings it over his shoulder.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS627
Standing behind his son, he looks at SOMEONE and his expression softens.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS628
He pauses and watches the young man, who turns around and stares at his father.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS629
Looking away, SOMEONE nods a little.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS630
SOMEONE starts to speak, then stops himself.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS631
He fixes his gaze on SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS632
The young man looks away. He opens his mouth and shakes it.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS634
SOMEONE looks down.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS635
SOMEONE gazes thoughtfully.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS636
SOMEONE swallows, and his glassy eyes drift away from SOMEONE toward the ground.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS637
He smiles at SOMEONE, then playfully lifts his chin in a nod.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS638
SOMEONE stares at his dad. The two men shake hands.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS639
SOMEONE shuts the trunk.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS640
Inside the plant, a drill bores into the deposit box. SOMEONE watches intently from behind his mask.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS641
SOMEONE shoots him a look. The drill breaks through to the other side, and the operator yanks it open.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS642
Another man opens the door completely to reveal a seemingly empty shelf.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS643
SOMEONE leans over and inspects the back wall of the locker.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS644
He turns around.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS646
SOMEONE hands him the old bundle from the radiator.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS647
With gloved hands, SOMEONE unwraps it as SOMEONE watches.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS648
SOMEONE drops the cloth and paper wrappings, and holds up a dark metal cylinder.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS649
He slowly turns the base. The cylinder pops open.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS650
Elsewhere, a dust covered gas mask lies among other piles of decrepit withering SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS651
SOMEONE cautiously enters in front of his dad, aiming a flashlight-mounted rifle around the decaying room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS652
SOMEONE's weapon hangs at his side.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS653
Scanning the mezzanine level, SOMEONE leads them forward.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS654
A steady trickle of water drifts in a nearby doorway, as they proceed toward another room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS655
In the vault, SOMEONE inserts the cylinder key into a lock at the back of the box.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS657
Tiny triangular wings pop out of the key.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS658
Inserting it further, SOMEONE turns the cylinder clockwise,
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS659
then slides the hands of its curved outer shell together in a perfect match.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS660
The prisoner twists the key, another quarter turn to the right.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS662
Two halves of the thick steel wall swing open like doors. A gust of air rustles the papers on the floor. They shine flashlights into the large hidden chamber, revealing dozens of aluminum cases stacked throughout.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS663
SOMEONE lifts a tablet, reading the levels of radiation.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS665
Now, a massive cylindrical tank in a steel cage with wheels, hangs beneath the helicopter as it cruises toward the sprawling facility.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS666
Spotlights illuminate a wide clearing by a building's entrance. Dust swirls as the chopper flies the tank above its landing zone.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS667
Inside, SOMEONE and his dad cautiously move down a corridor. Outside, the helicopter slowly lowers the tank into position on the ground.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS668
As the chopper flies away, SOMEONE's men reverse a large eight-wheel vehicle to the tank's hitch.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS669
Inside, the choppers light passes through the corridor windows and illuminates SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS670
An armed man in a ski mask arrives, and SOMEONE aims.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS671
SOMEONE takes out a second one.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS672
SOMEONE creeps forward.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS673
Outside, the vehicle parks the tank and SOMEONE's men rush towards it.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS675
Wearing hazmat suits, her men feed hoses into the vault as others enter with flashlight-mounted spraying devices.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS676
They douse everything with the tank's substance. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE find a large indoor pool, filled with leaves and dark stagnant water.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS677
SOMEONE eyes the scummy room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS678
In the vault, SOMEONE slowly walks between stacks of the armored cases.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS679
Watching the radiation levels decrease on her tablet.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS680
As she reaches the back wall, the tablet readings steadily drop to almost nothing.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS681
Lifting an arm the fair-skinned beauty carefully removes her gas mask.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS682
She tilts her head and takes a small slow breath.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS683
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb a set of stairs to a balcony level overlooking the pool.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS684
SOMEONE takes a few steps, then leads them up a vertical ladder on the wall.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS685
SOMEONE opens an armored case, revealing two rows of metallic objects.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS686
She steps away from SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS687
SOMEONE forces SOMEONE forward.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS688
He pushes SOMEONE aside.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS689
A bullet blasts through SOMEONE's head.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS690
SOMEONE lowers the gun.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS693
He empties the clip in SOMEONE's dead body, then connects a hard glare with his daughter's smiling sadistic gaze.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS694
SOMEONE steps forward and casually tosses the pistol on to the body.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS695
As SOMEONE saunters across the vault, the muscular bald thug drags SOMEONE's body away.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS702
Shifting her weight, she approaches her father.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS703
As she gazes into his eyes, SOMEONE flashes a loving smile and throws her arms around him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS704
Separating, their eyes connect.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS706
She beams as SOMEONE rubs her cheek and steps past.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS707
He turns back with a hardened look.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS710
Her smile quickly fades.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS713
Outside the entrance, the helicopter touches down in a whirlwind of dust.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS714
SOMEONE and SOMEONE creep along a rooftop with their weapons in hand.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS715
As they separate, SOMEONE glances over and receives a slight nod from his dad.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS716
Moving forward, they approach two masked guards, both facing the roof's edge.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS717
SOMEONE bashes his thug with the butt of his rifle, as SOMEONE slices the other's throat.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS718
In the vault, one of SOMEONE's men slides a uranium cylinder back into the case and secures the latch.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS719
Using a walk behind electric forklift,
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS720
he wheels the case on the path lit by the florescent lights.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS721
Meanwhile, SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach a large block letter sign on the roof's edge.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS722
They gaze down at all of SOMEONE's men and equipment.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS723
On the ground, two men carry a case of uranium, as a masked man barks orders. SOMEONE follows his son back across the roof.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS724
Now, SOMEONE hurries to her dad. SOMEONE hands her father a radio.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS727
He tucks radio into his breast pocket as she runs out of the vault.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS728
SOMEONE glances toward the doorway then steps forward, shifting his gaze across the room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS729
Strolling deeper inside, the elderly man eyes his merchandise and removes glasses from his pocket.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS730
SOMEONE unfolds the frame and puts them on, as he arrives at SOMEONE's body.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS731
With an aggressive kick, he rolls the body over and crouches beside it.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS732
He quickly searches SOMEONE's pockets and pulls a cellphone from his pants, eyeing it closely.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS733
Now shirtless, the bald muscular thug waves the truck driver on, as he jaunts to the chopper.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS734
A subordinate hands him a rifle.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS737
The bald thug cocks the gun and strolls up the chopper's loading ramp into its interior's red glow.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS738
Turning around, he waves the truck on board as it reverses into position.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS739
In the vault, SOMEONE holds the phone.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS740
At a spa, SOMEONE sits up in a steamy massage room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS741
The female masseuse hands him a phone and walks away.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS745
SOMEONE's face tenses.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS755
The masseur puts him in a chokehold.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS756
The phone flies from SOMEONE's hand, as he frantically yanks at the hit man's solid grasp.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS757
His legs flail beneath his white bath towel.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS758
A sadistic grin spreads on SOMEONE's face as he listens to SOMEONE gurgle his final breath.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS759
The hit man gently lays the body down. SOMEONE releases a triumphant sigh.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS761
He lowers the phone from his ear and whips it at the wall.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS762
Outside, SOMEONE exits the chopper.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS766
SOMEONE moves through the vault.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS767
The Russian freezes, then turns to face SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS768
SOMEONE slumps his shoulders and winces.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS769
With wide eyes, SOMEONE nods. As the old man leans on a rack, SOMEONE scans the room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS770
He eyes SOMEONE skeptically.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS771
SOMEONE steps forward.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS772
SOMEONE's gaze tenses.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS773
He studies an armored case.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS774
SOMEONE slowly follows SOMEONE, who eyes the pistol beside SOMEONE's body.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS775
Slowly turning, SOMEONE shares a tense look with his dad.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS776
SOMEONE aims toward SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS778
SOMEONE pins him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS779
SOMEONE shifts his gaze between them. Looking away, SOMEONE spots the pistol beside SOMEONE's dead body.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS780
SOMEONE smirks at SOMEONE as SOMEONE shakes his head.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS781
He looks down from SOMEONE's piercing glare. As SOMEONE pins him by the neck, SOMEONE reaches into his coat.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS783
A sinister grin spreads on SOMEONE's face.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS784
SOMEONE listens on the radio.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS785
He faces SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS786
SOMEONE raises his brow as SOMEONE seethes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS787
SOMEONE head-butts SOMEONE, then quickly pulls him back in.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS788
He shoves the old man toward the entrance
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS789
Outside, SOMEONE yanks the bald thugs weapon away and runs toward the building.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS790
SOMEONE forces SOMEONE forward at gunpoint, as they proceed on the illuminated path from the vault.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS791
Stepping through the rounded vault entrance, SOMEONE readies his weapon.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS792
His eyes scan the large cluttered room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS793
SOMEONE emerges.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS794
They take cover as the bald thug pops out.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS795
The gunfire pins them down and SOMEONE scampers across the room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS797
SOMEONE quickly fires, then retracts behind a cement pillar. As the bald shirtless thug fires wildly, bullets pierce the hoses, spraying chemicals into the air.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS798
SOMEONE returns fire.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS799
Fleeing, SOMEONE rushes up a stairwell. SOMEONE shoots quick bursts around the pillar and his father joins in.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS800
A glass panel shatters beside SOMEONE. Emptying his clip, SOMEONE tosses his rifle aside.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS801
SOMEONE uses the radio.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS803
SOMEONE runs off as SOMEONE fires.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS804
SOMEONE waves a hand signal to his son.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS805
Outside, SOMEONE hurries up the helicopter's loading ramp.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS806
Glancing back, she enters past the truck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS807
Inside, the hoses continue releasing gas.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS808
As the bald thug fires, SOMEONE tosses a grenade to his dad.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS809
Peeking out, SOMEONE notices the small forklift.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS810
SOMEONE sits in the chopper's cockpit.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS814
Bullets ricochet off the forklift, as it creeps toward the bald thug.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS815
SOMEONE returns fire from behind the pillar. The forklift comes to rest beside the thug, and he notices the grenade. SOMEONE covers his head.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS816
A massive explosion rips through the room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS817
Blue and orange flame swirl from the blast point, wrapping around the pillar as SOMEONE cowers behind.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS818
The flames settle throughout the incinerated room. Outside, the chopper's rotors spin.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS819
SOMEONE quickly stands. Bursting through a door, SOMEONE staggers on to the roof.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS820
He grabs a weapon beside one of his dead men. SOMEONE rips off his jacket and pulls a pistol from his waistband.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS821
He runs through the flaming room in his dirty and bloodstained white T-shirt. SOMEONE sprints up the stairs as his father exits the building. SOMEONE sees the helicopter still on the ground. Shielding his face, he rushes toward the loading ramp as the rotor intensifies. In the cockpit, the pilot readies for liftoff.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS822
Leaping up, SOMEONE grabs on to the open ramp door as the chopper slowly lifts off.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS823
The aging detective struggles to pull himself up.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS824
Thick dust swirls beneath the rising helicopter.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS825
SOMEONE continues sprinting up the stairs, as SOMEONE climbs into the cargo hold.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS826
He crawls forward with a pistol in his hand.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS829
As SOMEONE army-crawls beneath the truck, a thug enters by the front end.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS830
SOMEONE aims at his legs.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS832
The thug collapses and SOMEONE finishes him off.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS833
Inside, SOMEONE reaches the top and hurries on to the roof, with his pistol aimed.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS834
SOMEONE fires on him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS836
As SOMEONE returns fire, a bullet strikes his vest, knocking him down. SOMEONE blindly fires.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS838
There is a small arms fire coming from the roof. The chopper hovers toward the roof. Through a small window, SOMEONE peers into the cockpit at SOMEONE and the pilot. He grabs the steel handle and tugs. Stepping back, SOMEONE aims at the door.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS845
The chopper turns to face the roof.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS846
Looking out a side door, SOMEONE sees the guns engaging.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS847
SOMEONE fires his pistol in the air.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS850
The heavy caliber bullets rip into the building, following the helicopter's searchlights.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS851
SOMEONE secures a chain to the truck and tops inside.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS853
SOMEONE clenches her jaw and fires.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS854
As bullets strike the roof, the searchlights wash over SOMEONE. He shuts his eyes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS855
SOMEONE drives the truck out of the cargo hold, tilting the chopper's nose upward.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS857
The chain tightens and jolts the truck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS858
Opening his eyes, SOMEONE sees the chopper shooting upward and losing control.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS861
SOMEONE sees the truck hanging out and hurls the radio aside.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS862
Spinning wildly, the chopper's tail rotor chops through the block letter sign.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS865
SOMEONE hops to his feet.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS866
In slow motion, he runs across a series of docks spanning the roof as sparks fly from the rotor blades hitting the sign.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS867
SOMEONE zips through the dust-filled air.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS868
With glaring eyes, SOMEONE dives toward SOMEONE who tries to aim at him.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS870
He knocks SOMEONE down and quickly stands.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS872
SOMEONE drags SOMEONE to the edge.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS873
The truck smashes into the building and the door shoots open, SOMEONE barely hangs on.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS874
A plunging case nearly strikes SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS875
He hurls SOMEONE off the roof.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS876
In slow motion, he plummets - face up, his eyes wide.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS877
SOMEONE glares as the chopper's tail rotor obliterates SOMEONE.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS878
SOMEONE hangs from the truck's bumper, as the chopper spins.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS879
SOMEONE runs along the roof's edge.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS880
The spinning chopper nears the roof. Kicking his legs, SOMEONE keeps hold of the bumper. SOMEONE continues to the opposite side.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS881
As the truck swings wide, SOMEONE lets go.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS882
Flailing, he flies towards an enormous window in slow motion.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS884
SOMEONE lands hard, rolling in shattered glass on the floor.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS885
The truck swings into the building's side and breaks off from the chopper.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS886
Falling to the ground, it explodes on impact.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS889
Regaining control, SOMEONE loops the chopper around. Inside, SOMEONE kicks open a door to the flaming room.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS890
He shields his face from the smoke.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS891
Outside, the helicopter nears the building.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS892
SOMEONE helps SOMEONE to his feet, as burning SOMEONE rains down around them.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS893
Positioning the chopper in front of the room, SOMEONE narrows her eyes and grips the weapon trigger.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS899
SOMEONE flies at the building.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS900
This is for you, Papa. SOMEONE sees the helicopter rapidly approaching. In slow motion, he and SOMEONE leap out of the shattered window as the chopper's nose collides with the building.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS902
SOMEONE watches them fall with glaring eyes.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS903
Below her, the flaming truck swells on the ground.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS905
In extreme slow motion, the flailing men plummet beside the aircraft. The chopper's nose drags along the building, sending a barrage of SOMEONE into the air.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS906
SOMEONE and SOMEONE crash through a glass roof.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS907
They plunge into the leak-filled pool as the helicopter lands on the flaming truck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS908
As the chopper explodes, flames erupt through the glass wall and over the pool.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS909
The rapidly expanding blast launches propeller blades and metallic SOMEONE across the wide clearing.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS911
As the swirl of flames retracts,
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS912
a giant cloud of black smoke rises from the blazing remains.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS913
SOMEONE surfaces.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS914
Underwater, we view his slowly paddling legs.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS915
He dives beneath the surface.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS916
Large flecks of ash reign down, as dancing flames dock the room. SOMEONE surfaces again.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS917
SOMEONE leans his head back in a relieved sigh, then swims to the pool's edge.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS918
Sitting up, SOMEONE rests his back against the basin's elevated rim.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS919
Grabbing SOMEONE's shirt, he helps him out of the water.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS920
Settling next to his father, SOMEONE gulps down breaths of air and winces painfully.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS921
Coin-sized flecks of ash reign down on their wet clinging T-shirts.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS922
SOMEONE shifts his weight and grimaces.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS923
The two men work their way to their feet.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS924
Now as the building burns in the darkness, the father and son shuffle out among the wreckage.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS925
SOMEONE yields a smile as he limps alongside his father.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS926
From the burning structure, black smoke plumes into a sky cast rose and indigo by the light of a low sun.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS927
Now a bright early morning sun halos the cockpit of a sleek private jet.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS928
On the tarmac, government agents stand ready with assault rifles.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS929
They're vehicles sit parked nearby, emergency lights flashing.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS930
Before them, SOMEONE stands anxiously with her arms folded.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS931
An agent touches his earpiece, then signals to his colleague.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS932
The private jet's passenger door opens and the stairs fold out.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS933
SOMEONE wrings her hands and cranes her neck.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS935
Emerging, SOMEONE descends the steps with a stilted limp and his father at his heels.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS936
Facing his sister, the young agent gives a broad smile.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS937
Hurrying toward her family, SOMEONE breaks into a run. Her long auburn hair sways across her back with each stride.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS938
Reaching her brother, she flings her arms around him in a welcoming embrace. SOMEONE grins and hugs her back, while SOMEONE looks on with a fond, tender smile.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS940
The father and daughter beam softly at one another.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS941
In slow motion, SOMEONE signals forward with his hand,
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS942
then sets off across the tarmac with SOMEONE at his side.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS943
SOMEONE walks on the other side of her brother.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS944
In the sun's golden glow, the father, son and daughter converse animated.
A_GOOD_DAY_TO_DIE_HARD_DVS945
As SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE McClane smile, the sunlight flares around their figure. The image freezes.