Customers wave SOMEONE to the front of the line, where two burly men glare at him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS20
SOMEONE takes a complimentary coffee and leaves.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS21
He sips the coffee in a psychiatry session.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS22
Shaking the bearded doctor's hand, SOMEONE leaves. Later he drives up to a valet standing outside an office.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS24
Sitting at a crowded desk, stacked with manuscripts, a young man with dark curly hair and glasses answers telephones.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS25
SOMEONE opens a manuscript.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS27
SOMEONE leads a business meeting.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS28
At an outdoor retreat people exercise in flower gardens or walk along tree-lined paths.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS29
Inside an open sided pavilion chanting people wearing white clothing sit on the ground with their legs crossed and eyes closed.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS30
One woman opens her eyes and peeks sideways at SOMEONE who sits in their midst.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS31
Other people wrinkle their brows as they stare at SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS32
Barefoot SOMEONE walks among them.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS33
SOMEONE lays one hand on the head of a crying woman.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS34
SOMEONE begins to quiver.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS35
SOMEONE watches him passively as two men help up SOMEONE and lead him away.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS36
Later a woman dabs SOMEONE's forehead with a cloth.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS37
SOMEONE sits up and sips a drink.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS38
He winces and sticks out his tongue.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS39
SOMEONE checks his phone then returns it to his jacket pocket. He sits and smiles at SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS40
SOMEONE walks away.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS41
SOMEONE hurries after him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS42
SOMEONE flaps his hands like wings.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS43
SOMEONE recoils from a tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS44
SOMEONE extends his hand.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS45
SOMEONE shakes it.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS46
Carrying a vase of pink flowers, SOMEONE steps into a retirement home cafeteria, where people wear Mexican themed apparel. He steps up to SOMEONE, his grayed haired mother and kisses her on the forehead.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS47
A man wearing a sombrero dances.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS48
SOMEONE sits with his mother.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS49
SOMEONE glances down at his dark suit.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS50
SOMEONE looks away, shakes his head then faces his mother.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS51
SOMEONE smiles.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS52
Her smile fading, SOMEONE gazes downward.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS53
She looks back up at SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS54
SOMEONE stands and kisses SOMEONE's forehead.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS55
As SOMEONE walks away, SOMEONE gazes downward.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS56
At his house, SOMEONE gets out of his car, then steps past a tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS57
He peers down at his dark haired gardener.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS58
Later SOMEONE sits at the dining room table. His wife, SOMEONE, hands him a sheet of paper.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS59
SOMEONE glances toward the backyard.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS60
Standing close to SOMEONE, SOMEONE looks into his eyes, then smiles.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS61
The house shakes. In the backyard of fully formed Bodhi tree bursts out of the ground, next to the pool.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS62
SOMEONE glances around himself.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS63
SOMEONE walks through the dining room.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS64
Stopping, he peers into the backyard then slides open a patio door.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS65
SOMEONE steps outside toward the Bodhi tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS66
Pool lights shimmer across its green leaves.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS67
As SOMEONE stares at the tree, Gaudencio steps out of the shadows toward him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS68
They gaze at the tree. Wind rustles its leaves.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS69
SOMEONE pats the trunk.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS71
SOMEONE slides his hands up the trunk, then steps back and gazes up at the tall tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS72
As SOMEONE walks away, two leaves break away from the top of the tree, then drift to the ground.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS73
Daytime. SOMEONE follows SOMEONE into his office.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS74
A paper crown.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS75
SOMEONE holds up a scepter.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS76
Standing behind his desk, SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS77
SOMEONE pulls a pamphlet from his shirt pocket. He holds it out to SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS79
Cringing SOMEONE snatches the pamphlet. He flips through its pages, glances around himself, then closes it.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS81
At SOMEONE's house.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS82
SOMEONE inspects several bare branches at the end of one bough.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS83
He gazes up at the tree, then looks toward SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS84
SOMEONE places his hands together. SOMEONE glances around.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS85
Two leaves fall from the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS86
SOMEONE watches more leaves fall to the ground.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS87
SOMEONE gazes upward then slowly steps around the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS88
A leaf falls.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS89
A leaf falls near SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS90
More leaves tumble to the ground.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS91
Another leave falls.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS92
SOMEONE glances from the tree to SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS93
More leaves fall.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS94
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE, then gazes up at the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS95
SOMEONE storms off then returns with an axe.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS96
SOMEONE swings the axe, he hits the trunk and flies through the air and lands in a patch of spiky plants. Lying on the ground SOMEONE pulls down his waistband, revealing a dark bruise.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS97
SOMEONE stands.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS98
Smiling SOMEONE walks off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS99
SOMEONE takes out his cellphone.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS100
A leaf falls. Jacks grasps then glares at his phone.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS102
As SOMEONE laughs, leaves shoot out of his mouth.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS103
More leaves fly from SOMEONE's mouth.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS104
SOMEONE covers and uncovers his mouth.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS106
SOMEONE awakes in bed. He raises his head and looks at the other half of the bed, which is empty.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS107
SOMEONE gets up, steps to a window, and pulls aside a curtain.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS108
Outside sun shines on the Bodhi tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS109
A leaf falls from the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS110
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS111
Later, wearing a suit, SOMEONE steps through the house. SOMEONE and Tyler sleep on a sofa.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS112
SOMEONE sets his briefcase on to a couch, then picks up an appointment book and writes.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS114
The shadows of falling leaves sweep across SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS115
He stops writing and looks outside at the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS118
More leaves fall. SOMEONE stops writing and gazes at the tree, then writes Bye.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS119
Another leave falls.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS120
SOMEONE glares at the tree, then writes, "Die Tree".
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS122
One more leaf falls.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS123
SOMEONE turns, strides across the room, picks up his briefcase, then turns back to face the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS124
Smiling, SOMEONE turns toward the tree and raises his middle finger.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS125
Two more leaves drop.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS126
SOMEONE's smile falls.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS127
At the coffee shop SOMEONE stands at the counter and grins.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS128
SOMEONE holds up three fingers.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS129
SOMEONE spreads his hands apart.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS130
SOMEONE holds up three fingers again.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS131
SOMEONE mimes drinking a cup of espresso, then spreads his hands and opens his mouth wide.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS132
SOMEONE shakes his head. He mimes drinking a cup of espresso and spreads his hands.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS133
The clerk imitates him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS134
SOMEONE holds his hand like a gun, points at his own head, then mimics firing several shots.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS136
SOMEONE mimes shooting himself three times.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS137
SOMEONE frowns.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS138
Holding two cardboard trays filled with tall cups, SOMEONE pushes through the coffee shop door.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS140
He steps to the curb, then glances at the crosswalk sign, which shows a red hand.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS141
A man wearing sunglasses steps up to SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS143
SOMEONE glances from the blind man to the street.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS144
The man steps into traffic. Cars swerve around him as he walks across the street tapping his cane.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS145
Wide-eyed SOMEONE runs after the man and pushes him out of the way of a bus.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS146
Turned around, the blind man now walks down the middle of the street.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS147
Still holding his trays, SOMEONE runs after him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS148
A small car skids to a stop, knocking into SOMEONE and spilling his trays.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS149
SOMEONE grabs the man.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS151
A car swerves sideways, another car rams into it.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS152
A car drives over the man's cane, snapping it in half. SOMEONE hustles the man to the sidewalk.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS153
A truck's mirror hits SOMEONE's last coffee out of his hands.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS154
Later SOMEONE sits in the psychiatrist's office.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS155
The doctor taps a pen against an open notebook.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS156
SOMEONE points at the doctor, then drops his hand.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS157
The doctor shifts in his chair.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS158
SOMEONE squints at the doctor, then raises his eyebrows.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS159
The doctor raises his.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS160
SOMEONE glares.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS161
The doctor exhales.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS162
SOMEONE looks to his left then smiles at the doctor, who smiles back.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS164
Later SOMEONE drives up to the valet and gets out of his car.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS165
SOMEONE stops walking.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS166
SOMEONE twists his mouth.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS167
SOMEONE holds up one hand, gives his car keys to the valet, then strides to his office building.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS168
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE into his office.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS169
SOMEONE wags a finger, then sits at his desk.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS170
SOMEONE holds up his hands.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS171
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE as he leaves,
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS172
then returns.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS173
SOMEONE puts on his coat.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS174
SOMEONE points at SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS175
Later SOMEONE walks with Samantha.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS176
SOMEONE smile at Christian and holds up two fingers.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS177
Back at his house, leaves drop of the Bodhi tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS178
More leaves fall. Samantha grins at the French man.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS179
SOMEONE tilts back his head and rolls his eyes.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS180
Meanwhile, two squirrels chase each other around the Bodhi tree's trunk.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS181
At the office, SOMEONE shakes his legs and dances in place.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS182
Christian smiles, then begins to dance with him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS183
SOMEONE runs off. Samantha frowns at SOMEONE, who begins to shimmy.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS185
Later he follows SOMEONE into a restaurant.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS186
SOMEONE gestures to him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS187
SOMEONE smacks SOMEONE's ear.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS188
They walk to a table, where a bearded man stands and shakes SOMEONE's hand.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS189
SOMEONE shakes black haired Gil's hand, then gestures to SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS190
SOMEONE hugs Robert and fist bumps Gil.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS191
Robert stares at SOMEONE, then grins and sits.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS192
Back at SOMEONE's house, Gaudencio sprays water up and down the Bodhi tree's trunk with a hose.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS193
Back at the restaurant, SOMEONE fidgets as he sweats profusely.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS194
SOMEONE flinches, then glances at SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS195
SOMEONE stares wide-eyed at SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS196
Robert and Gil stand.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS197
In a daycare center, SOMEONE sits with his son in a group of men and boys.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS198
The teacher points at SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS199
The teacher raises his eyebrows and stares at SOMEONE who sits frozen.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS200
Leaves flutter off the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS201
The teacher pushes Tyler in a rocket-shaped swing.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS202
SOMEONE glances at his phone then looks up as Tyler swings into him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS205
Eating a bowl of food, SOMEONE smiles and nods.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS206
Smiling, SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE toward the patio doors and gestures outside.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS207
She turns and looks into the backyard.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS208
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS209
He arches his eyebrows and opens his mouth as if to speak, then furrows his brow.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS210
She shrugs at him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS211
SOMEONE storms into the next room and stares at a lit fire place.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS212
SOMEONE hurries after her.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS213
He chokes himself then opens and closes one hand like a jabbering mouth.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS214
SOMEONE strides off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS215
SOMEONE shakes his fists and walks into the backyard.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS216
He steps to the Bodhi tree and glares up at it.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS217
SOMEONE dials his cellphone.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS218
He nods vigorously.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS219
Several leaves fall.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS220
Two leaves drop off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS221
Several more leaves fall.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS222
At the coffee shop, SOMEONE mimes drinking, holding out his hands while opening his mouth wide, then pretends to pour something.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS223
SOMEONE shivers.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS224
SOMEONE pretends to squeeze his own breast.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS225
He nods. Back at the office, Samantha chases him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS226
SOMEONE nods.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS227
He crosses his heart.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS228
Samantha gestures toward the phone then walks off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS229
As SOMEONE stares at the ringing phone, SOMEONE walks back to his own desk.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS230
SOMEONE presses a button on the phone.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS231
SOMEONE looks around himself.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS232
He opens a  desk drawer.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS233
SOMEONE holds an Austin Powers doll.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS234
He shoots a paper wad through a hoop.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS235
SOMEONE frowns.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS236
SOMEONE runs to SOMEONE's desk, points at the Austin Powers doll, then at himself, then sweeps his arm in a circle.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS238
SOMEONE takes the doll and runs off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS239
SOMEONE knocks down a passing man then grabs another doll of a blond woman's desk.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS240
SOMEONE runs into SOMEONE's office and dumps an armload of dolls onto his desk.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS241
SOMEONE and brown haired Sharon work at a clothing store.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS242
Sharon holds out a black handbag.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS243
Smiling, SOMEONE takes the bag and opens it. Her mouth drops open as she peers inside.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS244
Elsewhere SOMEONE steps into an elegant hotel lobby.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS245
He strides to the front desk where a blond woman greets him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS246
SOMEONE points at his own throat then shakes his head. He glances over his shoulder, clasps his hands, and then taps his own chest.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS247
SOMEONE smiles.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS248
She hands SOMEONE a keycard. SOMEONE holds up the card, smiles, then walks off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS249
Later SOMEONE strolls down a long hallway.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS250
Stopping at a door, he straightens his tie, then knocks.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS251
As the door opens, SOMEONE frowns. A fat, shirtless man wears a British naval hat, stands in the room.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS252
The man sips a martini glass.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS253
At the front desk, the woman returns SOMEONE's driver's license.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS254
SOMEONE sneers at the woman as he walks off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS255
Later SOMEONE slips the card key into his coat pocket as he sneaks into a hotel suite.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS256
SOMEONE moves to an open door.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS257
Wearing a black bra, boots, gloves, and panties, SOMEONE stands with her hands on her hips in front of a bed.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS258
SOMEONE whips of his suit coat and loosens his tie.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS259
SOMEONE steps up to her.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS260
He unbuttons his shirt.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS261
SOMEONE steps behind him and loosens his belt.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS262
She pulls down his pants.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS263
SOMEONE cuffs SOMEONE's hands behind his back.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS264
She pushes him onto the bed.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS265
She takes of his shoe.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS266
SOMEONE stares, wide-eyed.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS267
SOMEONE squints, then smiles.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS268
SOMEONE moves his lips.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS269
He bears his teeth.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS270
She puts on an overcoat.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS271
SOMEONE indicates his cuffed hands. SOMEONE removes the handcuffs.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS273
SOMEONE nods once, then nods again.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS274
As SOMEONE steps toward the door, SOMEONE hurries after her and grabs her arm.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS286
Later SOMEONE waits outside at a valet station.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS287
Staring at him, a nearby woman grabs a young girls hand and leads her away.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS288
SOMEONE answers his phone.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS289
SOMEONE speeds off. Later, wearing pants and a T-shirt, SOMEONE steps into a restaurant where Samantha sits with several executives.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS290
Samantha stands.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS291
SOMEONE shakes his head.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS292
Meanwhile, Gaudencio prepares pesticide.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS293
Donning a mask, Gaudencio sprays the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS294
SOMEONE squints across the table at a bespectacled executive.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS295
SOMEONE turns to a blond woman beside him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS296
SOMEONE picks up a breadstick, sniffs it, then bites into it.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS297
One of the executives stares at SOMEONE as he nibbles the stick in small bites.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS298
SOMEONE leans close to the blond woman, picks up a French fry from her plate, places it halfway into his mouth, then smiles at her.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS299
The two executives stare at SOMEONE, who picks up another breadstick and runs it across Samantha's cheek,
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS300
then taps her nose with it.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS301
SOMEONE slides the breadstick up Samantha's nose.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS302
She jerks it away.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS303
SOMEONE hands an envelope to Samantha.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS304
The executives walk out.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS305
SOMEONE bites a breadstick.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS307
Smiling he holds out a breadstick to Samantha.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS308
She snaps it in half.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS309
Samantha walks off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS310
Later SOMEONE draws on a chalk board as SOMEONE watches.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS312
SOMEONE circles a stickman on the chalkboard.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS313
SOMEONE indicates a tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS314
SOMEONE points at SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS315
SOMEONE crosses his hands over his chest.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS316
SOMEONE draws a slash through the stickman.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS317
SOMEONE mimes a corpse and spreads his arms wide.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS318
He mimes a corpse again.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS319
SOMEONE jumps up and down.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS320
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE by his collar.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS321
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE into the backyard.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS322
SOMEONE steps up to the Bodhi tree, then holds up one finger.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS323
A leaf falls.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS324
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE and shoves him toward the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS325
He taps on SOMEONE's glasses, then points at the foliage.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS326
SOMEONE nods.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS327
SOMEONE places his palms together.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS328
He circles one finger over his own head.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS329
Smiling SOMEONE dashes off. SOMEONE turns and stares up at the tree's leaves.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS330
Later SOMEONE throws loaves of bread out of his car window as he drives.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS331
On the sidewalk homeless men wrestle each other for the bread.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS333
SOMEONE parks outside a church, then walks up to two nuns sitting at a table.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS334
He gives them a wad of money.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS335
One leaf flutters away from the Bodhi tree. SOMEONE glares at his phone then takes off his watch and hands it to a nun.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS336
Frowning SOMEONE snatches his watch back from the nun, who both make the sign of the cross.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS337
A young girl calls to an orange cat sitting in a tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS338
SOMEONE climbs a ladder and reaches for the cat.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS339
The cat leaps on to SOMEONE's face. He falls backward and lands on the girl's lawn.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS340
Smiling she cradles her cat.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS341
A Bodhi leaf falls.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS342
Fallen leaves float in SOMEONE's swimming pool.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS343
At dusk, SOMEONE switches on a bedroom light then walks through his house.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS344
Clear plastic sheeting covers bare shelves.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS345
SOMEONE gazes around the empty house then sighs.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS346
He opens a family photo album and pages through the pictures.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS347
SOMEONE takes out a photo of a young boy posing with a man and a woman.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS348
Later SOMEONE holds the photo in his hands and stares at it, as he leans against the base of the Bodhi tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS349
SOMEONE settles himself.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS350
He rests his elbows on his legs,
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS351
raises his hand, pinches his fingertips together,
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS352
and shuts his eyes.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS353
Family photos cover a shelf.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS354
Young SOMEONE sits at a kitchen table as his mother carries in a roasting pot.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS355
SOMEONE smiles as he sits with them.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS356
Young SOMEONE shakes food of his fork.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS357
Sitting under the Bodhi tree, SOMEONE jerks open his eyes.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS358
Later SOMEONE shovels into a family restaurant.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS359
SOMEONE waves to him from a booth.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS360
Covering his mouth with one arm as he coughs, SOMEONE sits across from SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS361
SOMEONE slams his fists on the table.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS362
SOMEONE holds up his left hand, points to his wedding band then runs a finger across his own throat.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS363
SOMEONE rocks his arms then sweeps his fingers into the air.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS364
SOMEONE draws something on a placemat then holds it up to SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS365
SOMEONE shakes a snow globe, then sets it in front of SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS366
He grabs SOMEONE's collar.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS367
SOMEONE shakes his head and shrugs.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS368
Glancing around himself, SOMEONE holds out his arms.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS369
He looks down and shakes his head slightly.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS370
SOMEONE holds up one palm.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS371
SOMEONE moves as if the speak, then shuts his mouth and smiles.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS372
Raising his eyebrows SOMEONE shrugs and walks off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS373
SOMEONE watches him leave, then stares at the table top.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS374
Back home SOMEONE drinks from a liquor bottle as he staggers into the front door.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS375
He shuffles to a bar and holds up another bottle as he examines its contents.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS386
SOMEONE tries to clap his hands over SOMEONE's mouth, but SOMEONE pushes him away.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS387
SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE into some shelves. SOMEONE throws SOMEONE into a wall, then limps away.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS388
SOMEONE stands and tackles SOMEONE to the floor.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS389
SOMEONE lies motionless, as SOMEONE rolls him onto his back.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS390
A phone lies in broken glass on the floor.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS391
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE, knocking him out cold.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS392
SOMEONE finds a roll of duct tape and wraps up the phone.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS393
He tears of a piece of tape and covers SOMEONE's mouth with it.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS394
SOMEONE leaves. Outside on the Bodhi tree, only a single branch still has leaves remaining.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS395
The next morning, SOMEONE awakes.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS396
With the piece of tape still covering his mouth, he sits up
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS397
then stands and stares at the tree in his backyard.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS398
SOMEONE slowly peels of the tape.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS399
With the sun shining brightly overhead, SOMEONE walks outside.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS400
His shadow falls across leaves lying on the grass.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS401
SOMEONE steps to the base of the tree and drops to his knees.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS402
SOMEONE gazes up at the bare branches, then begins to cry.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS403
Eyes shut he reaches out and grabs on to the tree's trunk.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS404
SOMEONE leans back and gazes up at the branches.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS405
He takes the piece of tape out of his pocket,
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS406
and places it over his mouth again.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS407
SOMEONE drags over a hose and waters the base of the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS408
Eyes wide, SOMEONE peers over his shoulder.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS409
Inside he untapes the phone and answers it.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS410
Emily lets the phone fall from her ear.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS411
Back outside, SOMEONE waters the Bodhi tree with the hose.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS412
He looks up as a butterfly flutters past his face.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS413
He watches the butterfly zigzag down and land on a small thin book lying on the ground.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS414
SOMEONE picks up the book, sits against the base of the tree and begins to read.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS415
The sun sinks low in the sky, casting long shadows across the yard,
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS416
SOMEONE jerks his head backward as he reads.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS417
Later SOMEONE walks to a large estate house and knocks at the front door.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS418
SOMEONE steps out holding Tyler in her arms.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS419
SOMEONE holds up one palm then clasps SOMEONE's hand.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS420
He lays his other hand on Tyler's head.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS421
Back at the house a leaf falls off the Bodhi tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS422
SOMEONE kisses his wife and son.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS423
He stares at SOMEONE then turns and walks off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS424
At the coffee shop SOMEONE takes his order, then hands the cashier a flat package.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS425
Another leaf drops to the ground.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS426
Two more leaves fall.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS427
Carrying a cup of coffee, SOMEONE smiles to himself as he exits the shop.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS428
At work, SOMEONE steps up to the valet stand.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS429
SOMEONE holds out a manuscript.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS430
Another Bodhi leaf falls.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS431
SOMEONE holds up a check.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS432
Another leaf drops to the ground.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS433
The valet hugs SOMEONE as another valet pulls up in his car, which is covered in bird droppings.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS434
SOMEONE holds up his hands and shakes his head, then leaves.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS435
Later SOMEONE purchases an ice cream sundae.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS436
SOMEONE eats the ice cream as he strolls along a crowded boardwalk.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS437
SOMEONE glances at a kissing couple then steps to a railing overlooking the ocean. An older man and woman stand beside him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS438
SOMEONE watches them hug and nuzzle each other.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS439
Later SOMEONE sits on a bench and watches a group of children playing on a swing set.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS440
In slow motion, a woman's hand adjusts Tyler's  clothing.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS441
Soft lighting illuminates SOMEONE's face.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS442
SOMEONE furrows his brow as he stares straight ahead.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS443
In a bed, SOMEONE sleeps beside Tyler.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS444
Sunlight glints of sparkling waves, as SOMEONE sits on the sandy beach.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS445
SOMEONE steps into his mother's room.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS446
One of the last remaining Bodhi leaves falls.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS447
SOMEONE points to his own throat.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS448
He shakes his head.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS449
SOMEONE leans forward as his mother stares at the floor.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS450
SOMEONE hangs his head.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS452
SOMEONE nods weakly.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS453
He nods more vigorously, then stares into his mother's eyes.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS454
She looks up and calls toward the door.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS455
SOMEONE's mouth drops open as she gazes at her son.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS456
SOMEONE stands and kisses her on the forehead.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS457
Back at the house, several more Bodhi leaves drop off.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS458
Leaving only three left on the branch.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS459
SOMEONE clasps his mother's hand and strokes his own face with it.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS460
Smiling SOMEONE turns and leaves.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS461
SOMEONE stares after him with a puzzled expression.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS462
Later two workers dig a grave in a sunny cemetery.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS463
Nearby the name McCall adorns a large headstone.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS464
In a field of golden grass a distant figure races toward a single tree standing on the horizon.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS465
In the cemetery SOMEONE kneels at his father's grave.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS466
In the field, SOMEONE's younger self sits at the base of the tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS467
SOMEONE chases after his young self through the field of tall grass, losing him in the blinding rays of the setting sun.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS468
Back at the cemetery SOMEONE opens his eyes and stares at his father's headstone.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS470
The Bodhi tree's three remaining leaves flutter in a breeze.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS471
SOMEONE looks up as it begins to rain.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS472
The last three leaves drop of the Bodhi tree, leaving it completely bare.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS473
SOMEONE winces, then collapses on the grass as raindrops stream down on him.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS474
At a nearby burial mourners gather for shelter.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS475
In the field of golden grass, the silhouette of young SOMEONE skips through the stalks.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS476
At the cemetery SOMEONE lies face down and motionless.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS477
His phone lies in the grass nearby.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS478
SOMEONE's hand trembles as he slowly reaches out and answers his phone.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS479
He holds the phone to one ear.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS480
Standing in SOMEONE's backyard, SOMEONE smiles up at the Bodhi tree, which is now covered with green leaves.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS481
Red flowers blossom on the Bodhi tree.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS483
Later SOMEONE holds a small book. A Thousand Words.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS484
SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS485
SOMEONE walks in wearing white robes and sandals.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS486
SOMEONE sits at a desk and picks up Jacks book.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS487
SOMEONE raises his eyebrow.
A_THOUSAND_WORDS_DVS488
SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand.