A Boston Market gift card.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS6
Now she pulls up outside a modern home and parks.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS7
SOMEONE struts inside leaving the double doors open.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS17
Now in SOMEONE's classroom.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS18
She circles the breasts on a photo of SOMEONE Perry.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS19
A matronly woman ventures in.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS22
Now in her classroom.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS23
Now a photo features a pretty blonde girl.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS25
A hefty boy coughs.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS28
No students raise their hands.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS29
SOMEONE shakes her head.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS30
The hefty boy frowns.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS33
As the movie starts SOMEONE wraps her sweater.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS34
Now in the cafeteria SOMEONE munches on a sandwich.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS36
SOMEONE sulks.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS38
As he goes SOMEONE sips a cup of coffee. SOMEONE arrives.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS39
SOMEONE steps closer with a menacing glare.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS40
She leaves. SOMEONE stares after her.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS42
He tracks.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS43
Handsome man in glasses and smiles.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS47
SOMEONE peers at the breasts.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS48
She fondles them with an appraising frown.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS50
SOMEONE leans forward.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS51
Now at an apartment.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS52
She uses a phone.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS53
The beefy man leaves the bathroom.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS55
Now at school.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS56
SOMEONE's class watches Lean on Me.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS58
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE's desk.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS59
SOMEONE perks up. Now the principal holds a nudie magazine.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS60
He shifts his baffled gaze.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS61
He reaches for his magazine.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS62
The boy passes SOMEONE on his way out and she covers her nose.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS63
SOMEONE notices dolphin figurines all around the office and photos of the principal swimming with dolphins. She picks up a dolphin paperweight.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS64
At the door.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS65
He shows her a certificate with a dolphin photo. Words above it read Dolphin Research Center, Dolphin Parent Wally Sneer.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS66
SOMEONE's face flushes.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS67
SOMEONE considers.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS68
Now in front of the school two students hold car wash signs. SOMEONE parks in a lot behind the building where 7th graders wash a car.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS81
Bike ride. SOMEONE watches her from a short distance away.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS84
Another teacher enters. SOMEONE waves him into a stall, then uses a urinal like a chair.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS85
SOMEONE scrunches her face into a fierce look, then calms herself.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS86
She turns to the stalls.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS87
She storms out.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS88
Now in the cafeteria SOMEONE talks to a student.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS89
SOMEONE and Lynn watch.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS90
SOMEONE gives a sour look. Lynn beams as SOMEONE strolls in.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS92
As she leaves SOMEONE grins at SOMEONE.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS94
SOMEONE's face lights up.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS95
SOMEONE glowers at her.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS96
Later at parent's night.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS97
A woman's hand shoots up.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS98
She points to some water and a package of Oreo's.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS99
She fakes a knowing look.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS101
Backing away he gives a sly smile.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS102
She approaches a couple.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS103
She opens her wallet and writes out a check.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS107
SOMEONE reads the cover, then gapes at SOMEONE.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS108
She gazes dreamily at him.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS111
She shows a container.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS112
Unrolling her window a third of the way SOMEONE reaches out.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS114
SOMEONE shakes her head.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS115
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS116
Shifting her bewildered gaze the student shrugs.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS117
SOMEONE glances away.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS118
Night time. At a winter wonderland.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS122
She slams her fist on a locker then forces a smile.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS123
Nodding SOMEONE fakes a SOMEONE.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS129
With uncertain eyes the matronly teacher takes the joint, pinching it between two fingers she lifts it to her lips, inhales, then holds her breath.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS132
Sauntering to a rope he takes a drag off the joint.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS133
Sticking the joint between his lips he jumps up and grabs the rope. Clutching, he awkwardly dangles a few feet off the ground, then let's himself drop.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS135
Her arm. As she glares he covers his mouth and points apologetically to the joint. SOMEONE grins and he laughs with her. They lie on a pile of mats.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS136
He hands her the joint and a lighter.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS137
Gazing at her SOMEONE smiles.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS140
She kicks the door.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS141
Then turns to a homeless man.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS144
She steals a dolphin figurine.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS145
SOMEONE grimaces.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS148
With a baffled look, SOMEONE tilts his head. On his way out the baffled look lingers on his face.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS149
SOMEONE bites the end off of her corndog and chews miserably.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS150
Now in SOMEONE's class.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS156
SOMEONE downs a shot.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS161
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS162
SOMEONE Waves to SOMEONE and she waves back.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS163
SOMEONE smiles bashfully.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS165
SOMEONE Glares at SOMEONE.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS166
Her breasts Bounce under a purple tank top.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS168
SOMEONE points. The spikey hair boy gathers his backpack.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS169
SOMEONE shakes her head.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS170
Chase glances around. SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS171
SOMEONE shakes her head.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS172
She has a dodgeball in her hand.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS176
SOMEONE narrows his eyes. SOMEONE enters with a coffee cup.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS177
SOMEONE raises his eyebrows.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS178
In the auditorium SOMEONE wears a curly red wig.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS179
SOMEONE's eyes light up.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS180
SOMEONE kicks a chair.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS182
SOMEONE backs away.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS183
She tightens her upper lip, bearing her top teeth.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS184
She closes her lips.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS185
The red head struggles to stop making the odd face. Now in class, SOMEONE grades papers.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS187
She crosses out fucking. Later she slams quizzes down.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS188
She points to a student of Asian descent.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS190
On the floor. Illinois Standard State Test Official Practice Test Manual.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS191
She notices an address on the back cover and tears it off. While driving SOMEONE lights a joint, then eats a cheeseburger.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS192
A man peers through a window divider.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS193
SOMEONE wears SOMEONE's wig.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS196
He twitches, holding a near empty glass of white wine.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS197
SOMEONE blinks a few times.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS199
SOMEONE sits seductively
BAD_TEACHER_DVS202
As SOMEONE takes a swig from the wine bottle SOMEONE tips the tumbler to his lips and takes a modest sip.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS203
SOMEONE tips the glass up for him, forcing him to drain it.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS204
SOMEONE gulps hard.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS207
Bathroom stall, yawning as she checks her cell phone. Now, she returns to the office finding SOMEONE semi reclined on the desk.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS209
Copier. Now she takes a restricted copy of the state test answer key from a file cabinet.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS210
Chalkboards. Write out on a
BAD_TEACHER_DVS211
SOMEONE frowns behind a lectern.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS213
As SOMEONE sits patiently SOMEONE reads from an index card.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS218
She takes out a few credit cards.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS221
She puts down her purse and puts on a pair of rubber gloves. SOMEONE takes a leafy sprig from a plastic baggie and rubs the plant over the surface of a large red apple. A sticker on SOMEONE's desk reads, "Learning is Funtastic." Later, SOMEONE enters her full classroom.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS232
SOMEONE crouches at the desk, hesitates and slides the drawer out revealing the SOMEONE wig.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS234
Now in this office, SOMEONE eyes a photocopy of SOMEONE's driver's license.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS235
SOMEONE's eyes dart, computing away. Now she visits SOMEONE who paces.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS236
He throws up his arms.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS239
Later visitors roam the State House lobby. SOMEONE admires a SOMEONE statue.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS241
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap a look.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS242
SOMEONE pats SOMEONE on the back and leaves.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS243
SOMEONE returns SOMEONE's smile.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS244
Hotel corridor, a door handle sign reads, Privacy Please. Inside on the bed two pairs of bare feet rub together. The otherwise fully clothed SOMEONE writhes atop of SOMEONE's clothes prone body. His eyes shut, SOMEONE rests his head next to SOMEONE's.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS246
Next to a bust of SOMEONE. She takes a sip then slowly picks up SOMEONE's cell phone. In a dim living room a cell phone vibrates on a coffee table.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS247
In the hotel SOMEONE tosses SOMEONE's cell down. A picture of SOMEONE shows on the phone and indicates a connected call. With SOMEONE on all fours, SOMEONE thrusts at her from behind. Both wear jeans.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS248
SOMEONE mimes locking her lips. SOMEONE grits her teeth.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS249
SOMEONE waits dispassionately.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS254
SOMEONE strokes her hair. She opens his mouth to receive his approaching lips but he detours upwards and plants a kiss on her forehead
BAD_TEACHER_DVS255
SOMEONE forces a demure smile. Now as she shuts the door, stepping into the corridor, SOMEONE approaches.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS256
SOMEONE nods, averting his gaze.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS257
They both move on. SOMEONE wheels around.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS258
By her pet tortoise at home, SOMEONE does sit-ups with an ab roller.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS260
SOMEONE recoils.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS261
SOMEONE interjects.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS263
He steps forward in his earmuff heat and gymnastics sweatshirt.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS264
Chase averts her gaze.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS268
He folds his hands over his heart.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS269
A boy feigns coughing.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS271
SOMEONE moles over her own comment.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS272
SOMEONE nods thoughtfully.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS273
SOMEONE works her jaw. Meeting his gaze, she cocks her head, stands, then reaches behind her back and under her sleeve.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS276
She bats off his earmuff cap. Now SOMEONE rejoins her group at several picnic tables.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS279
As SOMEONE grins, SOMEONE gives him a flirtatious glance.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS280
She pokes SOMEONE's chest.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS281
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS282
The kids part for SOMEONE who makes her way past them, leaving SOMEONE staring sadly.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS284
Elsewhere, SOMEONE makes his way to a parking lot. SOMEONE's hefty leather jacket
BAD_TEACHER_DVS286
Towards a modest parked sedan.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS287
He pushes him away.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS289
On one palm SOMEONE sees SOMEONE's name written down. On the other he reads envelope misspelled with an I. He hands SOMEONE the envelope.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS292
Now at school, SOMEONE sits in her empty classroom.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS293
Standing, she sticks her gum to the underside of her desk.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS294
The secretary points to SOMEONE's bumper sticker on the side.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS295
SOMEONE and the superintendent.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS296
SOMEONE holds up a hand and nods.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS297
Secretary opens the door and SOMEONE enters. As he takes a seat beside SOMEONE she gives a demure smile.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS298
SOMEONE frown, SOMEONE smiles.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS301
Frowning, SOMEONE nervously shifts his eyes.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS302
He shoots SOMEONE a fearful glance.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS303
The superintendent leans back.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS304
With a haughty look SOMEONE retires to the arm of a couch.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS305
SOMEONE raises her hand.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS307
The panel of glued down items, underneath the find a bag of pills and marijuana. SOMEONE gapes.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS308
SOMEONE's face contorts wrathfully and she charges SOMEONE.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS310
The other teachers nod.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS311
He turns his back to her, closes his eyes for a moment, then faces her again.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS312
With a smile she brushes past him. Now in the gym, SOMEONE collects scattered dodge balls and sets them in a bag. Standing in the doorway SOMEONE watches.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS313
SOMEONE straightens. A ball smacks him in the back.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS314
Turning, he finds SOMEONE striding over to him.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS315
She searches her handbag.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS316
She pulls out a thin hardcover book.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS317
He hands her the bag of dodgeballs.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS318
SOMEONE smiles.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS319
SOMEONE's smile fades.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS320
She averts her dejected gaze.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS321
SOMEONE gapes then cocks her head.
BAD_TEACHER_DVS325
A confident nod.