SOMEONE interviews SOMEONE.
BRUNO_DVS16
He squeezes between two people at a show.
BRUNO_DVS17
Later a model saunters past.
BRUNO_DVS18
Now, SOMEONE tries on an undersized hat.
BRUNO_DVS19
A bespectacled man holds a cup.
BRUNO_DVS20
Diesel uses an exercise.
BRUNO_DVS21
It pumps a dildo in and out of SOMEONE's backside. Later he sticks a fire extinguisher up Diesel's butt. White foam squirts everywhere.
BRUNO_DVS23
And shoots back to SOMEONE's hips.
BRUNO_DVS25
And SOMEONE's jiggling.
BRUNO_DVS26
While it sticks out of Diesel's butt.
BRUNO_DVS27
He pokes him, to yank it free.
BRUNO_DVS29
Backstage at a fashion show.
BRUNO_DVS31
SOMEONE stands.
BRUNO_DVS32
He staggers back and forth.
BRUNO_DVS33
He wrenches the curtain off his head.
BRUNO_DVS34
Several policemen take him away.
BRUNO_DVS35
Now, one doorman after another turns him away.
BRUNO_DVS36
Subtitles. You can't come in.
BRUNO_DVS37
The guards easily shove him back.
BRUNO_DVS38
He talks on his cell.
BRUNO_DVS39
He steps away, gesturing for us to stay back.
BRUNO_DVS40
Passers-by shun him as he walks.
BRUNO_DVS41
Now, in an airport terminal.
BRUNO_DVS42
Diesel saunters off.
BRUNO_DVS43
A blonde man joins Diesel.
BRUNO_DVS44
Smacks Diesel’s rear-end, and they leave together. SOMEONE swallows, and shifts his wounded gaze. Later, at a departure gate, he stands by a luggage.
BRUNO_DVS45
Backed high with white suitcases. He blows his nose, and tearfully dabs at it.
BRUNO_DVS47
SOMEONE runs through the terminal with a black blanket covered his body.
BRUNO_DVS48
He hits a pillar.
BRUNO_DVS49
Suite A Management.
BRUNO_DVS50
SOMEONE swaggers up before SOMEONE, script in hand. He bows, then reads.
BRUNO_DVS51
SOMEONE's brow furrows.
BRUNO_DVS52
He sobers instantly, and dramatically wags his finger at SOMEONE. The agent responds with a bemused frown. His script at his side, SOMEONE shifts his haunted wide-eyed gaze. Turning his back on SOMEONE, he crouches, revealing a red thong. He jumps around to face the agent.
BRUNO_DVS53
SOMEONE sits.
BRUNO_DVS54
Now, SOMEONE eyes a sign, Extras Holding.
BRUNO_DVS55
On a courtroom set, a hand claps a slate before the camera.
BRUNO_DVS56
As a juror, SOMEONE reacts broadly.
BRUNO_DVS57
SOMEONE pounds the jury stand. The director speaks to him.
BRUNO_DVS58
The actor playing the lawyer shakes his head. The slate claps again.
BRUNO_DVS59
SOMEONE takes out a cigarette.
BRUNO_DVS60
He lights it.
BRUNO_DVS61
The lead actor presses his hands to his brow.
BRUNO_DVS62
It shows an smart car in the street.
BRUNO_DVS63
Now a bleaching salon. SOMEONE talks with SOMEONE.
BRUNO_DVS64
He crouches on all fours.
BRUNO_DVS65
He talks on the phone.
BRUNO_DVS66
Now a new modern home, overlooking the hills.
BRUNO_DVS67
Three workers tend the pool area.
BRUNO_DVS69
He blinks thoughtfully.
BRUNO_DVS70
Paula Abdul, American Idol judge.
BRUNO_DVS71
In the living room, three workers wait on their hands and knees.
BRUNO_DVS72
She walks over hesitantly.
BRUNO_DVS73
She tentatively sits on one man's back.
BRUNO_DVS74
He holds out his microphone.
BRUNO_DVS75
A nude man is covered in sushi.
BRUNO_DVS76
Now, they drive off.
BRUNO_DVS77
He chases after them. Later, he leans against a bulletin board filled with celebrity photos. Angelina Jolie's has a black x over it.
BRUNO_DVS78
SOMEONE tilts his head, checking out SOMEONE's.
BRUNO_DVS79
Hangs up and turns to SOMEONE.
BRUNO_DVS80
Puts his marker to a photo of P Diddy.
BRUNO_DVS81
SOMEONE shakes his head.
BRUNO_DVS82
SOMEONE points to SOMEONE.
BRUNO_DVS83
He points to Mel Gibson. SOMEONE throws down his marker.
BRUNO_DVS85
SOMEONE and SOMEONE clink champagne flutes.
BRUNO_DVS86
SOMEONE averts his eyes. The focus group gawks. Text squirrels across the TV.
BRUNO_DVS87
He shows an ultrasound.
BRUNO_DVS88
SOMEONE shakes his head and glares.
BRUNO_DVS89
On the street, Harrison Ford hurries away from SOMEONE.
BRUNO_DVS90
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE.
BRUNO_DVS91
He bobs his head to the music.
BRUNO_DVS92
Who zooms into it. Back in the observation room, SOMEONE leans toward SOMEONE.
BRUNO_DVS93
SOMEONE looks away angrily with the focus group.
BRUNO_DVS94
SOMEONE leaves the observation room, and barges in on the focus group.
BRUNO_DVS95
SOMEONE waves his fist by his head, and spins in a circle.
BRUNO_DVS96
Later, SOMEONE sits in a hallway perusing the questionnaires. One reads, "Garbage. It was worse than cancer." He looks up as SOMEONE approaches.
BRUNO_DVS97
SOMEONE squats facing SOMEONE.
BRUNO_DVS100
Now, SOMEONE conducts an interview in a Western Hotel suite.
BRUNO_DVS102
And fix it.
BRUNO_DVS103
SOMEONE stands. He guides Ron SOMEONE into the bedroom, and shuts the door. The candidate glances at a newspaper on the bed, then sits primly.
BRUNO_DVS104
SOMEONE removes his jacket, revealing a tight shirt with cut-off sleeves.
BRUNO_DVS105
He lights up a tableful.
BRUNO_DVS106
Ron SOMEONE watches awkwardly.
BRUNO_DVS107
The candidate shakes his head.
BRUNO_DVS108
Ron SOMEONE shifts. SOMEONE turns off a lamp. Ron SOMEONE stands, and picks up a newspaper.
BRUNO_DVS109
SOMEONE swivels his hips seductively. With the newspaper in his hands, Ron SOMEONE turns his back to him. He glances around the room, then focuses on the paper. SOMEONE leans his hands against the wall, and wags his butt. He lets his pants fall, revealing his purple spandex briefs.
BRUNO_DVS110
Ron SOMEONE tosses a nespaper.
BRUNO_DVS111
SOMEONE, Psychic.
BRUNO_DVS112
The middle-aged psychic closes his eyes.
BRUNO_DVS113
SOMEONE closes his eyes, and strokes a leather collar.
BRUNO_DVS114
SOMEONE stands and mimes kissing SOMEONE's ghost. With his eyes closed, he laps at the air. He pretends to stroke SOMEONE's hair. SOMEONE waits patiently, his gaze fixed straight ahead. SOMEONE lowers himself to his knees. He imitates pulling down the zipper, parting the flaps on SOMEONE's pants, and removing them. SOMEONE pretends to hold SOMEONE's penis. His tongue flicking back and forth over its invisible tip.
BRUNO_DVS115
He spits into his hand, and then mimes stroking the shaft of SOMEONE's penis. Moving his head lower, SOMEONE simulates fondling SOMEONE's testicles. He then licks them, while pretending to stick a finger into SOMEONE's anus. He gestures, as if turning SOMEONE around, and spreading his butt cheeks. SOMEONE flutters his tongue in the invisible opening, then uses one hand to reach forward and stroke SOMEONE's penis again. He pretends to turn SOMEONE back to face him, and simulates oral sex, moving his head up and down.
BRUNO_DVS116
SOMEONE bobs vigorously, while pretending to stroke SOMEONE's penis. He throws his head back.
BRUNO_DVS117
SOMEONE shakes his head back and forth as he strokes SOMEONE's invisible member. He cringes, then wipes at his eye. His sits exhaustedly at the table, and SOMEONE extends his hand.
BRUNO_DVS118
Now, SOMEONE drives SOMEONE.
BRUNO_DVS119
A PR Consultant.
BRUNO_DVS120
The blonde twins exchange a look. Suzanne shrugs her hand.
BRUNO_DVS121
Later, in the smart car.
BRUNO_DVS122
A plane takes off.
BRUNO_DVS123
A globe shows the Middle East.
BRUNO_DVS124
SOMEONE holds a basket on her head.
BRUNO_DVS125
A man looks up to find him smoking up.
BRUNO_DVS127
He races away, as a group of men run toward him.
BRUNO_DVS130
The Israeli raises his eyebrows.
BRUNO_DVS131
He stands behind his chair, and gesticulates.
BRUNO_DVS132
Both of the men avert their gaze. SOMEONE sits, and takes each of their hands.
BRUNO_DVS133
He rubs the palms of their hands together.
BRUNO_DVS134
He rubs their hands on the back of his head, and on his shoulders.
BRUNO_DVS135
He raises their hands, and places them each on their own heads. Then, softly motions his own hands in front of his face in a dance, as the men look on.
BRUNO_DVS139
He says that your King Osama looks like a dirty wizard or a homeless Santa Claus.
BRUNO_DVS140
SOMEONE folds his hands over his crossed knees.
BRUNO_DVS141
SOMEONE, get that. Wearing an African robe, SOMEONE directs SOMEONE to pick up a package shaped like an elephant tusk.
BRUNO_DVS142
SOMEONE, there's another. SOMEONE grabs an elephant foot. A box marked fragile comes around. SOMEONE, here it is. His assistant grabs the box, and SOMEONE helps him set it down.
BRUNO_DVS143
Takes an African infant out the box - bystanders stare.
BRUNO_DVS144
In one-on-one interviews with patents.
BRUNO_DVS145
At night, in a hotel room.
BRUNO_DVS146
Aita was adopted baby.
BRUNO_DVS147
SOMEONE sings lullaby.
BRUNO_DVS148
SOMEONE rides the exercise bike.
BRUNO_DVS150
SOMEONE catches up to him.
BRUNO_DVS151
He lifts the baby's headphone.
BRUNO_DVS152
Who straddles a scooter. He sits the baby on the scooter.
BRUNO_DVS153
Turning abruptly into the street, he cuts off a speeding car, which skids.
BRUNO_DVS154
Now, on the set of Today
BRUNO_DVS155
Another shows baby O.J.-
BRUNO_DVS156
Four men pull him off the stage.
BRUNO_DVS157
A flashback shows the cardboard box arriving at the baggage claim carousel. In a silk robe, SOMEONE rocks his baby to sleep. O.J. wears his headphones and sunglasses, as SOMEONE holds him on the scooter. The speeding car nearly hits them.
BRUNO_DVS158
The security team carries him away. Now, SOMEONE walks alone across a parking lot to a restaurant - The Village Inn. Inside, he looks over a display of various pies near the cashier.
BRUNO_DVS159
Now, he eyes a photo. It shows him holding a boy.
BRUNO_DVS160
Now, SOMEONE sets a plate of pie in front of himself, and glances up from his seat. A couple of guys across the restaurant stare at him. SOMEONE raises a fork full of pie, pauses, then takes his first bite. Now, a waitress brings him a whole other pie and an ice cream sundae. SOMEONE digs into a piece of strawberry cream pie, and takes a bite. His face already covered with chocolate. SOMEONE enters and stops short as he sees SOMEONE in the dining room. He sits with him.
BRUNO_DVS163
SOMEONE carries him piggyback out of the restaurant.
BRUNO_DVS166
The next morning at the hotel.
BRUNO_DVS167
Together in leather bondage gear.
BRUNO_DVS168
Engineering guy knocks on their door.
BRUNO_DVS169
SOMEONE nods with a toilet brush.
BRUNO_DVS170
Employees enter SOMEONE's room.
BRUNO_DVS171
Now, at a God Hates Fags anti-gay activist group rally.
BRUNO_DVS172
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hobble up in their bondage gear.
BRUNO_DVS173
SOMEONE grabs a man's sign.
BRUNO_DVS174
The protester struggles to get away. He falls over. Later, still chained together, SOMEONE and SOMEONE waddle onto a bus. Now, they lie on top of each in the aisle. Other passengers stare. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand as a male police officer enters.
BRUNO_DVS175
Now, unchained, the guys leave the Madison County Office of Alternative Sentencing and Release.
BRUNO_DVS182
Both men are wrapped in gray blankets. SOMEONE glares at his assistant with a knit brow. His lips stutter open.
BRUNO_DVS183
SOMEONE gives a stunned blink. His jaw hanging slack, as he turns and trudges away. He pulls his blanket tighter.
BRUNO_DVS188
SOMEONE hikes away. Night-time. Wearing pants, cowboy boots, and a dark tee, SOMEONE pushes a shopping cart. It's pulling a train of wheeled clothing racks, with the exercise bike as the caboose.
BRUNO_DVS189
Two racks topple over by an electronics store, and he struggles to right them.
BRUNO_DVS191
TVs in the store window, show celebrities on red carpets.
BRUNO_DVS192
SOMEONE gets to his feet, his gaze locked on the TVs.
BRUNO_DVS193
Now, in Alabama, SOMEONE faces Pastor SOMEONE Trautwein, Gay Converter.
BRUNO_DVS194
SOMEONE saunters into a karate dojo. He faces SOMEONE Shirley, Martial Arts Master - a stocky man with a mullet.
BRUNO_DVS195
Effects punch and spins away.
BRUNO_DVS196
He wraps his leg around SOMEONE's knee.
BRUNO_DVS197
SOMEONE swats with a dildo. SOMEONE twists his arm, and forces him to the floor.
BRUNO_DVS198
SOMEONE demonstrates a counterattack.
BRUNO_DVS199
Hits SOMEONE with his knee.
BRUNO_DVS200
SOMEONE attacks from behind.
BRUNO_DVS201
But pretends to fall, and get back up. SOMEONE keeps kicking.
BRUNO_DVS202
SOMEONE rolls onto his back.
BRUNO_DVS203
SOMEONE wears a strap-on dildo. SOMEONE boots it.
BRUNO_DVS204
Back at Pastor Trautwein's house.
BRUNO_DVS205
At the Fort McClellan Army National Guard Training Center.
BRUNO_DVS206
The TAC Officer stares slack-jawed. Later.
BRUNO_DVS207
Now, SOMEONE wears a uniform wear a silk scarf.
BRUNO_DVS208
His hat sits sideways.
BRUNO_DVS210
The pastor's eyes twitch angrily.
BRUNO_DVS211
Cullman County, Alabama.
BRUNO_DVS212
Offers his limp hand to one of three hunters, and the man shakes it.
BRUNO_DVS213
Robert nods, as SOMEONE stares off. Now, in a field, the men hold rifles.
BRUNO_DVS214
SOMEONE bobs his head.
BRUNO_DVS215
As a full moon glows in the sky, the four men sit in collapsible chairs around a campfire.
BRUNO_DVS216
Blinking uncomfortably, SOMEONE puffs a cigarette and drops his gaze.
BRUNO_DVS217
SOMEONE continues to gaze upward. His legs crossed tightly, and his hands folded neatly on his knee, lowering his stare. He idly bobs his head. The three hunters sit motionless.
BRUNO_DVS218
SOMEONE glances at Robert, then shifts his eyes to SOMEONE and SOMEONE on his other side. SOMEONE looks away.
BRUNO_DVS219
SOMEONE scratches the back of his head under his camouflage cap.
BRUNO_DVS220
Now, a time appears - 2:23 a.m. A green-hued night-vision vision shows four tents glows from within. Wearing a silky robe. SOMEONE creeps toward one, and bends close.
BRUNO_DVS223
He unzips the flap, and peeks inside.
BRUNO_DVS227
He zips the tent back up. Now, at 3:42 a.m, SOMEONE stalks back toward SOMEONE's tent, totally naked. He unzips the flap.
BRUNO_DVS230
He seizes the camera. Now, words appear. One week later.
BRUNO_DVS231
At a house.
BRUNO_DVS232
Dr. SOMEONE Cameron, Second Stage Gay Converter.
BRUNO_DVS233
SOMEONE wears a buttoned-down shirt.
BRUNO_DVS234
Now words appear - Swingers party. Inside a house, SOMEONE chats with several couples.
BRUNO_DVS235
On the porch.
BRUNO_DVS236
Now, SOMEONE again sits. Reverse cowgirl on his lap smiling dreamily.
BRUNO_DVS237
Man demonstrates.
BRUNO_DVS238
Smile vanishes. Later in the house, he shifts uncomfortably as two men and a woman give another woman oral sex. A black box covers her crotch.
BRUNO_DVS239
Now, a voluptuous woman does reverse cowgirl with a red-haired guy. A black box covers her.
BRUNO_DVS240
SOMEONE pats the man's arm.
BRUNO_DVS241
Later, the man hugs the woman from behind. Perching beside them on the arm of the couch, SOMEONE leans forward, and tickles the man's knee.
BRUNO_DVS242
Now, the balding man humps a woman from behind.
BRUNO_DVS243
SOMEONE pats him on the back.
BRUNO_DVS244
SOMEONE bends into the man's line of sight.
BRUNO_DVS245
The man stares at the woman.
BRUNO_DVS246
SOMEONE smiles uncomfortably. A black box covers his genitals.
BRUNO_DVS247
On the stairs.
BRUNO_DVS249
They enter a bedroom.
BRUNO_DVS250
Later, she sits naked.
BRUNO_DVS251
He now wears only briefs.
BRUNO_DVS252
Strips them off, revealing smaller briefs underneath.
BRUNO_DVS253
It open and runs off.
BRUNO_DVS254
He races into the night. Now, words appear - Eight months later. Spotlights shine in a packed arena. A sign reads, Straight SOMEONE's Man Slammin' Maxout. Bikini clad women prance
BRUNO_DVS255
Now, an announcer holds a mic.
BRUNO_DVS256
SOMEONE walks though the audience, and approaches the octagon. SOMEONE glares coldly at him through the cage.
BRUNO_DVS257
He spits.
BRUNO_DVS258
As the fighting ceases, two confused female audience members exchange a glance. One man clutches his head in the octagon.
BRUNO_DVS260
SOMEONE enters, wearing a wedding dress with a veil obscuring his face.
BRUNO_DVS261
SOMEONE lifts it over his head, revealing SOMEONE's masculine features.
BRUNO_DVS262
The minister's jaw drops.
BRUNO_DVS263
SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze at him, as a happy couple.
BRUNO_DVS264
O.J. stands beside SOMEONE wearing a white tux.
BRUNO_DVS265
He shakes his head, then walks out.
BRUNO_DVS266
In a recording studio,
BRUNO_DVS267
SOMEONE steps up to the microphone.
BRUNO_DVS268
SOMEONE does a little dance. Now, SOMEONE stands at the microphone.
BRUNO_DVS269
SOMEONE plays guitar.
BRUNO_DVS270
Now, SOMEONE plays piano.