Later as the blonde packs a suitcase, the sexy dancers pump their hips.
BURLESQUE_DVS27
The blonde regards a framed photo of a woman.
BURLESQUE_DVS28
She sings in the empty dive.
BURLESQUE_DVS29
She leaves the trailer park behind.
BURLESQUE_DVS32
At a bus station.
BURLESQUE_DVS33
Now she peers dreamily out the window of a cruising bus.
BURLESQUE_DVS34
As the sequined-clad dancers command their stage, the blonde sings to empty chairs in SOMEONE's bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS35
Now the Hollywood sign fills the screen. On the bus, the sleepy blonde opens her eyes just as the sign's reflection skates across her window.
BURLESQUE_DVS36
Later in a run-down room at the old redbrick Hotel Rosslyn, she opens her suitcase. Other views show the glitzy athletic dancers in unison, then the blonde rocking out in SOMEONE's empty bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS37
Now the blonde seals her stash of money inside a plastic bag.
BURLESQUE_DVS38
In the bathroom, she lifts the lid off the toilet tank and carefully sets the bag inside, leaving its top edge over the back rim.
BURLESQUE_DVS39
She replaces the porcelain lid.
BURLESQUE_DVS40
Now she unpacks her framed photo.
BURLESQUE_DVS41
The blonde gazes fondly at the photo, which shows the brunette woman cradling a young girl.
BURLESQUE_DVS42
Now the newcomer to LA sits at a desk with a postcard of the old hotel.
BURLESQUE_DVS43
She counts up several windows,
BURLESQUE_DVS44
She marks one specifically, and labels it.
BURLESQUE_DVS46
She flips the postcard. Her pen tip hovers.
BURLESQUE_DVS47
Then she rips the card to shreds.
BURLESQUE_DVS48
At her open window, she tosses the scraps and watches them flutter downward.
BURLESQUE_DVS49
Now she steps onto a busy sidewalk.
BURLESQUE_DVS50
She lifts her gaze from an issue of Back Stage Magazine in her hand and finds a sign for Hollywood Boulevard.
BURLESQUE_DVS51
Her finger trails down an ad in the magazine that seeks background singers for urban group.
BURLESQUE_DVS52
At a street corner, a set of signs marks Hollywood and Vine.
BURLESQUE_DVS53
Our view sweeps up the towering circular Capitol Records building.
BURLESQUE_DVS54
The blonde enters another building, then exits and crosses off the ad in her paper.
BURLESQUE_DVS55
Later still, she Xs out two more ads for singers and dancers as she continues down the boulevard.
BURLESQUE_DVS56
She gives someone a polite smile, which instantly fades as she moves on.
BURLESQUE_DVS57
Golden sunlight dwindles on the LA skyline.
BURLESQUE_DVS58
Fade to black.
BURLESQUE_DVS59
In the evening, the blonde strolls a busy street.
BURLESQUE_DVS60
Her eyes sweeping her surroundings,
BURLESQUE_DVS61
she stops at an eye-catching archway.
BURLESQUE_DVS62
Flashing light bulbs arc over a gleaming sign,
BURLESQUE_DVS63
Burlesque Lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS64
On the building's fire escape, she sees a woman in a sexy corset with a short feathery skirt.
BURLESQUE_DVS65
As the woman adjusts her striped thigh-highs, her gaze meets the blonde's. They share a smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS66
A bald man with a cigarette between his lips emerges from the building.
BURLESQUE_DVS67
The blonde heads toward the burlesque lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS68
Our view sweeps up a nearly completed high-rise behind her that advertises, Luxury Condos for Sale.
BURLESQUE_DVS69
The blonde checks out a poster outside the lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS70
It shows a pixie-faced blue-eyed brunette and reads, The Best View on the Sunset Strip.
BURLESQUE_DVS73
Entering the building, the blonde makes her way down a dim wood-paneled hall.
BURLESQUE_DVS74
As she heads down a staircase, she eyes the lounge's stage through a window.
BURLESQUE_DVS75
Onstage, cool-blue light bathes dancers in skimpy sailor-themed outfits as they strike provocative poses.
BURLESQUE_DVS76
A doorman holds out his hand.
BURLESQUE_DVS77
Onstage, six captivating dancers - three on a platform, three in front - scoop their hips and twirl their hands. They point skyward.
BURLESQUE_DVS78
The blonde opens her wallet and hesitates. She casts another glance at the show, then hands over a $20.
BURLESQUE_DVS79
Onstage, the reclined dancers snap then raise their arms in the air.
BURLESQUE_DVS81
Behind them, a woman with dark curly hair and high cheek bones faces us.
BURLESQUE_DVS82
She wears a low-cut black unitard with tails and fuchsia lapels.
BURLESQUE_DVS84
The dancers rise and strut around the singer.
BURLESQUE_DVS85
The dancers tap their heels, then nod to a neighboring stage where musicians play. One-by-one the dancers face the audience.
BURLESQUE_DVS86
They pump their chests.
BURLESQUE_DVS87
The mesmerized blonde watches as varying dancers respond to their names.
BURLESQUE_DVS88
An auburn-haired dancer waves coyly. Now all of the dancers curl their fingers at us, beckoning mischievously.
BURLESQUE_DVS89
The dancers squat.
BURLESQUE_DVS90
The dancers strike alluring seductive poses and line up downstage. One lifts a leg higher than the singer's head.
BURLESQUE_DVS91
The posed dancers frame the smiling diva.
BURLESQUE_DVS92
Tears in her eyes, the blonde woman claps, transfixed.
BURLESQUE_DVS93
As the band plays, a spotlight shines on dancers in silver-sequined outfits. A handsome toned bartender in eyeliner and a bowler hat leans toward the blonde.
BURLESQUE_DVS94
They swap a smile. Then she returns her eyes to the stage where the dancers shake their hips.
BURLESQUE_DVS95
The bartender interrupts a pink-haired waitress who's busy flirting.
BURLESQUE_DVS96
The blonde turns back to the bartender.
BURLESQUE_DVS97
She points to the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS98
He hands her a business card.
BURLESQUE_DVS99
As she leaves, the bartender smiles. Now the blonde enters a bustling backstage area.
BURLESQUE_DVS100
A dancer bumps into her as she hurries past. The blonde sees another dancer pulling on a sparkling garter over black stockings.
BURLESQUE_DVS101
Two dancers wear light-satin corsets with black spirals at the breasts. The blonde visitor finds the bald stage manager conferring with the diva.
BURLESQUE_DVS102
The naysayer faces the singer.
BURLESQUE_DVS103
As SOMEONE does the dancer's hair, the blonde approaches.
BURLESQUE_DVS104
She finds SOMEONE applying makeup at a mirror and leans over her shoulder.
BURLESQUE_DVS105
The eager woman slouches sadly.
BURLESQUE_DVS106
On her way out, she collides with the brunette in large sunglasses.
BURLESQUE_DVS107
She shows her nails.
BURLESQUE_DVS108
As the pixie-faced dancer brushes on blush, the blonde tilts her head at her. SOMEONE glances over.
BURLESQUE_DVS109
As she leaves, Jesse reaches for SOMEONE's makeup.
BURLESQUE_DVS110
Now, the young hopeful from Iowa sees the pink-haired waitress snubbing a customer. So she doffs her brown-leather jacket and grabs an empty tray from the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS111
She walks out among the tables. Collecting empty glasses, the ambitious girl starts taking drink orders.
BURLESQUE_DVS112
As she brings the tray back to the bar, SOMEONE notices her.
BURLESQUE_DVS113
The image revolves, framed in light bulbs like a dressing-room mirror. Now in black hot pants, the young hopeful collects a spent glass and draws a smile from SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS114
Onstage, SOMEONE slides down beaded strands forming a curtain. In a black bra and panties, she lands in a split.
BURLESQUE_DVS115
As the girl from Iowa serves drinks, SOMEONE notices her.
BURLESQUE_DVS116
She gestures for the young woman to come over.
BURLESQUE_DVS117
SOMEONE sits back down beside SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS118
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap smiles.
BURLESQUE_DVS119
SOMEONE windmills a leg, then seizes a bracelet off of Jesse.
BURLESQUE_DVS120
SOMEONE mimics a dance step, then resumes her work.
BURLESQUE_DVS121
SOMEONE leads four dancers downstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS122
Now a rugged man gets SOMEONE's attention.
BURLESQUE_DVS123
He slides her his AmEx.
BURLESQUE_DVS124
She looks back.
BURLESQUE_DVS126
SOMEONE smirks.
BURLESQUE_DVS127
SOMEONE pushes the beads aside. She sees SOMEONE performing, then SOMEONE waiting tables.
BURLESQUE_DVS128
She dons a white stole.
BURLESQUE_DVS129
The curtain parts and SOMEONE struts into the limelight.
BURLESQUE_DVS130
She passes her stole to SOMEONE, who pitches it and competitively joins SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS131
They swipe kitty paws at each other, then take turns upstaging each other.
BURLESQUE_DVS132
Entranced, SOMEONE flourishes a hand in front of a customer's face.
BURLESQUE_DVS133
Now the dancers drum their hips. SOMEONE taps SOMEONE's nose. Then they trade phrases.
BURLESQUE_DVS134
At the bar, SOMEONE imagines herself performing, showered by silver confetti.
BURLESQUE_DVS135
She flings away her serving tray.
BURLESQUE_DVS136
She twirls a string of diamonds overhead.
BURLESQUE_DVS137
Standing on a fringed pedestal surrounded by dancers, she coils the strand around her wrist. Snapping to, she gazes longingly at the performance. SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE offstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS138
She opens her arms to the crowd.
BURLESQUE_DVS139
SOMEONE taps her.
BURLESQUE_DVS140
While SOMEONE chats at Marcus' table, SOMEONE peers over his glasses. SOMEONE glances at the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS141
He slides her a tray of drinks. Now a stack of burlesque-related books lands on her hotel bed.
BURLESQUE_DVS142
SOMEONE lies on her stomach, flipping through photos of famed performers. At the lounge, she studies the dancers.
BURLESQUE_DVS143
Lying on her back, she rests another book on her chest.
BURLESQUE_DVS144
We glimpse the Burlesque Lounge sign. Then SOMEONE and SOMEONE at work.
BURLESQUE_DVS145
As she serves a drink, the bartender eyes her and rubs his unshaven cheek.
BURLESQUE_DVS146
Now a soundman preps a vocal CD.
BURLESQUE_DVS147
Sitting on the edge of the stage, SOMEONE crosses her legs.
BURLESQUE_DVS148
SOMEONE looks on with a tray of empty glasses.
BURLESQUE_DVS149
An overhead light shines down on three sexy nurses at an exam chair.
BURLESQUE_DVS150
In a lace bodysuit, SOMEONE stands and rocks her hips.
BURLESQUE_DVS151
Now in SOMEONE' office.
BURLESQUE_DVS152
SOMEONE looks on.
BURLESQUE_DVS153
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a document.
BURLESQUE_DVS154
He grins.
BURLESQUE_DVS155
SOMEONE paces to a framed photo of her burlesque troupe.
BURLESQUE_DVS156
The picture reflects her porcelain complexion.
BURLESQUE_DVS157
As SOMEONE waits, she regards him plainly.
BURLESQUE_DVS158
In the hall, SOMEONE overhears.
BURLESQUE_DVS159
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE turns on his way out.
BURLESQUE_DVS160
Onstage, the nurses roll SOMEONE along in the chair.
BURLESQUE_DVS161
She rises to her knees.
BURLESQUE_DVS162
A nurse eyes the crowd.
BURLESQUE_DVS163
SOMEONE watches her and SOMEONE looks up from pouring a drink. With a dramatic swoon, SOMEONE wipes her brow and lies back.
BURLESQUE_DVS164
Later a bartender pours two tequila shots. In the dressing room, the dancers fix their makeup.
BURLESQUE_DVS165
SOMEONE sets down her tray.
BURLESQUE_DVS166
SOMEONE picks up the shot glasses.
BURLESQUE_DVS167
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch her down both shots.
BURLESQUE_DVS168
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE at a costume rack.
BURLESQUE_DVS170
SOMEONE glances back.
BURLESQUE_DVS171
SOMEONE peers through the rack.
BURLESQUE_DVS172
He wraps his legs around her.
BURLESQUE_DVS173
Now at the Hotel Rosslyn,
BURLESQUE_DVS174
SOMEONE finds her door broken in. She enters her ransacked studio apartment, then drops her purse and hurries into the bathroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS175
She finds the empty sandwich baggie on the floor.
BURLESQUE_DVS176
On the bed, SOMEONE finds her photograph under broken glass, halfway out of its now-bent frame.
BURLESQUE_DVS177
She holds the photo of the mother and child.
BURLESQUE_DVS178
SOMEONE glances around, then sits on the edge of the bed and covers her mouth.
BURLESQUE_DVS179
Now SOMEONE rides down a street on a motorcycle and parks.
BURLESQUE_DVS180
She sits on the stoop of a picturesque Spanish-style apartment building.
BURLESQUE_DVS181
Later he lets her in.
BURLESQUE_DVS182
He takes back his phone and they sip their drinks.
BURLESQUE_DVS183
Later, SOMEONE
BURLESQUE_DVS184
reclines on a daybed.
BURLESQUE_DVS185
SOMEONE sits at a synthesizer.
BURLESQUE_DVS186
She nestles in and pulls her blanket close.
BURLESQUE_DVS188
Rain pounds the street outside.
BURLESQUE_DVS189
SOMEONE wakes,
BURLESQUE_DVS190
then opens his bedroom's French doors and steps out in jeans and a white tank.
BURLESQUE_DVS191
SOMEONE ogles SOMEONE's short pajama top.
BURLESQUE_DVS192
As she hops into some jeans, she tips over.
BURLESQUE_DVS193
She collects her suitcase and bag.
BURLESQUE_DVS194
SOMEONE steps out of the apartment building and peers morosely at the rain-pelted street.
BURLESQUE_DVS195
She grabs a newspaper and holds it overhead.
BURLESQUE_DVS196
SOMEONE peers out of his window and watches her walk out to the curb.
BURLESQUE_DVS197
SOMEONE watches a car pass by. Then SOMEONE leaves the window.
BURLESQUE_DVS198
As SOMEONE waits in the downpour at a bus stop,
BURLESQUE_DVS199
SOMEONE steps out, barefoot.
BURLESQUE_DVS200
He picks her up.
BURLESQUE_DVS201
Now inside.
BURLESQUE_DVS202
He pushes the door shut.
BURLESQUE_DVS203
Now at the club, an employee polishes mirrored panels behind the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS204
The cashier puts down chairs.
BURLESQUE_DVS205
As the band practices, a bartender wipes down a bottle.
BURLESQUE_DVS206
SOMEONE enters a bathroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS207
She notes someone in a stall.
BURLESQUE_DVS208
The red-haired dancer steps out.
BURLESQUE_DVS209
SOMEONE shakes her head.
BURLESQUE_DVS210
The young woman leans on the sink.
BURLESQUE_DVS211
They hug.
BURLESQUE_DVS212
SOMEONE peers nervously skyward.
BURLESQUE_DVS213
Now beaming dancers in plain clothes leap through the air.
BURLESQUE_DVS214
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from a table on the empty floor.
BURLESQUE_DVS215
SOMEONE enters the club and observes the girls onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS216
As she doffs her jean jacket, she keeps watching.
BURLESQUE_DVS217
As the dancers leave, SOMEONE strides purposefully ahead.
BURLESQUE_DVS218
They notice SOMEONE onstage, swinging her hips and running her fingers down her blonde hair.
BURLESQUE_DVS219
SOMEONE peers back to the deejay booth.
BURLESQUE_DVS220
SOMEONE walks away.
BURLESQUE_DVS221
She wheels around.
BURLESQUE_DVS222
SOMEONE shoots a satisfied glance toward SOMEONE at the back of the house. SOMEONE returns to the table, where SOMEONE raises an eyebrow.
BURLESQUE_DVS223
SOMEONE and Coco enter and spot SOMEONE onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS224
Standing at a chair with her back turned, SOMEONE lets her hair down.
BURLESQUE_DVS225
SOMEONE joins the girls.
BURLESQUE_DVS226
Our view rises up SOMEONE's slender body
BURLESQUE_DVS227
As SOMEONE enters with a box of liquor, he notices her too.
BURLESQUE_DVS228
SOMEONE gyrates her backside, then looks over her shoulder.
BURLESQUE_DVS229
Holding the back of the chair, she seductively points her knees in and out.
BURLESQUE_DVS230
She whips her hair back and steps forward.
BURLESQUE_DVS231
SOMEONE and the others keep watching.
BURLESQUE_DVS232
SOMEONE holds her hands out like paws, then slaps her backside with her right, then with her left,
BURLESQUE_DVS233
then twice more before resuming the wild dance.
BURLESQUE_DVS234
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, who eyes her knowingly.
BURLESQUE_DVS235
The club owner affords a slight nod.
BURLESQUE_DVS236
Now SOMEONE rubs her hands over her head and body, then points her knees in.
BURLESQUE_DVS237
SOMEONE softly shakes his head to himself. As SOMEONE leans forward and pouts her full lips, SOMEONE's cool gaze hardens even more. Onstage, SOMEONE prances, paws out, and grins adorably.
BURLESQUE_DVS238
SOMEONE remains watchful.
BURLESQUE_DVS239
A smiling SOMEONE points her knees and pops out her hands, then swings her arms, shakes her hips, and whips her hair back.
BURLESQUE_DVS240
SOMEONE smiles. SOMEONE glares. SOMEONE folds his hands.
BURLESQUE_DVS241
SOMEONE beams. SOMEONE claps.
BURLESQUE_DVS242
SOMEONE and SOMEONE leave.
BURLESQUE_DVS243
SOMEONE joins the excited young woman onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS244
A delighted SOMEONE approaches, clapping.
BURLESQUE_DVS245
He nods.
BURLESQUE_DVS246
SOMEONE gives a silent scream.
BURLESQUE_DVS247
As she runs off, SOMEONE wears a muted smile. Now at the costume rack.
BURLESQUE_DVS249
A golden SOMEONE gun.
BURLESQUE_DVS250
It blasts him with gold confetti.
BURLESQUE_DVS251
He eyes her flatly and she forces a grin.
BURLESQUE_DVS252
Now SOMEONE struts confidently among pedestrians outside.
BURLESQUE_DVS253
At the club, she rehearses with the girls at the end of the line.
BURLESQUE_DVS254
Back with the pedestrians, she practices a move.
BURLESQUE_DVS255
In rehearsal, the dancers bounce, bop their heads, and gyrate their hips. On a sidewalk, SOMEONE practices the routine.
BURLESQUE_DVS256
The rehearsing dancers spin. Then SOMEONE spins on the street and resumes her walk.
BURLESQUE_DVS257
Onstage, a spotlight sweeps across the costumed girls.
BURLESQUE_DVS258
We cut from their routine to SOMEONE strolling down another street.
BURLESQUE_DVS259
She flourishes her wrist and gives a satisfied smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS260
In a performance, the dancers frolic downstage, SOMEONE among them. The newest dancer runs her hands through her hair and shakes her hips. The view veers to SOMEONE backstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS261
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE perform.
BURLESQUE_DVS262
The girls leave the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS263
Later in the dressing room.
BURLESQUE_DVS264
As SOMEONE pulls on her sweater, the other dancers head out of the dressing room.
BURLESQUE_DVS265
She slings her bag over her shoulder,
BURLESQUE_DVS266
then turns and sees the group disappearing down a staircase without her.
BURLESQUE_DVS267
With a heavy look,
BURLESQUE_DVS268
SOMEONE drops her bag back on the floor and plops into her chair at the dressing table.
BURLESQUE_DVS269
Resting her chin on her fist, she gazes at a black-and-white photo stuck to her mirror.
BURLESQUE_DVS270
It shows a glamorous burlesque dancer.
BURLESQUE_DVS271
SOMEONE's eyes shift to her makeup,
BURLESQUE_DVS272
then return to the photo.
BURLESQUE_DVS273
She picks up a thin makeup brush.
BURLESQUE_DVS274
As SOMEONE nears the dressing room,
BURLESQUE_DVS275
she stops in the doorway and watches as SOMEONE tries to paint on eyeliner.
BURLESQUE_DVS276
The blonde pushes her eyelashes up with a brush
BURLESQUE_DVS277
and flinches.
BURLESQUE_DVS278
SOMEONE moves beside her.
BURLESQUE_DVS279
returns her gaze to the mirror and lifts the brush to her lashes again.
BURLESQUE_DVS280
SOMEONE unzips a pouch and withdraws a brush.
BURLESQUE_DVS281
She holds it out to SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS282
As SOMEONE starts up again,
BURLESQUE_DVS283
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
BURLESQUE_DVS284
She sits beside her.
BURLESQUE_DVS285
She paints black lines along SOMEONE's eyelid.
BURLESQUE_DVS286
She applies color to SOMEONE's lids.
BURLESQUE_DVS287
SOMEONE grins.
BURLESQUE_DVS288
SOMEONE uses a large soft brush to apply rouge to SOMEONE's cheeks.
BURLESQUE_DVS289
She playfully taps SOMEONE's nose with the bristles.
BURLESQUE_DVS290
Holding SOMEONE' gaze, SOMEONE gives a mild shrug.
BURLESQUE_DVS291
With a faint smile, SOMEONE uses another brush to paint lipstick onto SOMEONE's parted lips.
BURLESQUE_DVS292
SOMEONE averts her eyes. As she stares off,
BURLESQUE_DVS293
SOMEONE skillfully finishes painting her lips.
BURLESQUE_DVS295
she gently tilts SOMEONE's face and examines her handiwork.
BURLESQUE_DVS296
SOMEONE turns to the mirror and sees her red lips and painted eyelids.
BURLESQUE_DVS297
Tilting her head back and forth, she touches her face.
BURLESQUE_DVS298
Now SOMEONE reaches out of the shower and finds bras and stockings hanging on a hook.
BURLESQUE_DVS299
He turns to a towel rack where more undergarments hang.
BURLESQUE_DVS300
He spots his towel on the floor.
BURLESQUE_DVS301
SOMEONE sleeps in the living room.
BURLESQUE_DVS302
He picks up a newspaper.
BURLESQUE_DVS303
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE grabs his phone off the bed.
BURLESQUE_DVS304
He swings the bedroom door shut.
BURLESQUE_DVS305
Later SOMEONE reads a housing ad in the newspaper.
BURLESQUE_DVS306
SOMEONE comes out.
BURLESQUE_DVS307
SOMEONE bites her thumb.
BURLESQUE_DVS308
pulls on his shirt.
BURLESQUE_DVS309
He takes the newspaper from her.
BURLESQUE_DVS310
She snatches the paper back.
BURLESQUE_DVS311
She backs into his bedroom and closes the doors.
BURLESQUE_DVS313
At the lounge, a bartender carries crates of glasses and the band rehearses. SOMEONE storms out of SOMEONE' office.
BURLESQUE_DVS314
SOMEONE pauses from organizing costumes on a rack and watches SOMEONE stalk away.
BURLESQUE_DVS315
In her office, SOMEONE folds a piece of paper into an airplane.
BURLESQUE_DVS316
As she smooths the final crease, creating its wings,
BURLESQUE_DVS317
SOMEONE enters.
BURLESQUE_DVS318
SOMEONE tosses her paper plane at him.
BURLESQUE_DVS319
The backstage manager's gaze follows it as it lands on the floor at his feet.
BURLESQUE_DVS320
He picks it up and unfolds it.
BURLESQUE_DVS321
SOMEONE crumples the paper.
BURLESQUE_DVS322
Averting his gaze, SOMEONE shakes his head.
BURLESQUE_DVS323
SOMEONE lifts his chin.
BURLESQUE_DVS324
He bows his head.
BURLESQUE_DVS325
He locks his eyes with SOMEONE' desperate gaze, then moves forward to the couch where she sits.
BURLESQUE_DVS326
He sits beside her.
BURLESQUE_DVS327
He wraps his arms around her and she rests her head on his shoulder.
BURLESQUE_DVS328
He pats her arm.
BURLESQUE_DVS329
Later in the crowded lounge, SOMEONE plays piano with the band.
BURLESQUE_DVS330
As the dancers get ready backstage, SOMEONE descends the staircase with a drink in her hand.
BURLESQUE_DVS331
Wearing a skimpy biker-themed costume, she heads toward the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS332
SOMEONE sniffs the drink.
BURLESQUE_DVS333
SOMEONE pushes SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS334
SOMEONE throws up her hands.
BURLESQUE_DVS335
SOMEONE tosses SOMEONE a costume. Meanwhile, SOMEONE enters the sound booth.
BURLESQUE_DVS336
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE leave, then moves to his soundboard. Onstage, a spotlight shines on Coco.
BURLESQUE_DVS337
The light shines on another dancer.
BURLESQUE_DVS338
As the red spotlight fixes on SOMEONE for her turn to lip-sync, SOMEONE pulls a plug.
BURLESQUE_DVS339
SOMEONE stops dancing and gazes across the lounge toward the sound booth.
BURLESQUE_DVS340
SOMEONE gives a satisfied smile. Meanwhile, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE backstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS341
Onstage, SOMEONE sees the curtain descending. The doorman eyes departing patrons.
BURLESQUE_DVS342
SOMEONE tentatively steps to the front of the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS343
As the curtain continues to drop, she opens her mouth.
BURLESQUE_DVS344
SOMEONE, the doorman, and SOMEONE stare.
BURLESQUE_DVS345
The curtain freezes above SOMEONE's head.
BURLESQUE_DVS346
SOMEONE moves closer. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare, awestruck.
BURLESQUE_DVS347
The stagehand pulls a rope and the curtain rises back to the ceiling.
BURLESQUE_DVS348
A stagehand swivels a spotlight onto SOMEONE. As the band joins her, she struts toward the audience.
BURLESQUE_DVS349
Dancing, she swings her hips from side to side. SOMEONE smiles and shakes her head.
BURLESQUE_DVS350
Audience members bop their heads and shimmy their shoulders. SOMEONE grins.
BURLESQUE_DVS351
SOMEONE tips her biker cap.
BURLESQUE_DVS352
The crowd claps and the two dancers behind SOMEONE sing backup as they step from side to side. SOMEONE glares down at them. SOMEONE beckons the backup dancers and they join her downstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS353
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange a disbelieving look.
BURLESQUE_DVS354
SOMEONE grabs a musician out of the band and pulls him onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS355
Dancing around her, he plays the tambourine.
BURLESQUE_DVS356
SOMEONE strikes a pose with her arms in the air and the stage lights blink off.
BURLESQUE_DVS357
As Coco hugs SOMEONE, the crowd rises in a standing ovation.
BURLESQUE_DVS358
SOMEONE storms out of the sound booth with a sour expression.
BURLESQUE_DVS359
A spotlight fades up onstage and the bartenders, including SOMEONE, clap for the performers.
BURLESQUE_DVS360
SOMEONE's backup dancers push her forward.
BURLESQUE_DVS361
She curtsies, then bows with the others.
BURLESQUE_DVS362
The curtain falls.
BURLESQUE_DVS363
Backstage, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the other dancers crowd around.
BURLESQUE_DVS364
SOMEONE looks on.
BURLESQUE_DVS365
SOMEONE's jaw drops. SOMEONE gives her dancers a thumbs up, then turns to SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS366
SOMEONE glares at her.
BURLESQUE_DVS367
With a smile, SOMEONE strides away. SOMEONE juts out her chin.
BURLESQUE_DVS368
As the dancers disperse, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS369
He heads away, passing SOMEONE, who stares at SOMEONE, her arms crossed.
BURLESQUE_DVS370
She smiles.
BURLESQUE_DVS371
She turns away with a conniving smirk.
BURLESQUE_DVS372
Now SOMEONE exits the backstage area and finds SOMEONE waiting for her.
BURLESQUE_DVS373
Grinning, he claps.
BURLESQUE_DVS374
SOMEONE nods as she walks off.
BURLESQUE_DVS375
After hours, SOMEONE and the other dancers hang out at the bar with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS376
SOMEONE gets up. Coco looks at SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS377
SOMEONE shifts her gaze from Coco to another dancer, who nods.
BURLESQUE_DVS378
SOMEONE stares after her as she leaves with them.
BURLESQUE_DVS379
He pretends to think.
BURLESQUE_DVS380
As SOMEONE grabs her stuff, SOMEONE self-consciously looks away.
BURLESQUE_DVS381
With a smile, SOMEONE cocks his head.
BURLESQUE_DVS382
SOMEONE moves to his side.
BURLESQUE_DVS383
He points to a mirror.
BURLESQUE_DVS384
He sweeps her hair up.
BURLESQUE_DVS385
She gives the bald man a playful nudge. Now a light rises on SOMEONE in a platinum bobbed wig.
BURLESQUE_DVS386
She rises from the chaise lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS387
SOMEONE watches dreamily.
BURLESQUE_DVS388
She tugs on a gold rope.
BURLESQUE_DVS389
As the curtain rises, SOMEONE resumes his work.
BURLESQUE_DVS390
SOMEONE makes her way up some stairs, toward a platform. She tosses her head and shoulders back with each beat, then wiggles her hips at the crowd.
BURLESQUE_DVS391
Bending forward, she shakes her rear and the feathers on her short skirt flutter.
BURLESQUE_DVS392
She sits on a step and kicks her feet in the air.
BURLESQUE_DVS393
Facing the audience, she quickly spreads her knees, then crosses her legs. She dances up the rest of the stairs to the platform where another curtain opens, revealing more dancers.
BURLESQUE_DVS394
Now SOMEONE dances on the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS395
As a glass slides toward her, she kicks it out of the way. She struts to the wall of mirrored panels behind the bar and strikes a pose. As she pushes on one panel, it spins and she disappears behind it.
BURLESQUE_DVS396
A different panel spins and SOMEONE rotates into the room, then whirls away again.
BURLESQUE_DVS397
All of the panels turn with dancers in front of each.
BURLESQUE_DVS398
A bartender leans forward,
BURLESQUE_DVS399
bridging the wall and the bar with his back.
BURLESQUE_DVS400
Two others lead SOMEONE across.
BURLESQUE_DVS401
She swoons backwards off the bar. Two bartenders catch her and carry her to the chaise lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS402
She pretends to take a shot.
BURLESQUE_DVS403
The stage lights turn off.
BURLESQUE_DVS404
Later as SOMEONE works behind the bar, SOMEONE appears, still in her short sequined dress and platinum blonde wig.
BURLESQUE_DVS405
SOMEONE gives her a sidelong look.
BURLESQUE_DVS406
She spins on her stool.
BURLESQUE_DVS407
Her smile fades and she walks away. SOMEONE stares after her.
BURLESQUE_DVS409
SOMEONE struggles to uncap a spray bottle.
BURLESQUE_DVS410
SOMEONE easily removes the cap, then leans closer.
BURLESQUE_DVS411
SOMEONE gapes as SOMEONE strides away.
BURLESQUE_DVS412
In the lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS413
SOMEONE sets drinks on Marcus' table and sits across from him.
BURLESQUE_DVS415
at SOMEONE's place.
BURLESQUE_DVS416
Coming home, SOMEONE spies SOMEONE in the bedroom, wearing only pink panties and a matching bra.
BURLESQUE_DVS417
He steps further into the apartment,
BURLESQUE_DVS418
his mesmerized gaze fixed on her curves.
BURLESQUE_DVS419
His bag topples candles on the coffee table.
BURLESQUE_DVS420
He returns to the door.
BURLESQUE_DVS421
SOMEONE joins her at a mirror and zips up her dress.
BURLESQUE_DVS422
He notices SOMEONE's photo.
BURLESQUE_DVS424
SOMEONE glances up at him with a winsome pout.
BURLESQUE_DVS425
SOMEONE smiles warmly as she holds his gaze.
BURLESQUE_DVS426
Grinning boyishly, he steps away.
BURLESQUE_DVS427
SOMEONE's smile fades.
BURLESQUE_DVS428
Now feather fans lift away to reveal SOMEONE reclined on the lounge piano, in a skimpy two-piece outfit made of pearls.
BURLESQUE_DVS429
She pushes the pianist's head past her lap, then shimmies her pearls.
BURLESQUE_DVS430
At home, SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a comfortable laugh in the living room.
BURLESQUE_DVS431
At the lounge, SOMEONE pops a champagne bottle's cork and smirks.
BURLESQUE_DVS432
At a table, SOMEONE thoughtfully rubs his chin as he watches her.
BURLESQUE_DVS433
Now as she rides with SOMEONE on his motorcycle, her sheer scarf flies away.
BURLESQUE_DVS434
As SOMEONE puts her back to the audience, her top flies off.
BURLESQUE_DVS435
A dancer hands her a fan and she covers her chest. Turning away, she lowers the fan and shimmies.
BURLESQUE_DVS436
Quickly covering herself, she faces the crowd again.
BURLESQUE_DVS437
Her pearl briefs fly off. She snatches another fan from a dancer.
BURLESQUE_DVS438
Now SOMEONE hurries into the dressing room with a giddy smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS439
She shows an engagement ring. The girls rush to hug her.
BURLESQUE_DVS440
Back onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS441
Peeking out from behind a fan, she comically blows feathers and hair out of her face.
BURLESQUE_DVS442
Now SOMEONE blows out birthday candles. Standing apart, SOMEONE snaps a photo, then smiles and winks at her.
BURLESQUE_DVS443
SOMEONE gazes tenderly at him.
BURLESQUE_DVS444
Onstage, she shimmies her fans.
BURLESQUE_DVS445
As she flings them away, her backup dancers raise two more in their place.
BURLESQUE_DVS446
They part the fans, revealing her naked form.
BURLESQUE_DVS447
A pair of bongos cover her breasts and a candle conceals her crotch.
BURLESQUE_DVS448
SOMEONE winks. Later she meets SOMEONE at the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS449
He stares, slack-jawed.
BURLESQUE_DVS450
SOMEONE carries a crate of glasses away.
BURLESQUE_DVS451
SOMEONE arrives at SOMEONE's side.
BURLESQUE_DVS452
He grabs her bag.
BURLESQUE_DVS453
Later SOMEONE rides in a vintage convertible speedster as SOMEONE drives.
BURLESQUE_DVS454
SOMEONE shakes her head.
BURLESQUE_DVS455
The speedster makes a turn.
BURLESQUE_DVS456
Later it pulls up outside a glamorous party.
BURLESQUE_DVS457
Primping, SOMEONE takes her hair down.
BURLESQUE_DVS458
As she and SOMEONE enter, several trendy upscale guests take notice.
BURLESQUE_DVS459
He takes her into a kitchen staffed with caterers and grabs one of the many bottles of wine.
BURLESQUE_DVS460
He takes two glasses and a tray of hors d'oeuvres.
BURLESQUE_DVS461
Leading her downstairs, he meets two guests.,
BURLESQUE_DVS462
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE onward.
BURLESQUE_DVS463
She halts in a doorway.
BURLESQUE_DVS464
A city view.
BURLESQUE_DVS465
SOMEONE gives her a smirk and sips his wine.
BURLESQUE_DVS466
Turning away, SOMEONE sips her wine with a cynical smirk.
BURLESQUE_DVS467
Now SOMEONE lies on the daybed with his eyes closed.
BURLESQUE_DVS468
His eyes open as SOMEONE arrives home.
BURLESQUE_DVS469
Now a gift box sits on a dressing-room stool.
BURLESQUE_DVS470
SOMEONE reads the card: To the best view in LA - SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS471
As the other girls look on, she opens the present and pulls out a pair of Louboutin shoes just like SOMEONE's.
BURLESQUE_DVS472
SOMEONE marches over and grabs the card.
BURLESQUE_DVS473
As she reads it, her smirk fades.
BURLESQUE_DVS474
SOMEONE leaves.
BURLESQUE_DVS475
Facing her mirror, SOMEONE dons a bowler hat.
BURLESQUE_DVS476
Now with the stage set to resemble the dressing room, SOMEONE and the dancers mime preparations for a show.
BURLESQUE_DVS477
The fake mirrors whisk upstage and three more dancers crawl out of them to simple wooden chairs.
BURLESQUE_DVS478
SOMEONE and the first two dancers pose erotically in their own chairs and snap their fingers.
BURLESQUE_DVS479
A dance begins.
BURLESQUE_DVS481
SOMEONE watches from his corner table.
BURLESQUE_DVS482
At home, SOMEONE adds notations to sheet music, then stares thoughtfully at it. SOMEONE arrives.
BURLESQUE_DVS483
As she removes her coat, he shakes his head and smiles.
BURLESQUE_DVS484
He notices her Louboutins.
BURLESQUE_DVS485
He watches from his keyboard as she walks into the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS487
her costume bears two handprints on her buttocks.
BURLESQUE_DVS488
SOMEONE works her hands up her body to her hair. Her backup dancers move upside-down on their chairs in acrobatic positions. At home, SOMEONE struts in her sparkly four-inch Louboutins as she puts on the new outfit.
BURLESQUE_DVS489
She leaves. Onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS492
At the entrance, a long line appears.
BURLESQUE_DVS493
Back inside the packed lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS494
Looking on, SOMEONE smiles proudly.
BURLESQUE_DVS495
SOMEONE lifts her knee in a sexy pose with one of her backup dancers. SOMEONE seethes as she watches.
BURLESQUE_DVS496
Mesmerized by the performance, SOMEONE interlaces his fingers.
BURLESQUE_DVS497
Now he drives SOMEONE in his vintage convertible.
BURLESQUE_DVS498
At his home, they share an intimate laugh as they sit on the couch by candlelight.
BURLESQUE_DVS499
Back in the lounge, the dancers advance downstage, reaching their hands toward the audience.
BURLESQUE_DVS500
SOMEONE turns in profile and bumps her shoulders forward into an animalistic slouch.
BURLESQUE_DVS501
Spreading their legs, the dancers bend over and whip their hair.
BURLESQUE_DVS502
At home, SOMEONE finds a note taped to a mirror written on sheet music paper: Going out. See you tomorrow - SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS503
Back onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS504
SOMEONE and the others dance with precision and raw sensuality as the stage lights strobe.
BURLESQUE_DVS505
Now a makeup mirror reflects a newspaper photo of SOMEONE performing in the burlesque lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS506
SOMEONE smiles in her office as she reads the article on the front page of the LA Times Calendar section.
BURLESQUE_DVS507
The photo shows SOMEONE with Coco and another dancer.
BURLESQUE_DVS508
SOMEONE sets down the paper and picks up a bank letter headed, Notice of Defaulted Payment. A red stamp reads, Final Notice.
BURLESQUE_DVS509
SOMEONE crumples it up.
BURLESQUE_DVS510
In the dressing room, the girls huddle around the newspaper feature.
BURLESQUE_DVS511
Coco faces SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS512
Meanwhile, two contortionists lie with their chins to the stage. Posed in deep backbends, they flick their toes over their heads. The doorman crouches between them.
BURLESQUE_DVS513
They scissor kick.
BURLESQUE_DVS514
One does a handstand and wraps her thighs around the doorman. The other sticks her leg straight up along his back.
BURLESQUE_DVS515
At Marcus' table.
BURLESQUE_DVS516
SOMEONE arrives.
BURLESQUE_DVS517
The doorman falls face-first into a contortionist's crotch.
BURLESQUE_DVS518
A patron spits out his drink with laughter.
BURLESQUE_DVS519
From the bar, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch SOMEONE with the two men.
BURLESQUE_DVS520
One of the contortionists passes the doorman a banana between her legs. He peels it, then gets distracted by her breasts, and lowers the phallic fruit to his crotch.
BURLESQUE_DVS521
The other contortionist deep-throats it.
BURLESQUE_DVS522
From a table overlooking the crowd, SOMEONE notices SOMEONE with SOMEONE and Harold.
BURLESQUE_DVS523
SOMEONE arrives at her side.
BURLESQUE_DVS524
One contortionist spreads her legs overhead and the doorman strikes a triangle between her thighs. Now in the dressing room.
BURLESQUE_DVS525
She picks up her clutch purse.
BURLESQUE_DVS526
SOMEONE gives an affectionate smile as SOMEONE walks away.
BURLESQUE_DVS527
She bites her lip worriedly.
BURLESQUE_DVS528
SOMEONE brings costumes.
BURLESQUE_DVS529
SOMEONE glances after SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS530
He kisses SOMEONE' cheek.
BURLESQUE_DVS531
She watches him go with a grateful smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS532
Now she enters the stage area, her arms loaded with costumes.
BURLESQUE_DVS533
SOMEONE calls out from the deejay booth.
BURLESQUE_DVS534
She drops the costumes, then removes her
BURLESQUE_DVS535
coat, revealing a black sparkling top with a matching cardigan and pants.
BURLESQUE_DVS536
She climbs wearily onto the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS537
SOMEONE puts on a CD labeled, Instrumental Only, Last of Me.
BURLESQUE_DVS538
He cuts the stage lights.
BURLESQUE_DVS539
SOMEONE places a chair center stage and straddles it.
BURLESQUE_DVS540
SOMEONE focuses a blue-tinted spotlight on her.
BURLESQUE_DVS541
Silhouetted by an offstage light, she strolls away stoically.
BURLESQUE_DVS542
SOMEONE gazes after her with a small admiring nod, then switches off the spotlight.
BURLESQUE_DVS543
SOMEONE steps outside with
BURLESQUE_DVS544
costumes and heads down the entrance stairs.
BURLESQUE_DVS545
SOMEONE waits for her at the bottom.
BURLESQUE_DVS546
Wearing fingerless leather gloves, she takes a drag off a cigarette.
BURLESQUE_DVS548
SOMEONE gets in a convertible and wrestles her bag down beside her.
BURLESQUE_DVS549
SOMEONE gives an incredulous stare. As SOMEONE backs out of her spot, her old mentor tosses her keys down onto her car's trunk.
BURLESQUE_DVS550
SOMEONE takes out a crowbar and smashes SOMEONE's passenger window as she drives past. The car stops abruptly.
BURLESQUE_DVS551
With an indignant gape, she peels off. SOMEONE flings the crowbar back into her trunk then turns and leans on the bumper.
BURLESQUE_DVS552
Now SOMEONE arrives home in a red clingy dress.
BURLESQUE_DVS553
Eyeing the daybed, she pauses briefly, then crosses to the French doors and opens them.
BURLESQUE_DVS554
She finds SOMEONE sleeping in the bed.
BURLESQUE_DVS555
SOMEONE rolls her eyes resentfully and pulls the doors shut.
BURLESQUE_DVS556
Now in their apartment, SOMEONE irritably grinds coffee. SOMEONE stirs awake in the red cocktail dress.
BURLESQUE_DVS557
He shuts the bedroom doors. She flings a pillow at a lamp.
BURLESQUE_DVS558
Now at a wedding.
BURLESQUE_DVS559
SOMEONE kisses Damon.
BURLESQUE_DVS560
Later at the reception, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE talk on his cell phone.
BURLESQUE_DVS561
With his eyes on SOMEONE, he lowers the phone. Now SOMEONE sits with Coco.
BURLESQUE_DVS562
As SOMEONE sips his drink, the deejay grins at him.
BURLESQUE_DVS563
At a bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS564
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE dance.
BURLESQUE_DVS565
He hugs her from behind.
BURLESQUE_DVS566
He kisses her cheek.
BURLESQUE_DVS567
Now leaning on the bar, SOMEONE sips the last of a cocktail. SOMEONE approaches and leans on the bar beside him.
BURLESQUE_DVS568
She ignores his toast.
BURLESQUE_DVS569
SOMEONE giggles, then downs her shot.
BURLESQUE_DVS570
SOMEONE nudges her with his elbow and leans in close.
BURLESQUE_DVS571
He points at the deejay, who points back. As SOMEONE leaves the bar, SOMEONE grabs her hand.
BURLESQUE_DVS572
They face each other on the dance floor.
BURLESQUE_DVS573
He grins.
BURLESQUE_DVS574
They dance.
BURLESQUE_DVS575
He spins her.
BURLESQUE_DVS577
As they enter the darkened apartment, SOMEONE knocks over a lamp.
BURLESQUE_DVS578
He bumps the lamp again.
BURLESQUE_DVS579
SOMEONE looks demurely up at him from the daybed. SOMEONE smiles genteelly.
BURLESQUE_DVS580
He hands SOMEONE her shoes.
BURLESQUE_DVS581
SOMEONE steps into the bedroom and shuts the doors.
BURLESQUE_DVS582
A disappointed SOMEONE glances after him.
BURLESQUE_DVS583
He reopens the doors, wearing bright red pajamas.
BURLESQUE_DVS584
He flourishes his arms.
BURLESQUE_DVS585
She watches him cross back to the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS586
He shuts the doors.
BURLESQUE_DVS587
He reopens the doors, shirtless.
BURLESQUE_DVS588
As he enters the kitchen, she admires his toned back on the sly.
BURLESQUE_DVS589
As he returns to the bedroom, she checks him out again.
BURLESQUE_DVS590
SOMEONE spins around in the doorway and SOMEONE shakes her head.
BURLESQUE_DVS591
SOMEONE removes her earrings, her back to the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS592
SOMEONE reemerges naked.
BURLESQUE_DVS593
A chair, then a lamp conveniently hide his groin.
BURLESQUE_DVS594
SOMEONE still has her back to him.
BURLESQUE_DVS595
SOMEONE sees his bare tush.
BURLESQUE_DVS596
She covers her eyes, but peeks.
BURLESQUE_DVS597
He innocently holds a box of Famous Amos cookies over his privates.
BURLESQUE_DVS598
He returns to the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS599
He shuts the French doors.
BURLESQUE_DVS600
As SOMEONE looks over her shoulder, the bedroom lights go out.
BURLESQUE_DVS601
She lowers her disappointed gaze and purses her lips, then gets up from the daybed.
BURLESQUE_DVS602
Reaching behind her back, she goes to unzip her dress.
BURLESQUE_DVS604
SOMEONE reopens the doors.
BURLESQUE_DVS605
With a smoldering gaze, he steps out of the bedroom and approaches SOMEONE, then gently brushes her long blonde hair off her shoulder.
BURLESQUE_DVS606
He kisses her smooth neck and they share a peck on the lips.
BURLESQUE_DVS610
Facing each other, SOMEONE runs his fingers through her hair. They kiss again.
BURLESQUE_DVS611
They gaze into each other's eyes.
BURLESQUE_DVS614
Daytime. In bed, SOMEONE rests her head on SOMEONE's chest.
BURLESQUE_DVS615
Pouring rain streaks their bedroom window.
BURLESQUE_DVS616
Onstage, SOMEONE sings in a satiny chartreuse gown.
BURLESQUE_DVS617
The image dissolves from SOMEONE onstage to the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS618
SOMEONE lies in bed with a camera as SOMEONE pulls a black stocking over her knee.
BURLESQUE_DVS619
She pulls the stocking back down her leg, then bites her bottom lip.
BURLESQUE_DVS620
SOMEONE beckons.
BURLESQUE_DVS621
Onstage, SOMEONE sings to a full house.
BURLESQUE_DVS622
They lounge in bed.
BURLESQUE_DVS623
They embrace.
BURLESQUE_DVS624
Back onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS625
Silhouetted against a brilliant spotlight, SOMEONE closes her hands and gently lowers her arms.
BURLESQUE_DVS626
Now a young woman enters the apartment.
BURLESQUE_DVS627
She sets down a suitcase and tosses aside her keys. Scanning the living room, she finds an article of clothing.
BURLESQUE_DVS628
She barges into the bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS629
She shoves past him.
BURLESQUE_DVS630
Now SOMEONE's wedding deejay opens a front door.
BURLESQUE_DVS631
In SOMEONE's bedroom.
BURLESQUE_DVS632
SOMEONE looks up from his bed and they smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS633
Wearing only a blanket, SOMEONE covers up.
BURLESQUE_DVS634
In the kitchen, SOMEONE makes coffee.
BURLESQUE_DVS635
SOMEONE sighs and lowers a spoon.
BURLESQUE_DVS636
Now at Jacks apartment. SOMEONE leaves with her luggage.
BURLESQUE_DVS637
Later at SOMEONE's second floor apartment, SOMEONE steps outside.
BURLESQUE_DVS638
SOMEONE pulls into the driveway on his motorcycle.
BURLESQUE_DVS639
SOMEONE passes the deejay on his way upstairs.
BURLESQUE_DVS640
He heads off.
BURLESQUE_DVS641
SOMEONE looks pointedly after SOMEONE walking to his car.
BURLESQUE_DVS642
SOMEONE turns.
BURLESQUE_DVS643
Now in SOMEONE' office.
BURLESQUE_DVS645
SOMEONE heads for the door.
BURLESQUE_DVS646
Now at Marcus' contemporary three-story mansion, SOMEONE walks up a staircase to the top floor and its breathtaking view of the city.
BURLESQUE_DVS647
She looks out a window and spots SOMEONE pacing outside on his phone.
BURLESQUE_DVS648
She leaves the window and regards an architectural model of a city block set up on a table.
BURLESQUE_DVS649
SOMEONE notes an address on the model:
BURLESQUE_DVS650
8080 Sunset Boulevard.
BURLESQUE_DVS651
SOMEONE joins her and hands her a coffee mug.
BURLESQUE_DVS652
She grabs her jacket.
BURLESQUE_DVS653
She walks out and leaves SOMEONE standing alone.
BURLESQUE_DVS654
Now we descend to the lit-up sign for the Burlesque Lounge.
BURLESQUE_DVS655
Inside SOMEONE crosses a dim hallway adorned with memorabilia.
BURLESQUE_DVS656
She stops and takes a second long look at a red neon sign which reads, The Best View on the Sunset Strip.
BURLESQUE_DVS657
SOMEONE hurries on.
BURLESQUE_DVS658
Onstage, dancers move in unison while the seated band performs.
BURLESQUE_DVS659
In the dressing room, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS660
She holds up a bottle of tequila.
BURLESQUE_DVS661
SOMEONE enters SOMEONE' office.
BURLESQUE_DVS662
SOMEONE lowers her gaze, then looks up and gives an amused roll of the eyes.
BURLESQUE_DVS663
Onstage, the dancers finish their number to the delight of a packed house.
BURLESQUE_DVS664
Now SOMEONE chats with SOMEONE as they exit the lounge, passing under its unlit archway.
BURLESQUE_DVS665
They head across the street to the high-rise of luxury condos. Inside, a white-haired man sits at a desk, talking on the phone.
BURLESQUE_DVS666
SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter his office.
BURLESQUE_DVS667
As he hangs up, the women sit.
BURLESQUE_DVS668
He gives SOMEONE a brochure.
BURLESQUE_DVS669
The white-haired businessman gives a confused look.
BURLESQUE_DVS671
The lights on the lounge's archway glow onto the sidewalk.
BURLESQUE_DVS672
Inside the club, SOMEONE strolls up to SOMEONE, who sits at a table looking through a stack of paperwork.
BURLESQUE_DVS673
She takes a seat across from him.
BURLESQUE_DVS674
Smiling, she drops an envelope in front of him.
BURLESQUE_DVS675
He opens it and finds a check for $500,000.
BURLESQUE_DVS676
He stares at her with wide eyes.
BURLESQUE_DVS677
She glances skyward.
BURLESQUE_DVS678
He shakes his head at the check.
BURLESQUE_DVS679
He gives her a nod and she presses her lips to his.
BURLESQUE_DVS680
Pulling away, she eyes him.
BURLESQUE_DVS681
As she leaves, SOMEONE's lips curl into a smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS682
Meanwhile, SOMEONE chats with a bartender.
BURLESQUE_DVS683
SOMEONE strolls up to the bar and leans her back against it.
BURLESQUE_DVS684
SOMEONE swivels her stool to face the same direction.
BURLESQUE_DVS685
They share a grin and SOMEONE good-naturedly smacks SOMEONE's leg.
BURLESQUE_DVS686
Entering the lounge, SOMEONE spots them.
BURLESQUE_DVS687
The women's smiles fade as they notice her.
BURLESQUE_DVS688
As she approaches SOMEONE, SOMEONE turns back to the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS689
SOMEONE hangs her head, then lifts her tearful gaze.
BURLESQUE_DVS690
She gives SOMEONE an earnest look.
BURLESQUE_DVS691
The club owner replies with a gentle smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS692
SOMEONE beams.
BURLESQUE_DVS693
With a nod, SOMEONE hurries off.
BURLESQUE_DVS694
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS695
She puts her head on SOMEONE' shoulder.
BURLESQUE_DVS696
She hops off her stool and walks away.
BURLESQUE_DVS697
SOMEONE stares after her.
BURLESQUE_DVS698
With a serene look, she turns away and sips from a glass of dessert wine.
BURLESQUE_DVS699
SOMEONE approaches and leans beside her on the bar.
BURLESQUE_DVS700
He heads away, leaving SOMEONE at the bar with a faint smile on her lips and a faraway look.
BURLESQUE_DVS701
Meanwhile, SOMEONE climbs the stairs to the dressing room.
BURLESQUE_DVS702
She sets down her bag, removes her jacket, and sits at her vanity table.
BURLESQUE_DVS703
Behind her, SOMEONE combs her hair, her eyes fixed on the blonde.
BURLESQUE_DVS704
SOMEONE lifts a brush to her eyes then spots her rival in the reflection of her mirror.
BURLESQUE_DVS705
She gives SOMEONE a cordial nod.
BURLESQUE_DVS706
With her lips pursed in a haughty expression, the diva looks away.
BURLESQUE_DVS707
The corner of SOMEONE's mouth twitches in a thoughtful smirk as she continues to watch SOMEONE in the mirror,
BURLESQUE_DVS708
then returns to her makeup.
BURLESQUE_DVS709
then lowers her gaze, her lips curling into a genial smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS710
The brunette shoots her another look,
BURLESQUE_DVS711
As she stares off dreamily, another dancer reaches for her makeup.
BURLESQUE_DVS712
SOMEONE slaps her hands away, her jaw dropping in exasperation.
BURLESQUE_DVS713
SOMEONE smiles as she watches in her mirror, then touches up her mascara.
BURLESQUE_DVS714
SOMEONE appears in a doorway.
BURLESQUE_DVS715
SOMEONE lowers her mascara brush as she sees him.
BURLESQUE_DVS716
SOMEONE moves closer.
BURLESQUE_DVS717
He gives a pleading look.
BURLESQUE_DVS718
SOMEONE avoids his gaze.
BURLESQUE_DVS719
He gently lifts her chin.
BURLESQUE_DVS720
He stares into her pale-blue eyes.
BURLESQUE_DVS721
With her head tilted, SOMEONE shifts her gaze over his face.
BURLESQUE_DVS723
he opens his mouth to speak,
BURLESQUE_DVS724
then closes it again.
BURLESQUE_DVS725
His face scrunches up as he gives a charming grin.
BURLESQUE_DVS726
Glancing away, SOMEONE bites her lip.
BURLESQUE_DVS727
He leans in and they kiss. SOMEONE presses her hands to his toned chest, then wraps her arms around his neck.
BURLESQUE_DVS728
He clutches her shoulders, returning the embrace.
BURLESQUE_DVS729
They part and SOMEONE slides her hands back down his chest as he presses his lips to her
BURLESQUE_DVS731
He moves in to kiss her again, then pulls back with a smile.
BURLESQUE_DVS732
He steps away.
BURLESQUE_DVS733
He grins widely.
BURLESQUE_DVS734
Heading for the door, he pauses.
BURLESQUE_DVS735
He walks back to her and hands her some sheet music.
BURLESQUE_DVS736
The title reads, Show Me How You Burlesque, by SOMEONE.
BURLESQUE_DVS737
Now on a dark stage, a spotlight shines down on SOMEONE, who wears a sparkling outfit and her platinum wig.
BURLESQUE_DVS738
Strobe lights flash and giant block letters spelling Burlesque light up onstage. As the other dancers grind against the letters, SOMEONE sits atop the E at the center.
BURLESQUE_DVS739
More girls dance on tables in the audience.
BURLESQUE_DVS741
The dancers on the tables swing their arms and flip their hair. The stage performers mirror them. With a smile, the doorman bobs his head. SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch proudly from the balcony. Onstage, the dancers pump their chests.
BURLESQUE_DVS742
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sing backup from atop the bar. More dancers strut out from the revolving mirrored panels behind them. Another girl tickles the doorman's lips and he smiles. An outline of red neon flashes around the letters onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS743
The dancers on the bar fall back into the arms of the bartenders, who carry them to the stage.
BURLESQUE_DVS744
All of the girls cluster together, with SOMEONE at the center.
BURLESQUE_DVS745
They each strike a pose, coolly snapping their fingers.
BURLESQUE_DVS746
Several bartenders run onstage.
BURLESQUE_DVS747
They surround SOMEONE and grind their hips.
BURLESQUE_DVS748
The women sit on some steps in front of her.
BURLESQUE_DVS749
The male and female dancers now stand staggered on the staircase, moving in unison.
BURLESQUE_DVS750
As they shake their butts at the audience, SOMEONE imitates them and SOMEONE grins.
BURLESQUE_DVS751
The dancers hop from foot to foot, their hands beckoning the audience.
BURLESQUE_DVS752
The stage lights flash and the dancers disappear, leaving only the glowing letters. Remaining opening titles: Dianna Agron,