A dusting of snow covers the floor, exposed railing, and beams.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS19
Slowly, the two men make their way toward the nose of the plane.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS20
One man slips and staggers momentarily as he steps down a small ledge.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS21
The men shine their lights on a desk-sized object covered with snow.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS22
One man kneels beside the object and scrapes away a layer of frost.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS23
Visible under the ice, a symbol consisting of a white star and a blue circle with a wide, red border.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS24
Tonsberg, Norway, March 1942. At night, a goateed man sprints across the small town square. He hurries into a castle tower lit by torches, then bars the door.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS26
They've come for it.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS27
A bearded man with gray hair shuffles to meet him. They have before, not like this. Let them come. They'll never find it.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS28
The two men peer around themselves as the tower trembles. A chandelier bounces on its chains.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS29
The men back away from the door.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS30
The front wall collapses, knocking the goateed man down.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS31
As the dust settles, the bearded man lifts a stone block off the goateed man who lies motionless.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS32
Outside, a large tank backs up as a long, black convertible car pulls to a stop.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS33
The car sports a hood ornament resembling an octopus with a human skull for a head.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS34
A Nazi officer wearing shiny black boots and a dark trench coat steps out.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS35
Inside the tower, helmeted German soldiers push on the lid of a large sarcophagus.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS37
The soldiers stop pushing and turned to face the Nazi officer as he strides into the tower.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS38
Soldiers lift the bearded man to his feet.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS39
The Nazi officer removes his hat and hands it to a nearby soldier as he steps toward the sarcophagus.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS40
Placing both hands on the thick stone lid, he pushes it open.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS42
Inside, a skeleton grips a crystalline cube measuring about six inches per side.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS43
The Nazi officer grabs the cube.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS44
He turns to the bearded man and drops the cube onto the floor, shattering it.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS46
The bearded man gazes toward bright light shining through the hole in the tower, then glances at a wall panel.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS47
The Nazi officer turns and walks toward the wooden panel which is carved with the image of a tree.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS49
A snake is curled around one of the tree's roots.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS50
The Nazi officer pushes the snake's eye.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS51
A box pops out of the panel.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS52
The Nazi officer slides it out.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS53
The bearded man's bottom lip quivers as the Nazi officer opens the box and peers inside, his face illuminated by a bright blue light.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS54
The Nazi officer closes the box's lid.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS56
The Nazi officer shoots the bearded man, then touches the side of his own face as he works his jaw.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS57
A brooch of the tentacled skull is pinned on his lapel.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS58
Elsewhere, New York City.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS59
In a recruitment office, men wearing only boxer shorts sit or stand in line.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS60
A short, scrawny young man with parted brown hair steps up to a doctor wearing a white coat.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS61
The doctor scans Rogers' long medical file.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS62
The doctor stamps the file 4F.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS63
Next, wartime film footage.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS64
SOMEONE sits in a crowded movie theater.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS65
The boisterous movie patron stands and looms over SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS66
Outside in an alley, the large man punches SOMEONE to the ground.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS67
SOMEONE stands but the thug punches him again. SOMEONE holds up a trash can lid like a shield, but the large man tosses it aside and punches SOMEONE in the face.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS68
Blood streaming from his mouth, SOMEONE stands and raises his fists.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS69
SOMEONE takes a swing, but the man easily blocks it and punches SOMEONE into some trashcans.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS71
A dark-haired man wearing an Army uniform pulls the thug away. The thug takes a swing but misses. The Army man punches the thug and kicks him down the alley.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS72
The man glances at Rogers' medical form.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS73
SOMEONE hangs his head.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS74
SOMEONE smiles and throws one arm around his friend's shoulders.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS75
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a newspaper ad. World Exposition of Tomorrow, 1943.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS76
At the World's Fair, SOMEONE waves to a pair of young women.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS77
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and their dates stroll past futuristic displays.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS78
They push through the crowd toward a stage.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS79
Female models lean against a red car as a dark-haired mustached man in a tuxedo struts onto the stage. He hands his top hat to one of the models, then kisses her on the lips. Taking a microphone, Stark dabs his mouth with a handkerchief.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS80
The models remove the car's tires.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS81
As Stark operates a control panel, devices in the car's wheel wells levitate the vehicle off the ground.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS83
The devices spark as the car crashes to the stage.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS84
Standing in the crowd, SOMEONE glances over his shoulder. An Army recruitment poster featuring Uncle SOMEONE hangs on a column.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS86
SOMEONE turns to where SOMEONE was standing but finds him gone. In a nearby recruitment booth, a man steps in front of a mirror which shows his reflected face on a body of a soldier.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS87
As a woman pulls the man away, SOMEONE steps up, only his eyes and forehead are reflected above the soldier's collar.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS88
A short distance away, a balding man with a goatee and glasses studies SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS89
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE, then shakes his head as he backs away.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS90
SOMEONE returns and the two friends hug.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS91
SOMEONE salutes then walks off after the girls.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS92
SOMEONE walks in the opposite direction and into the recruitment office.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS93
The goateed man glances down, then follows SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS94
As SOMEONE dresses in an examination room, a nurse walks in and whispers into a doctor's ear.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS95
As the doctor steps out, SOMEONE glances at a sign on the wall.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS96
It is illegal to falsify your enlistment form.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS97
SOMEONE puts on his shoes as a military police officer walks into the room.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS98
SOMEONE stares at him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS99
A moment later, the goateed man steps in behind him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS100
The MP leaves.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS101
Dr. SOMEONE shakes Rogers' hands then opens a folder.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS102
Dr. SOMEONE returns Rogers' enlistment form, now stamped 1A.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS103
SOMEONE lets out a deep sigh.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS104
Elsewhere in an isolated mountain range,
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS105
a barred window is set into the side of a jagged mountain peak dusted with snow.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS107
Inside, a man with round frame glasses works in a laboratory. The Nazi officer strides toward him. The Nazi officer places the box he removed from the tower onto a table. As the officer opens the box and releases bright blue light, Dr. SOMEONE puts on glasses with dark lenses.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS108
The Nazi officer slides a clear canister into the box, then transfers the light source into a large machine, and locks it into place.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS109
As Dr. SOMEONE operates a control panel, the machine glows with blue light.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS110
Dr. SOMEONE slowly turns a dial.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS111
The Nazi officer touches the side of his own face.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS112
A needle on a dial creeps upward.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS113
The Nazi pushes Dr. SOMEONE out of his way and cranks the dial. The machine crackles with blue energy which zips along thick wires and shimmers over another large, complex apparatus.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS114
The control panel sparks and the blue energy dissipates.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS116
On an Army base drill field, SOMEONE stand in a line with other recruits.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS117
A brown-haired officer strides up.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS118
A light-haired soldier saunters forward.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS120
SOMEONE punches Hodge's face, toppling him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS121
Hodge stands in formation with the other men as grey-haired Col. SOMEONE paces.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS122
The colonel eyes SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS123
SOMEONE falls as he climbs a cargo net.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS124
As SOMEONE crawls under barbed wire during training, Hodge kicks out a post, tangling SOMEONE in the wire.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS125
Later, SOMEONE lags behind the rest of his squad as they run.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS126
SOMEONE watches the other soldiers fight off one another as they try to climb a flagpole.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS127
Hodge climbs several feet of the pole and slides to the ground.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS128
As the other men reassemble, SOMEONE walks up to the flagpole.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS129
SOMEONE removes two pins at the base of the flagpole, tipping it over.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS130
He walks to the flag, picks it up, and then hands it to the corporal.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS131
SOMEONE climbs into the backseat of a Jeep carrying Agent SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS132
She turns and smiles at him as they pull away. Later, SOMEONE oversees the men as they perform push-ups.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS133
Nearby, Col. SOMEONE walks with Dr. SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS134
The recruits jump to their feet and perform jumping jacks.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS135
SOMEONE walks to the back of an ammo truck and picks up a grenade.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS136
He pulls the pin and rolls the grenade onto the field full of recruits.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS137
As the other men scatter, SOMEONE leaps onto the grenade as SOMEONE approaches him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS138
He hugs the grenade to his torso as he lies in a fetal position. Slowly, SOMEONE opens his eyes and sits up.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS139
SOMEONE glances toward Dr. SOMEONE who turns to the colonel.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS140
Dr. SOMEONE shrugs.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS141
As Col. SOMEONE walks off, Dr. SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS142
Later, SOMEONE sits in an empty bunkhouse and reads.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS143
Dr. SOMEONE walks in carrying a liquor bottle.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS144
The doctor turns the bottle in his hand.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS145
Nazi officer's face appears.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS146
In a flashback, SOMEONE interrogates SOMEONE at gunpoint.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS147
SOMEONE injects himself with a hypodermic needle.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS148
Surrounded by flames, SOMEONE's face distorts as he screams.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS150
Dr. SOMEONE smiles, then motions for SOMEONE to pick up a glass.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS151
He fills it from his bottle.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS152
SOMEONE clinks his glass against Erskine's, then lifts it to his lips.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS153
Dr. SOMEONE drinks both glasses worth. SOMEONE smiles.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS154
In the Hydra mountain fortress, Dr. SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE,
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS155
who stands silhouetted in front of large windows. SOMEONE flips a switch on a panel.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS156
Nearby, an artist stands beside a palette covered in red paints.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS157
Dr. SOMEONE walks to a table and examines surveillance photos of Dr. SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS158
Dr. SOMEONE turns and walks away.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS159
SOMEONE stops and turns to face SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS160
SOMEONE turns on bright lights behind the artist.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS161
SOMEONE gazes at the man's canvass.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS162
The artist gulps. Dr. SOMEONE strides out of the room.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS163
Boys playing stickball on the street move aside as SOMEONE and Agent SOMEONE pass in a car.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS164
SOMEONE smiles as she looks out her window. Their car pulls up to a curb.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS165
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step out.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS166
Standing a short distance down the street, two men in suites watch SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter a shop,
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS167
Brooklyn Antiques.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS168
Inside, a white-haired woman steps forward to greet them.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS169
The white-haired woman steps behind a counter and presses a button located beside a submachine gun.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS170
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk into a backroom and face a bookcase which swings open,
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS171
revealing a tiled hallway.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS172
An MP eyes them as they walk down the hallway into a large operating theater filled with machines and electronic devices.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS173
People in white lab coats turn and stare at SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS174
He glances at SOMEONE who turns and leads him to Dr. SOMEONE who stands beside a padded table in the center of the room.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS175
A photographer snaps their picture.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS176
As the photographer walks away, SOMEONE stares at the operating table.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS177
SOMEONE nods.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS178
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, then begins to undress.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS179
As the bare-chested SOMEONE lies on the table, the senator, the colonel, and other men gaze down at him from an observation booth.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS180
SOMEONE glances back at SOMEONE as she heads upstairs to the observation booth. SOMEONE meets her gaze.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS181
Gazing up at the observation booth, Dr. SOMEONE taps a microphone.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS182
Technicians lower clamps onto Rogers' chest.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS183
Nurses load vials into panels flanking the operating table. One nurse gives SOMEONE an injection in his left arm.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS184
He winces.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS185
Dr. SOMEONE shrugs.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS187
A technician flips a lever.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS188
The vials empty as injectors pump serum into Rogers' body. He grimaces, then snaps his eyes open.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS189
Standing nearby, SOMEONE Stark pulls a switch.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS190
The operating table tips upright as panels close around SOMEONE,
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS191
cocooning him inside a metal pod.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS192
A technician plugs a hose into the pod and locks him into place.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS193
Dr. SOMEONE raps his knuckles on a small window in the front of the pod.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS195
Pacing in front of a long control panel, Stark turns a dial.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS196
Putting on a pair of glasses with dark lenses, he grabs a metal wheel and turns it with both hands.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS197
A needle rises on a Vita-Ray gauge.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS199
Dr. SOMEONE shields his eyes as bright light shines out of the pod's window, filling the room.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS200
Stark glances at SOMEONE and resumes turning the wheel.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS201
The bright light streaming out of the pod flickers. Control panels around the operating room spark and smoke. Shielding his eyes with one hand, Dr. SOMEONE gazes at the pod as it dims, then goes dark.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS202
People crowd against the windows of the observation booth. Stark lowers his protective glasses.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS203
The pod slides open and reveals SOMEONE, now several inches taller and extremely muscular.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS204
Dr. SOMEONE steps up and helps his groggy subject out of the apparatus.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS208
Standing at the back of the room, SOMEONE watches Senator Brandt shake Dr. SOMEONE's hand.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS209
SOMEONE glances toward SOMEONE as he takes out a Zippo lighter and opens it.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS210
An explosion blows out the observation booth's windows, raining down glass.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS211
SOMEONE grabs the last vial of serum and shoots Dr. SOMEONE in the chest. As SOMEONE flees the room, he shoots an MP. Agent SOMEONE takes out a pistol and shoots SOMEONE on the shoulder, but he escapes into the hallway and shoots another guard. SOMEONE runs after him as SOMEONE huddles over Dr. SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS216
The woman's gun fires skyward as she falls.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS217
SOMEONE grabs the machine gun and runs out of the shop and into the street.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS218
SOMEONE dashes past a man who provides covering fire, then jumps into a waiting car. Pursuing agents shoot the gunman as SOMEONE's car speeds away. SOMEONE cuts down the agents with machine gun fire as he passes, then grabs his wounded shoulder. SOMEONE runs into the street and aims her pistol as SOMEONE flicks his lighter causing a car parked behind her to explode.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS221
The bullet hits the getaway car's driver in the head causing him to crash. SOMEONE leaps out, steals a cab, and speeds back toward SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS222
Still standing in the middle of the street, the stern-faced SOMEONE fires her pistol into the windshield of the oncoming cab. SOMEONE leaps and tackles SOMEONE out of the street as the cab rushes past.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS223
SOMEONE stands and runs after the cab. SOMEONE checks his rear-view mirror as he negotiates the bullet-ridden taxi down crowded city streets.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS224
SOMEONE races up a parallel street, then tries to turn on to a main road, but instead crashes through a shop's front window.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS225
SOMEONE leaps out unharmed.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS226
SOMEONE runs up an alley, then leaps over a chain-link fence in a single bound. Cars swerve as he emerges in a street.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS228
SOMEONE checks his rear-view mirror again as SOMEONE gains on him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS229
Jerking the steering wheel, SOMEONE weaves through traffic.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS230
SOMEONE leaps onto the roof of an oncoming car, then jumps from vehicle to vehicle.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS231
He hurtles himself off the truck and lands face down on the roof of the taxicab.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS232
SOMEONE hangs on to the top of the cab as SOMEONE swerves several times, then turns sharply down an alley.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS233
SOMEONE skids onto a road running parallel to the waterfront, then fires his pistol straight up through the cab's roof.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS234
Rolling from side to side, SOMEONE avoids the bullets but slips off the roof and clings to the cab's passenger side door. Taking his eyes off the road, SOMEONE fires at SOMEONE once, then slams into a passing truck. The taxi flips and rolls over several times, losing a door and spilling SOMEONE onto the roadway. SOMEONE staggers out of the crashed cab and waves his pistol at people standing by a bus. SOMEONE picks up the cab door and uses it as a shield. SOMEONE fires at him, then nabs a young boy from a woman's side.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS235
A man restrains the frantic woman.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS236
Carrying the boy, SOMEONE runs down an alley, then fires back at SOMEONE as he ducks behind a metal tank.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS237
As SOMEONE steps around the building's corner, SOMEONE aims his pistol at the boy's head.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS238
SOMEONE aims at SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS239
SOMEONE tosses the boy into the river and flees. SOMEONE peers down into the water.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS240
Further down river, SOMEONE takes out his lighter and flips it open. A small submarine rises out of the water. SOMEONE hops in to the single person sub and closes its canopy as the craft descends.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS241
SOMEONE dives into the river and swims after the escaping submarine.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS242
SOMEONE pilots the craft into deeper water, but SOMEONE catches up and punches through its glass canopy.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS243
As water rushes in, SOMEONE rips off the canopy, yanks out SOMEONE, and tosses him onto the shore.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS244
SOMEONE pulls out a knife and swings it at SOMEONE who kicks him on the face. The violet serum smashes on the pavement.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS245
SOMEONE sucks out a fake tooth and bites down.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS246
White foam bubble out of SOMEONE's mouth as he shudders, then falls still.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS247
SOMEONE stares down at the dead Hydra agent, then studies his own chest and arms.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS248
Later, inside the Hydra compound, SOMEONE walks with three Nazi officers.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS249
SOMEONE stops and slowly turns to face the other men.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS250
SOMEONE escorts the men into Dr. SOMEONE's lab.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS251
One officer examines a war map.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS252
SOMEONE operates a mechanical cannon.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS254
The futuristic weapon vaporizes two of the officers with beams of blue light, then swivels toward the last officer as he scrambles to open a locked door.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS256
The officer disintegrates in a flash of blue light.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS257
As nearby guards raise both of their fists in salute, SOMEONE faces Dr. SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS258
Smirking, SOMEONE strides out of the room.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS259
Dr. SOMEONE sags against a wall.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS260
Meanwhile, a nurse draws blood from Rogers' arm.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS261
Nearby, SOMEONE Stark examines the captured Hydra submarine.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS262
As Col. SOMEONE walks out, Senator Brandt steps up to SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS263
A newspaper headline, Mystery Man Saves Child.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS264
Later, SOMEONE stands backstage at a small theater.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS265
Wearing a red, white, and blue costume and mask, SOMEONE picks up a shield decorated like the American Flag and runs onstage.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS266
Smiling chorus girls march in place behind SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS267
SOMEONE poses for photographs with a baby and then the senator. Later, he makes a film with American troops.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS268
The chorus of marching women in short skirts joins SOMEONE on another stage.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS269
The women salute as they march. Sitting in the audience, the senator gazes behind himself at the applauding crowd and nods to his assistant.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS270
SOMEONE turns and pretends to punch out a Hitler impersonator sneaking up behind him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS271
Children in the audience applaud as he repeats the same act for audiences in Buffalo, Milwaukee, Philadelphia, and Chicago. Senator Brandt smiles and nods. Later, children buy comics featuring Captain America from a newsstand.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS272
A GI reads a Captain America comic on his bunk.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS273
In the finished movie, SOMEONE blocks bullets with his arrowhead-shaped shield, then fires a machine gun as he leads a squad of soldiers into battle. Sitting in an audience, SOMEONE grins as people around him cheer. Later, he signs an autograph for a boy backstage, then pauses as a blonde woman steps up to him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS274
On a stage in New York City, SOMEONE holds a motorcycle holding three singing women over his head as a long chorus line performs high kicks in front of him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS275
Elsewhere, SOMEONE stands on a stage in front of a crowd of US servicemen. Italy, November 1943, five miles from the front.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS276
SOMEONE glances away as one serviceman moons him. Others throw rotten fruit which he blocks with his shield. SOMEONE turns and walks off the stage as the showgirls return.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS277
With his head down, SOMEONE walks off the back of the stage.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS278
Later, SOMEONE sits alone on the stage and sketches himself as Captain America.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS279
Agent SOMEONE walks up to him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS280
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder at SOMEONE, then stares at the falling rain.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS281
They both turn as a military ambulance pulls to a stop beside a medical tent.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS282
SOMEONE runs after SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS283
SOMEONE gazes at Agent SOMEONE, then stands and leafs through a stack of documents.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS284
SOMEONE' eyes fall.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS285
As Col. SOMEONE walks off, SOMEONE eyes a war map tacked to the back of the tent.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS286
Agent SOMEONE watches SOMEONE stride out then stares at the map.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS287
Back in his own tent, SOMEONE wears his costume as he packs a bag.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS288
Putting on a brown leather jacket, SOMEONE carries his bag and shield to a parked jeep.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS289
He climbs behind the wheel and starts the engine.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS290
Backstage, showgirls grab helmets.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS291
Wearing a helmet with the letter A on it, SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE in a plane.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS293
SOMEONE taps his shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS294
SOMEONE Starks smirks as he pilots the plane. SOMEONE glances at him, then at SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS295
She hands SOMEONE a small device.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS297
As anti-aircraft shells burst in the sky, SOMEONE grabs his shield and moves toward the plane door.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS298
Grinning, SOMEONE lowers his goggles over his eyes and jumps out of the plane. Wide-eyed, SOMEONE stares down as explosions light the night sky, revealing an open parachute. The airplane banks sharply and soars out of the area.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS300
Elsewhere, SOMEONE and SOMEONE tour a bustling Hydra factory.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS301
A man holding a clipboard steps up to SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS302
On the factory floor, workers assemble mechanical parts with glowing blue components.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS303
Meanwhile, Hydra guards lead prisoners into a cell. One guard knocks off a mustached man's bowler hat with a nightstick.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS304
The burly prisoner turns to the guard as he puts his hat back on.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS305
The guard closes the cell door and leaves.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS306
Meanwhile, SOMEONE jogs through a foggy forest to the edge of a clearing where searchlights sweep the perimeter of a tall barbed wire fence.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS307
SOMEONE ducks as a convoy of vehicles passes nearby.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS308
He runs and leaps into the back of the last transport truck where inside, two masked
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS309
Hydra soldiers turn to face him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS310
The canvas tarp covering the back of the truck bulges repeatedly. The bodies of the two soldiers flop out onto the road as the truck follows the rest of the convoy into the fenced compound.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS311
The truck backs up to a loading dock where an armed soldier lifts the tarp and peers inside to face the Captain America shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS312
The shield bashes the guard in the faces, knocking him backward. SOMEONE hops on to the dock, then runs and hides amid several parked vehicles marked with the Hydra symbol.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS313
He dashes across the yard and scurries up one of the armored vehicles, then climbs onto the roof of a low building.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS314
He runs along the roof toward another massive building beyond sweeping searchlights.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS315
Later, inside the facility, SOMEONE' silhouette fills a small window on a door.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS316
A nearby guard opens the door and peeks out.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS317
SOMEONE knocks the guard unconscious and drags out his body, then closes the door behind himself as he enters.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS318
Hiding amid large mechanical parts, SOMEONE draws a pistol as he creeps around the factory's main floor.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS319
He examines a chest-high cylindrical object studded with glowing blue components, then grabs a small device about the size of a cigarette lighter and slips it into his pants pocket.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS320
In the darkened prisoners ward, a guard paces along a catwalk above circular jail cells.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS321
Men seating in one cell glance upward as a guard's limp body falls onto the barred opening above them.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS322
The prisoners stand as SOMEONE frisks the guard's body and takes his keys.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS323
SOMEONE unlocks the cell doors and releases prisoners including an Asian man.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS324
Dugan, the mustached man with the bowler, glances at his companions as SOMEONE runs off. Later, the escaping men rush into the yard, clobbering guards and stealing their weapons. One Hydra soldier shoots several prisoners before being tackled to the ground.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS325
Flashes of blue light streak across the yard as Dugan climbs atop one of the armored vehicles.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS326
SOMEONE, the Asian-American GI, snaps a guard's neck as Dernier, a balding man with a dark mustache, picks up a Hydra blaster rifle.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS327
Dernier fire the blaster, exploding a huge hole in a building wall.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS328
SOMEONE watches the breakout on a monitor,
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS329
then presses a button on a control panel.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS331
Out in the yard, SOMEONE, an African-American GI, drops beside Dugan inside the armored vehicle.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS332
Dugan drives forward as a gunner fires a blaster mounted on the top of the armored vehicle.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS333
Inside the facility, escaped prisoners fire on a group of guards as explosions rip through the compound.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS334
SOMEONE views the chaos on the monitor. He rotates a security camera and watches SOMEONE as he fights his way past several Hydra soldiers.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS335
SOMEONE flips several switches, activating timers which count down from seven minutes.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS336
SOMEONE gestures toward the monitor. Dr. SOMEONE gapes as he watches SOMEONE bash a guard with his shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS338
SOMEONE runs out of the control room and onto a catwalk. On another catwalk above the factory floor, SOMEONE kicks a guard on the chest, knocking him over a railing.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS341
SOMEONE scans his surroundings, then pulls out his pistol as he continues on. Outside, escaped prisoners shoot down several Hydra soldiers.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS342
SOMEONE grabs a grenade from an open crate and hurls it into enemy ranks, exploding several Hydra soldiers. In the control room, SOMEONE picks up a clear canister containing the glowing blue energy source as the timers continue to countdown. In an office, Dr. SOMEONE stuffs documents into a case.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS343
He runs into the hallway where SOMEONE stands at its far end. SOMEONE turns and flees in the opposite direction.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS344
SOMEONE chases after him, then slows and turns into another room.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS345
SOMEONE rushes up to SOMEONE who lies on a padded table.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS347
SOMEONE rips off leather restraints.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS348
SOMEONE helps the shorter SOMEONE to his feet.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS349
SOMEONE glances over one shoulder, then gazes at a wall map of Europe with several small flags pinned to it.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS350
SOMEONE leans on SOMEONE as he limps out of the room.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS351
Outside, several prisoners follow alongside the stolen armored vehicle as it blasts through the front gate.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS352
The armored vehicle rolls through the flaming gate, escaped prisoners run out behind it. In the control room, one of the timers reaches zero.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS353
Massive explosions tear through the factory, destroying the half-built equipment.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS354
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run onto a catwalk above the fiery factory floor.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS355
They retreat from the flames, dashing upstairs, and running onto an upper catwalk.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS358
A short distance away, SOMEONE and Dr. SOMEONE emerge from a doorway.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS359
SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach one another.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS360
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE in the face.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS361
Rubbing his jaw, SOMEONE straightens.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS362
SOMEONE punches back, denting SOMEONE' shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS363
SOMEONE loses his pistol as a second punch knocks him down.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS364
He kicks SOMEONE in the chest, throwing him several feet backward. Dr. SOMEONE pulls a lever and the catwalk slides apart, leaving SOMEONE and SOMEONE on opposite sides.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS365
SOMEONE reaches one hand under his own chin. SOMEONE stares open-mouthed as SOMEONE peels off his face, actually a mask, and reveals his true face, a ghoulish red skull.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS366
SOMEONE tosses the mask into the flames below.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS368
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step into an elevator and escape. As the flames rise higher, SOMEONE gazes around the factory. A light flashes above an exit door at the end of the uppermost catwalk.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS369
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run up the staircase.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS370
SOMEONE nods.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS371
The elevator opens revealing a single-person aircraft.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS372
Handing SOMEONE a set of keys, SOMEONE walks toward the aircraft as the elevator closes.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS373
Meanwhile, SOMEONE and SOMEONE reach the upper catwalk. The exit is on the other side of a chasm spanned by a thin metal beam. On the ground floor, Dr. SOMEONE hops into SOMEONE's black convertible town car.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS374
On the roof, a bridge slides away from the aircraft which is shaped like an upright torpedo.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS375
Rockets spin three large fins like a fan, propelling the craft into the sky.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS376
Dr. SOMEONE speeds out of the facility in the car as more explosions tear through the compound.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS377
SOMEONE steps onto the beam and inches his way across.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS378
Explosions bellow up from the floor below.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS379
The beam shakes and its far end detaches from the wall.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS380
SOMEONE runs and leaps, grabbing on to the far railing just before the beam falls. He pulls himself up onto the catwalk and looks back at SOMEONE on the opposite side.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS381
SOMEONE bends back the broken railing on his side, creating a gap.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS382
He takes several steps backward, sighs, then races forward and leaps off the catwalk.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS383
Flames bloom upward and engulf SOMEONE as he sails across the chasm.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS384
Back at the base, Col. SOMEONE reads dictation to a typist.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS385
Agent SOMEONE walks into Phillips' tent.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS386
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE out of the tent as they joined soldiers rushing to a gate at the end of the dirt road.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS387
SOMEONE and SOMEONE march toward them at the head of the group of freed prisoners, now outfitted with stolen Hydra weapons and several armored vehicles.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS388
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE as they walk past lines of cheering soldiers.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS389
Col. SOMEONE stalks through the crowd and approaches SOMEONE who salutes him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS390
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS391
She steps up to SOMEONE as the colonel walks off.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS392
SOMEONE takes the broken transceiver out of his pocket.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS393
SOMEONE offers a slight smile.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS394
Still smiling, SOMEONE locks her eyes on SOMEONE as he gazes at the faces of the cheering soldiers all around him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS395
Later at a press conference, Senator Brandt stands at a podium.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS396
Brandt gestures toward an empty doorway.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS397
A senator's aide steps out and whispers into the senator's ear.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS398
Big SOMEONE looms over a city street as barrage balloons float overhead. A Daily Mail billboard reads, Captain America To Receive Medal For Valor.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS399
In a bunker filled with military personnel, SOMEONE marks a map.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS400
An officer takes the map.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS401
SOMEONE and SOMEONE join Col. SOMEONE at another map marked with tiny flags.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS402
Later, SOMEONE drinks with the rescued men.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS403
Dernier addresses SOMEONE, then converses with SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS404
SOMEONE shakes Dernier's hand and turns to the others.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS405
Dugan raises his glass of beer.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS406
Dugan chugs a beer and slams down his empty mug.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS407
Grinning, SOMEONE takes the men's empty mugs to the bar.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS408
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE who sits alone at the bar.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS409
SOMEONE sips liquor from a tumbler.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS410
A Captain America poster hangs nearby.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS411
At the table, Dugan and the other men sing.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS412
They stop and stare as SOMEONE, wearing a long, dark dress, enters the bar.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS413
SOMEONE glances over at the drinking men.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS414
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS415
She walks off.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS416
In a lab, Stark examines a glowing blue pellet.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS417
An engineer smiles as he takes notes.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS418
Shielded behind a blast screen, Stark uses mechanical claws to touch a wire to the glowing pellet. An explosion inside the chamber blows out the glass and sends Stark and the engineer flying backward across the room.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS419
At headquarters, SOMEONE approaches a blonde woman reading a newspaper.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS420
SOMEONE nods and stands with his hands behind his back. The woman looks up from her paper and smiles at him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS421
As SOMEONE leans against the table, the woman holds up her newspaper, 400 Prisoners Liberated.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS422
The secretary flexes the foot of her crossed-leg as she eyes SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS423
The woman sashays to SOMEONE who folds his arms and glances away.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS424
She grabs his tie and pulls him behind a bookcase.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS425
She pulls him closer and kisses him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS426
SOMEONE walks up behind them. SOMEONE stares with her hands on her hips as the woman reaches her arms around SOMEONE' neck.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS427
SOMEONE runs after SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS428
SOMEONE stops and stares at SOMEONE, and rolls her eyes, and continues on.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS430
Later, SOMEONE meets with Stark.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS431
Stark points to several modified shields.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS432
A round shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS433
SOMEONE slips the concave shield onto his left arm.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS435
Smiling, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE. She picks up a handgun and fires at the shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS436
She lowers the gun and smiles.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS437
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE icily as she walks out. Stark walks over. SOMEONE pulls a piece of paper from his pocket and hands it to him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS438
Later, wearing a new Captain America uniform and mask, SOMEONE picks up the round shield painted with a white star inside a blue circle surrounded by red and white bands. SOMEONE hold the shield in front of himself as he and his squad members barge into a factory, firing their weapons.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS439
SOMEONE smacks several Hydra soldiers with the shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS440
As his fellow soldiers run outside, SOMEONE flies out of the exploding building on a motorcycle. Approaching in his long, black convertible, SOMEONE stops and grimaces as he watches the Hydra factory burn. In the strategy room, an assistant uses a long stick to remove a flag from the war map and pass it to SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS441
In a snowy forest, SOMEONE walks ahead of his men.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS443
He glances back and motions for them to follow. SOMEONE moves ahead into a small clearing, then turns and hurls the shield into a treetop. The shield strikes a hidden Hydra soldier. As the man falls out of the tree, the shield boomerangs back into SOMEONE' hand.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS444
Later, SOMEONE and his team run through the forest while bombs explode around them.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS446
SOMEONE signals as a Hydra tank approaches on a forest road. Dernier runs onto the road, rolls underneath the armored vehicle, and places a detonator on its frame.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS447
Dernier stands and plugs his ears as the tank rolls on.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS448
Dugan smiles.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS449
In a small movie theater, SOMEONE sits and watches a film of SOMEONE and his men riding in the back of a truck. Studying a map, SOMEONE holds a compass with a picture of her inside the lid. Sitting in the seat beside SOMEONE, Col. SOMEONE glances at her and smiles.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS450
Outside another destroyed factory, a Hydra guard aims a gun at SOMEONE but SOMEONE shoots the guard first.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS451
SOMEONE looks up at SOMEONE and salutes him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS452
In the strategy room, SOMEONE removes another flag from a wall map. Outside a Hydra facility, SOMEONE leaps on to the top of a large armored tank and slices the hatch open with his shield. SOMEONE pulls out the masked driver and hurls him through the air.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS453
A squad member tosses SOMEONE a bomb which he throws into the tank. SOMEONE jumps off as it explodes. Later, outside the ruins of a Hydra factory, SOMEONE scowls at Dr. SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS454
Hydra guards bring over a dark-haired factory manager.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS455
SOMEONE points a blaster gun at the man.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS456
SOMEONE fires.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS457
Elsewhere, atop a snow-covered mountain, a mustached Falsworth peers through binoculars. While SOMEONE and SOMEONE work a radio, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand under a cable stretching down to distant train tracks.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS458
SOMEONE puts on his helmet. With the binoculars, Falsworth watches a train speed across a distant trestle.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS459
SOMEONE grabs a handle attached to the cable.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS460
SOMEONE slides down the cable toward the tracks.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS461
SOMEONE and SOMEONE grab handles and slide down the cable. They glide over the train as it speeds beneath them along the snow-covered track.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS462
One by one, they let go of the handles and land on top of the train.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS463
SOMEONE and SOMEONE follow SOMEONE over several train cars to a ladder.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS464
SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb down the ladder and enter a compartment while SOMEONE stands guard atop the train.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS465
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE as he moves through the empty compartment.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS466
SOMEONE glances back at SOMEONE, then moves across a hallway into a connecting compartment.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS467
As SOMEONE approaches the hallway, doors slide shut.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS468
A Hydra trooper wearing an armored suit and helmet enters SOMEONE' compartment and opens fire with a blaster. SOMEONE watches the action on a monitor.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS474
SOMEONE watches the monitor as SOMEONE and SOMEONE fight the Hydra soldiers.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS475
In his compartment, SOMEONE leans out from behind the crates and returns fire with a pistol.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS481
SOMEONE picks up a shield as the trooper fires. SOMEONE drops the shield as he flies backward out of the train. SOMEONE grabs the shield and hurls it into the trooper.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS482
SOMEONE leans out of the train, clinging to the side. SOMEONE dangles over a deep canyon.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS483
SOMEONE climbs outside the train and reaches for SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS486
The metal bar SOMEONE clings to breaks and he plummets into the canyon.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS487
SOMEONE stares downward and closes his eyes.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS488
As the train enters a tunnel, SOMEONE crashes through the engine room ceiling and points his machine gun at Dr. SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS489
Inside the Allied headquarters, a guard ushers SOMEONE into an interrogation room and hands him his eyeglasses.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS490
As the guard leaves, SOMEONE puts on his glasses.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS491
Dr. SOMEONE glances around as he walks across the room.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS492
In one corner stands an examination table on wheels. Dried blood stains the floor beneath the table.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS493
Dr. SOMEONE flinches as Col. SOMEONE enters the room carrying a food tray.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS494
As he places the tray on a table, SOMEONE sits.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS495
SOMEONE sits across from SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS496
SOMEONE picks up utensils and cuts the steak.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS497
SOMEONE takes a bite of the steak.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS498
SOMEONE pushes a document to SOMEONE who reads it.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS499
At a Hydra airfield, SOMEONE approaches a stool bearing  a bottle of white wine and a glass.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS500
Standing beneath the wing of a huge airplane, he addresses a small group of masked pilots.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS501
Behind him, thousands more stand in formation.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS502
SOMEONE lifts a glass of wine.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS503
SOMEONE drinks, then raises his glass toward the pilots as they pump both of their fists in the air.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS504
Elsewhere at night, SOMEONE steps over rubble and SOMEONE as she walks through a bombed out pub.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS505
SOMEONE steps through a doorway and finds SOMEONE drinking whiskey at a table near the bar.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS506
He glances at her, then pours another shot.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS507
SOMEONE sits across from SOMEONE who stares downward.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS508
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, Stark, SOMEONE, and others sit around a table at Allied headquarters.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS509
SOMEONE throws photographs of mountains in front of SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS510
Everyone turns to SOMEONE who gazes ahead with a furrowed brow.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS511
In a forest, SOMEONE kick-starts an armored motorcycle and speeds along a dirt road.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS512
Several Hydra troopers on motorcycles drive onto the road behind him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS513
The troopers shoot blasters at SOMEONE as they speed closer. SOMEONE fires hooks attached to a cable into trees on either side of the road.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS514
The troopers in front duck, but two troopers in the back strike the cable and fly off their bikes. SOMEONE pushes a button and flames shoot out of his tailpipe, setting a pursuing trooper on fire. Another trooper crashes into the burning wreck and sails off his bike. A pair of additional troopers merge onto the road in front of SOMEONE. He speeds up and pulls the pin out of one of their as he passes.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS515
Both motorcycles explode. Approaching the Hydra base, SOMEONE mounts his shield on the front of his motorcycle. A cannon blaster fires bolts of energy which strike the ground and trees around him. An armored vehicle rolls out of the base's fortified entrance.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS516
SOMEONE pushes a button, firing missiles which destroy the tank.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS517
He speeds up a sloped rampart and lands inside the base.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS518
Troopers fire at him with blasters.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS519
Grabbing his shield, SOMEONE leaps off the moving motorcycle and tackles a trooper.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS520
He hurls his shield at another as his motorcycle coasts into a wall and explodes.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS522
SOMEONE fights off troopers as they charge toward him. He kicks one on the chest and slams another with his shield. As more Hydra soldiers converge on him, SOMEONE throws his shield which bounces off an armored vehicle and knocks a trooper in the head.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS523
SOMEONE tosses another soldier into the air, then catches his shield as it boomerangs back to him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS524
A pair of heavy troopers with arm-mounted flamethrowers arrive and enclosed SOMEONE in walls of fire. As the flames die, dozens of Hydra soldiers surround SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS525
Later, troopers lead SOMEONE, now handcuffed, into a large room inside the base.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS526
SOMEONE steps up to him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS527
SOMEONE smiles and shakes his head.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS528
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE, backhands him, and jabs him in the chest.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS529
SOMEONE falls to his knees. His chest heaves as he gazes up at SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS531
SOMEONE pulls out a blue energy pistol. Outside, grappling hooks and cables shoot into the mountainside above the barred window.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS532
SOMEONE pulls a trooper in front of himself as SOMEONE fires, incinerating the trooper. Sliding in on the cables, Falsworth, Dugan, and SOMEONE burst through window and fire weapons while SOMEONE flees down a long corridor. Falsworth tosses SOMEONE his shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS535
SOMEONE runs down the corridor as dozens of armed Hydra troops run after him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS536
In another corridor, metal doors blow apart in a burst of flames. SOMEONE and Dernier enter.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS538
In the forest, SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE and his men rush toward the base. Inside, Allied soldiers and Hydra troopers exchange fire. More US soldiers emerge from the forest.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS540
SOMEONE carries a machine gun as she runs alongside the advancing soldiers. Hydra guards and troopers fire blaster weapons, incinerating some soldiers as they approach the base.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS542
A bullet takes out a Hydra trooper kneeling beside an armored vehicle. Other troopers fall back toward the base as they fire at approaching soldier. Phillips' men explode armored vehicles, killing nearby troopers and clearing a path into the base.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS544
Flames engulf the entrance to a corridor.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS545
As Allied soldiers pour in, SOMEONE picks up a blaster and incinerates several of them before running off.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS546
A Hydra trooper charges toward the entering soldiers with his blaster raised.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS548
SOMEONE shoots the trooper.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS549
Meanwhile, SOMEONE chases SOMEONE while deflecting blasts with his shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS550
SOMEONE dashes between two closing doors. SOMEONE throws a shield which wedges between the doors. A Hydra trooper appears and shoots flamethrowers at SOMEONE who ducks into a doorway to avoid the streams of fire. SOMEONE approaches from a connecting corridor and shoots her machine gun.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS553
The trooper's armored suit explodes as he falls dead.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS554
SOMEONE runs up to SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS555
He steps closer to her.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS556
SOMEONE runs to his shield and pulls it free, then dashes through the doors as they close.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS557
In a huge hangar, SOMEONE climbs up a ladder into a bomber plane. Allied soldiers shoot three Hydra troopers trying to climb up behind him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS558
In the cockpit, SOMEONE inserts the canister containing the blue energy source into a large mechanism, then climbs into the pilot's seat.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS559
He turns on the cockpit control panel. On a display screen, an image of North America appears with a blinking bull's-eye over New York City.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS560
Propellers lining the back of the boomerang-shaped bomber spin to life as the plane fires twin thrusters and rolls down the hangar's runway. SOMEONE runs into the hangar and glances around at the battling Hydra troopers and Allied soldiers. He sprints through the fray, knocking troopers down with his shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS561
SOMEONE leaps and grabs a cable, then swing over the heads of the battling soldiers.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS562
He lands on the runway and chases after the plane.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS563
The plane pulls ahead.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS564
As SOMEONE stops, SOMEONE and SOMEONE pull up in SOMEONE's convertible.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS565
SOMEONE hops into the passenger seat and SOMEONE drives off after the plane. In the cockpit, SOMEONE watches the car approach on a monitor. As he slides a lever forward, the plane accelerates toward the hangar exit.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS566
Driving the car, SOMEONE glances down and pushes a button on the dashboard.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS567
Flames shoot out of the back of the car as it shoots forward.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS568
As the car pulls closer to the plane, SOMEONE stands and glances at SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS569
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE, pulls him close, and kisses him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS570
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS571
SOMEONE puts the shield on his back and climbs onto the hood of the car as SOMEONE maneuvers underneath the plane.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS572
Propeller blades strike SOMEONE' shield.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS573
SOMEONE drives past the propellers. SOMEONE stands, then leaps onto the plane's back wheel mount as the bomber takes off.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS575
SOMEONE turns the steering wheel and stomps on the brake pedal. The car skids sideways out of the hangar, slides backward, and stops at the edge of a cliff.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS576
SOMEONE stands and gazes up at SOMEONE clinging to the rising bomber.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS577
SOMEONE climbs up into the hold as the wheels retract. He hops onto a railed catwalk between two bombs with small cockpits and propellers labelled Chicago and New York.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS578
Several Hydra troopers enter the hold and run along the catwalk.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS579
SOMEONE jumps down and kicks the last trooper over the railing as he passes.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS583
The trooper falls. SOMEONE fights off two more troopers, hurling one of them through the open bay.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS584
A trooper climbs into one of the flying bombs as bay doors beneath it open.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS585
SOMEONE leaps on to the bomb and raises his shield, but a trooper dives onto SOMEONE from behind, knocking his shield to the floor.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS586
The bomb drops out of the plane with SOMEONE and the other trooper clinging to its canopy.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS587
The flying bomb's wings unfold and a rear propeller spins.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS588
The pilot tilts the flying bomb left and right, then dives straight down.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS589
SOMEONE and the trooper slide around atop the canopy.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS590
Pulling back on the joystick, the pilot flies straight up.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS591
The trooper falls into the bomb's rear propeller.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS593
The pilot levels out and glances around. SOMEONE forces open the cockpit hatch and pulls the eject handle.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS594
SOMEONE hops into the now empty cockpit and closes the canopy. He steers the flying bomb clockwise around SOMEONE's plane.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS595
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE on a radar screen and fires bolts of blue energy from the plane's rotary cannon.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS596
SOMEONE dodges the blasts, then flies in behind the bomber.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS597
He speeds toward the open bay door and crashes into the plane's hold.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS598
SOMEONE opens the hatch and climbs out. He picks up his shield and slides it onto his left forearm.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS599
SOMEONE slowly opens a door and peers into the plane's spacious cockpit where a high-backed chair sits in front of a bank of windows.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS600
Passing the mechanism containing the glowing blue energy source, he creeps toward the back of the chair.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS601
SOMEONE steps out from behind him and fires a blaster.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS603
SOMEONE blocks the shot.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS604
Using his shield as cover, SOMEONE runs up and punches SOMEONE in the stomach causing him to drop his blaster. He slices at his throat with the shield, but SOMEONE dodges and punches SOMEONE to the deck.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS605
SOMEONE kicks him in the stomach. SOMEONE grabs his leg and the two men grapple. SOMEONE reaches for the blaster, but SOMEONE throws a box and knocks it away. SOMEONE puts SOMEONE in a chokehold.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS606
The two men roll across the energy mechanism in the center of the cockpit and spill onto the floor. SOMEONE picks up his shield, but SOMEONE wrests it away and smacks SOMEONE across the face with it. SOMEONE pins down SOMEONE but he head-butts SOMEONE off of him. SOMEONE hurls SOMEONE into the controls causing the plane to head into a steep dive.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS607
Now in free fall, the two men continue to fight as they float weightlessly.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS608
SOMEONE leaps and pins SOMEONE to the ceiling.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS609
They trade punches, then SOMEONE boots SOMEONE into the far wall.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS611
As the plane dives through a layer of clouds, SOMEONE pulls himself to the controls and re-engages the autopilot.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS612
As the plane levels out again, SOMEONE slams onto the deck.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS614
SOMEONE turns and pulls out a pistol blaster as he scans the room.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS618
SOMEONE dives behind metal struts as SOMEONE fires at him. SOMEONE flings his shield, striking SOMEONE and smashing him into the energy mechanism which begins to spark and flicker with blue light. SOMEONE staggers to his feet.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS619
SOMEONE picks up the cube-shaped energy source.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS620
As he stares into it, vaporous flashes of blue light fill the air.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS622
A sphere of energy expands around SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS623
SOMEONE stands at the far end of the cockpit as the cube brightens.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS624
An intensifying beam shoots out of the top of the cube and SOMEONE's fingers begin to smoke.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS625
The energy beam shoots out of the top of the plane and into the sky.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS626
The light inside the cockpit dims. SOMEONE is gone. The cube drops onto the floor.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS627
SOMEONE picks up his shield and watches as the cube burns a hole through the deck, and plummets out of sight. SOMEONE takes of his helmet and sits in the pilot's chair.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS628
A radar display reads, ZIEL, New York City.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS629
Grabbing the controls, SOMEONE steers out of the vast expanse of clouds.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS630
Meanwhile, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and Col. SOMEONE wait in the control tower.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS631
A pair of vapor trails stream behind the plane as it banks through a layer of clouds.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS632
SOMEONE blinks, then furrows her brow, and presses her lips together.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS633
SOMEONE takes out his compass with the photo of SOMEONE in the lid
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS634
and sets it atop the plane's controls.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS635
He stares at the photo then pushes down on the steering yoke causing the plane to dive steeply.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS636
SOMEONE continues to stare at the photo as the plane descends.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS638
The plane dives toward an ice-covered land mass.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS639
In the control tower, tears stream down SOMEONE's cheeks.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS640
SOMEONE closes her eyes and smiles.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS641
SOMEONE looks down.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS642
As SOMEONE lowers her head, SOMEONE walks out, leaving her alone.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS643
The sun shines low in the sky across a windblown expanse of ice and snow.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS644
Scarring the landscape, deep furrows run toward the remains of the crashed plane.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS645
Dark smoke pours out of an engine as the plane shifts and settles.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS646
A broken wing reaches skyward as snow blows over it.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS647
In Trafalgar Square, planes streak over cheering crowds waving British flags. A serviceman holds a newspaper, V-Day It's Over In Europe.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS648
In a pub, the men of the 107th clink glasses together.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS649
The men drink as people smile and hug one another around them.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS650
Now, an underwater robot stretches out a claw and picks up the glowing blue energy cube off the ocean floor.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS651
In a ship's pilothouse, SOMEONE Stark watches the robot on a monitor.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS652
Back in the Allied headquarters, people pack up supplies.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS653
Col. SOMEONE walks up to Agent SOMEONE and sets down a folder, then continues on.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS654
She picks up the classified file which is marked Captain America,
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS656
She opens the folder, revealing a half-hidden photo.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS657
Taking a deep breath, she takes out the photo which depicts SOMEONE before his transformation, just a skinny kid from Brooklyn.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS659
Outside, a young boy holds a garbage can lid painted like Captain America's shield as he plays with his friends.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS660
Lying in a brightly lit hospital room, SOMEONE flickers open his eyes.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS661
He slides his feet to the floor and sits up.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS662
SOMEONE stares at a nearby radio.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS663
A woman with curly brown hair walks in.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS664
Furrowing his brow, SOMEONE stares at her, then glances toward a sunlit window.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS665
The woman's smile falls as SOMEONE stands.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS666
Two men in Kevlar body armor step into the room. A moment later, their bodies fly through a false wall revealing the hospital room to be inside a warehouse.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS667
SOMEONE runs out of an exit.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS668
SOMEONE barrels past security guards as he races down a hallway. He dashes out of a modern office building and into a city street. SOMEONE runs into the middle of Times Square, then stops and gazes at the brightly lit signs and video screens all around him.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS669
Black SUVs converge on his position.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS671
A goateed man wearing a black turtleneck trench coat and eye patch strides up to SOMEONE.
CAPTAIN_AMERICA_DVS672
SOMEONE blinks, then gazes at his surroundings.