Another wave hits the rocks and his head pops out of the water,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS38
his outstretched hands lap against the surface.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS39
He tries to shake the salty water off his face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS40
The girl watches in anguish as another wave rolls over him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS41
Foam rains down.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS42
His white tennis shoes dangle helplessly toward the deep.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS44
As a yellow shape floats overhead, a hand reaches down and pulls him up by the scruff of his collar.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS45
A shaggy haired man with the same colored beard lays the boy, face first, on his surfboard.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS46
He glances over his shoulder and paddles his muscular arms, breathing hard.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS47
As a 15-foot wave begins to crest, he drops down through the face of it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS48
The front of the board bounces through the breaking wave as they emerge safely.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS49
The girl watches, then runs to meet them with the dog in tow.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS50
As they glide through calmer water, SOMEONE looks around with an ecstatic, open-mouthed grin.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS52
The man drives them along a coastal road in his boxy white van.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS54
His rescuer narrows his eyes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS55
Night falls as the van heads into a beach town.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS57
Words appear. "Santa Cruz, California, 1987."
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS58
The van pulls up beside a small house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS59
As the man turns back to the wheel, SOMEONE knocks on his window.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS60
He rolls window down with a wry look.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS61
He rolls ahead.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS62
He puts the van in park.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS64
The man nods and pulls away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS65
As SOMEONE pushes his bike, he turns back to see the van park a few doors down the street.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS66
The girl watches, holding her dog, as the man gets out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS67
He turns away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS68
SOMEONE looks at the girl.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS69
She gives him a peck on the cheek and dashes away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS70
SOMEONE blinks with a starry-eyed smile.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS71
The man passes through a white picket fence and pauses.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS72
Beyond a window, a demure, dark haired woman bounces a crying baby in her arms.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS73
The man hesitates. SOMEONE flicks on a light.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS75
He sets his jacket on a counter.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS76
He notices a US Armed Forces savings check for $400 payable to SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS78
He spots a crumpled hand-written note atop an unopened envelope marked, Past Due.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS80
As he reads the note, his brow creases.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS81
He looks off then hurries down the hall.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS82
He stops in a doorway.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS83
In the dim light of a bedside lamp,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS84
a blonde woman lies on her side in a rumpled bed.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS85
SOMEONE creeps in and picks up a bottle on her nightstand.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS86
Sniffing it, he recoils.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS88
As he turns to go, she reaches for his hand.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS89
She rolls onto her back, one arm bent over her head.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS90
She looks at him through bleary eyes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS91
She turns away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS92
He takes the bottle.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS93
In the kitchen, he pours its contents down the drain.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS94
Taking off his shirt, SOMEONE passes a couch and a divider that separates the living room from his bed.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS95
An envelope on his pillow reads.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS97
He turns on the light and takes it in his hands, looking down at it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS98
Later, he places a wooden cigar box on his bed and sets the unopened envelope inside.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS101
in his dimly hit kitchen, the sandy haired man unscrews the top of a canister.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS102
He opens a blue cabinet and the top hinge breaks loose.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS103
The dark haired woman peeks in.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS104
He leans down and kisses her.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS105
She walks away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS106
Dawn breaks over a rundown cottage with a dirt drive.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS107
Inside, a cleaned up radiant SOMEONE stands before him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS108
He watches her walk out, a hopeful smile on his face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS109
Later, a clock on the wall reads 1:15.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS111
Nibbling on pretzel rods, SOMEONE sits at the kitchen table, eyeing it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS112
With a sigh, he rises.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS113
He opens the doors of a shed and pads inside barefoot.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS114
An old bicycle rests beside a bunch of garden tools.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS115
SOMEONE squats down and looks behind a metal utility shelf.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS116
He hoists up a dirty six foot long surfboard,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS117
examining a crack running horizontally across its deck.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS119
Laying the board flat, he paints a thin layer of glue along the crack with a small applicator.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS120
He grimaces then picks up the can, pouring it along the length of the crack.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS121
He presses the board together and the clear glue bubbles up from the mended seam.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS122
He squints around the shed.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS123
Now, he duct tapes the seam, flips the board over and smooths it across the other side.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS125
He looks down the length of the board to the tail and finds three empty slits.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS126
He sighs.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS127
Now, in a baggy black wet suit, he lugs the board over to the shaggy haired man's house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS128
In the front yard, his wife sits on the grass with another woman and her little girl.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS130
the woman opens the doors of a well-stocked surf shed and walks to the back.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS131
SOMEONE gazes at two paddle boards stored overhead then over to a red long board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS133
She notes the look of wonder on his face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS134
A picture of SOMEONE on a giant wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS135
She hands him the fins.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS136
Now, SOMEONE walks down the street to the beachfront, struggling to keep the board under his arm.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS137
He takes a rundown path, passing graffiti that reads, "Surf where you live."
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS139
A man sips from a paper bag.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS140
Surfboards lean against a rusted metal guardrail.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS141
SOMEONE rounds a corner and stops, gazing past a cliff to the ocean below.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS142
A long gentle wave rolls toward dozens of waiting surfers.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS143
Behind him, a boy smashes a side view mirror with a bat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS145
The boy scowls under his black knit cap and swaggers off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS146
With a furrowed brow, SOMEONE heads down to the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS147
A trio of surfers his own age sits on the sand by their boards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS148
They watch SOMEONE pass, lugging his old, dirty board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS149
He stops and looks out at the waves.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS150
SOMEONE, on his bright yellow long board, drops into a gentle five-foot curl.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS152
He rises and crouches, carving up and down the face of the wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS153
With each effortless swerve, his fingertips graze the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS154
SOMEONE grins, completely entranced.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS155
SOMEONE smacks the lip of the wave, glides back down, and cross-steps up the board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS156
With his left foot planted on the nose, he bows his head, letting the lip of wave wet his hair.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS157
SOMEONE purses his lips with determination and heads in.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS159
Now, lying on his stomach, he paddles out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS160
Two surfers paddling in front of him duck dive under an oncoming wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS161
SOMEONE takes a deep breath and lowers his head.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS162
The board crashes over the break.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS163
He holds on, shaking his drenched head, and keeps paddling.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS164
Another wave of froth rushing into him, pushing him back.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS165
He shakes it off again and keeps paddling.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS166
Farther out, a round faced boy sits on his board, observing with a worried look.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS167
As another break hits SOMEONE, the board goes vertical and flips out of his hands.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS168
The round faced boy shakes his head.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS169
SOMEONE surfaces, blood trickling from his mouth.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS170
The boy paddles over.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS171
SOMEONE struggles back onto the board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS172
SOMEONE shoots him an impatient look.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS173
He puts his hand on SOMEONE's tail.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS174
They look over their shoulders.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS175
A swell builds behind them.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS176
On the beach, SOMEONE turns around and watches.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS177
SOMEONE paddles and pushes onto his hands and knees.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS178
He brings his left foot up, then his right.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS179
Crouching, he lets go of the rails.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS180
A grin pulls at SOMEONE's lip.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS181
Hunched over and jaw hanging slack, SOMEONE looks up.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS182
The cliffs get closer as he glides across the water toward shore.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS183
Words appear - "Seven years later."
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS184
A curly haired teenage SOMEONE runs his hand along a wave as he easily carves up and down its face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS185
Clad in a blue sleeved wetsuit, he maneuvers around other paddling surfers, then cross-steps up the board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS188
He crouches down, swerves his board back to the lip, and rides it back down.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS189
Now, he does a floater, riding along the top of the curl.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS190
High above on the cliff, a teenage boy scowls, watching him with his buddies.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS192
SOMEONE finishes by carving up the top of the wave and leaping over it with his hands on the rails.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS193
Wearing an ear-to-ear grin, he paddles toward shore.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS194
He nears a younger surfer as a swell creeps up behind them.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS195
The novice gets to his feet. Another teen holds out his arm in mock indignation.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS196
The scowling boy sits with his pals at the top of the steps, tapping a bat in his hand.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS197
SOMEONE gives it a light tap and walks on.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS198
SOMEONE and Blond carry their surfboards down the street.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS199
A teenage girl with long blonde hair climbs into a rainbow colored VW bus.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS200
As she climbs into the passenger seat and shuts the door, SOMEONE's smile fades.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS201
He gazes after the van as it putters away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS202
SOMEONE takes off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS203
He races through an open door to find SOMEONE on the kitchen floor.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS204
A man stands over her.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS205
SOMEONE grabs the man.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS206
The man backs out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS207
SOMEONE tackles him out the front door.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS208
They land on the grass.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS209
Blond tries to pull SOMEONE off as a police car rounds the corner.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS210
Across the street, SOMEONE stands with his hands in his pockets watching the scene.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS211
SOMEONE throws Blond off of him and looks up to see SOMEONE frowning.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS212
The older surfer turns away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS213
Now, SOMEONE races down a darkened beach to the waves.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS214
He leaps onto the board and paddles out, away from the flashing lights of the boardwalk.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS215
He sits up on the board, letting his feet dangle in the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS216
Now on his bed, SOMEONE sketches a surfer entering a tube.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS217
Using a pen on notepaper, he adds intricate detail to the drawing.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS218
Nearby, a trophy bearing his name stands by an alarm clock reading 4:00.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS220
In his sweats, SOMEONE sits up and peeks out a window to find SOMEONE heading out to his van across the street.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS222
In the darkness, he hefts a surfboard up to the roof.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS223
SOMEONE hurriedly grabs his things and rushes out the door.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS224
He dashes down the quiet pre-dawn street.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS225
As SOMEONE's van pulls away,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS226
he hops onto the rear bumper, clutching the ladder.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS228
At the wheel, SOMEONE rides on the van's roof.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS230
the van passes a sign marking California Highway 1N.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS231
SOMEONE stares at it, then zips up his jacket.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS232
Now, the van travels through misty hills in the pale light of dawn.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS233
Later, it follows a coastal road that ascends parallel to a shelf of dizzying ocean-side cliffs.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS234
Now, fishing boats drift in a calm bay as the van follows a winding road uphill.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS236
Still on the roof, SOMEONE clutches the front bar of the surfboard rack as he rides on his belly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS237
Ahead, a man gets out of an old pickup.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS238
SOMEONE climbs down the back of the van and hops off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS239
As the van passes between two posts,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS240
SOMEONE blocks them off with a chain.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS244
Crouched in nearby brush, SOMEONE creeps closer. On a ridge ahead, three athletic dark haired men in wetsuits wait with surfboards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS245
One with close cropped hair crouches, waxing his down.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS246
Carrying a cherry red board, SOMEONE joins the men and greets the shorthaired one with a casual handclasp.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS247
The men head off with their boards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS248
Creeping around a knoll, we find them descending a winding path
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS249
cutting through a slope blanketed with vegetation.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS251
Peering over a ridge, SOMEONE finds the men approaching a small isolated beach at the base of the slope.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS252
The team moves along the ridge, keeping his eager gaze fixed on the older surfers.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS254
From the sandy beach, the four men trot into the water and stretch out on their boards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS256
As they paddle far out, we spot a meteorological complex, complete with a satellite dish perched on a bluff in the distance.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS259
SOMEONE skirts around the end of a chain-linked fence and dashes along the edge.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS260
Staggering, he finds his balance then gazes out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS261
On the water, waves swell and crest several stories high.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS262
Their powerful crashes send up massive bursts of white foam.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS263
A cleanly breaking wave forms a long tube.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS264
Wearing a wetsuit with a billed skull-fitted hood,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS265
SOMEONE paddles his board up a high wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS266
SOMEONE pants excitedly, his lips curled into a faint smile.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS267
The older surfer faces a cresting wave that towers stories above him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS268
SOMEONE follows his friends to the top, then rides his board down the other side.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS271
From the distant bluffs, SOMEONE appears as a tiny speck as he looks on.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS272
One of SOMEONE's friends takes a wave and rides down the 20-foot face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS273
The men take one wave after another, their boards cleanly skimming the glassy water beneath their feet.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS274
SOMEONE's shoulders heave as he takes in the spectacle.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS275
One surfer skirts just ahead of the white water which seems to pursue him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS276
Two others share a broad section of the wave's foamy face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS277
Near shore, a wave crashes violently against a huge jagged rock formation.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS278
Further out, a swelling wave fills our view.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS279
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder as he paddles along its face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS280
As SOMEONE looks on ecstatically, the older surfer pops up at the wave's crest,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS281
then rides his board 20 feet down the glassy face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS282
The wave breaks behind him, forming an oncoming mass of churning white water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS283
SOMEONE reaches the foot of the wave, briefly vanishing from view within the rolling tides before he emerges to take more of the face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS284
He skirts the ends of the pursuing white water, staying up as the wave diminishes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS285
SOMEONE joyfully raises both fists.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS286
Looking around, SOMEONE spots the teen on the bluffs.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS287
As SOMEONE catches his breath, the older man regards him gravely.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS288
Now in the speeding van.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS289
SOMEONE gives a sheepish nod.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS290
SOMEONE slaps a small cube shaped weather radio perched on a cup holder tray.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS291
SOMEONE shifts his gaze and gulps, then faces him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS292
Later, the van pulls up in front of SOMEONE's house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS293
A short board hangs over the garage door.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS294
SOMEONE cuts the van's ignition.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS295
Beside him, the teen shifts his intimidated gaze
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS296
but lingers in his seat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS297
The boy stares at his lap.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS299
SOMEONE glances toward SOMEONE's house and nods understandingly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS300
SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb out of the van.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS301
SOMEONE and SOMEONE clasp their hands.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS302
He backs the teen against the shed.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS303
SOMEONE swaggers into his shed.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS304
He gathers up some tools.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS305
SOMEONE stares up at him earnestly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS306
SOMEONE turns away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS307
Shaking his head, the teen turns away and heads home.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS308
SOMEONE hefts a box of tools and supplies.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS309
Coming out of the shed, he gazes after SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS310
Turning, he finds his wife watching from the front door of their home.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS311
As she slips inside, he follows her to a baby's nursery.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS312
She gives him a pointed look.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS313
SOMEONE stares as his wife with a furrowed brow, then concedes a small nod.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS315
Later in his shed, he tends to his cherry red surfboard.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS316
Other boards rest in a rack at the back of the shed.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS317
Taking a break, SOMEONE thoughtfully wipes his hands off with a rag.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS319
At Pleasure Pizza, SOMEONE ladles sauce over shredded cheese on a disk of dough.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS320
Putting the order in, Blond notices SOMEONE's handiwork.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS321
SOMEONE spots SOMEONE's van outside.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS322
He rushes out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS323
As SOMEONE drives away, a grin spreads across SOMEONE's features.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS324
He pumps his fists.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS325
Now, SOMEONE's watch reads 6:30 as he waits in the doorway of his shed.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS326
SOMEONE jogs into view, carrying a surfboard.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS327
He points to the two long paddleboards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS328
Now in wetsuits, they each carry a board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS329
SOMEONE taps a car with his board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS330
Now, they carry the boards into the surf.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS331
Later, on calm waters, they kneel on their respective boards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS332
They bend over, paddling both hands through the water at the same time.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS333
Brackets on the boards hold water bottles.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS334
They pause and sit up.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS335
At night, a figure jumps from a tree to a second story window of a house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS336
Inside, SOMEONE reads on her bed.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS337
Sofie leaves her side to greet SOMEONE at the window.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS338
SOMEONE dashes over.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS339
Clad in a silky robe, SOMEONE beams at him fondly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS340
Now, a skateboard rolls over a sunlit speed bump.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS341
As SOMEONE rides it up the street, Blond skateboards a short distance behind him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS342
As his friend splits off, SOMEONE pauses in front of an electronic store display window.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS343
The young surfer notices a weather radio priced at $89.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS344
In the window glass, a reflection shows Blond passing something off to two of thuggish bullies.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS345
SOMEONE gazes after his friend with a concerned frown
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS346
then follows him off on his skateboard.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS347
They take turns jumping another speed bump.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS348
Now outside an abandoned house, a hammock hangs over a back patio.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS349
In a drained swimming pool, a kid with glasses and a hunter's cap preform skateboarding tricks on the curved concrete.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS350
Blond joins him, skateboarding up and down the walls of the basin.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS351
At the rim, SOMEONE holds onto a fence as he flips his board with his feet.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS352
The glass of the house's sunroom reflects the three teens as they skateboard in and out of the dry pool.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS353
The bespectacled kid wipes out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS354
Recovering, he takes a smooth turn around the pool.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS355
The bespectacled kid practices some more.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS356
Blond taps him on the stomach then joins their other friend.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS357
Later, SOMEONE rides a bike up to a house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS358
Working on the roof, SOMEONE climbs down a ladder and carries his tools over.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS359
He sets the tools in his van.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS360
SOMEONE picks up a large shovel.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS361
He leaves SOMEONE clutching the shovel by a large pile of SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS362
Now we float over the Santa Cruz boardwalk's Giant Dipper rollercoaster.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS363
SOMEONE paddles on the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS364
SOMEONE stops paddling then rolls off his board and into the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS365
SOMEONE halts and looks back.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS366
The gently rolling current shows no sign of the boy.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS367
He pops up and shakes out his curls.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS368
SOMEONE shakes his head and faces the sea.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS370
Now at home, SOMEONE makes a poster charting his training goals.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS371
One bar tracks the miles to Monterey
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS372
while another counts 4 minutes in 30-second increments.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS373
He hangs the poster on two panels of corkboard on his wall.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS374
Now, sipping tea in her kitchen,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS375
SOMEONE's wife flips through a small book of black and white baby pictures.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS376
SOMEONE makes a sandwich.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS377
SOMEONE chuckles fondly at his wife as she eyes the pictures wistfully.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS378
As he turns away, she leaves the table,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS379
steps in close, and rubs his back.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS380
SOMEONE turns to face her, his gaze receptive.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS381
SOMEONE shifts his conflicted gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS382
Looking down, he finds his wife's delicate features set in a solemn expression.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS383
SOMEONE hangs his head and nods.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS384
His wife beams gratefully.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS385
She steps out of the kitchen.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS386
Now, a wall clock reads 6:25.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS387
Heading out the door, SOMEONE finds a set of keys on a table.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS388
SOMEONE opens her door then turns on a shower.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS389
She remains curled up on her belly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS390
At a sink piled high with dirty dishes,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS391
SOMEONE shakes out a cup, then fills it with coffee and shifts his anxious gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS392
Now, SOMEONE's van sits in the pouring rain outside his house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS394
SOMEONE flips through the old photos documenting his childhood.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS395
One shows him on skis in the snow.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS396
Another shows his boyhood-self sitting close to a father figure.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS397
The next page is blank as well as the pages after it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS399
SOMEONE's brow furrows sadly as he flips through them.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS400
SOMEONE arrives and climbs in.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS401
SOMEONE takes a folded page from the teen and opens it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS402
As he looks it over, he lifts his brow and nods.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS403
Now, SOMEONE's van speeds along the coastal highway.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS404
Inside, SOMEONE eats a chocolate cupcake.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS405
SOMEONE grabs the cupcake from him, eyes it, then tosses it in the back.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS406
He tosses down a sandwich.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS407
From overhead, crashing waves sweep white foam onto the stunning California shore.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS408
Standing together, SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold long boards and gaze out at the waves.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS409
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a determined look and nods.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS410
He pulls his wetsuit hood over his blonde curls.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS411
Now, the young surfer paddles out alone.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS412
Using his arms, SOMEONE pushes up and floats over the crest of a modest wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS413
He turtle rolls, dipping underneath the board as a much larger wave crashes down.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS415
The board shoots out of the water with SOMEONE unseen and SOMEONE smiles from the beach.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS416
As SOMEONE swims back to his board, another towering wave crashes down on him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS417
SOMEONE shakes his head, wearing a slight grin on his weathered face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS418
SOMEONE tries to regroup with his board but another wave catches him off guard and sweeps him back toward the beach.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS419
Standing in chest high water, a small wave knocks him over and SOMEONE smiles.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS420
Now, the young surfer stumbles onto the sand, drops his board, and collapses.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS421
SOMEONE rips off his hood.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS422
Now he follows SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS423
SOMEONE sets down his board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS424
They crouch down together.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS425
SOMEONE pulls up his hood.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS426
He grabs his board and heads to the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS427
Watching closely, SOMEONE stands up as SOMEONE paddles beside the protruding rock formations.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS428
He pushes up over several small waves and continues further out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS429
SOMEONE's wide smile fades as SOMEONE heads for a much larger wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS430
The veteran surfer lies flat on the board and busts through the top portion as it breaks.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS431
Sitting on his board, SOMEONE holds two arms in the air and SOMEONE shows a beaming smile from the beach.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS432
Now they walk the incline back to the van.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS433
He stops and admires his mentor.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS434
Later, SOMEONE rides his bike through an alley,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS435
popping a wheelie on the way.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS436
He notices SOMEONE walking nearby.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS437
The bike slides out from under him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS438
Now, SOMEONE climbs onto a roof.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS439
She hops onto a flat section next to SOMEONE and they walk to the edge overlooking a pool.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS440
He takes off a shoe.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS441
Blond arrives.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS442
He and SOMEONE touch folded arms in a handshake.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS443
He removes his shirt.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS444
Blond drops his pants and front flips off the roof.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS445
He looks up at them with extended arms.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS446
He takes off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS447
SOMEONE lands safely in the pool off a daring back tuck and SOMEONE beams.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS448
She quickly removes her top.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS449
SOMEONE leaps feet first into the pool.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS450
As SOMEONE takes off across the pool, SOMEONE rips off his wet shirt and tosses it aside.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS451
Swimming underwater, he grabs her ankle and pulls her back.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS452
SOMEONE passes the lively blonde and beats her to the edge.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS453
She emerges right in front of him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS454
Blond watches as SOMEONE playfully splashes SOMEONE and swims off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS455
At home, SOMEONE does push-ups.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS456
His mom enters the living room.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS457
Later, SOMEONE paddle boards to a navigational buoy far off the coast.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS458
At home, he crosses week two off his Maverick's chart.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS459
Now, SOMEONE treads water in a pool, holding a chair above his head.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS460
SOMEONE casually bites an apple and reads the paper as SOMEONE struggles in the pool.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS461
Later, SOMEONE starts a timer on his watch and skateboards beside a bus.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS462
His friend in a hunter's cap skateboards holding onto the moving bus and flashes the surfer a shaka sign.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS463
Stopping, SOMEONE exhales and checks his watch.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS464
Outside the school, the young surfer handwrites an essay titled, The Power of Observation.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS465
SOMEONE sits nearby with a group of students.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS466
Looking up from the essay, SOMEONE watches her closely.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS467
A sweet smile spreads his boyish face as she giggles with her friends.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS469
Later in his room, SOMEONE sits before a typewriter, transcribing his handwritten essay.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS470
Now he approaches SOMEONE's house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS471
SOMEONE pulls the essay from his sweatshirt and hands it to SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS472
SOMEONE smiles and nods.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS473
Now, the teen shovels food into his mouth.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS474
The eight-year-old SOMEONE watches as he piles mashed potatoes onto a roll and stuffs the oversized bite down.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS475
SOMEONE's wife glances at her husband who raises his brow.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS477
Holding a half-eaten chicken leg, SOMEONE faces her and smiles.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS478
She grabs a pot from the stove as SOMEONE continues feasting.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS479
Putting on reading glasses, SOMEONE unfolds the essay.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS480
SOMEONE notices him reading and focuses on the food as SOMEONE's wife returns with another scoop of potatoes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS482
SOMEONE turns the page and looks up.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS483
SOMEONE quickly looks up.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS484
His wide eyes shift between SOMEONE and the essay.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS485
SOMEONE's wife eyes her husband then looks down.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS486
SOMEONE nods and swiftly stands.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS487
She hugs SOMEONE and leaves the kitchen.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS488
SOMEONE gazes nervously at SOMEONE's glare and swallows hard.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS489
He stands up.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS490
She leaves SOMEONE with the baby and joins SOMEONE in the bedroom.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS491
Slack jawed, SOMEONE closes his eyes and shakes his head.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS492
She kneels before SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS493
Rubbing his arms, she lovingly gazes into his eyes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS494
She glances toward the kitchen.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS495
They hurry out of the room to find SOMEONE holding the baby.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS496
SOMEONE hands baby to her.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS497
She eyes SOMEONE and leaves them alone.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS498
SOMEONE shifts his weight anxiously and SOMEONE stares.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS499
They both take seats at the table.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS501
The teacher glances at an empty desk.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS502
On the coastal highway, SOMEONE rides in the bed of an old pickup truck with four labor workers.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS503
They sit quietly with arms crossed,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS504
huddling from the chilly wind.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS505
White surf sweeps along the coast and surrounds a small peninsula.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS506
SOMEONE takes notes atop the cliff.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS507
He spots a lone surfer.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS508
SOMEONE smiles.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS509
A large wave breaks as SOMEONE focuses.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS510
SOMEONE's surfing buddy catches a towering wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS511
SOMEONE smiles enviously as the veteran starts a 30-foot drop.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS512
The surfer suddenly falls off the board and the colossal wave smashes down on him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS513
SOMEONE drops his notebook and quickly stands.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS514
He moves to the cliff's edge, staring out into the frothy white surf.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS515
The churning wave rapidly sweeps toward the coast and collides with rock formations.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS516
SOMEONE's mouth falls open.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS517
The surfer's bright orange board shoots out of the wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS518
A massive burst of water blasts upward as the wave crashes into more rock formations.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS519
The young surfer trembles, frantically scanning the seething ocean for SOMEONE's buddy.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS520
The board lies in a calm spot on the surface as another wave crashes into a large rock.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS521
The water clears and SOMEONE spots the surfer clutching onto the rock.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS522
The veteran surfer appears uninjured as he climbs onto the rock's peak.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS523
Now at home, SOMEONE's observation notes lie strewn on his bed along with ocean maps and various science books.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS524
The young surfer sits cross-legged, drawing in his private notebook.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS525
Focusing ardently, SOMEONE puts the finishing touches on a pencil drawn picture.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS527
A longhaired surfers claws at the air as a beastly octopus clenches him with a tentacle.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS528
He admires his work and breathes deep.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS530
SOMEONE rides his bike into SOMEONE's driveway and slides to a stop.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS532
As he drops an essay in the mailbox, SOMEONE's wife emerges from the garage.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS533
SOMEONE raises her brow.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS534
Her lips part as she nods.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS535
She smiles sweetly and looks off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS536
SOMEONE rides off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS538
Later at Pleasure Pizza, SOMEONE exits the back door with his bike.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS539
He sees Blond across the parking lot exchanging a small plastic bag for money with a scowling bully.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS540
The bully spots SOMEONE and nods.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS541
Blond approaches the door as the bully drives off and SOMEONE blocks him with his bike.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS542
Blond's smile fades.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS543
He tosses Blond the keys.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS544
They make brief eye contact, then SOMEONE rides away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS545
Now, he arrives home and slides to a stop in his dirt driveway.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS547
At his desk, the young surfer pulls out the cigar box and turns on a lamp.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS549
Holding a handful of dollar bills, SOMEONE eyes a print ad for $89 weather radio.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS550
He presses his thumb against the ad and looks down at the unopened envelope from his father.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS551
SOMEONE grabs the letter and gazes longingly then turns it over in the box.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS553
He shoves the money inside and closes it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS554
Now his mom arrives home from work.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS556
She tosses her purse and keys down then removes her coat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS557
SOMEONE enters the bathroom and notices the bathtub full of water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS558
As she reaches for the faucet, SOMEONE bursts out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS559
Later, he crosses week four off the chart and colors the breath-holding graph just under two minutes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS560
SOMEONE carefully pins a surfing poster over his Maverick's chart.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS561
She rubs her wrist anxiously as SOMEONE stares off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS562
He pulls the cigar box from the drawer and grabs his wad of cash.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS563
SOMEONE saunters toward her son as he counts out one-dollar bills.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS564
He stares at his hard-earned money.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS565
SOMEONE holds out the cash.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS566
His mom snatches it and turns.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS567
SOMEONE's sad eyes shift about as she leaves.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS568
Now a park features an overlook where waves crash against the base of steep cliffs.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS569
A warning sign stands at their edge.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS570
Clad in a wetsuit and carrying a surfboard, SOMEONE climbs over a barrier fence and takes a seat next to a brooding Blond.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS571
Paddling on a surfboard, the scowling boy faces a wave, bites his lip, and picks up his pace.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS572
Standing at the top of a wave, SOMEONE shoves another surfer forcing him off his board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS573
SOMEONE surfs the wave just ahead of the white water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS574
SOMEONE clasps his friend's hand, hauls him to his feet, and gently taps his stomach with his board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS575
In churning water, a surfing SOMEONE glances over his shoulder.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS576
On the ridge, SOMEONE takes a running start and leaps from the edge.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS577
He plummets 30 feet to the breakers below.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS578
Surfacing, he shakes out his curls.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS579
Blond lingers on the cliff, watching his friend inscrutably.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS580
SOMEONE paddles over a misty sunlit wave and joins up with the other surfers.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS581
SOMEONE regards him with a weary sneer.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS583
Eyeing a wave, SOMEONE turns and paddles along with it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS584
He pops up as it crests beneath him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS585
SOMEONE's board leaves a white wake as he surfs along the face, executing tight curls at the crest.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS586
From the lookout point, SOMEONE snacks on sunflower seeds as he watches the teen.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS587
Skirting the white water, SOMEONE executes a 360.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS588
Frowning resentfully, SOMEONE paddles away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS589
Blond watches with a faint hard smile as the bully claims a wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS590
SOMEONE carves his way up and down the face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS591
As the white water catches up to him, he waves SOMEONE on daringly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS592
With a good-natured smile, SOMEONE paddles back out toward the waves.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS593
From the lookout, SOMEONE watches him intently.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS594
SOMEONE paddles along the top of a wave then pops up at its crest.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS596
The gifted teen surfs along its face, trailing his fingertips through the green water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS597
He carves up the wave, descends to the base, then rides up the face for another turn.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS598
SOMEONE allows the white water to surround him, then crouches low and glides out of it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS599
SOMEONE watches jealously as SOMEONE allows a faint proud smile.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS601
Back on the wave's face, SOMEONE executes a 180 at the crest.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS602
As the white water converges around him, he leaps from his board and dives head first into the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS603
On the high ridge, Blond pumps his fists.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS605
SOMEONE seethes on his board as SOMEONE joyfully surfaces and shakes his hair out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS606
With a satisfied smile, SOMEONE steps away from the overlook.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS607
Now SOMEONE runs a hand through her hair as she walks up the walk to her front door.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS608
Opening it, she pauses and listens.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS610
Coming in, she glances down the hall and finds no sign of anyone.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS611
She moves to the kitchen and finds SOMEONE and SOMEONE renovating the cabinets.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS612
Seeing her, SOMEONE pauses.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS614
As SOMEONE beams lovingly, he removes his goggles, steps on a foot switch, and lowers a paper facemask.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS615
SOMEONE rolls his eyes and faces SOMEONE whose smile vanishes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS616
The older man smiles at SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS617
His brow furrowed, he gives a nod.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS619
Now at Pleasure Pizza's counter, SOMEONE and his buddies come in.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS620
He staggers drunkenly while his friends rough house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS621
SOMEONE marches behind the counter and attacks Blond.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS622
SOMEONE struggles to pull him off and raises a fist.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS623
SOMEONE's buddies restrain him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS624
He knocks a bell off the counter.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS625
As they leave, Blond rubs his throat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS626
SOMEONE finds a roll of cash on the floor and thrusts it as his chest.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS627
He steps away and Blond shifts his guilty gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS628
Now SOMEONE's van travels up a winding road in a light fog.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS630
Riding shotgun, SOMEONE stares out his window broodingly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS631
SOMEONE takes the essay from his pocket and sets it on the tray.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS632
SOMEONE faces his mentor with wide eyes and finds him beaming.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS633
Now at Mavericks, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand in a small fishing boat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS634
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE plunge into the water wearing diving masks, suits, and flippers.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS636
The paddle down to a reef.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS637
SOMEONE curls in his ring finger.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS638
They pause among giant knobs of coral growth.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS639
SOMEONE checks his wristwatch.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS640
Facing SOMEONE, he jerks his thumb upward.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS641
Lifting his contented gaze, the teen does a double take.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS643
A great white shark swims above them.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS645
As SOMEONE watches it calmly, SOMEONE flails his arms and recoils.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS646
The shark turns, giving a view of its glassy black eyes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS648
Noticing SOMEONE's rising panic, SOMEONE turns the boy to face him and gives calming gestures.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS649
Large air bubbles escape from the teen's mouth.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS650
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE looks up at the shark again and exhales more air.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS652
As the creature swims away, the mentor grabs the teen and urges him up toward the surface.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS653
As SOMEONE grabs onto the boat's diving step, its grizzled owner cocks a gun from the deck.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS654
The teen edges back against the cabin.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS655
Climbing on board, SOMEONE removes his mask and faces his breathless protege.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS656
As SOMEONE steps away, SOMEONE warms his hands under his arms and shifts his thoughtful gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS657
Now at home, he types out the first words of an essay entitled,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS659
He taps the keys with two fingers.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS660
Now at school, a wall clock read 8:48.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS661
Watching the clock, SOMEONE holds his breath.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS662
With a pencil, he makes a third SOMEONE on his notepaper.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS663
SOMEONE passes out, landing in a heap beside his desk.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS664
The teacher regards him with a concerned gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS665
At night, SOMEONE takes out the trash behind Pleasure Pizza.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS666
A large group of teens ride past on bicycles.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS668
Spotting SOMEONE, SOMEONE splits off and rides over.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS670
SOMEONE leans behind the counter and grabs his stuff.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS671
Blond glares after him, then spies SOMEONE's notebook on the floor.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS672
He opens it and flips through the pages.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS673
Blond peruses his friend's surfing related sketches
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS674
then comes across a page filled with handwriting and halts.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS675
Now SOMEONE's van pulls up outside him home,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS676
its headlights cutting through the dark.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS677
In the kitchen, SOMEONE shuts a cabinet, a dishtowel in her free hand.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS678
He pulls out books.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS679
His wife smiles.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS680
She watches with glistening eyes as SOMEONE shuffles to a partially open door at the end of the hall.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS681
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE carry surfboards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS682
Nearing a rocky shore, SOMEONE pauses and looks back at her.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS684
Stopping on the winding path, SOMEONE smiles and follows him onward.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS685
Now, stars twinkle in a clear night sky.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS686
Standing at SOMEONE's side, SOMEONE beams at him affectionately.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS687
SOMEONE returns his solemn gaze to the sky.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS688
SOMEONE's smile fades and she regards him compassionately.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS689
Facing her, SOMEONE smiles and shrugs it off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS690
Now, pitch-black waves send up snow-white foam as they break.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS691
Wearing wetsuits, SOMEONE and SOMEONE paddle out on their surfboards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS692
They ascend a cresting wave and ride down the other side.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS693
Now, SOMEONE stands while SOMEONE rides the wave on her belly beside him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS694
She gets to her feet.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS695
SOMEONE surfs his board close to hers and reaches out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS696
The two join hands.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS697
Losing their balance, they fall off their boards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS698
SOMEONE surfaces with SOMEONE and shakes his hair out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS699
The blonde beauty grins joyfully and gives him a playful splash.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS700
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE propel their paddleboards over sunlit glassy waters hued a deep peacock blue.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS701
The two pause and sit up, straddling their boards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS702
SOMEONE trails his fingertips through the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS703
Squinting in the sunlight, SOMEONE sips from his water bottle.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS704
From underwater, we gaze up at the seasoned surfer.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS705
Its rippling surface distorts his appreciative gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS706
Now the two walk along a misty isolated beach.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS707
SOMEONE nods emphatically.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS708
Now, the light of a low sun casts a rosy glow on the waves.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS709
At night, SOMEONE and SOMEONE dance together by a campfire as two women sing and play ukuleles.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS710
SOMEONE beams as she watches her parents.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS711
Perched in a portable chair, SOMEONE looks on appreciatively.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS713
Holding each other close, SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze into each other's eyes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS714
He kisses her lips and dips her.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS715
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's hand.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS716
SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS717
Facing forward, SOMEONE spies SOMEONE hiking up from the water with a fishing pole in one hand and a huge fish in the other.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS719
SOMEONE springs from her chair and he chases her off across the sand.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS721
Now at a section of the school overlooking the ocean, SOMEONE arrives with friends and joins a group.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS722
Sitting yards away, SOMEONE stands eagerly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS723
SOMEONE greets a few friends then turns and notices him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS724
He lifts his hand in a wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS725
Her smile fades and she averts her gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS727
SOMEONE's brow knits and he blinks at her woundedly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS728
Now, autumn leaves cover the back patio of the abandoned house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS729
Arriving with his skateboard, SOMEONE finds Blond lounging in the pool with the kid in a hunter's cap,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS730
SOMEONE and his friends.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS731
SOMEONE removes his backpack and faces his friend.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS732
SOMEONE picks up SOMEONE's notebook.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS733
Sneering, he opens it and reads.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS734
SOMEONE faces Blond who returns his gaze remorselessly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS735
SOMEONE tosses the notebook over and it lands in the dirt.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS736
His cheeks flushed, SOMEONE lowers his humiliated gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS738
Blond picks at a tennis ball and he eyes his friend coldly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS739
SOMEONE backs away from him and picks up the notebook.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS740
Steeling himself, he walks past the bullies.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS741
At an isolated nighttime beach, SOMEONE crouches over his surfboard and waxes it aggressively.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS742
Later, his board rests on a chair outside as he comes in.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS743
Shuffling through the kitchen,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS744
he puts on his wristwatch and notices a stack of mail on the table.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS746
Amid the envelopes, he finds one with his name scrawled in red ink beside SOMEONE's crossed out name.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS748
He finds a single notation at the top of his latest essay. "Go deeper."
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS750
Now, SOMEONE marches into SOMEONE's shed where his mentor tends to a board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS751
He tosses down the envelope.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS752
SOMEONE runs in.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS753
Following her into the kitchen, SOMEONE and SOMEONE find SOMEONE sprawled on the floor.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS754
SOMEONE rushes to her.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS755
SOMEONE cradles her as SOMEONE rushes to a phone.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS756
Her face pale, SOMEONE stares off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS757
SOMEONE cradles her head.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS758
Now, the sun shines wanly through a thick haze and gleams on a calm grey sea.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS759
Wearing a black suit, SOMEONE stares out at the water with a knitted brow.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS761
Also in black, SOMEONE jogs out from a church and looks around.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS763
Passing arriving mourners, the teen spots his mentor across the street.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS764
SOMEONE arrives in a dark green jeep.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS766
Glancing toward SOMEONE, SOMEONE approaches the pretty teen who wears an anguished gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS767
SOMEONE shakes his head.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS768
Catching sight of SOMEONE, he bites his lip.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS769
SOMEONE regards her grieving friend with glistening eyes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS770
She gives an understanding nod.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS771
Taking deep breaths, SOMEONE marches off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS773
SOMEONE looks over her shoulder and finds him approaching his mentor.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS774
SOMEONE stands with both hands braced on a railing, his tie slightly loosened.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS775
SOMEONE fiddles with his wristwatch as he nears his heartbroken friend.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS776
Keeping his gaze fixed ahead,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS777
SOMEONE works his mouth.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS778
His jaw clenches.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS779
The teen turns and takes a few steps back
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS780
but lingers nearby.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS781
A tall bald man with a white mustache comes over.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS782
He steps up beside SOMEONE and faces him expectantly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS783
His brow furrowed, the older man turns his face toward the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS784
SOMEONE's eyes well with tears.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS785
SOMEONE gives a sorrowful nod and faces the older man.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS786
As the older man leaves,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS787
SOMEONE stares at his mentor helplessly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS788
Later, the teen enters his dark house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS790
In bed, SOMEONE lies on her back.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS791
As SOMEONE comes in and sits on the edge of her mattress,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS792
she scoots over to make room for him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS793
The teen shifts his pensive gaze then lies down beside his mother.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS795
Stare at the ceiling, their hands folded over their chests.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS796
SOMEONE's chest sags in a deep sigh.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS797
She rolls over to face her son.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS798
On an overcast day, SOMEONE brings a pizza to SOMEONE's house.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS799
He steps through the wide-open gate and swings it shut behind him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS800
Finding the front door standing ajar, he calls inside.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS801
He brings the pizza in.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS802
He turns and his eyes widen.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS803
The kitchen stands in shambles, the cabinets heavily battered and torn from their hinges.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS804
SOMEONE shifts his bewildered gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS805
Stepping outside, he approaches the shed and peers in with a worried gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS806
In one corner, and empty armchair faces a TV that plays a home movie of SOMEONE with one of her babies.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS807
SOMEONE notices an empty water bottle on the floor beside a broken rack rod.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS808
Looking up, he finds one of the paddleboards gone.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS809
SOMEONE hurriedly takes down the other board, ducks down, and carries it from the shed.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS810
Now he paddles over the water speedily.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS811
His board glides swiftly over the gently rolling water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS812
SOMEONE looks around anxiously and shakes water from his hair.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS813
The surrounding current shows no sign of his grieving mentor.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS814
SOMEONE gets up on his knees, bends over, and paddles both hands in synchronized strokes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS815
We peer at the seemingly endless expanse.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS816
Pausing, SOMEONE looks around helplessly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS817
The teen pants hard and swigs from his water bottle, then angrily throws down its cap.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS818
His gaze fixes on it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS819
As the current carries the plastic cap away, SOMEONE's eyes widen.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS820
SOMEONE flattens himself on his stomach and paddles in the direction of the softly rippling waves.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS821
A lone dark shape appears on the water ahead.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS822
Kneeling, SOMEONE picks up the pace and paddles with both hands in synchronized stokes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS823
Drawing near, he finds his mentor sprawled out on his board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS824
SOMEONE's board roughly bumps his on arrival.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS825
SOMEONE shifts his bewildered gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS826
His expression anguished, his mentor turns his face away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS828
SOMEONE stares at his protege appreciatively.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS829
SOMEONE offers him water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS830
SOMEONE takes it and sips.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS832
His bleary, SOMEONE twists around and looks over his shoulder.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS833
Spying hills in the hazy distance,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS834
he faces his protege with a surprised delighted smile.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS835
The youth stretches out on his stomach and heads for the distant shore.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS836
His mentor follows closely.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS837
Now, pebbles dot a sandy beach nestled at the base of rocky hills.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS838
Rustic houses and a patio decorated with colorful fishing buoys form a barrier around the secluded spot.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS839
Our view drifts past the two paddleboards to find SOMEONE and SOMEONE sitting side by side, enjoying their accomplishment.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS841
Now in his room, SOMEONE uses a blue marker to fill the remaining empty space in the miles bar on his poster of training goals.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS842
Going to the kitchen, he finds SOMEONE making breakfast.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS843
He pauses at her tidy appearance.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS844
She gestures to the table.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS845
A colorfully wrapped present sits by a place setting.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS846
SOMEONE holds out cash.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS847
SOMEONE takes the money uneasily.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS848
SOMEONE strides back to the stove and resumes cooking.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS849
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS850
Grinning proudly, SOMEONE pours orange juice.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS851
Yielding a smile, the teen goes to the table and sits.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS852
His beaming mother looks on as she scoops scrambled eggs from a pan.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS853
Tearing off the wrapping paper, SOMEONE reveals a weather radio.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS854
SOMEONE takes it from its box with a stunned gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS855
She brings him breakfast.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS856
SOMEONE regards his smiling mother appreciatively.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS857
He gets up from his seat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS859
He kneels close to hers, and gives her an emotional hug.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS861
Her brow furrowed, SOMEONE holds him tight.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS862
The teen blinks back tears.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS863
Now beneath a stormy sky, slate hued waves roil and churn along the coast,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS864
crashing violently into its rocks.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS865
At the swimming pool, rain pelts the concrete patio.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS867
At a nine foot depth marker, a bubble erupts at the surface.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS869
Kneeling underwater, SOMEONE holds up a single finger.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS870
An occasional air bubble slips between his lips
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS871
but he maintains a serene expression.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS872
He curls in his finger, surfaces and checks his watch.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS873
Its timer reads four minutes and five seconds.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS875
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter a shop.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS876
A square faced man greets them.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS877
He leads them down a corridor.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS878
Following them, SOMEONE steps into a room with a gorgeously painted long board at its center.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS880
The teen stares at it with an overwhelmed gaze then ventures closer.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS881
Peering at the green tipped board, he glides a hand over its lemon yellow body, appreciating the curves of its design.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS883
His hand trails toward the front where the yellow hue blends into a deep red, resembling a sunset.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS884
SOMEONE clasps SOMEONE's hand.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS885
Now, a wetsuit-clad figure treads churning water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS886
Above the surface, a green wave crashes powerfully.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS887
Silhouetted against the blue sky, SOMEONE and his three surfing buddies gaze out at the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS888
The swimming figure surfaces at the foot of a wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS889
As SOMEONE smiles proudly, SOMEONE allows one wave after another to crash down on him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS890
Beside the mentor, a friend of his with weathered features peers through narrowed eyes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS891
Out in the water, SOMEONE submerges himself in a wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS892
Squinting in the sun, his shortest friend wears a knit cap.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS893
As a giant wave rolls over the teen, a surfing buddy with longer hair faces SOMEONE solemnly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS894
Now, SOMEONE listens to his weather radio at work.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS895
SOMEONE switches off his radio and leaves the deserted after-hours kitchen.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS896
Unlocking the front door, he lets SOMEONE inside.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS898
She steps in past him, halts, then lowers the hood of her raincoat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS899
She wears a troubled gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS900
Turning away, she sinks down to the floor.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS901
she sinks down to the floor and leans her back against a booth seat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS902
SOMEONE joins her on the floor.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS903
SOMEONE gives a sad smile.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS904
SOMEONE stares breathlessly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS906
He stares at her imploringly but find her gaze confused.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS907
SOMEONE leans in close.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS909
SOMEONE follows his example.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS910
Their lips meet in a tender kiss.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS913
As they part, She then kisses him again.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS914
Now, a wave several stories tall fills our view as it continues to gather mass.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS915
It curls into a barrel as it breaks and sends up massive blasts of foam and spray.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS916
The sea churns violently in its wake.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS917
Now, SOMEONE's surfing gear lies neatly on his bed.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS918
The teen takes in his inventory with deep nervous breaths.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS919
His gaze lifts to his drawing of a giant tentacle dragging a man down into the sea.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS920
SOMEONE's eyes dart toward his cigar box.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS921
Crossing the room, he flips open the lid and dumps out its contents.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS922
Plucking out the envelope, he rips it open and reads the letter within.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS923
His jaw muscles tense as he peruses his father's words.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS924
The teen lifts his disillusioned gaze and swallows.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS925
Now, SOMEONE types out, "Dear Frosty."
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS927
He pauses thoughtfully then proceeds with a resolute glare.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS928
Now, from overhead, we follow a giant wave as it rolls along the water toward the bluffs.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS929
Camped out on his couch, SOMEONE rushes to the phone and answers it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS930
SOMEONE steps out, wrapping herself in a sweater.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS931
Ending the call, he notices her nervous gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS932
She musters a smile.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS934
she gives an encouraging nod.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS935
Now, SOMEONE's van travels up the ocean side highway.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS936
He shows SOMEONE a surfing magazine exposing the existence of Mavericks.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS937
In the back. SOMEONE naps against SOMEONE's shoulder.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS938
His face pale, SOMEONE pants and blinks queasily.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS939
As the van pulls over on the shoulder, SOMEONE rushes out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS940
Now, the sun shines brightly on a slate blue sea rolling beyond the meteorological complex.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS941
A wave the size of a large house curls into a barrel, filling our view with its snow-white foam.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS942
From a makeshift parking area, countless surfers and spectators make their way toward the beach.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS943
Taking his new surfboard down from the van's roof, SOMEONE pauses at the sight of Blond approaching.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS944
Behind him, SOMEONE bundles up his beaming daughter as SOMEONE looks on.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS945
Blond taps a buddy on the arm.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS946
Blond extends his fist and SOMEONE gives it a friendly bump.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS947
Smiling at him, Blond moves on.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS948
A white pickup arrives, its bed loaded with rowdy young surfers.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS949
Standing with a friend,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS950
SOMEONE observes them gravely.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS951
His friend nods.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS952
The two men return to the side of the van where SOMEONE prepares his wetsuit.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS953
SOMEONE's buddy pats SOMEONE's shoulder and heads out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS954
SOMEONE nods understandingly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS955
Now, massive waves roll in tiers toward the shore. A breaking wave sends up a giant blast of foam and spray.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS956
Hiking down with his loved ones, SOMEONE holds SOMEONE's hand.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS957
A monstrous wave curls into a barrel big enough to hold a bus.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS958
Now, in his wetsuit, SOMEONE waxes his board on the beach.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS959
He pauses, staring out at the intimidating surf.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS960
SOMEONE arrives and kneels down beside him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS961
SOMEONE takes in the roiling foamy waters crashing the bone yard then faces SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS962
Taking in his resolute expression, SOMEONE backs off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS963
SOMEONE's doubtful friend stands close to the water's edge.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS965
Glancing at SOMEONE, he pulls up his scalp fitted hood.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS966
SOMEONE arrives at SOMEONE's side and crouches.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS967
Nearby, SOMEONE's three buddies paddle out into the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS968
Staying by SOMEONE's side, SOMEONE lowers his emotional gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS969
SOMEONE takes this in, then turns his gaze out toward the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS971
His eyes glistening tearfully, SOMEONE pats the youth and stands.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS972
Reaching into his supply bag, SOMEONE produces a letter.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS973
He gives it to his mentor then takes up his board and marches off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS974
SOMEONE watches emotionally.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS975
Adjusting his hood, SOMEONE steps into the surf with the board under his arm.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS976
SOMEONE walks up beside SOMEONE as the watch SOMEONE paddle out, one foot in the air.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS977
SOMEONE throws his arm around her.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS978
The grey undulating ocean gathers itself up and rolls beneath SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS979
Further out, SOMEONE's three surfing buddies disappear over the top of a cresting 15-foot wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS980
SOMEONE follows, paddling up the wall of water and over the lip just seconds before it breaks.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS981
The veteran surfers look back, give him a respectful nod, and they paddle on together as a foursome.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS982
Up ahead, a blue boat and a smaller fishing boat lurch through the sea spray.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS983
Motorized rafts race past them at full bore.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS984
SOMEONE steps out of the cabin of the blue boat wearing a wetsuit.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS985
He and his friends peer over the rail to see SOMEONE paddling by.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS986
As he pounds on the cabin, a veteran surfer shakes his head.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS989
High on the bluffs with SOMEONE by his side, SOMEONE raises a pair of binoculars to his eyes. He watches as the blue boat lurches up and over a cresting 15 footer.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS990
SOMEONE's friends pitch their boards into the water and dive in.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS991
Another surfer hops out of a raft.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS992
They all paddle out to join about two dozen surfers sitting on their boards.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS993
As the water swells, one of the surfers drops down the face of a glossy 25-foot wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS994
It quickly curls over him and he vanishes in the barrel.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS996
On the bluffs, SOMEONE shades her eyes as she watches.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS997
SOMEONE sets his jaw.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS998
SOMEONE wanders over to his side.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS999
SOMEONE peers through the binoculars. He watches as another surfer loses his balance halfway down the face of a 20-foot wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1000
He falls off his board and vanishes in the crushing break.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1001
SOMEONE watches as he paddles out.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1002
Now, two surfers drop in, dangerously close to one another.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1003
One stumbles over sideways, soon both are lost in a white thundering plume of water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1005
SOMEONE pushes up on the next swell.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1006
But at the last moment, he sits back on his board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1007
SOMEONE, with a concerned look, watches the next wave curl over a group of surfers as they paddle up its face.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1008
It breaks too fast.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1009
The surfers call to one another as they beat a path to the right.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1010
Now, the waves break one right after another.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1011
A nasty 30-foot wave curls over onto itself.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1012
The blue boat floats dangerously close to the impact zone.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1013
The captain barks into his radio.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1014
The raft riders power up over the lip, bouncing back down roughly.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1015
SOMEONE and the veterans perform turtle rolls, flipping their boards on top of them and punching through safely to the other side.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1016
As the 30 foot monster starts to break, the group paddles up and over it in the SOMEONE of time.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1017
Through his binoculars, SOMEONE watches a handful of surfers being rolled up into the wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1018
SOMEONE draws a sharp breath.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1019
SOMEONE frowns.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1020
The blue boat groans up a wave at a 30-degree angle, pitching port side.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1021
It makes it over, nearly capsizing as it slams down behind the fishing boat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1022
A rider bounces out of his raft.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1023
An unmanned surfboard slaps against the back of a swell.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1024
The foursome hurls themselves up and over a 25-footer through a fog of sea spray.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1025
SOMEONE paddles at a steady pace, breathing out through his mouth.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1026
He eyes a building swell and sits up on his board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1027
He glances behind him, first to the bluffs, then to the weather station.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1028
He sizes up the wave one more time
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1029
then turns around and paddles, preparing to catch this one.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1030
The veterans look over their shoulders and press ahead.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1031
SOMEONE shields her eyes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1032
SOMEONE raises his binoculars to see SOMEONE arrowing down the face of a cresting wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1033
His mouth hangs open.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1034
On a fishing boat, a white haired photographer with a battered baseball cap aims his lens.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1035
SOMEONE shifts her weight, lips parted.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1036
SOMEONE pops up.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1037
With the board jutting out perpendicular over the wave, SOMEONE takes a wide stance.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1038
The camera captures his image.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1039
The board goes vertical.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1040
The photographer lowers his camera to see the board tumble backwards behind the wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1041
SOMEONE clutches SOMEONE's arm as they watch the surf explode like a volcano.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1042
It sends clouds of foam high into the air.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1043
With a grave look, one of SOMEONE's buddies sits up.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1044
The others look back to see receding break fling SOMEONE's tiny surfboard up and swallow it.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1045
SOMEONE breathes hard, watching in anguish.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1046
SOMEONE takes a step forward, his eyes locked on the surf.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1047
Under water, SOMEONE flails his arms against the turbulence.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1048
His ankle strap yanks him upside down.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1049
SOMEONE looks through his binoculars and spots his board sticking straight up out of the turmoil.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1050
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE in terror.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1051
SOMEONE twists under water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1052
Another monster wave thunders down.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1053
The undertow churns likes a storm cloud.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1054
As the breaking wave rushes over SOMEONE's board, his ankle strap comes off.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1055
The board pops up into the air and twirls over the waves untethered.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1056
SOMEONE gasps.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1057
SOMEONE lowers his binoculars.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1058
The veterans watch the white water ram into the treacherous rocks of the bone yard.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1059
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a pleading look.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1060
On his hand, one finger uncurls around the barrel of the binoculars.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1061
Slowly, a second finger uncurls.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1062
The fishing boat makes it way over to the board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1063
SOMEONE soberly wipes his mouth and chin.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1064
SOMEONE scans the bone yard but sees no sign of SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1065
He lowers his binoculars.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1066
The fishing boat hauls his board on deck.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1067
SOMEONE uncurls a third finger.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1068
An aerial of the bone yard reveals nothing but roiling white foam.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1069
SOMEONE sighs, dropping his head.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1071
SOMEONE looks from SOMEONE to the surf.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1072
SOMEONE emerges from the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1073
She points to the tiny head and shoulders just before they disappear again in an oncoming surge.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1074
SOMEONE wears a proud look.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1075
SOMEONE pops out again, tears off his hood and loosens his collar.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1076
With her hand concealing a relieved smile, SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1077
SOMEONE swims over to the fishing boat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1078
The photographer reaches down from the stern.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1079
The photographer smiles, then turns.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1080
A deck hand brings the board and the photographer hands it down to SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1081
The photographer nods.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1082
SOMEONE lies down on his board and paddles away.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1083
SOMEONE squints from the bluffs.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1084
SOMEONE makes his way over another swell.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1085
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1086
A grin pulls at the corner of his mouth.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1087
SOMEONE paddles by the blue boat as it takes in a broken board.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1088
Exhausted surfers haul themselves into rafts.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1089
Another casualty pads along the shore,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1090
the two halves of his board under his arm.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1091
Only a handful of surfers remain in the water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1092
Sitting on his board, SOMEONE turns as SOMEONE sits up next to him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1093
They watch another crusher.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1094
SOMEONE stifles a smirk.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1095
He leans down and paddles off as SOMEONE watches with a little smile.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1096
On the bluffs, SOMEONE squints down at the envelope in his hand.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1097
As SOMEONE paddles out over the swells,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1098
he reads the typewritten letter.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1099
He looks up to see SOMEONE rejoin his surfing buddies.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1100
He sits on his board, adjusting his hood.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1102
The foursome look patiently out to sea where another swell begins to build.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1104
In slow motion, he surfs down a 30-foot wave.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1105
As he reaches the bottom, it breaks right behind him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1106
SOMEONE's face drops.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1107
The avalanche of white water catches up behind him fast.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1108
As he struggles to keep his balance, it overtakes him and he disappears again.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1109
SOMEONE and SOMEONE take deep breaths.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1110
The surfers aboard the blue boat stand watch.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1111
The photographer frowns.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1112
A veteran surfer's mouth hangs open.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1113
Suddenly, SOMEONE emerges, still surfing, from the cloud of spray.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1114
Up on the bluff, onlookers cheer and clap.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1115
SOMEONE breaks into a smile and throws his arm around the beaming SOMEONE.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1116
SOMEONE swerves right and shoots through the hollow, letting the wave curl over him.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1117
SOMEONE stands on the deck of the boat, griping the rail and watching.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1118
SOMEONE comes out of the barrel near the bone yard and speeds toward shore, the froth nipping at his heels.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1119
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE the letter and leaves.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1120
As SOMEONE slows down, he turns to see the veterans sitting on their boards smiling.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1121
One lifts his hands and claps.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1123
With a grin, SOMEONE heads into shore.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1124
SOMEONE clutches her throat.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1125
SOMEONE walks into the surf to meet SOMEONE and they throw their arms around each other.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1126
Now, a magazine cover features the photo of his wipe out at Mavericks.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1127
A photo shows SOMEONE and SOMEONE together.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1129
Now, a man free dives in turquoise sun-streaked water
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1130
wearing only fins and board shorts.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1131
He turns around and looks up at the surface.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1133
Bubbles float from his nostrils
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1134
and three fingers curl into his palm.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1135
SOMEONE curls another finger into his palm, leaving only his thumb up.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1136
Now, SOMEONE stands on the beach,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1137
a knit black cap on his head.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1138
He stares at the surf with his hands in his pockets.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1139
He lifts his hand to the back of his neck
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1140
and gives it a squeeze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1141
He turns to see SOMEONE looking up at him with pain in her eyes.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1142
Her lips part.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1143
He blinks pensively.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1146
Words appear. Seven years after his historic ride, SOMEONE drowned while free diving in the Maldives. He was 22 years old.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1149
Now, SOMEONE sits on a surfboard, a white lei around his neck.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1150
He scoops his hands through the water and throws it in the air.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1151
Beside him, SOMEONE watches with a pained expression.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1153
SOMEONE looks on with a mournful gaze.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1154
Dozens of surfers around them toss up water.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1155
SOMEONE joins in.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1156
Everyone, floating on surfboards and wearing leis,
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1157
splashes water into the air.
CHASING_MAVERICKS_DVS1158
An aerial view shows their multi-colored surfboards in a circle.