Our view crests an overcrowded hillside slum with narrow stairways leading upwards between the dilapidated buildings.
COLOMBIANA_DVS50
To black. Words appear. Colombia, 1992.
COLOMBIANA_DVS53
Armed guards patrol the courtyard of a tropical mansion.
COLOMBIANA_DVS54
On a covered patio, a man with thick dark hair and a beard sits across a small table from a younger stubble faced man.
COLOMBIANA_DVS55
SOMEONE clutches SOMEONE's hand between his.
COLOMBIANA_DVS56
He places his free hand on his mentor.
COLOMBIANA_DVS57
He hands SOMEONE a glass.
COLOMBIANA_DVS58
The younger man lifts his drink.
COLOMBIANA_DVS59
They tap glasses.
COLOMBIANA_DVS60
With their weary eyes fixed on each other, they both take a sip.
COLOMBIANA_DVS61
He reaches into his pocket.
COLOMBIANA_DVS62
He hands over a small stack of floppy disks.
COLOMBIANA_DVS63
SOMEONE rises and spreads his arms. SOMEONE embraces him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS64
He returns to his seat.
COLOMBIANA_DVS65
A bearded man with shoulder length hair pats SOMEONE on the back.
COLOMBIANA_DVS66
SOMEONE sips his drink as he watches his friend leave.
COLOMBIANA_DVS67
Meanwhile, SOMEONE hurries to a car guarded by armed men.
COLOMBIANA_DVS68
One opens a door for him. Inside, he bangs his hand on the dashboard.
COLOMBIANA_DVS69
The car speeds off.
COLOMBIANA_DVS70
Two of SOMEONE's men sit in the back seat with rifles ready.
COLOMBIANA_DVS71
Bobbing down a narrow street with a ridged surface, the vehicle halts beside a multi-story home at the top of a hill.
COLOMBIANA_DVS72
SOMEONE and his guards get out.
COLOMBIANA_DVS73
The stubble faced man looks out on the city,
COLOMBIANA_DVS74
his thoughtful gaze sweeping over the clustered buildings before him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS75
Turning away, he heads toward the home.
COLOMBIANA_DVS76
The armed bodyguards follow him closely.
COLOMBIANA_DVS78
a woman serves milk to a young girl sucking a lollipop.
COLOMBIANA_DVS79
SOMEONE's mother leaves her at the kitchen table.
COLOMBIANA_DVS80
SOMEONE turns over a framed family photo, removes a computer chip from under a piece of tape, then opens a drawer and rifles through it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS81
He pulls out a business card.
COLOMBIANA_DVS82
He kneels in front of her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS83
He shows the chip.
COLOMBIANA_DVS84
He tucks it into her pocket.
COLOMBIANA_DVS85
He scribbles a Chicago address on a piece of paper, folds it, and tucks it into her jumper.
COLOMBIANA_DVS86
He takes off a necklace with a flower pendant.
COLOMBIANA_DVS87
He puts it on his daughter.
COLOMBIANA_DVS88
Releasing her hand, he draws her in and kisses her brow. They hug.
COLOMBIANA_DVS89
He closes his eyes as he clutches his daughter, then opens them with a fearful look.
COLOMBIANA_DVS90
Outside, a beat up sedan stops in front of the building.
COLOMBIANA_DVS91
One of SOMEONE's men peers in.
COLOMBIANA_DVS92
SOMEONE watches from a window.
COLOMBIANA_DVS93
Toting a suitcase, his wife ushers SOMEONE into the next room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS94
Moving past them, SOMEONE opens a back door. He stops as he sees another car approaching.
COLOMBIANA_DVS95
The family hurries back into the kitchen. SOMEONE looks out a window at the sedan below. The beefy man in the passenger seat uses a radio.
COLOMBIANA_DVS97
as his wife rushes into the next room, SOMEONE takes his daughter's hands and drops to one knee.
COLOMBIANA_DVS98
He kisses her hands then pats her cheek.
COLOMBIANA_DVS99
The beefy thug shoots at the bodyguards.
COLOMBIANA_DVS100
Their bodies convulse as bullets tear into them.
COLOMBIANA_DVS101
Inside, SOMEONE removes a hand gun from a magnetic strip on the underside of the kitchen table.
COLOMBIANA_DVS102
A knife rests on another strip beside it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS103
As he guides his daughter to sit back down at the table, his wife returns with two more guns.
COLOMBIANA_DVS104
She kneels in front of her daughter. Outside, SOMEONE's men exit the sedan.
COLOMBIANA_DVS105
SOMEONE pulls his wife away, leaving SOMEONE alone at the table.
COLOMBIANA_DVS106
The gunmen charge into the building.
COLOMBIANA_DVS107
SOMEONE leads Alicia to the staircase, firing a shotgun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS108
SOMEONE sees her mother racing back up the stairs. Just as Alicia reaches the doorway, two bullets tear through her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS109
Her eyes squeeze shut in agony.
COLOMBIANA_DVS110
More shots riddle her body.
COLOMBIANA_DVS111
With her anguished gaze fixed on her daughter,
COLOMBIANA_DVS112
she slumps to the floor.
COLOMBIANA_DVS113
SOMEONE watches with a creased brow, a hint of tears glistening in her wide eyes. SOMEONE retreats up the stairs, still firing his shotgun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS114
Bullets hit his chest sending bursts of blood from his back as they tear through him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS115
SOMEONE flinches slightly at the gun shots.
COLOMBIANA_DVS116
Tears continue to well up in her eyes as she watches her father in the doorway.
COLOMBIANA_DVS117
He turns away from the stairs and drops to his knees.
COLOMBIANA_DVS118
Raising his helpless gaze to his daughter,
COLOMBIANA_DVS119
he lifts a trembling hand toward his face, then drops to the floor beside his dying wife.
COLOMBIANA_DVS120
As Alicia falls still, SOMEONE rolls onto his back and shuts his eyes.
COLOMBIANA_DVS121
From the kitchen table, SOMEONE stares at her dead parents, her body trembling slightly.
COLOMBIANA_DVS122
Through the open door, she sees the beefy thug ascend the staircase.
COLOMBIANA_DVS123
He steps into the kitchen with his gun raised.
COLOMBIANA_DVS124
Another thug enters with SOMEONE behind him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS125
As the gunmen search the place tearing up couch cushions, the bearded gangster removes his sunglasses and crouches over his dead enemy.
COLOMBIANA_DVS126
He shifts his gaze to SOMEONE who continues to stare straight ahead with a stoic expression.
COLOMBIANA_DVS127
As SOMEONE inspects the framed family photo, the beefy thug points his gun at the girl's head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS128
SOMEONE sits across from SOMEONE and folds his arms on the table, then eyes the beefy gunman.
COLOMBIANA_DVS129
Under the bearded gangster's haughty gaze, the thug lowers his gun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS130
He strides off.
COLOMBIANA_DVS131
She shakes her head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS132
He spots her necklace.
COLOMBIANA_DVS134
She nods.
COLOMBIANA_DVS135
He pinches his fingers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS136
SOMEONE glances down then nods.
COLOMBIANA_DVS137
SOMEONE extends his hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS138
SOMEONE grabs the hidden knife and stabs his hand to the table.
COLOMBIANA_DVS139
Racing into a bathroom, she slides open a window, pulls herself out and drops onto a ledge.
COLOMBIANA_DVS140
SOMEONE yanks the knife out of his hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS141
Lowering herself to another ledge, she uses the top one for cover as a bald gunman shoots down at her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS142
She swallows the computer chip. SOMEONE grabs the gunman.
COLOMBIANA_DVS143
As SOMEONE swings down to a corner ledge, a brawny gunman climbs out a window after her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS144
She drops onto the roof of a parked car.
COLOMBIANA_DVS145
The gunman follows her as she races across the street and enters a building.
COLOMBIANA_DVS146
A guy on a Honda motorcycle halts in front of SOMEONE's home.
COLOMBIANA_DVS147
The motorcyclist takes off down the hill.
COLOMBIANA_DVS148
SOMEONE sprints through an apartment then exits onto a balcony.
COLOMBIANA_DVS149
As she acrobatically makes her way down to a terrace, the brawny gunman spots her from the rooftop.
COLOMBIANA_DVS150
He leaps down after her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS151
Two others join him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS152
Meanwhile, SOMEONE and some men take off in an SUV
COLOMBIANA_DVS153
while another group gives chase in the sedan.
COLOMBIANA_DVS154
Scrambling over a low wall, SOMEONE smashes through a wood plank roof and lands on a table. She races past an elderly man in a garden.
COLOMBIANA_DVS155
Behind her, a gunman smashes through a different part of the roof.
COLOMBIANA_DVS156
In a courtyard, SOMEONE weaves around sheets hanging on clotheslines
COLOMBIANA_DVS157
then passes a row of women doing laundry in plastic tubs.
COLOMBIANA_DVS158
As SOMEONE's men burst in after her, she races down a balcony.
COLOMBIANA_DVS159
She climbs through an open window into a man's apartment.
COLOMBIANA_DVS160
She runs off. Following her, a gunman rushes past the angry resident.
COLOMBIANA_DVS161
Outside, SOMEONE glances over her shoulder.
COLOMBIANA_DVS162
SOMEONE hurries down a flight of stairs into an alley.
COLOMBIANA_DVS163
The gunman follows.
COLOMBIANA_DVS164
As SOMEONE emerges on a sidewalk, she spots the motorcyclist approaching and takes off down a stone staircase.
COLOMBIANA_DVS165
The biker gives chase with two gunmen running behind him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS166
Turning a corner into a covered marketplace, SOMEONE sprints past an arcade and various vendors. She leaps over a man crouching on the ground and he glances after her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS167
The motorcyclist closes in.
COLOMBIANA_DVS168
SOMEONE turns a sharp corner around a display of bowls holding chili peppers. The biker crashes into it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS169
The colorful chili peppers fly into the air.
COLOMBIANA_DVS170
Now our view soars over the city.
COLOMBIANA_DVS171
SOMEONE runs down a long staircase between the crowded tiers of rundown homes.
COLOMBIANA_DVS172
As some of his gunmen give chase, SOMEONE talks into his radio.
COLOMBIANA_DVS173
SOMEONE dashes down the stairs with the three gunmen close behind.
COLOMBIANA_DVS174
Rounding a corner, she navigates a labyrinth of alleyways. As she nears the end of one alley, her gaze falls on a metal fire escape ladder against the side of an apartment building.
COLOMBIANA_DVS175
Stepping onto a stack of wooden crates, she grabs the first rung.
COLOMBIANA_DVS176
She climbs up as the beefy thug arrives in the alley.
COLOMBIANA_DVS177
He spots her feet disappearing over the rooftop's edge.
COLOMBIANA_DVS178
Meanwhile, the acrobatic brawny gunman leaps from a stack of crates onto another roof.
COLOMBIANA_DVS179
He and two others search the vacant area.
COLOMBIANA_DVS180
Returning to the ground, he looks down a staircase and sees the beefy thug peering around the corner of a building.
COLOMBIANA_DVS181
The thug gestures and his acrobatic cohort climbs back onto the roof.
COLOMBIANA_DVS182
The gunmen leap from building to building, searching the surrounding area. The acrobatic man peers down into an alley where the beefy thug barks an order into his radio.
COLOMBIANA_DVS183
The gunmen return to the alley.
COLOMBIANA_DVS185
A view down a chimney shows SOMEONE huddled at the bottom, rocking slightly with her hand clapped over her mouth.
COLOMBIANA_DVS186
Now she emerges from an alley onto a quiet road.
COLOMBIANA_DVS187
As she casually strolls along, the sedan full of gunmen turns a corner and rolls up behind her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS188
Noticing it, she breaks into a run.
COLOMBIANA_DVS189
The SUV with SOMEONE inside approaches from the opposite end of the road.
COLOMBIANA_DVS190
He aims a gun out his window.
COLOMBIANA_DVS191
They cut her off.
COLOMBIANA_DVS192
Finding herself boxed in, she slides down a storm drain opening and disappears.
COLOMBIANA_DVS193
The thugs peer after her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS194
SOMEONE shoots his handgun into the storm drain opening.
COLOMBIANA_DVS195
The others follow suit with their automatics.
COLOMBIANA_DVS196
Dust billows into the air from their flying bullets. The motorcyclist and the three guys on foot join the group and peer at the storm drain.
COLOMBIANA_DVS197
Meanwhile, a manhole cover rises from the middle of a street.
COLOMBIANA_DVS198
Sliding it aside, SOMEONE lifts her face to the bright sunlight and squints.
COLOMBIANA_DVS199
She rubs her eyes then glances around and climbs out of the hole.
COLOMBIANA_DVS200
Cars and pedestrians take little notice as they bustle past the dirty faced girl in her sullied school uniform.
COLOMBIANA_DVS201
Later, she reaches a building surrounded by a tall wrought iron fence.
COLOMBIANA_DVS202
Armed soldiers stand posted at its gate.
COLOMBIANA_DVS203
Consulting the business card from her father,
COLOMBIANA_DVS204
the dazed girl walks toward one of the security guards.
COLOMBIANA_DVS205
She offers the card.
COLOMBIANA_DVS207
Now inside, a man reads a name on it - John C. Davies, Embassy of the United States of America. He gazes at SOMEONE who sits in front of his desk.
COLOMBIANA_DVS208
As SOMEONE averts her gaze, the American leans closer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS209
She lifts her eyes to his then glances at an older man at a desk nearby.
COLOMBIANA_DVS210
Taking a deep breath, she sticks a finger down her throat.
COLOMBIANA_DVS211
He recoils as she barfs on his desk.
COLOMBIANA_DVS212
Wiping her mouth, she settles back into her seat and uses one finger to poke around the vomit.
COLOMBIANA_DVS213
She finds the computer chip and holds it out.
COLOMBIANA_DVS214
He grabs a tissue.
COLOMBIANA_DVS215
Grimacing, he uses it to take the chip.
COLOMBIANA_DVS216
His older colleague watches in disbelief as he cleans it off and places it in a disk which he then inserts into his computer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS217
He types a command and information scrolls up the screen.
COLOMBIANA_DVS218
His mouth hanging agape, he shifts his astonished gaze to SOMEONE.
COLOMBIANA_DVS219
Two subordinates leave.
COLOMBIANA_DVS220
His older colleague hits a button on his desk which activates a camera.
COLOMBIANA_DVS221
He glances at his computer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS222
She eyes him steadily.
COLOMBIANA_DVS223
Now we flight toward Acosta City's jutting skyscraper.
COLOMBIANA_DVS224
On a government jet, a woman sits with SOMEONE.
COLOMBIANA_DVS225
On the ground, the jet slows as it taxis on a tarmac.
COLOMBIANA_DVS226
Later, SOMEONE and her escort stride down a jet way.
COLOMBIANA_DVS228
Now a man's hand stamps a passport.
COLOMBIANA_DVS229
SOMEONE and her escort sit in front of his desk.
COLOMBIANA_DVS230
The bureaucrat sets a short stack of cash in front of the girl.
COLOMBIANA_DVS231
With a frown, she grabs the passport and money.
COLOMBIANA_DVS232
Now a security guard leads her and her escort down a corridor.
COLOMBIANA_DVS233
As they pass a restroom, SOMEONE tugs on the woman's wrist.
COLOMBIANA_DVS234
Entering the bathroom, SOMEONE strides to the last stall
COLOMBIANA_DVS235
which sits beside a row of windows at her eye level.
COLOMBIANA_DVS236
She steps inside and pulls the door shut.
COLOMBIANA_DVS237
In the corridor, her escort checks her watch then peers inside the restroom.
COLOMBIANA_DVS238
Finding the door to the last stall closed, she walks over.
COLOMBIANA_DVS239
She opens it and finds it empty.
COLOMBIANA_DVS240
A window lies ajar.
COLOMBIANA_DVS241
The woman hurries off past the security guard.
COLOMBIANA_DVS242
Now SOMEONE stands at a ticket kiosk in a bus station.
COLOMBIANA_DVS243
She hands him the address written out by her father.
COLOMBIANA_DVS244
She holds up her wad of cash.
COLOMBIANA_DVS245
Now hazy sunlight glimmers off the mirrored panels of Chicago's skyscrapers as we move over the downtown area.
COLOMBIANA_DVS246
A Trailways bus crosses a bridge and a bird's eye view follows it up a street.
COLOMBIANA_DVS247
Inside, SOMEONE rests her arm against a window and stares out at the passing city.
COLOMBIANA_DVS248
Later, she enters Union Station's great hall and sweeps her gaze around the high ceilinged atrium.
COLOMBIANA_DVS249
She timidly strides between two columns of benches shooting furtive glances at the other commuter.
COLOMBIANA_DVS251
SOMEONE reads a comic book as she waits on a platform for an approaching L train.
COLOMBIANA_DVS252
Its doors open.
COLOMBIANA_DVS253
SOMEONE climbs on and takes a seat.
COLOMBIANA_DVS254
She peers out her window then lowers her gaze to her Zena Warrior Princess comic.
COLOMBIANA_DVS255
Later, SOMEONE walks a dimly lit alleyway
COLOMBIANA_DVS256
where shady looking men talk along its edges.
COLOMBIANA_DVS257
She hands the man her scrap of paper with the address.
COLOMBIANA_DVS258
He reads it then meets her gaze.
COLOMBIANA_DVS259
Now he slams his hand against a shabby building's door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS260
It opens and he steps inside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS261
SOMEONE sits waiting at a low window sill.
COLOMBIANA_DVS262
The man steps into a dingy room where a tall dark haired figure punches a guy sitting in a chair.
COLOMBIANA_DVS263
SOMEONE pats his victim's bald head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS264
Another punch sends thick streams of his blood flying.
COLOMBIANA_DVS265
SOMEONE wipes sweat from his face.
COLOMBIANA_DVS266
SOMEONE winds up for another blow.
COLOMBIANA_DVS267
His fist stops mid punch and his brow furrows.
COLOMBIANA_DVS268
He shoots his lackey a stunned look.
COLOMBIANA_DVS269
Now SOMEONE's associate leads SOMEONE into a small waiting area within a network of offices.
COLOMBIANA_DVS270
As two women leave one of them, she watches them go with a solemn curious gaze.
COLOMBIANA_DVS271
A tall shadowy figure arrives on the other side of her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS272
Turning, she finds SOMEONE staring at her through a set of windows.
COLOMBIANA_DVS273
As he strides around a corner, she watches him through the windows.
COLOMBIANA_DVS274
SOMEONE arrives before her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS275
As he drops to his knees and embraces her, she allows herself to cry.
COLOMBIANA_DVS276
Large tears stream down the little girl's cheeks.
COLOMBIANA_DVS277
Holding her close, SOMEONE cradles her head in his hand as she sobs into his shoulder.
COLOMBIANA_DVS278
He eases her back to look her in the eye.
COLOMBIANA_DVS279
Cupping her face in his hands, he wipes away her tears with his thumb.
COLOMBIANA_DVS280
He kisses her forehead three times then hugs her again.
COLOMBIANA_DVS281
Now a sunbeam shines on SOMEONE's face as she sleeps.
COLOMBIANA_DVS282
Waking, she takes in her surroundings.
COLOMBIANA_DVS283
As she sits up, we notice guns hanging on the wall behind her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS284
She gets out of bed, crosses to a window, and peers outside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS285
A rising sun crests the Chicago skyline.
COLOMBIANA_DVS286
An elevated train travels along a track below.
COLOMBIANA_DVS287
Now SOMEONE shuffles to a stairway where family photos decorate the wall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS288
She touches one of her mother as she passes.
COLOMBIANA_DVS289
Later, she arrives at a kitchen and pauses, her fingers lightly drumming her thigh.
COLOMBIANA_DVS290
As SOMEONE drinks coffee at a table, an older woman spots SOMEONE.
COLOMBIANA_DVS291
She crosses to the girl and kneels before her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS292
She caresses SOMEONE's face.
COLOMBIANA_DVS293
Mama leads her to the kitchen table then returns to the stove.
COLOMBIANA_DVS294
Holding a newspaper, SOMEONE gives the girl a sidelong look.
COLOMBIANA_DVS295
As he flips pages in his newspaper, Mama serves SOMEONE food.
COLOMBIANA_DVS296
Mama pauses and faces the table gravely.
COLOMBIANA_DVS297
SOMEONE shifts his gaze and turns over his paper.
COLOMBIANA_DVS298
He turns over SOMEONE's slip of paper.
COLOMBIANA_DVS299
It bears a drawing of Zena on the back.
COLOMBIANA_DVS300
Eating her breakfast, the little girl shakes her head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS301
She looks up at her uncle with a resolute gaze.
COLOMBIANA_DVS302
SOMEONE leans back in his chair and takes a deep breath through parted lips.
COLOMBIANA_DVS303
He stares at her then affects a casual gaze.
COLOMBIANA_DVS304
His brow furrowed, he plants his hands on the table
COLOMBIANA_DVS305
and shares a brief uneasy look with his mother.
COLOMBIANA_DVS306
Now SOMEONE leads SOMEONE up the steps to a school's entrance.
COLOMBIANA_DVS307
Later in a principal's office, an elegant woman with blonde curls opens a stuffed yellow envelope.
COLOMBIANA_DVS308
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit facing her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS309
She presents a folded paper to the girl.
COLOMBIANA_DVS310
The principal stands.
COLOMBIANA_DVS311
She smiles down at the girl who coldly gets to her feet.
COLOMBIANA_DVS312
As SOMEONE leads her out, the principal sinks back down in her chair and lets out a nervous sigh. Outside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS313
Turning, he finds SOMEONE standing motionless.
COLOMBIANA_DVS314
He nods and glances around.
COLOMBIANA_DVS315
He thrusts SOMEONE's backpack at her, draws a huge handgun and opens fire on a passing car.
COLOMBIANA_DVS316
It swerves off the road and hits a fire hydrant, knocking it from it base.
COLOMBIANA_DVS317
As fearful bystanders scatter, SOMEONE angrily faces his niece.
COLOMBIANA_DVS318
He swipes off his fedora and glances coolly at his handiwork.
COLOMBIANA_DVS319
He crouches before the girl.
COLOMBIANA_DVS320
He snatches her backpack.
COLOMBIANA_DVS321
He holds out the gun and the backpack.
COLOMBIANA_DVS322
SOMEONE snatches the backpack from his grasp and slings it over her shoulder.
COLOMBIANA_DVS323
SOMEONE holsters his gun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS324
A police cruiser pulls up by the wrecked car. He straightens, takes out his fedora and beats it back into shape.
COLOMBIANA_DVS325
As he puts it back on.
COLOMBIANA_DVS326
SOMEONE turns his niece away by the shoulder.
COLOMBIANA_DVS327
Keeping his arm around her, he saunters off casually down the sidewalk.
COLOMBIANA_DVS328
Now as we peer across a sprawling suburb, words appear.
COLOMBIANA_DVS329
California, 15 years later.
COLOMBIANA_DVS330
In a parking lot, a cop brings lunch to his partner.
COLOMBIANA_DVS331
A red muscle car plows into their cruiser.
COLOMBIANA_DVS332
Its door opens and an empty vodka bottle tumbles to the pavement.
COLOMBIANA_DVS333
A slender woman in a slinky mini dress staggers out.
COLOMBIANA_DVS334
The cops accost her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS335
They bend her over her car's hood and cuff her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS336
She wears the orchid pendant.
COLOMBIANA_DVS337
Now the cops drag SOMEONE through a police station booking room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS338
She stumbles and one of her shoes slips off.
COLOMBIANA_DVS339
A portly desk sergeant looks up at her approach.
COLOMBIANA_DVS340
The cops sit her down in front of him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS341
She slumps over, her long black bangs covering her face.
COLOMBIANA_DVS342
One of the cops retrieves her shoe and hands it to the sergeant then nudges her up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS343
The sergeant looks through her purse.
COLOMBIANA_DVS344
She rests her head on the desk.
COLOMBIANA_DVS345
She tries to take some candy but he snatches it away.
COLOMBIANA_DVS346
She dry heaves.
COLOMBIANA_DVS347
As the cops haul her off, the sergeant sets her abandoned shoes on his desk.
COLOMBIANA_DVS348
Now a bus pulls up in an alley.
COLOMBIANA_DVS349
Men in US Marshall vests march into view.
COLOMBIANA_DVS350
A bald mustached SOMEONE leads a team escorting a hooded prisoner.
COLOMBIANA_DVS351
He grabs a thermos. Now at a cell.
COLOMBIANA_DVS352
A SOMEONE unhoods a hatchet faced man with wild black hair.
COLOMBIANA_DVS353
The prisoner starts to enter the cell then pauses.
COLOMBIANA_DVS354
He takes gum from his mouth and sticks it on Warren's badge.
COLOMBIANA_DVS355
The SOMEONE smiles.
COLOMBIANA_DVS356
He leaves the gum on a crossbar then shuts the door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS357
He leaves the coffee thermos with the young SOMEONE.
COLOMBIANA_DVS358
Now a heavyset female guard brings a mug with a spoon in it to a cell where SOMEONE snores on a cot.
COLOMBIANA_DVS359
The guard leaves the mug on a crossbar.
COLOMBIANA_DVS360
As she leaves, the cell block lights blink out.
COLOMBIANA_DVS361
SOMEONE promptly sits up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS362
Reaching into her shaggy black locks, she pulls out a small hairpin.
COLOMBIANA_DVS363
Next she removes her wig, gathers her real hair at the back of her head and ties it in a bun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS365
From beneath her skirt, she rolls down a pair of black leggings.
COLOMBIANA_DVS366
She stands up, peels off the dress,
COLOMBIANA_DVS367
removes her bra, and pulls up a stretchy top attached to the leggings.
COLOMBIANA_DVS368
Kneeling to the cell door, she picks the lock with her hairpin then tucks it back into her bun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS369
She stands up, slides the cell door open and eyes a surveillance camera posted in a corner.
COLOMBIANA_DVS370
In a security room, a guard reads a newspaper, ignorning several monitors set up before him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS371
Back in the cell block, SOMEONE pivots the camera.
COLOMBIANA_DVS372
At his station, the guard turns on a portable radio.
COLOMBIANA_DVS373
He sets it by a monitor showing a view of a shadowy wall, then obliviously picks up his newspaper again.
COLOMBIANA_DVS374
In the female cell block, SOMEONE takes the spoon from the mug.
COLOMBIANA_DVS375
She presses a red button on the wall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS376
She slowly opens a door, slips out and shuts it behind her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS377
Creeping stealthily down a hallway, she reaches a break area.
COLOMBIANA_DVS378
She pads across the floor to a water cooler and fills a clear plastic cup.
COLOMBIANA_DVS379
Bubbles gurgle up into the water tank.
COLOMBIANA_DVS380
SOMEONE cautiously scans her surroundings as she backs away, then faces a door labeled Electrical Room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS381
She slips in and opens a cabinet revealing circuit breakers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS382
She sets the water on top then climbs a table and opens an air duct on the ceiling.
COLOMBIANA_DVS383
Next, she returns to the cabinet and balances the spoon in the circuit breaker.
COLOMBIANA_DVS384
She bites a tiny hole in the water cup
COLOMBIANA_DVS385
then sets it above the spoon.
COLOMBIANA_DVS386
Eyeing her wristwatch, she pushes a button.
COLOMBIANA_DVS387
She shuts the cabinet,
COLOMBIANA_DVS388
climbs into the air duct, and pulls up the vent cover.
COLOMBIANA_DVS389
From a hole in the cup, a drop of water escapes.
COLOMBIANA_DVS390
It lands in the spoon which dips slightly.
COLOMBIANA_DVS391
SOMEONE crawls through the air duct as more water weighs down the spoon.
COLOMBIANA_DVS392
Reaching a grated cover, she peers down at a male prisoner asleep in his cell.
COLOMBIANA_DVS393
As she crawls on by, he wakes.
COLOMBIANA_DVS394
SOMEONE reaches a large ventilation fan and checks her watch.
COLOMBIANA_DVS395
The spoon falls and the water shorts out the fan.
COLOMBIANA_DVS396
At his desk, the sergeant looks up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS397
In the air duct, the fan slows to a stop.
COLOMBIANA_DVS398
SOMEONE lies on her back and slithers her feet between the blades.
COLOMBIANA_DVS399
Below, Doyle shuffles into the electrical room and eyes the circuit cabinet.
COLOMBIANA_DVS400
A red light glows on its door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS401
In the duct, SOMEONE slides her chest between the blades then squeezes her arms down her to side.
COLOMBIANA_DVS402
Doyle opens the cabinet as she works her shoulders through the fan.
COLOMBIANA_DVS403
He flips a reset switch.
COLOMBIANA_DVS404
SOMEONE emerges safely on the other side just as the fan whirs back to life.
COLOMBIANA_DVS405
The policeman finds the plastic cup and shakes his head at it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS406
As SOMEONE crawls onward, Doyle chucks the cup in the trash.
COLOMBIANA_DVS407
Now the intruder lowers a ceiling vent hatch and stealthily climbs out.
COLOMBIANA_DVS408
In the secure cell block, SOMEONE finds his coffee thermos empty.
COLOMBIANA_DVS409
He checks on SOMEONE.
COLOMBIANA_DVS410
Finding the prisoner asleep, he shuffles to the cell block door and pushes a button.
COLOMBIANA_DVS411
He wakes the guard in the security room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS412
He buzzes SOMEONE through.
COLOMBIANA_DVS413
Later in a men's room, the young SOMEONE sets the thermos on a sink and crosses to a urinal.
COLOMBIANA_DVS414
As he relieves himself, SOMEONE slips out of the stall and creeps up behind him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS415
She kicks him as he turns, knocking him out cold.
COLOMBIANA_DVS416
Now in the security room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS417
A monitor shows SOMEONE standing at the door to the secure cell block with his face hidden by his arshal's cap.
COLOMBIANA_DVS418
The guard buzzes him through.
COLOMBIANA_DVS419
As the door opens, the unconscious SOMEONE sinks to his knees then falls face down.
COLOMBIANA_DVS420
Crouched in the hallway, SOMEONE creeps in after him and gently pushes the door shut.
COLOMBIANA_DVS421
She takes SOMEONE's gun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS422
Checking the clip, she finds it fully loaded.
COLOMBIANA_DVS423
She stands, holding the weapon pointed at the floor, and moves to SOMEONE's cell.
COLOMBIANA_DVS424
The prisoner sleeps sprawled on the cot.
COLOMBIANA_DVS425
SOMEONE slides the door open and saunters in.
COLOMBIANA_DVS426
She leans over SOMEONE, pointing the gun at his chest.
COLOMBIANA_DVS427
Tilting her head, she nudges the barrel against his brow.
COLOMBIANA_DVS428
SOMEONE wakes with a start and sits up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS429
The hatchet faced criminal hastily opens his gaudy shirt.
COLOMBIANA_DVS430
In a corridor, SOMEONE and the desk sergeant halt in their tracks. Blood splatters the wall behind SOMEONE as he collapses.
COLOMBIANA_DVS431
SOMEONE leads the charge as cops converge on the cell block from all over the station.
COLOMBIANA_DVS432
As they enter the cell block, SOMEONE wakes with a gun in his hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS433
He notices the weapon and stares. SOMEONE takes aim at him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS434
SOMEONE surrenders the gun and his fellow marshals restrain him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS435
SOMEONE's dead body bears an orchid design drawn on his chest underneath the word traitor.
COLOMBIANA_DVS436
SOMEONE leads his men through a sweep of the station.
COLOMBIANA_DVS437
Meanwhile, SOMEONE kicks open a grated vent cover leading her outside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS438
In the alley, officers run past the prison bus. Several stories above, SOMEONE climbs out of the duct and clings to the wall. The officers hurry up a set of emergency access stairs. SOMEONE stretches her leg up to a shoulder high ledge. As she climbs, the officers arrive on the rooftop.
COLOMBIANA_DVS439
She reaches the top ledge.
COLOMBIANA_DVS440
Her feet scramble up the brick wall, propelling her over.
COLOMBIANA_DVS441
Landing in a crouch, she spots the police across the rooftop.
COLOMBIANA_DVS443
She breaks into a sprint.
COLOMBIANA_DVS444
Crossing to the roof's edge, she leaps over and grabs onto a pipe just beneath the other side.
COLOMBIANA_DVS445
Her toes touch down on a slim ledge.
COLOMBIANA_DVS446
She starts to reach up but withdraws her hand as an officer arrives above her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS447
He sweeps his flashlight over the edge.
COLOMBIANA_DVS448
Flattening herself against the wall, SOMEONE evades his detection.
COLOMBIANA_DVS449
The cop leaves and she pulls herself up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS450
Her legs accidentally sweep tiny bits of mortar off the ledge.
COLOMBIANA_DVS451
The SOMEONE lands behind two cops in an alley who turn and look up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS452
SOMEONE pulls herself into an air duct as an officer comes over.
COLOMBIANA_DVS453
Back in the women's cell block, she kicks open a ceiling vent cover and lowers herself to the floor.
COLOMBIANA_DVS454
She hurries to her cell and shuts herself in.
COLOMBIANA_DVS455
The heavyset female officer arrives with SOMEONE Warren and his men.
COLOMBIANA_DVS456
He stops at SOMEONE's cell.
COLOMBIANA_DVS457
Back in her party girl disguise, she lies curled up on her cot.
COLOMBIANA_DVS458
SOMEONE Warren turns away and faces the desk sergeant.
COLOMBIANA_DVS459
He leads the local police out of the cell block.
COLOMBIANA_DVS461
SOMEONE's eyes open and she rolls over.
COLOMBIANA_DVS462
Now a middle aged man in a dark suit squints in the sunlight as he steps off a private jet.
COLOMBIANA_DVS463
Accompanied by a small team of associates, he meets SOMEONE Warren and his men.
COLOMBIANA_DVS464
We glimpse an FBI jacket as the two teams approach a pair of waiting SUVs.
COLOMBIANA_DVS465
Now in a morgue, a body bag lies on a slab.
COLOMBIANA_DVS466
Agent SOMEONE opens it, revealing SOMEONE's chest.
COLOMBIANA_DVS467
He eyes the markings then faces a tall powerfully built colleague.
COLOMBIANA_DVS468
He glances at SOMEONE Warren who nods.
COLOMBIANA_DVS469
At the station, Doyle takes SOMEONE's fingerprints.
COLOMBIANA_DVS470
The sergeant glances past her and she turns.
COLOMBIANA_DVS472
From the security camera's point of view, SOMEONE's wig hides her face.
COLOMBIANA_DVS473
Outside, Agent SOMEONE and SOMEONE Warren exit a car.
COLOMBIANA_DVS474
Reporters and photographers swarm them as they walk upstairs to the open front door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS475
SOMEONE slips out unnoticed.
COLOMBIANA_DVS476
The station doors shut as she reaches the sidewalk and peels a rubbery substance off her right hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS477
Passing between two parked press vans,
COLOMBIANA_DVS478
she drops it on the pavement.
COLOMBIANA_DVS479
Now SOMEONE Warren watches, arms folded, as SOMEONE stands in SOMEONE's cell.
COLOMBIANA_DVS480
Facing the cop, the FBI agent aims an imaginary gun and visualizes the murdered criminal.
COLOMBIANA_DVS481
He looks up with a furrowed brow at the sizable vent cover
COLOMBIANA_DVS482
then peers down at the cot again and backs up toward the cell door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS483
He steps out of the cell and notices the surveillance camera.
COLOMBIANA_DVS484
Now a video camera captures SOMEONE entering a lobby. She discreetly brushes her hair over her face as she crosses the polished floor. Glass doors behind her show a bus parked at a curb.
COLOMBIANA_DVS485
She enters an employee locker room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS488
She opens a locker, and pulls out a purse and a travel bag.
COLOMBIANA_DVS489
Now she enters a bathroom stall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS490
She removes her wig and lets down her hair,
COLOMBIANA_DVS491
then kicks off her high heeled party girl shoes and wriggles out of the tight mini dress.
COLOMBIANA_DVS492
Later, the stall door swings open.
COLOMBIANA_DVS493
A blonde woman turns from a mirror as a now casually dressed SOMEONE emerges.
COLOMBIANA_DVS494
The assassin steps out into the hall and looks both ways.
COLOMBIANA_DVS495
She puts on a floppy knit hat then strides off.
COLOMBIANA_DVS496
At home, SOMEONE answers a cordless phone. On the other end, SOMEONE stands at a payphone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS497
She hangs up, runs to the bus, and turns in her ticket.
COLOMBIANA_DVS498
In an FBI office.
COLOMBIANA_DVS499
Now a black luxury car approaches a mansion nestled among palm trees.
COLOMBIANA_DVS500
A cigarette smolders between a bodyguard's fingers as he turns and lifts his chin.
COLOMBIANA_DVS501
The car comes to a stop.
COLOMBIANA_DVS502
A Caucasian man with chestnut hair gets out. A figure stalks toward him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS503
SOMEONE goes to SOMEONE and shows a newspaper covering SOMEONE's death.
COLOMBIANA_DVS504
SOMEONE swirls a snifter of brandy.
COLOMBIANA_DVS505
SOMEONE gestures and SOMEONE sits facing him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS506
He throws down the newspaper.
COLOMBIANA_DVS507
He stands.
COLOMBIANA_DVS508
From around a corner, SOMEONE watches him swagger out, then approaches SOMEONE.
COLOMBIANA_DVS509
His boss exhales a plume of smoke as he crosses to a railing and gazes out over his grounds.
COLOMBIANA_DVS510
SOMEONE arrives at his side and leans against a pillar.
COLOMBIANA_DVS511
In Chicago, our view soars over skyscrapers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS512
Inside Union Station, SOMEONE walks down stairs into the sunlit great hall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS513
She pauses, most of her hair tucked under a hat and her features disguised by large sunglasses pushing them up on her nose, she crosses the sunny atrium.
COLOMBIANA_DVS514
Now she enters an apartment.
COLOMBIANA_DVS515
Two walls of frosted glass make a small foyer. SOMEONE pauses cautiously.
COLOMBIANA_DVS516
then shuts the door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS518
SOMEONE goes to a table, and puts down her things.
COLOMBIANA_DVS519
She pulls off her hat then removes her flannel shirt,
COLOMBIANA_DVS520
revealing a loose fitting tank top.
COLOMBIANA_DVS521
Brushing back her long hair, she opens a brown paper bag.
COLOMBIANA_DVS522
She takes out a cup of noodles. She eats some with her hands as she crosses to a complex media console
COLOMBIANA_DVS523
where she turns on a set of security monitors.
COLOMBIANA_DVS524
Scanning the feeds, she plucks out some more noodles, tilts her head back, then drops some into her mouth.
COLOMBIANA_DVS525
She sets the cup down then claps her hands and raises her arms above her head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS526
The live young assassin swivels her hips with sensual grace as she dances her way into a living area.
COLOMBIANA_DVS527
To her right, a large square painting depicting a pink SOMEONE orchid at the center of a gold rimmed medallion stands propped against the wall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS528
She looks at it for a moment then dances away.
COLOMBIANA_DVS529
In a cage, a finch on a perch ruffles its feathers as its owner sashays across the room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS530
SOMEONE sets down a handgun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS531
Now we watch from overhead as she gets into the shower.
COLOMBIANA_DVS532
She plants her hands on the wall and bows her head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS533
Water drips from her pendant then streams down her nose, lips, and chin.
COLOMBIANA_DVS534
She briskly soaps up her flawless skin and shifts her weary gaze.
COLOMBIANA_DVS535
Later, she sucks on a lollipop
COLOMBIANA_DVS536
as she cleans her handgun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS537
She sets the weapon down and turns away, twirling the candy in her mouth.
COLOMBIANA_DVS538
At the FBI, Agent SOMEONE gives a briefing.
COLOMBIANA_DVS539
A blonde woman gets strangled in a restroom.
COLOMBIANA_DVS540
The killer electrocutes a man taking a bath.
COLOMBIANA_DVS541
The killer shoots them.
COLOMBIANA_DVS542
Agent SOMEONE sits down at his desk and plays the prison security footage.
COLOMBIANA_DVS543
A female agent distributes clipboards.
COLOMBIANA_DVS544
At night, a man with broodingly handsome features gets out of a parked car.
COLOMBIANA_DVS545
Now an elevator opens and he steps out, toting a portfolio and a sack full of canvases.
COLOMBIANA_DVS546
Arriving at a door, he takes out his keys before noticing that it's ajar.
COLOMBIANA_DVS547
He cautiously looks down the hall then steps into a dark apartment.
COLOMBIANA_DVS548
A single lamp shines on sketches taped all over the walls
COLOMBIANA_DVS549
and candles burn throughout the cluttered space.
COLOMBIANA_DVS550
The man steps further in, passing an electric fan and a jar of paintbrushes.
COLOMBIANA_DVS551
He halts and turns around to find SOMEONE watching him from a leather sofa.
COLOMBIANA_DVS552
She switches on the lights.
COLOMBIANA_DVS553
She smiles, springs up, and greets him with a hungry kiss.
COLOMBIANA_DVS554
His arms envelope her and his hands travel down her back.
COLOMBIANA_DVS555
SOMEONE abruptly ends the kiss and faces a stylized portrait of an old man.
COLOMBIANA_DVS556
SOMEONE peels off his jacket then removes her own as she resumes their embrace.
COLOMBIANA_DVS557
SOMEONE gently takes hold of her wrists.
COLOMBIANA_DVS558
Grinning, she pulls her dress off over her head to reveal her black bra and matching panties.
COLOMBIANA_DVS559
She plants a kiss on SOMEONE's lips then removes his t-shirt.
COLOMBIANA_DVS560
His tattooed arms wrap around her
COLOMBIANA_DVS561
and he lifts her up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS562
SOMEONE's legs grip his waist as he carries her to the sofa.
COLOMBIANA_DVS563
He sits with her straddling his lap.
COLOMBIANA_DVS564
She lifts her head ecstatically and tilts it side to side as the handsome artist nibbles her neck and kisses her chest.
COLOMBIANA_DVS565
Now he sleeps curled up in bed while SOMEONE lies awake at his side.
COLOMBIANA_DVS566
She gingerly sits up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS568
She puts on her bra.
COLOMBIANA_DVS569
Padding into the living area, she picks her dress up off the floor and pulls it on.
COLOMBIANA_DVS570
In bed, sunlight shines softly on SOMEONE's sleeping form.
COLOMBIANA_DVS571
He reaches an arm behind him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS572
His hand hits SOMEONE's side of the bed and finds it unoccupied.
COLOMBIANA_DVS573
Now in a humble Chicago neighborhood, SOMEONE rides a red motorcycle with chrome trim.
COLOMBIANA_DVS574
Turning, he pulls up onto a sidewalk and parks beneath an overhanging roof at a building's entrance.
COLOMBIANA_DVS575
He steps inside a laundromat through a pair of glass doors covered in newspaper.
COLOMBIANA_DVS576
He glances at a blonde woman who sits reading near a similarly blanketed window.
COLOMBIANA_DVS577
Looking around, he moves to a coin operated washing machine and starts a load.
COLOMBIANA_DVS578
He sits down.
COLOMBIANA_DVS579
SOMEONE sits beside him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS580
SOMEONE shows a magazine cover featuring a portly bald man.
COLOMBIANA_DVS581
She accepts an envelope stuffed with large bills.
COLOMBIANA_DVS582
Gathering up her bags, she pauses and turns. SOMEONE holds up a newspaper clipping.
COLOMBIANA_DVS583
An article on SOMEONE Rizzo's death shows a photo of the orchid design on his chest.
COLOMBIANA_DVS584
SOMEONE gives a weary shrug then leans forward and rests his elbows on his legs.
COLOMBIANA_DVS585
Our focus shifts to his niece as she leans forward as well.
COLOMBIANA_DVS586
SOMEONE avoids her gaze.
COLOMBIANA_DVS587
She reaches out a dainty hand and affectionately wraps it around one of his fingers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS588
Now in the FBI office, Agent SOMEONE studies a transparency of SOMEONE's drawing.
COLOMBIANA_DVS589
The office mail man notices it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS590
Agent SOMEONE sets down the transparency and types at his computer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS591
An image of the orchid appears.
COLOMBIANA_DVS592
The agent holds up the drawing and finds that it matches perfectly.
COLOMBIANA_DVS593
He types some more and turns up a map of Amazonia.
COLOMBIANA_DVS594
A message appears, "Access denied."
COLOMBIANA_DVS595
He sits back in his chair.
COLOMBIANA_DVS596
Now SOMEONE approaches two caged mastiffs.
COLOMBIANA_DVS597
She enters their fenced in area.
COLOMBIANA_DVS598
She shows a steak.
COLOMBIANA_DVS599
She places a steak in each of their bowls.
COLOMBIANA_DVS600
Stepping out from the cage, she closes the door and gives them a firm look.
COLOMBIANA_DVS601
The mastiffs rush to their bowls.
COLOMBIANA_DVS602
Nearby, a long haired mechanic works on a car. SOMEONE touches a wind chime made from tire rims as she enters the garage.
COLOMBIANA_DVS603
She kisses Pepe's cheek.
COLOMBIANA_DVS604
She opens a tall safe standing against a wall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS605
Taking out a stack of money, she fans through it
COLOMBIANA_DVS606
then examines four different passports and settles on a Mexican one.
COLOMBIANA_DVS607
Now our view glides over a mansion with a Paris styled courtyard at its center.
COLOMBIANA_DVS608
A bodyguard patrols the estate with an automatic rifle.
COLOMBIANA_DVS609
A woman in sexy lingerie reclines on top of a pool enclosed in glass panels.
COLOMBIANA_DVS610
Sharks swim in the water beneath her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS611
Lounging with two women, the SOMEONE laughs.
COLOMBIANA_DVS612
That night, four women in their underwear accompany him to a bedroom. He turns to a bodyguard.
COLOMBIANA_DVS613
SOMEONE winks and pats the guard's face, then turns to the women who pillow fight on his canopy bed.
COLOMBIANA_DVS614
He frames his crotch with his hands then hurries over and belly flops onto the bed.
COLOMBIANA_DVS615
Outside, a van pulls into the estate and stops in front of the mansion.
COLOMBIANA_DVS616
Several bodyguards get out and SOMEONE approaches them.
COLOMBIANA_DVS617
The bodyguards file into the mansion.
COLOMBIANA_DVS618
As SOMEONE supervises the men, SOMEONE rolls out from the under the van just before it pulls away.
COLOMBIANA_DVS620
The head security guard steps into the mansion and closes the door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS621
SOMEONE scurries to another entrance and creeps into a dark foyer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS622
An oblivious bodyguard stands at a window holding a handgun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS623
In the courtyard, a guard puffs on a cigarette then heads inside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS624
A view through the pool's glass panels shows a shark gliding through the pale blue water.
COLOMBIANA_DVS625
As it swims away, a hand appears under the glass.
COLOMBIANA_DVS626
Wearing a black short sleeved leotard and a utility belt, SOMEONE pulls herself along the panels.
COLOMBIANA_DVS627
Two sharks swim nearby paying little attention to the graceful intruder.
COLOMBIANA_DVS628
SOMEONE nears the opposite end of the pool and pushes up one of the thick glass panels.
COLOMBIANA_DVS629
Gripping its edge, she slides it away.
COLOMBIANA_DVS630
Her head breaks the water's surface and she peers into the courtyard.
COLOMBIANA_DVS631
Pushing herself out of the pool, she draws a gun at her hip.
COLOMBIANA_DVS632
She glances around as she screws a silencer onto its barrel.
COLOMBIANA_DVS633
With her fingers curled around the gun's handle, she hurries into the mansion.
COLOMBIANA_DVS634
In his bedroom, the portly scam artist sleeps amid his scantily clad companions.
COLOMBIANA_DVS635
SOMEONE marches quietly toward the bed, water still glistening on her slender neck.
COLOMBIANA_DVS636
She carries the gun at her side, her finger crooked around the trigger.
COLOMBIANA_DVS637
Halting a few yards from the foot of the bed, she regards the Ponzi schemer with a cold determined gaze.
COLOMBIANA_DVS638
As she aims her weapon, a blonde snuggles up to the portly man in her sleep
COLOMBIANA_DVS639
draping herself across his chest.
COLOMBIANA_DVS640
Our view arcs around SOMEONE's gun until the silencer muzzle aims right at us.
COLOMBIANA_DVS641
A bright golden flash clouds our view.
COLOMBIANA_DVS642
SOMEONE bolts upright then looks down at his bare chest.
COLOMBIANA_DVS643
He finds the words thief written in black lipstick above a drawing of the SOMEONE orchid.
COLOMBIANA_DVS644
With his brow creased worriedly, he tries to rub it off
COLOMBIANA_DVS645
then glances around and scoots off the bed.
COLOMBIANA_DVS646
In the hall, he finds a bodyguard lying on the floor with a pool of blood by his head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS647
Another guard lies dead beside him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS648
Staring cautiously, SOMEONE grabs a gun resting in one of men's hands.
COLOMBIANA_DVS649
His bare legs tremble slightly as he moves down a dark corridor past another dead bodyguard.
COLOMBIANA_DVS650
He creeps down a flight of stairs, then presses his back to a wall as he reaches the bottom.
COLOMBIANA_DVS651
Bending over another dead bodyguard, he takes his gun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS652
Armed with a pistol in each hand, he steps into the courtyard.
COLOMBIANA_DVS653
He notices a flower resting three panels away on the pool's glass.
COLOMBIANA_DVS654
His nervous eyes scan the area as he walks across the pool.
COLOMBIANA_DVS655
Stopping in front of the SOMEONE orchid, he picks it up and squints as he examines it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS656
He lifts the flower to his nose, closes his eyes, and takes a sniff.
COLOMBIANA_DVS657
Opening his eyes, he smirks as he lifts his face from the flower.
COLOMBIANA_DVS658
SOMEONE rises from a chair in the portico behind him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS659
SOMEONE shakes his head as he turns to face her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS660
He fires one gun then the other but finds them both empty.
COLOMBIANA_DVS661
She shoots him in his leg and he sinks to one knee.
COLOMBIANA_DVS662
A shot to his other leg sends him down on all fours.
COLOMBIANA_DVS663
He glances at the sharks below him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS664
SOMEONE shoots him in the shoulder and he tumbles into the uncovered gap in the panel.
COLOMBIANA_DVS665
As the sharks attack, he flails and grabs futily at the glass.
COLOMBIANA_DVS666
His blood billows in the water.
COLOMBIANA_DVS667
Walking onto the glass, SOMEONE picks up the orchid and drops it into the pool.
COLOMBIANA_DVS669
In his office, SOMEONE reads a newspaper's front page.
COLOMBIANA_DVS670
A photo displays the bloody swimming pool and a caption reads, "Sharks eat shark."
COLOMBIANA_DVS671
With a scowl, SOMEONE answers his phone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS672
He slams down the receiver.
COLOMBIANA_DVS673
Agent SOMEONE hangs up. Now a plane soars overhead.
COLOMBIANA_DVS674
Later at an airport, a woman and a goateed man follow SOMEONE past a baggage claim area.
COLOMBIANA_DVS675
SOMEONE pockets his cellphone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS676
He and his two bodyguards stride outside to a pick up area where a car awaits.
COLOMBIANA_DVS677
He climbs into the front passenger seat.
COLOMBIANA_DVS678
Now SOMEONE descends a staircase from a train platform.
COLOMBIANA_DVS679
As a man passes, she bows her head, letting her hair shield her face.
COLOMBIANA_DVS680
Later, she enters SOMEONE's apartment.
COLOMBIANA_DVS681
Walking past easels and paint supplies,
COLOMBIANA_DVS682
she spots the painting of the elderly man resting off to the side.
COLOMBIANA_DVS683
A drop cloth covers half of the canvas.
COLOMBIANA_DVS684
SOMEONE reads a note written in a sketchbook.
COLOMBIANA_DVS685
She slides off her jacket and falls back on his bed.
COLOMBIANA_DVS686
Her fingers fidgets with the orchid pendant around her neck.
COLOMBIANA_DVS687
as she stares up at the ceiling.
COLOMBIANA_DVS688
She turns on to her side, adjusting the pillow under her head
COLOMBIANA_DVS689
and notices one of SOMEONE's shirts lying on top of the covers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS690
Lifting it to her face, she smells it
COLOMBIANA_DVS691
then draws it into her arms and clutches it against her chest.
COLOMBIANA_DVS692
At the FBI office.
COLOMBIANA_DVS694
Two clips show SOMEONE at the police station, her face obscured.
COLOMBIANA_DVS695
Agent SOMEONE hits a command on his computer then sips from a travel mug.
COLOMBIANA_DVS696
As a laser like line scans down the image of SOMEONE, a message on the monitor blinks, "Morphological analysis."
COLOMBIANA_DVS697
A data match calculator runs above 13%.
COLOMBIANA_DVS698
At night, lights from Chicago's skyscrapers glimmer on the horizon.
COLOMBIANA_DVS700
In SOMEONE's apartment, SOMEONE pours red wine into a glass.
COLOMBIANA_DVS701
Lit candles around the room give it a warm glow.
COLOMBIANA_DVS702
SOMEONE glances over as her artist boyfriend comes home. She breaks into a smile.
COLOMBIANA_DVS703
She offers a glass.
COLOMBIANA_DVS704
She gives him a kiss then takes his hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS705
He gazes at food on a nearby table then sits facing her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS706
From a bag, she produces a plush alligator and hands it to him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS707
Smiling, she steps closer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS708
She kisses SOMEONE lustfully, running her fingers through his hair.
COLOMBIANA_DVS710
He gently pushes her away and she takes a seat in front of him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS711
SOMEONE looks away.
COLOMBIANA_DVS712
She stares off, her eyes shining with tears.
COLOMBIANA_DVS713
then gives a small shake of her head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS714
Blinking her woeful eyes, she opens her mouth to speak
COLOMBIANA_DVS715
then turns away and rests her elbow on the table.
COLOMBIANA_DVS716
She leans her head on her hands.
COLOMBIANA_DVS717
Tilting her head, she rumples her lips then grazes them with her fingers as her eyes fill with tears.
COLOMBIANA_DVS718
She glances back at SOMEONE
COLOMBIANA_DVS719
who flashes a tight smile.
COLOMBIANA_DVS720
SOMEONE breaks into a grin.
COLOMBIANA_DVS721
She leans closer and presses her lips to SOMEONE's.
COLOMBIANA_DVS722
As her kisses grow more passionate,
COLOMBIANA_DVS723
SOMEONE grabs her arms and holds her at bay.
COLOMBIANA_DVS724
Under his steady gaze, she gives a yielding look.
COLOMBIANA_DVS727
She raises her arms letting him lift off her shirt. He sets it aside. With both hands, he brushes SOMEONE's hair away from her face,
COLOMBIANA_DVS728
then leans forward and places a gentle peck on her cheek.
COLOMBIANA_DVS729
As he sprinkles her with more kisses,
COLOMBIANA_DVS730
she nuzzles her head against his. The next morning, the stuffed alligator sits on a table in front of a tray holding glasses of orange juice,
COLOMBIANA_DVS731
coffee mugs, and two plates of food.
COLOMBIANA_DVS732
Spotting the plush gift, SOMEONE picks it up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS733
He glances toward the bedroom where SOMEONE lies asleep under rumpled covers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS734
Grabbing his phone, he heads over and gazes down at the slumbering beauty.
COLOMBIANA_DVS735
He snaps a photo.
COLOMBIANA_DVS736
He dances the alligator in front of SOMEONE.
COLOMBIANA_DVS737
She jumps up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS738
She dresses.
COLOMBIANA_DVS739
SOMEONE looks out a window with a frustrated look.
COLOMBIANA_DVS740
Now SOMEONE strides down an aisle in a used book store.
COLOMBIANA_DVS741
Turning a corner,
COLOMBIANA_DVS742
she finds SOMEONE reading a newspaper.
COLOMBIANA_DVS743
He hurls the newspaper at her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS744
She lowers her gaze to a headline.
COLOMBIANA_DVS745
He presses her against a shelf.
COLOMBIANA_DVS746
He starts to leave.
COLOMBIANA_DVS747
He pauses.
COLOMBIANA_DVS748
He turns and glares at her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS749
She wipes away tears as he steps over to her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS750
He slaps a folded paper into her palm, wraps her fingers around it, and presses it to her chest.
COLOMBIANA_DVS751
As he leaves, she opens the paper and sees it's an old photo of herself with her parents.
COLOMBIANA_DVS752
Cupping a hand over her mouth, she sits on a bench then kicks the shelf in front of her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS753
She hangs her head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS754
Her shoulders tremble.
COLOMBIANA_DVS755
Now rain pours on a small cafe across the street from us.
COLOMBIANA_DVS756
His friend's eyes light up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS757
He shows the photo on his cell.
COLOMBIANA_DVS758
He spots a meter maid by his car.
COLOMBIANA_DVS759
He hurries outside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS760
His friend grabs his left behind phone off the table and makes a call with it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS762
In a police station, SOMEONE pulls it up on her computer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS763
She types. Her computer runs the photo through a database.
COLOMBIANA_DVS764
SOMEONE hangs up then glances outside at his friend.
COLOMBIANA_DVS765
He sets the cellphone back on the table.
COLOMBIANA_DVS767
In the FBI office, a message appears on Agent SOMEONE's computer, "Alert, database, new element."
COLOMBIANA_DVS768
He makes a phone call.
COLOMBIANA_DVS769
He hangs up and types a command into his computer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS770
A satellite map of Chicago appears then zooms in several times.
COLOMBIANA_DVS771
The trace hones in on a building and a label reads, "Third Precinct, Chicago, Illinois."
COLOMBIANA_DVS772
Agent SOMEONE makes another phone call.
COLOMBIANA_DVS773
In Chicago, we soar through the tall buildings, skimming a white steeple set with a gold cross.
COLOMBIANA_DVS774
In the spacious cathedral, congregants fill the pews.
COLOMBIANA_DVS775
Among them sit SOMEONE and Mama who murmurs a prayer under her breath.
COLOMBIANA_DVS776
SOMEONE arrives
COLOMBIANA_DVS777
wearing her large sunglasses.
COLOMBIANA_DVS778
Sitting beside her great-aunt, she stares ahead coldly.
COLOMBIANA_DVS779
Mama watches her remove her sunglasses.
COLOMBIANA_DVS780
The older woman turns to face SOMEONE who keeps his gaze fixed forward.
COLOMBIANA_DVS781
A tear streams down Mama's cheek and she shakily suppresses a sob.
COLOMBIANA_DVS782
SOMEONE's gaze softens.
COLOMBIANA_DVS783
As she lays her head on the old woman's shoulder, Mama nuzzles against her and closes her eyes.
COLOMBIANA_DVS784
SOMEONE smiles.
COLOMBIANA_DVS785
Later, he drives Mama.
COLOMBIANA_DVS786
Pepe rides with them.
COLOMBIANA_DVS787
SOMEONE parks at a curb and gets out.
COLOMBIANA_DVS788
Nearby, a car's side mirror reflects a man smoking a cigar as he watches SOMEONE's uncle through sunglasses.
COLOMBIANA_DVS789
Sitting in another parked car, SOMEONE chews gum.
COLOMBIANA_DVS790
At the Third Precinct, Shari approaches her desk and finds a female FBI agent working at her computer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS792
At the FBI office, he compares SOMEONE's hands in two photos.
COLOMBIANA_DVS793
He gets a 100% match on her nose.
COLOMBIANA_DVS794
Agent SOMEONE and his powerfully built colleague briskly march away.
COLOMBIANA_DVS795
Now a low sun casts a golden glow in the sky over Chicago.
COLOMBIANA_DVS796
In her apartment, SOMEONE soaks forlornly in a tub.
COLOMBIANA_DVS797
One arm dangles over the side holding a lit cigarette.
COLOMBIANA_DVS798
She drops it in a glass of water.
COLOMBIANA_DVS799
At his apartment, SOMEONE brings up his photo of SOMEONE on his phone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS800
He smiles fondly.
COLOMBIANA_DVS801
His display reads, "Unknown number."
COLOMBIANA_DVS802
The FBI listens in.
COLOMBIANA_DVS803
He knocks on a wall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS804
They're in a van followed by a police car.
COLOMBIANA_DVS807
One of her monitors reads, "Third party on line."
COLOMBIANA_DVS808
A surveillance feed shows the SWAT truck arriving outside. The team storms the building.
COLOMBIANA_DVS809
She drops her cell and rummages through a drawer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS810
Outside, SOMEONE puts on a bulletproof vest.
COLOMBIANA_DVS811
SOMEONE finds a key then takes a handgun from a table's underside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS812
Rushing through the apartment,
COLOMBIANA_DVS813
she turns on the shower then opens the birdcage.
COLOMBIANA_DVS814
She peeks out her apartment door into the hall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS816
In the lobby, SOMEONE takes an elevator. SWAT officers climb a stairwell.
COLOMBIANA_DVS817
SOMEONE runs barefoot down the hall, gun in hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS818
As the elevator approaches the 11th floor, Agent SOMEONE draws his gun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS819
SOMEONE reaches a stairwell and descends just as the elevator arrives.
COLOMBIANA_DVS820
Two SWAT officers cautiously scope out the area.
COLOMBIANA_DVS821
In the stairwell, SOMEONE pauses briefly, looking down.
COLOMBIANA_DVS822
Meanwhile, the SWAT team accompanying SOMEONE reaches her apartment door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS823
Agent SOMEONE arrives in another corridor with more gunmen.
COLOMBIANA_DVS824
From the stairwell, SOMEONE evades the ascending SWAT team by ducking into a hallway.
COLOMBIANA_DVS825
She races to a door, unlocks it, and slips into a living room where a long haired man watches TV.
COLOMBIANA_DVS826
He bolts up as she enters.
COLOMBIANA_DVS827
She slams his head against a coffee table, knocking him out.
COLOMBIANA_DVS828
Her gun ready, she proceeds to a bathroom,
COLOMBIANA_DVS829
climbs up on the rim of the tub and lifts a ceiling tile.
COLOMBIANA_DVS830
In a hallway.
COLOMBIANA_DVS831
In the bathroom, SOMEONE takes a huge assault rifle down from the crawl space.
COLOMBIANA_DVS832
On the 11th floor, a SWAT officer slips a snake camera under a door while Agent SOMEONE watches its video monitor.
COLOMBIANA_DVS833
He finds SOMEONE's living room empty.
COLOMBIANA_DVS834
A SWAT officer fixes explosives to the door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS835
In the bathroom, SOMEONE collects a hidden arsenal of weapons,
COLOMBIANA_DVS836
attaching the smaller ones to a belt around her waist.
COLOMBIANA_DVS837
She sets a charge on the tiled wall and pushes a button.
COLOMBIANA_DVS838
Taking up her enormous rifle, she marches down her neighbor's hallway.
COLOMBIANA_DVS839
She pauses by the door and raises a detonator.
COLOMBIANA_DVS840
At Agent SOMEONE's command, the apartment door explodes. A fire ball blossoms out from the unit and rolls down the hall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS841
Meanwhile, SOMEONE punches her detonator.
COLOMBIANA_DVS842
A fiery blast rips a hole in the bathroom wall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS843
Agent SOMEONE stands calmly in an elevator that jostles with the force of the explosion.
COLOMBIANA_DVS844
In the neighbor's apartment, the flames quickly fill the bathroom
COLOMBIANA_DVS845
then lap into the hall where SOMEONE takes cover.
COLOMBIANA_DVS846
Both fires die down.
COLOMBIANA_DVS847
The SWAT team enters her apartment while she approaches the fresh hole in the wall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS848
Agent SOMEONE waves smoke out of his face.
COLOMBIANA_DVS849
In the bathroom, SOMEONE uses a cable to lower her rifle down a now exposed shaft.
COLOMBIANA_DVS850
In her apartment,
COLOMBIANA_DVS851
Agent SOMEONE notices the empty birdcage then the orchid painting.
COLOMBIANA_DVS852
SOMEONE slides down a cluster of pipes in the shaft, passing several stories.
COLOMBIANA_DVS853
She lands gracefully at ground level.
COLOMBIANA_DVS854
In her apartment, Agent SOMEONE peers at her surveillance monitor.
COLOMBIANA_DVS855
Now a vent cover flies loose and a bare foot steps out.
COLOMBIANA_DVS856
SOMEONE crawls out from the shaft.
COLOMBIANA_DVS857
In an elevator, Agent SOMEONE speaks into his radio.
COLOMBIANA_DVS858
SOMEONE eyes monitors in the lobby.
COLOMBIANA_DVS859
Meanwhile, SOMEONE shoots out a camera.
COLOMBIANA_DVS861
Now sweat glistens on SOMEONE's skin as she pads briskly through the garage.
COLOMBIANA_DVS862
Arriving at another vent cover, she sets her rifle aside and unscrews the grating with her finger.
COLOMBIANA_DVS863
She turns as the authorities march into the garage,
COLOMBIANA_DVS864
then lifts the grate and feeds her rifle inside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS865
SWAT officers sweep the space with rifle lights. SOMEONE climbs backward through the narrow vent hole.
COLOMBIANA_DVS866
She contorts, struggling to fit her long limbs inside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS867
Her foot retracts from view just as the SWAT team rounds the corner.
COLOMBIANA_DVS868
Agents Ross and SOMEONE arrive and march through the damp garage.
COLOMBIANA_DVS869
SOMEONE tiptoes through a vent system.
COLOMBIANA_DVS870
As they search, SOMEONE pads through a shadowy tunnel.
COLOMBIANA_DVS871
A SWAT Humvee arrives in the garage with its lights flashing, trailed by two police cruisers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS872
Agent SOMEONE turns to face them.
COLOMBIANA_DVS873
Meanwhile, SOMEONE arrives in a changing room and checks a set of lockers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS874
She finds one unlocked and opens it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS875
Now as a subway train moves through the tunnel, a uniform clad SOMEONE slips out onto a catwalk above it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS876
A worker mends a track below as she creeps along,
COLOMBIANA_DVS877
her rifle bundled in a large sack.
COLOMBIANA_DVS878
She strides up a walkway toward daylight.
COLOMBIANA_DVS879
Later, she arrives at SOMEONE's house.
COLOMBIANA_DVS880
She halts at the sight of an unfinished cigar on a side table.
COLOMBIANA_DVS881
Drawing a handgun, she proceeds through the foyer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS882
She heads upstairs.
COLOMBIANA_DVS883
Nearing the top, she finds Pepe's shattered sunglasses lying on the second floor, inches from his limp hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS884
She aims her gun upward then ventures on.
COLOMBIANA_DVS885
Reaching the kitchen, she bursts into tears.
COLOMBIANA_DVS886
She kneels down to the old woman's crumpled body beside the overturned table and chair.
COLOMBIANA_DVS887
SOMEONE scrambles to her feet,
COLOMBIANA_DVS888
raises her gun and rushes through the house.
COLOMBIANA_DVS889
Reaching a doorway, she stops and slumps against the frame.
COLOMBIANA_DVS890
Her arms sink to her sides as she stares ahead.
COLOMBIANA_DVS891
She shuffles through a living room to a sitting room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS893
In front of her, a bloody SOMEONE sits tied to a chair, his head drooped forward.
COLOMBIANA_DVS894
The gun drops from her hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS896
She moves closer, She sinks down before her murdered uncle, and sobs against his shoulder.
COLOMBIANA_DVS897
She buries her face in his lap.
COLOMBIANA_DVS898
In the FBI office, Agent SOMEONE thoughtfully stares at a SOMEONE orchid
COLOMBIANA_DVS899
as he turns it in his fingers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS900
Now he leaves.
COLOMBIANA_DVS901
At a store, he buys a frozen dinner.
COLOMBIANA_DVS902
Later, he passes a neighbor walking his dog.
COLOMBIANA_DVS903
The agent heads through an iron security gate and approaches the entrance of a brownstone building.
COLOMBIANA_DVS904
Now he arrives in a modest apartment. He sets his gun and badge in a drawer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS905
He wearily takes his frozen dinner to the kitchen and puts it tray in the microwave.
COLOMBIANA_DVS906
Turning, he finds SOMEONE standing nearby in the shadows with her handgun pointed at him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS907
He sits as she shows the disconnected cameras.
COLOMBIANA_DVS908
With a sad smile, she lowers her gun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS909
Agent SOMEONE looks down. A wired timer blinks under his seat.
COLOMBIANA_DVS910
SOMEONE nods.
COLOMBIANA_DVS911
She pulls out a newspaper clipping and tearfully holds it out.
COLOMBIANA_DVS912
It includes a photo of SOMEONE.
COLOMBIANA_DVS913
She shakes her head with a sorrowful childlike pout
COLOMBIANA_DVS914
then shows a photo on a cellphone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS915
She takes a framed photo from a shelf and stares down at it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS916
She puts the photo back.
COLOMBIANA_DVS917
It shows Agent SOMEONE with his wife and two young children.
COLOMBIANA_DVS918
She turns away.
COLOMBIANA_DVS919
She halts in the kitchen, her weary gaze cast downward.
COLOMBIANA_DVS920
She starts the microwave then leaves.
COLOMBIANA_DVS921
Agent SOMEONE glances at his chair.
COLOMBIANA_DVS922
The microwave timer ticks down to zero.
COLOMBIANA_DVS923
Agent SOMEONE stands up quickly,
COLOMBIANA_DVS924
spins around, and leans his hands on the seat.
COLOMBIANA_DVS925
He springs back safely.
COLOMBIANA_DVS927
At the CIA, he throws down a file.
COLOMBIANA_DVS928
He gives the FBI agent a cold smirk. SOMEONE turns away.
COLOMBIANA_DVS929
SOMEONE smiles behind his back as he answers his cell.
COLOMBIANA_DVS930
Listening to the caller, he looks out the windows as he makes his way back to SOMEONE's desk.
COLOMBIANA_DVS931
A red laser point appears on SOMEONE's chest. He responds with a sneer.
COLOMBIANA_DVS932
SOMEONE backs away and ducks close to a wall by the window.
COLOMBIANA_DVS933
He peeks out and finds SOMEONE crouched behind a rifle on a neighboring balcony.
COLOMBIANA_DVS934
A bullet pierces the glass and hits a photo of SOMEONE with President SOMEONE W. Bush.
COLOMBIANA_DVS935
SOMEONE stares at his phone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS936
He peers cautiously out the window then returns to the desk, takes his file, and goes.
COLOMBIANA_DVS937
SOMEONE sits stiffly, his mouth agape.
COLOMBIANA_DVS938
Now beneath a hazy sky, we soar over Chicago's skyscrapers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS939
SOMEONE arrives in Pepe's garage and slides a pair of chain link doors open.
COLOMBIANA_DVS940
She removes a locker's padlock,
COLOMBIANA_DVS941
takes out a selection of rifles, and sets them on a worktable.
COLOMBIANA_DVS942
The assassin loads a clip into an assault rifle
COLOMBIANA_DVS943
then shuts a weapons case.
COLOMBIANA_DVS944
As she loads an armored truck, she notices the dogs watching her.
COLOMBIANA_DVS945
SOMEONE shifts her gaze then looks back at the dogs.
COLOMBIANA_DVS946
Now the truck's headlights switch on and the vehicle pulls out of its spot.
COLOMBIANA_DVS947
With SOMEONE at the wheel, it smashes through a gate and out onto the street.
COLOMBIANA_DVS948
At twilight, the truck splashes through puddles as it progresses down a narrow uneven alley.
COLOMBIANA_DVS949
Now as we peer down a hallway's polished floor, we find a portly bespectacled man marching toward us, a briefcase in hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS950
He arrives at a door and passes through.
COLOMBIANA_DVS951
Its stenciled lettering reads, "Stanley J. SOMEONE, Chief Land Surveyor."
COLOMBIANA_DVS952
SOMEONE sits in his chair.
COLOMBIANA_DVS953
She aims a gun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS954
Now at the mansion.
COLOMBIANA_DVS955
SOMEONE shifts his gaze to an open door straight away and sees a rocket flying right at him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS956
He lunges sideways avoiding the projectile which explodes as it hits a wall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS957
A burst of roiling flames fills the room
COLOMBIANA_DVS958
then blasts out doors and windows.
COLOMBIANA_DVS959
A crystal chandelier crashes to the ground.
COLOMBIANA_DVS960
As the flames give way to a haze of smoke,
COLOMBIANA_DVS961
SOMEONE and SOMEONE's gunmen writhe.
COLOMBIANA_DVS962
Looking into the adjacent room, SOMEONE finds his boss unconscious on the floor.
COLOMBIANA_DVS963
He hurries over and starts to lift him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS964
The man stirs.
COLOMBIANA_DVS965
He stands.
COLOMBIANA_DVS966
With their weapons raised, four gunmen rush into a spacious garage.
COLOMBIANA_DVS967
Scurrying to a row of luxury cars, they climb into a Mercedes.
COLOMBIANA_DVS968
As it speeds toward the garage's exit, the armored truck backs through a wall beside it and smashes into the vehicle's nose.
COLOMBIANA_DVS969
It continues to reverse, driving over the Mercedes's hood and crushing it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS970
SOMEONE climbs out with a sub machine gun raised.
COLOMBIANA_DVS971
She fires at the car.
COLOMBIANA_DVS973
As the barrage of bullets kills the men inside, smoking casings pop out of her gun and shower the ground.
COLOMBIANA_DVS974
SOMEONE leads his boss away.
COLOMBIANA_DVS975
They turn down a corridor.
COLOMBIANA_DVS976
He pushes a statue on the wall.
COLOMBIANA_DVS977
A panel behind the statue pushes inward to reveal a hidden compartment.
COLOMBIANA_DVS978
SOMEONE closes himself inside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS979
Meanwhile, SOMEONE creeps through a crawl space under the mansion.
COLOMBIANA_DVS980
Dust sprinkles down through the floorboards above.
COLOMBIANA_DVS981
Pressing her back to a wall, she fires up through the floorboards.
COLOMBIANA_DVS982
As her shots hit a gunman, others take cover.
COLOMBIANA_DVS983
The shooting ceases and the bullet riddled man falls.
COLOMBIANA_DVS984
SOMEONE peers out from another room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS985
A beefy gunman shows him a grenade and the bearded gangster nods.
COLOMBIANA_DVS986
The gunman tosses it over and SOMEONE pulls its pin.
COLOMBIANA_DVS987
He lobs it into the other room where it lands beside the murdered gunman.
COLOMBIANA_DVS989
The explosion tears into the floor and churning fire surges through the crawl space.
COLOMBIANA_DVS990
SOMEONE watches from a safe distance as smoldering SOMEONE rains down.
COLOMBIANA_DVS991
In the hidden compartment, SOMEONE presses his ear to the panel
COLOMBIANA_DVS992
then takes out his cell and dials.
COLOMBIANA_DVS993
SOMEONE answers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS994
Stepping into the destroyed room, the beefy gunman fires down the hole in the floor
COLOMBIANA_DVS995
then jumps into the crawl space, his weapon still blasting.
COLOMBIANA_DVS996
More gunmen follow.
COLOMBIANA_DVS997
With the phone still to his ear, SOMEONE aims a handgun as he cautiously steps toward the hole.
COLOMBIANA_DVS998
SOMEONE gives a relieved look.
COLOMBIANA_DVS999
A burst of bullets hits the gunmen in the crawl space.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1000
Hiding behind a pillar, SOMEONE lowers his phone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1001
On the opposite side of the room, SOMEONE stands on a mezzanine with a sub machine gun in each hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1002
SOMEONE squeezes his eyes closed as her bullets hit the floor near his feet.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1003
Her shots rip side by side paths of holes in the wood then lift to three gunmen in the adjacent room, killing one after another.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1004
SOMEONE turns to the mezzanine and fires. SOMEONE races away.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1005
As a thin gunman and a bald one shoot up at the mezzanine, SOMEONE rushes out of the room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1006
The bald gunman follows and the thin one takes cover behind a pillar.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1007
Now alone, the thin gunman peers around his pillar at the mezzanine.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1008
SOMEONE stands beside him holding a gun to his cheek.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1009
Meanwhile, SOMEONE listens on his phone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1010
Now SOMEONE steps over the thin gunman's dead body and strides off.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1011
Elsewhere in the mansion, SOMEONE and the bald gunman hurry into a bedroom.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1012
As the gunman shuts the door and waits,
COLOMBIANA_DVS1013
his weapon raised, SOMEONE closes himself into a bathroom.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1015
SOMEONE talks into his cell.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1016
The bearded gangster hangs up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1017
In the bedroom, the gunman grits his teeth as he stares at the door paned with textured glass.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1019
SOMEONE sets his phone on a shelf by a tub and glances at the closed door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1020
He checks the chamber in his pistol then tosses the weapon on the floor.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1021
Meanwhile, SOMEONE slumps against a wall in the compartment.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1022
Setting his tinted glasses on the shelf, SOMEONE watches the bathroom door open.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1023
SOMEONE enters with her gun raised.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1024
As she kicks his pistol away, he grabs her wrist and redirects her aim.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1025
She releases the weapon, catches it in her other hand, and points at him again.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1026
He grabs its barrel and strikes her in the head, snatching it away as she stumbles.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1027
He raises it and she grabs a glass off a shelf and hurls it at him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1028
She wraps a towel around his gun wielding wrist and pulls down as if operating a lever, using her own shoulder as a fulcrum to break his arm.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1029
Yanking her ponytail back, SOMEONE wiggles out of her hold.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1030
She whips the towel at his hand and knocks the gun into the tub.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1031
As she whips at him, he dodges
COLOMBIANA_DVS1032
then grabs the towel's other end.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1033
She spins toward him, punches him in the throat, then kicks him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1034
Holding him against a wall, she strikes him over and over.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1036
He shoves her away but she wraps the towel around his neck and starts to choke him from behind.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1037
He backs her into a wall, breaks the hold, and hurls her aside.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1038
As he grabs the gun from the tub, she knocks it to the floor. She kicks him in the groin.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1039
Standing behind her, he wraps the towel around her neck and starts to choke her. Removing her belt, she flips it over her head, wraps it around the back of his neck, and faces him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1040
She swings him into a fireplace and they both tumble to the ground.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1041
Pushing himself to his feet, SOMEONE moves to SOMEONE and pulls her hair. She grabs a toothbrush on the ground and stabs him with it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1042
As she picks up another, he yanks her to her feet.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1043
She swipes at him with a brush in each hand.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1044
He grabs her wrists, holding her back, but she twists free and slashes at him.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1045
Spinning, she backhands him with one of the brushes.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1046
He charges, grabbing her around the waist.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1048
As she gets thrown against the wall, the brushes fall from her grasp.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1049
She lands a punch, sending SOMEONE crumpling to the floor where he grabs the abandoned gun.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1050
As he points it at SOMEONE, she quickly releases the weapon's magazine from its hand grip then yanks the slide from the barrel and stabs him in the neck with it.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1051
His head droops.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1052
SOMEONE withdraws her hand, trembling as she falls back in exhaustion.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1053
She stares at the dead gangster.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1054
The clip juts grotesquely from his neck.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1056
A bloody nosed SOMEONE scoots back from him,
COLOMBIANA_DVS1057
her body quivering with emotional sobs.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1058
Meanwhile, SOMEONE shifts his panicked eyes, then opens the compartment's panel.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1059
Back in the bathroom, SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's phone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1060
SOMEONE races to the garage and gets into a van.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1061
Spinning its wheel, he steers past the destroyed Mercedes
COLOMBIANA_DVS1062
and squeezes between the armored truck and a wall, side swiping both on his way through.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1063
He speeds out a door and onto a narrow road.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1064
With a frantic look, he pulls onto the main road leading out of his estate, passes through the front gate and swerves onto a street.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1065
The van fishtails, its spinning tires leaving a wake of churning dust.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1066
Meanwhile, SOMEONE exits the mansion.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1067
Turning a corner, SOMEONE finds the road blocked by a garbage truck.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1068
He answers a phone on the van's dash.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1069
Turning, SOMEONE sees her dogs in the back seat.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1070
The dogs attack and blood splatters the phone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1071
A view from outside shows the van shaking.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1072
Blinking her weary eyes, SOMEONE lowers her cell from her ear and sucks in an anguished breath.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1073
A thin trickle of blood leads from one nostril
COLOMBIANA_DVS1074
to the tip of her chin.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1075
Warm sunlight washes over her face as she drops to her knees in the grass under a towering tree.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1076
She bows her head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1077
Back in Chicago, SOMEONE sits with Agent SOMEONE in an office at the FBI.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1078
Agent SOMEONE heads to the door.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1079
As he leaves, SOMEONE gives a perturbed look.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1080
Checking his phone's display, he glances around then answers.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1082
The agent hurries off.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1083
SOMEONE tears up. Agent SOMEONE enters the office.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1084
He grabs the phone.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1085
Depressing the payphone's hook, SOMEONE hangs up.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1086
She allows a tiny smile.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1087
At the FBI, Agent SOMEONE shoots his partner a frustrated look.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1088
With the phone's receiver cradled against her neck,
COLOMBIANA_DVS1089
SOMEONE lets out a whisper.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1090
She wipes away a tear then replaces the receiver.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1091
At the FBI, Agent SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1092
SOMEONE takes his cell back and heads out of the room.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1093
As he leaves, Agent SOMEONE bows his head.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1094
Meanwhile, SOMEONE brushes a tear from her eye then slides on a pair of sunglasses.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1095
Golden sunlight glows down on her as she turns away from the phone and dons a hat.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1096
She strides toward a bus parked at the side of the road.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1097
A woman sitting on a bench stares off with disinterested eyes as SOMEONE passes by then boards the bus.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1099
Its door closes after her and the vehicle pulls into the road.
COLOMBIANA_DVS1100
The bus trails billows of exhaust as it trundles into the distance.