SOMEONE throws the second soldier over the railing, then heads after them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS17
He jumps a stairway railing. SOMEONE fires at him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS19
SOMEONE and SOMEONE head through a door and pull it shut. SOMEONE jumps down to the dungeon floor and finds the door locked.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS20
Meanwhile, Benedict peers through balusters. The wavy haired man taps him with his revolver, then points the gun at the clergyman's head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS21
A silver hatchback busts through a door. The SOMEONE spots the escaping vehicle. With a frustrated roll of his eyes, he executes the clergyman.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS22
SOMEONE hurdles a low wall and runs to him motorcycle.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS23
Kicking up gravel, he rides out of the fortress. Now the silver hatchback emerges from the tunnel on the mountainside road. SOMEONE peers intensely over the steering wheel. SOMEONE gains on the car as he rounds a bend. SOMEONE glances over his shoulder then trades a look with SOMEONE. The black SUV rounds a corner. The wavy haired man rides shotgun.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS25
SOMEONE glances back.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS26
An oncoming car swerves around the hatchback, almost hits SOMEONE, then swipes the SUV. SOMEONE accelerates. SOMEONE peeks over her shoulder. The three vehicles round another bend, now one right behind the other.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS27
The wavy haired man hangs out the passenger window with his revolver in hand. He shoots out the hatchback's rear window, then the motorcycle's back tire, launching SOMEONE over a safety railing. In slow motion, SOMEONE twists his body and takes aim at the SUV with only the distant forest floor below him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS28
One of SOMEONE's bullets pierces the vehicle back tire, causing the SUV to tip on its side. SOMEONE looks back. As the SUV slides across the road, our view meets its roof.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS30
Now an animated sequence.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS31
In association with Imagination Abu Dhabi, Ghost Rider: Spirit of Vengeance. Now SOMEONE kneels before a contract.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS32
He smashes a bottle with his fist.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS33
He splatters the contract with blood.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS34
Flames envelope his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS35
Lights beam from his eyes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS36
In a flash, his fist breaks the bottle. SOMEONE wakes with a start.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS37
His face glistening with sweat, he turns his head toward the noise outside. He looks at a scar on the palm of his hand then sits up. Daylight shines through cracks in a door.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS38
SOMEONE enters the dingy garage.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS39
SOMEONE grabs him, slams him into a shelving unit, then clutches the collar of his leather jackets and peers into his eyes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS40
SOMEONE hangs upside down from a branch jutting off the steep mountainside.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS41
SOMEONE lets him go then crosses the grungy room.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS42
SOMEONE grabs a new empty bottle of wine from a table and smells its contents.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS43
He dumps out the remaining alcohol, grabs the bottle by its neck, then chucks it past SOMEONE through a window.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS44
Daylight floods in and SOMEONE backs into a corner.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS45
SOMEONE leaves the corner. SOMEONE confronts him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS46
SOMEONE meets his gaze then shoves a shirt in a bag.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS47
Stepping outside, he covers his eyes. SOMEONE follows him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS48
SOMEONE uncovers his bike. He grabs a chain from his bag, hurls it at SOMEONE, then wraps it around his neck.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS50
SOMEONE lets him go. SOMEONE throws the chain off, leaning over the back of the motorcycle.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS51
He stands upright then reaches into his jacket pocket and takes out a photo of SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS52
He leaves the photo wedged in the motorcycle's seat.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS53
SOMEONE snatches the photo from the seat and gives it a look.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS54
SOMEONE shares a long gaze with his visitor, staring at him with his ice blue eyes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS55
Now pedestrians cross a bustling town square.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS56
A policeman walks among them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS57
A man haggles with an older woman.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS58
In a cafe, SOMEONE sits alone at a table, watching a man in a grey suit take off his wedding ring.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS59
She averts her flirtatious gaze and sips a cup of coffee.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS60
The man joins her.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS61
He shifts his delighted gaze. She looks him over.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS62
He glances aside and smiles.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS64
As he steps past, SOMEONE pickpockets him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS65
The businessman heads off, bumping into a woman's chair.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS66
SOMEONE shows the man's wallet to SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS67
She winks at him and they head out.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS68
On the street, they hurry over to the silver hatchback parked among other cars. The wavy haired man and his men watch from their own vehicles.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS69
In the hatchback, SOMEONE shows SOMEONE the businessman's wedding ring.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS70
SOMEONE meets her gaze and she rubs the back of his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS71
She smiles then kisses his brow.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS72
They drive away. Our view lurches backward in brief irregular bursts of fast motion as we watch a pair of black SUVs pull out and follow them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS73
Now SOMEONE perches in a crumbling pane-less window high above the ground.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS74
He sips from his flask as lightning flashes in the stormy sky. In the converted garage, SOMEONE sits hunched at a cluttered table.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS75
He clenches SOMEONE's photo in his trembling hands.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS76
Now lightning flashes in the sky as SOMEONE drives. SOMEONE sleeps in the passenger seat. She changes the radio station and turns her tender gaze to SOMEONE. Reaching out, she strokes his cheek with her finger then ruffles his hair.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS77
Three SUVs come up behind them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS78
Meanwhile, SOMEONE overturns a cart. SOMEONE wakes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS80
On the road, the lead SUV rear ends the silver hatchback. In the garage, SOMEONE lurches. The hatchback swerves and the SUV pulls up to side swipe it. SOMEONE topples a shelving unit.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS81
The SUV runs the hatchback off the road and down a rugged slope. SOMEONE staggers across the floor. The SUV rams the hatchback against a wall. SOMEONE's back arches, his eyes two dark hollow pits. In his perch, SOMEONE puts a cigarette in his lips and strikes a match. The flame blazes at a horizontal angle.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS82
SOMEONE turns then throws the match down. Now he runs towards SOMEONE's garage to find a blazing light moving within. As he approaches the side of the building, a flaming blast erupts from its door. SOMEONE staggers back, shielding his eyes. Recovering, he finds a trail of fire stretching along the ground to a point of light speeding up the road.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS83
In a deserted lot, the SUVs surround the hatchback.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS84
SOMEONE gets out in a glare of headlights, gun in hand. Shielding her face, she shoots blindly.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS86
A male figure lunges out and beats her.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS87
He forces her down as other thugs get out of their SUVs. SOMEONE's attacker holds her arms behind her back.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS88
Their wavy haired leader steps close.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS89
A thug beats at the car door.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS90
As SOMEONE struggles, SOMEONE smirks and bends down.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS91
The other thug drags SOMEONE from the car.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS92
As the heavyset thug looks on, SOMEONE punches his mustached attacker in the gut.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS93
The mustached thug slams him down, zip ties his hands and throws him head first against the SUV.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS94
SOMEONE crumples to the ground. SOMEONE elbows her attacker's knee and grabs for his gun. It fires into the rocky ground. Her attacker regains control of the gun and pistol whips her.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS95
SOMEONE crouches beside SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS96
SOMEONE's head droops forward defeatedly.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS97
SOMEONE stands, aims his revolver at her and cocks the hammer.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS98
Nearby a goateed thug turns. SOMEONE looks up. Following their gaze, SOMEONE discovers a fiery blast erupting on a far wall.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS99
From it, Ghost Rider's flaming motorcycle arcs through the air. It lands in the middle of the lot, filling our view as it spins to a halt. The heavyset thug staggers back fearfully. The others stand motionless, staring at the Rider's flaming skull.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS100
A heavy black boot with burn marks steps off the footrest and grinds into the gravel.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS101
The rider swings himself off of the monstrous vehicle. Flames glow within its engine and exhaust vents.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS102
The rider's gloved fingers close around his heavy duty chain. Lightening casts a glow on the mustached thug as he holds his shotgun ready. The chain links glow and the rider turns his scorched flaming skull.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS103
Staring, SOMEONE rolls unsteadily in the gravel. The rider's head cocks erratically. He raises his fist to his opposite shoulder, then lifts his other hand and at angle. SOMEONE's slack jawed gaze shifts of the otherworldly creature to his henchmen.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS105
The goateed thug shoots, his bullets making glowing holes in the rider's scorched leather jacket. Turning, the creature slings his chain back, grazing SOMEONE's shoulder. He flings it around the thug and gives it a yank, incinerating him in a flash. Lowering his chain, the rider sways side to side, his head tilting to and fro. A smudge of smoking embers stands in place of the goateed henchman. The mustached thug eyes them fearfully, then faces the swaying demonic creature. The rider wheels around to face him. In a rapid series of erratic movements, the rider charges. He stops inches from the mustached thug and looms over him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS106
The rider lowers his bony jaw, his mouth a swirl of flames. He leans over his victim who trembles and sputters incoherently. Looking along, the heavyset thug drops his rifle and sinks to his knees. The riders jaws abruptly snap shut.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS107
Staring, SOMEONE grabs his brutish henchmen's shoulder.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS108
Ghost Rider grabs the mustached thug's face. The henchman's wide eyes reflect his ghastly flaming visage as the rider cocks his head appraisingly then leans in to peer more closely at the man. Nearby, a scratch on SOMEONE's cheek seeps blood. SOMEONE opens the rear hatch of his SUV, pulls out an enormous rifle and hands it off to his brutish henchman.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS109
The mustached thug's features twist in a helpless sob. The rider keeps his head in a firm grip, staring relentlessly. Our vision doubles as the thug's eyes cross and he sinks down. Nearby, SOMEONE stirs. A drop of his blood falls from his cheek and hits a stone. The mustached thug incinerates and the rider turns. SOMEONE's eyes snap open.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS110
The rider clasps his own hand and massages his palm. SOMEONE's eyes shift upward and his head rolls to follow them. Facing him, the rider breaks into a march. A thug steps in and shoots but the demonic creature incinerates him with shot. Beside SOMEONE, the heavyset thug scrambles back. The boy regards the rider calmly as it arrives before him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS111
Lying in the dirt, SOMEONE reaches out desperately.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS113
SOMEONE and his brutish henchmen run out beside her, each armed with an enormous rifle. They both fire. The shots send the rider flying. He hits the side of an SUV, caving it in.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS114
SOMEONE fires a grenade. It explodes on impact, destroying the SUV.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS115
He joins SOMEONE and the heavyset thug.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS116
The heavyset thug forces SOMEONE into the back of another SUV while SOMEONE gets in the front. As it pulls away, SOMEONE reaches out for it then slumps breathlessly.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS117
Cut to black.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS118
Now we gaze down on SOMEONE as he lies in a hospital bed. His brow knits painfully and he stirs awake.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS119
SOMEONE looks around, notices an IV in his hand and lifts up his hospital gown.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS120
Jagged pink scars mar his flesh. A pretty young nurse steps in through a ring of curtain.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS123
He flops back on his pillow.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS124
Eyeing him uneasily, the nurse leaves. SOMEONE notices his jacket draped over a chair near a cabinet of drugs and medical supplies. Now he opens the cabinet and rummages through the drugs. He takes two handfuls of pill bottles. Now fully dressed, he slips out of his room and hurries down the hall.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS125
Ahead, two doctors try to stop SOMEONE from leaving.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS127
He pauses, watching her. Leaving the doctors, she halts at the sight of him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS128
SOMEONE's eyes look her over then narrow his eyes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS129
With an uneasy gaze, she steps away.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS130
SOMEONE clutches her wounded shoulder as she heads up a ramp.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS131
SOMEONE stares after her, glances back over his shoulder and follows.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS132
Now in a sunlit clearing, SOMEONE's SUV sits parked with the driver's door open.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS133
The heavyset thug stands nearby as SOMEONE opens SOMEONE's door and yanks him out.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS134
The boy lands on all fours in the dirt. SOMEONE steps away.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS135
Now at a busy transit platform, a figure in a black suit, matching coat, and well-shined shoes steps off a train.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS136
Carrying a briefcase, he pulls out a sleek cellphone, slides it open and answers it.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS137
His back to us, the man stops at a newsstand.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS138
The man turns, revealing a long pale face with aging features.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS139
SOMEONE thrusts his cell at SOMEONE's ear.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS140
The screen splits down the middle. On the left, we watch the mysterious man's moving lips.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS141
On the right, the phone at SOMEONE's ear.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS142
The boy slumps on his knees, his hand limp in his lap. His shoulders heave.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS143
Leaning back, his jaw distends in a supernatural roar.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS144
SOMEONE drops the phone and staggers back. SOMEONE collapses on the dirt.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS145
SOMEONE picks up his phone and puts it to his ear.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS147
The well-dressed man ends the call.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS148
SOMEONE lowers the phone.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS149
From above, we drift down toward the boy as a wind blows a drift of sand over the ground. Nearby, SOMEONE angrily kicks the SUV's door shut. SOMEONE lies motionless, his brow knitted as his breath comes in shallow gasps. Light fills our view.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS150
At the hospital, SOMEONE's head lurches back.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS151
Blinking confusedly, he gives it a shake.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS152
Stepping outside, he pauses and massages his right palm.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS153
SOMEONE looks around and glimpses SOMEONE hurrying alongside the building. He staggers down the steps, clutching his abdomen. Peeking around the corner, he finds SOMEONE moving through a parking lot with affected nonchalance. She pauses by a car, checking its doors. They don't budge. Moving on to the car beside it, she turns. SOMEONE darts back behind the wall.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS154
SOMEONE moves on then pauses warily.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS155
She jogs out of view.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS156
SOMEONE staggers after her.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS157
Stepping past an ambulance, he looks around. SOMEONE lunges, aiming a gun at him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS159
SOMEONE adjusts her stance and narrows her eyes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS160
Grabbing her wrist, he brings the gun to his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS161
SOMEONE wrenches herself from his grasp. SOMEONE lowers his regretful gaze. The mother regards him disgustedly but makes no move to leave him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS162
SOMEONE shakes his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS163
SOMEONE sighs tearfully.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS164
He offers a kind nod. SOMEONE's gaze hardens and she swallows. SOMEONE tilts his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS165
Now SOMEONE's motorcycle sits on a truck's flatbed.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS166
He knocks back some pills.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS167
At the wheel, SOMEONE faces him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS168
A flashback.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS169
Light overwhelms our view. Back in the present.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS170
The truck takes an exit. Now in stylized animation, we view SOMEONE and other satanic incarnations.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS171
SOMEONE Springer ends the series.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS172
A man on fire shakes hands with a human.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS173
We focus on the clasped hands. Now in SOMEONE's SUV, SOMEONE sits with his eyes closed.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS174
His eyes open and he turns.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS175
SOMEONE shifts his indignant gaze.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS176
Turning away, SOMEONE flops back against his seat.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS177
His gaze calm, SOMEONE lunges forward between the seats and wrenches the steering wheel. SOMEONE swipes at the boy as the SUV swerves wildly then fishtails. SOMEONE fastens his seat belt then gives his abductor a smirk. The SUV hits a concrete barrier and flips over on its roof. Steam wafts from the upturned undercarriage. Inside, SOMEONE hangs upside down, his eyes half closed in a placid gaze.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS178
He blinks and looks around.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS179
His hand finds his seat belt buckle and pushes the release button.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS180
SOMEONE tumbles down and wrestles his way past the heavyset thug.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS181
As he crawls from the wrecked SUV, the thug grabs his ankle.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS182
SOMEONE tugs himself free and runs away.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS183
We spy flames spreading over the undercarriage as SOMEONE and his brutish henchman escape, leaving the heavyset thug stuck in his crushed doorway.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS184
SOMEONE shakes loose of his grasp and follows SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS185
SOMEONE runs under a bridge along a river.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS186
SOMEONE and his henchman follow. A massive fireball erupts from the bridge as the SUV explodes. SOMEONE and SOMEONE both stare then continue the chase. The henchman leaps from a concrete barrier to the riverbank. SOMEONE jumps from a ridge. As he lands on slippery rocks, his ankle snaps.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS188
SOMEONE arrives and hauls him up by his jacket.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS189
Two campers look on.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS191
He points at the mohawked camper's brightly painted van.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS192
The henchman fixes a menacing glare on the camper.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS193
Their carefree smiles fade as they notice his large gun.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS194
Now SOMEONE rides shotgun and his henchman drives the hippy-dippy vehicle. He looks over his shoulder at SOMEONE who sits slumped and blindfolded on the floor. Covered in swirling day-glo patterns, the van sputters fumes as it travels up the road.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS195
Now the flatbed truck speeds down a dark stretch of road. Inside, SOMEONE's closed eyes flutter. We glimpse Ghost Rider's skull.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS196
SOMEONE wakes with a jolt. He massages his palm and eyes SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS197
Now two bodyguards flank a man in a tacky suit as he heads up a winding stone stairway. Camera flashes erupt around him as he ends a call on his cellphone. He heads up another flight of stone steps to a crowded warehouse floor where two men face off on a round platform.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS198
Chewing gum, SOMEONE twitches.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS199
Below, a fighter faces a hog on a leash. In a back room, the tacky man addresses thugs counting cash.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS200
"Count every dollar. I don't want these idiots robbing me. Everyone's robbing me. It makes my balls hurt."
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS201
Now as SOMEONE's associate lights a cigarette, SOMEONE approaches. Subtitles: "Hello, Vasil."
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS202
SOMEONE shoves him against a wall and SOMEONE holds up a knife.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS204
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE's phone.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS205
Cringing, SOMEONE shakes his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS206
Part of his face becomes skeletal then morphs back.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS207
SOMEONE shoves the cellphone in SOMEONE's mouth.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS208
His eye transforms into an empty black socket.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS209
He shakes his head and the socket reverts to human form.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS210
SOMEONE grits his teeth in pain then eyes SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS211
SOMEONE nods.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS212
He slams SOMEONE against the wall.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS213
Two thugs appear and SOMEONE hurls SOMEONE into them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS214
SOMEONE begins to change as he races through the warehouse's abandoned rooms. A thug charges and he shoves the man away, setting him on fire. With flames now dancing on his arms, SOMEONE rushes outside. He sees his motorcycle surrounded in billowing fire, waiting for him at the end of an alley. Now he rides alternately cringing and grinning crazily as his face morphs from his human form to the Ghost Rider and back again.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS215
His nose and eyes take skull form and he blows fire from his nostrils. Cringing, he reverts to a human face. He struggles to remain composed. Half of his face morphs again. Flames lick his cheek and burst from his eye socket.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS216
His motorcycle's billowing fire rises and engulfs him. Now in the quarry, our view sweeps down a hulking bucket chain excavator's giant cutting wheel. A caravan of SUVs drives under the machine's long truss boom followed by a pair of cargo trucks. As the last truck passes under, a man climbs a ladder to the excavator's control cab which sits just behind the cutting wheel. At the boom's opposite end, armed guards keep watch on a balcony on the excavator's base structure. The trucks pull into an area surrounded by towering stacks of shipping containers. A bearded man exits an SUV and his men carry out two military crates.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS217
He hands one of his men the missile shoulder launcher.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS218
He ignites a lighter.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS219
He blows out its flame.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS220
The bearded supplier turns to his guards.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS221
He smiles disbelievingly at SOMEONE, now in a storage room.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS222
He sits wearing a blindfold.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS223
She pulls it off.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS224
She cuts the restraints tying him to a support beam then helps him up.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS225
As she supports him, the brutish henchman appears. She flips open her knife but he twists her around and dips her as if for a kiss then hurls her to the floor. He extended his gun's telescopic handle. SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a fearful glance.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS226
All three of them lift their eyes skyward.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS227
Outside, SOMEONE glances around. The brutish henchman frowns.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS228
SOMEONE throws her knife at him but he catches it. As he turns to her with a smile, she shoots him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS229
Outside, SOMEONE smirks.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS230
He beckons the bearded supplier who hurries over with the missile launcher. They move to the edge of the quarry.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS231
A man hands the launching tube to SOMEONE. Lifting it onto his shoulder, the wavy haired criminal peers through its thermal sight and finds Ghost Rider's glowing image as he speeds along the cliff above the quarry. He fires and the missile arcs high into the air.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS232
As Ghost Rider speeds down into the quarry, the missile dives at him and explodes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS235
A mushroom cloud of flames billows into the air.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS237
The bearded supplier's grin fades. Following his gaze, SOMEONE finds Ghost Rider unharmed, standing at the explosion's outskirts.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS238
He backs away.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS239
As Ghost Rider advances on a line of guards, they fire their assault rifles. He whips his chain at three of them and they disintegrate into flames and ash. He whirls the chain above his head, then strikes another. Dropping his gun, a guard races away. Ghost Rider whips him in half. As another guard pulls the pin on a grenade, Ghost Rider whips him and the grenade drops. Ghost Rider stares at it.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS241
The guards turn from the explosion's blinding light. As it fades, they see Ghost Rider's horizontal body rotating three feet above the ground. The men aim their guns. Ghost Rider looks at one who flinches. Now on his feet, Ghost Rider faces him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS242
The guard shoots into Ghost Rider's open mouth. The flaming skeleton waits as bullets fly in. The man lowers his gun and Ghost Rider's head slumps. He bellows a stream of flaming bullets at the guard.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS243
SOMEONE shoulders the reloaded launcher.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS244
Through its sight, he sees Ghost Rider approaching. As the flaming skeleton knocks him onto his back.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS245
SOMEONE fires the launcher aimed right at him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS246
The missile drives him high into the sky. In midair, the missile extinguishes Ghost Rider's flames, then propels him to the ground.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS247
A brilliant fire cloud billows high into the sky. Ghost Rider's smoldering hand reaches out of the fiery crater left behind.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS248
Ghost Rider's gaze shifts from the excavator's giant wheel to the control cab on the boom. As guards shoot at him, the leather clad skeleton rises to his feet.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS249
His skull charred and smoking. As shots pierce his chest, the bullet holes glow. He starts to climb the ladder to the control cab, then pauses and turns to SOMEONE who gawks. He resumes climbing while a mass of guards unleashes a barrage of bullets. Now inside the cab, Ghost Rider shoots flames from his skull, shattering the cab's windows.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS250
Fire billows down the excavator's boom and bursts around its giant wheel.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS252
Sitting in the control seat between two levers, he pulls one back and pushes the other forward.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS253
The flaming boom swivels around.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS254
Shifting the levers, he raises the wheel high into the air, then smashes it onto a watchtower. He lifts the flaming wheel again, then heaves both levers forward with a maniacal grin.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS255
The wheel crashes down on a trailer. From a balcony, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch with wide eyes as the wheel slams a truck and some shipping containers then grabs them with the toothy ridges along its perimeter. The spinning wheel catapults a piece of flaming metal into the sky.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS256
SOMEONE drags SOMEONE away.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS257
The bearded supplier readies a launcher then spots the wheel above him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS258
Ghost Rider shifts the levers and the wheel crashes down.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS259
It crushes the supplier in a burst of flames which sends SOMEONE flying back. The wavy haired man stands, blood dripping from his mouth.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS261
SOMEONE helps SOMEONE down a flight of stairs. SOMEONE draws a gun. As he aims it at them, Ghost Rider's chain wraps around his ankle. It yanks him off his feet then drags him to the flaming skeleton. Ghost Rider lifts him off the ground.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS265
SOMEONE drives off with SOMEONE in the flatbed truck.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS266
As SOMEONE struggles in Ghost Rider's grip, the flaming skeleton hurls him away then gazes into the distance. He heads off. In the truck, SOMEONE gives an alarmed look.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS267
SOMEONE shoots him a fearful glance. In the rearview mirror, she sees Ghost Rider closing in on his motorcycle.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS268
She looks over her shoulder at him but finds no one. As she turns back, she sees him beside her. He grabs her.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS269
Pulling her out through the driver's side window, he dismounts his motorcycle and grips her by the arms. Nearby, the truck rolls to a stop. SOMEONE's feet dangle a few inches from the ground.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS271
SOMEONE climbs out of the truck.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS272
SOMEONE's eyes widen as the rider gazes into them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS274
He looks back at SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS275
Under the boy's steady stare, he releases SOMEONE. As he heads toward SOMEONE, his flames briefly fade.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS276
He stumbles back a few steps, then continues toward SOMEONE who holds his ground. The fire dancing around his skull dims in a billow of smoke and Ghost Rider staggers, swatting at it. He shakes himself out of the daze. With his gaze fixed on the boy, he trudges closer, stopping a few feet away as inky smoke swirls around him. SOMEONE watches the smoke ringed skeleton drop to one knee.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS277
The flames on his skull subside and he holds his hands in front of his face as if to protect it. The smoke dissipates, leaving SOMEONE in a kneeling position. He glances around.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS278
He lifts his gaze to a boy.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS280
At a truck stop diner, SOMEONE sits alone at a booth with a frown, his eyes fixed on a nearby family.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS281
He sees the father ruffle his son's hair.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS282
Approaching from behind with a tray of food, SOMEONE stops and follows SOMEONE's gaze. He watches the father affectionately touch his son's head then glances back at SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS283
Sitting across from him, he slides the tray over.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS284
He glances at the family then reaches out and touches SOMEONE's hair. The boy recoils.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS285
SOMEONE stares sullenly.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS286
Tilting his head, SOMEONE scrutinizes him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS287
SOMEONE gives an impassive look.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS288
SOMEONE quirks a smile. SOMEONE joins them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS289
Sitting beside SOMEONE, she wraps an arm around him and kisses his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS290
She gives a critical look as she sees SOMEONE lift a water pitcher and drink from it.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS291
He chugs obliviously.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS292
He flashes a grin at them then resumes drinking.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS293
He drinks some more and SOMEONE nods. SOMEONE glances at her.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS294
He clears the inside of his cheek with his tongue, then takes another drink.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS295
Now at the quarry, emergency workers tend to the destruction. SOMEONE lies unconscious under a cement slab. SOMEONE approaches.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS297
Subtitles appear as he speaks.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS298
His expression becomes flat and he stares out lifelessly.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS299
Lowering himself to his knees, SOMEONE slides his hand between SOMEONE and the cement slab. He presses SOMEONE's chest and the dead man's eyes open.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS300
His lips stutter.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS301
The left side of SOMEONE's face becomes withered and wrinkled,
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS302
and blood vessels burst in his eye.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS303
Splotches of sores appear on his skin.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS304
SOMEONE's body trembles as his dark hair morphs to blonde.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS305
He withdraws under the cement slab.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS306
Grabbing the slab, SOMEONE lifts it.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS307
He tosses it aside to expose SOMEONE who now has straight shoulder-length platinum hair and ashen skin.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS308
The resurrected man scrambles on his hands and knees in the dirt then glances around. He rises to his feet and eyes his gloved hands.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS309
SOMEONE tosses him a smoldering piece of wood.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS310
It rots in SOMEONE's hand.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS311
He stares at SOMEONE with a pleased gaze.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS312
Glancing over his shoulder, SOMEONE sees an EMT standing at an ambulances open side door.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS313
SOMEONE follows his lackey's gaze. As they stare, the EMT furrows his brow and takes a step back.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS314
He shifts his perplexed eyes. As he turns around, darkness engulfs him. SOMEONE grabs his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS315
He presses a hand to the man's face which becomes dark with rotting flesh.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS316
Smiling, SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE's touch decays the EMT's body until it crumbles apart.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS317
SOMEONE gazes steadily at his lackey.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS318
Later, SOMEONE works on his bike as he and SOMEONE ride on the truck's flatbad.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS319
SOMEONE shakes his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS320
He jumps up to his feet.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS321
As SOMEONE mimes urinating, SOMEONE imagines Ghost Rider shooting out a powerful stream of fire.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS322
He pictures the skeleton nodding at him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS323
SOMEONE glances at the passing landscape, his face becoming somber. SOMEONE sits beside him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS324
He eyes the boy.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS325
SOMEONE meets his gaze with a grave look.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS326
He bows his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS327
Riding a motorbike, SOMEONE catches up to them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS328
He pulls up to the driver's side window.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS329
Grinning, he speeds ahead of the truck.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS330
SOMEONE mimes firing her gun with her fingers.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS331
Now the rear wheel of SOMEONE's motorcycle burns rubber as it races past the tow truck, trailing a billow of smoke.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS332
It pulls up beside then passes SOMEONE who shakes his head at SOMEONE. The boy sits in front of SOMEONE on the gas tank with his legs draped over the handlebars.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS333
SOMEONE sets a bent knee at the rear of his seat then straightens it, pushing his weight onto his back foot.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS334
Popping a wheelie, they glide along on only the bike's rear wheel.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS335
Watching from the truck, SOMEONE smiles. SOMEONE shifts his motorcycle onto only its front wheel.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS336
As the bike comes to a full stop, its rear wheels stay up in the air for a moment then drops back to the ground.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS337
The tow truck cruises past. Now SOMEONE's motorcycle catches up to SOMEONE again. Meanwhile, the hijacked ambulance glides down an otherwise vacant road through desert landscape.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS338
Driving it, SOMEONE reaches into a lunch box on the seat beside him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS339
He pulls out a sandwich. It grows moldy and disintegrates at his gloved touch. Glancing into the lunch box, he takes out an apple and watches the bright green fruit turn grey and crumble.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS340
He rubs his gloved fingers against each other cleaning the dust from them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS341
He finds a plastic wrapped Twinkie and examines it then gives it a squeeze.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS343
The top of the wrapper pops open and the end of the spongy cream-filled yellow cake peeps out.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS344
SOMEONE bites into the still fresh snack and chews thoughtfully.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS345
He shoves half of the remaining sheathed Twinkie into his mouth, then bites down on the wrapper using his teeth to hold the cake in place. He slides the wrapper out. It's now empty plastic smeared with cream.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS348
Later, in the desert, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE along a path between jutting cliffs and barren mountains with cave-like openings.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS349
They approach towering rock formations that appear constructed into, creating buildings within their natural structures.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS350
SOMEONE gazes around.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS351
He sees some robed monks.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS352
A group of monks greets them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS353
The one in front removes his hood revealing tattooed writing covering his face and bald scalp. He places a hand on SOMEONE's head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS354
SOMEONE's fingers caress the cross hanging around his neck.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS355
The monk glances at SOMEONE who gives an awkward nod.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS356
They embrace then switch sides and embrace again. SOMEONE notices more monks surrounding their group.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS357
The tattoo faced monk shifts his intense gaze to SOMEONE who lifts his chin.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS358
The monk twitches a tight smile.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS359
SOMEONE turns to his companion.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS361
He winks at SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS362
He moves to SOMEONE's side.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS363
SOMEONE gives an uncertain look as she and SOMEONE start off with the monks.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS364
A monk reaches for him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS365
SOMEONE kneels in front of him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS366
He touches SOMEONE's cheek.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS367
SOMEONE guides her dejected son away.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS368
SOMEONE glances aside.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS369
Now they walk through a vast wine cellar.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS370
SOMEONE grabs a bottle from a table in the middle of a rotunda.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS371
He takes a swig.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS372
He looks heavenward.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS373
Our view ascends to find an angel spreading its wings over the earth.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS374
The angel's eyes bulge, glimpsing a barrage of images - war, money, riots, napalm, a seductive woman.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS376
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE and grins. He leaves a wall of cubby holes stocked with wine.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS377
Fire engulfs a winged skeleton.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS378
SOMEONE lowers his troubled gaze.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS379
SOMEONE grins then wraps his arm around his friend.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS381
At a cubby hole, he takes out an ancient bottle of ruddy wine.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS382
He kisses the bottle then looks at SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS383
He walks off and SOMEONE gazes thoughtfully.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS384
He puts the cross around his neck in SOMEONE's hand and looks him in the eyes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS385
SOMEONE shifts his gaze. SOMEONE grabs the possessed man's shoulder and they sit down.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS386
Holding the cross, SOMEONE looks into the priests eyes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS387
Daylight shines down on them from a hole in the ceiling.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS388
He wipes a tear from his eye.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS389
SOMEONE turns to his bag and takes out a small loaf of bread.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS390
He breaks it in half.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS391
He puts one half back.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS392
He breaks off a piece for SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS393
SOMEONE takes it from him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS394
He takes a bite then shifts his gaze.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS395
SOMEONE pats him on the shoulder.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS398
Now SOMEONE wanders through a tunnel.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS399
He reaches the end of the passage and a huge slab blocks him from turning back. He enters an empty room.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS400
Our view whirls, glimpsing numerous passageways. SOMEONE looks up at the room's domed ceiling.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS401
A brilliant light flashes then shines down on him. He collapses to his knees.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS402
He rolls on his back, his eyes morphing into hollow sockets.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS403
As he convulses, the image distorts.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS404
As he grimaces, his memories move in reverse. His blood lifts from the contract and the broken bottle reforms.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS405
As SOMEONE arched his back in pain, we see him as a flameless Ghost Rider falling through a white void.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS406
He drops into the distance, his arms and legs flailing.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS408
He shoots a seemingly endless length of chain from his mouth. As it pulls taut, it breaks from his skull with a fiery flash.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS409
His skull emits a flow of smoke, distorting his bone structure.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS410
Cut to black.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS411
Now on the floor of the empty room, SOMEONE lies flat on his back with his eyes closed.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS412
Our view draws near the side of his face.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS413
He wakes with a start and rises to a crouch then looks at his gloved right hand, gives it a rub, and brightens.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS414
He hurries through one of the passages.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS415
He runs down another.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS416
He reaches the mouth of a cavern.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS417
He heads down a stairway carved into the stone.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS418
The path leads him to bluff overlooking the region.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS419
He shifts his gaze.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS420
SOMEONE hurries off. He enters a vaulted hall.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS421
He finds the monks detaining SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS422
A monk seizes his arm.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS423
SOMEONE falls to his knees, his gloved hand trembling.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS425
SOMEONE swipes at another monk with his free hand but the monk grabs his throat.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS426
The tattoo faced monk addresses SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS427
He runs the backs of his fingers down her cheek then jams his thumb just below her chin, knocking her unconscious. SOMEONE looks on.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS428
"Take them away until the thing is done."
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS429
The monks drag SOMEONE and SOMEONE out.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS430
The tattoo faced monk marches off.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS431
Outside, the hooded monks stand in a circle.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS432
Two more bring SOMEONE to the center and bend him over a rock.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS433
The tattooed monk follows. A monk pulls back the nervous boy's collar. The others sway side to side.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS434
The tattoo faced monk draws a sword and taps its long curved blade to the back of SOMEONE's neck.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS435
With both hands, the executioner raises the sword overhead.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS436
He finds himself surrounded by darkness, then twirls his sword defensively.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS437
As another monk gropes in the dark, SOMEONE grabs him from behind, rip him and lets him fall.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS438
He runs to another and throws him down.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS439
The tattoo faced monk spots SOMEONE leaping from his victim. SOMEONE snaps a decaying monk's neck. He grabs another from behind. The tattoo faced monk swings his sword. SOMEONE catches his wrist then vanishes. As the tattoo faced monk looks for him, SOMEONE grabs the swords hilt, causing its blade to rust and crumble. The monk grabs SOMEONE's throat and he collapses to his knees, waving his hands in surrender.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS440
The monk lets go, his hand decomposing.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS441
SOMEONE smashes the monk's hand, grabs his jaw, then slams him onto his back. Sneering at his victim, he holds two fingers over the monk's tattooed face. The monk's bald head withers, his skin crumpling. As he rots completely, SOMEONE holds up his two fingers.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS443
In the light of day, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE jump back from his kill. He glances at the surrounding bodies of the other monks, each petrified in frightful poses. The boy steps back nervously.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS444
SOMEONE eyes him, stroking his platinum hair.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS446
Now as we rove over the craggy landscape, glaring sunlight overtakes our view.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS447
Then shrinks to a pinpoint as we drift among two petrified monks left permanently kneeling in prayer.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS448
As a butterfly lands on a sprouting mushroom, the image focuses on a moss ridden monk.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS449
Crouching over one of the dead, SOMEONE picks up his cross necklace. She looks at SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS450
SOMEONE joins them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS451
He heads off.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS452
SOMEONE shifts her worried gaze. SOMEONE nods for her to follow.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS453
Now we soar over the ruins of the demolished structure overgrown with weeds. Uzak gokten, Turkey.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS454
An ambulance pulls up to the archways of an ancient amphitheater's outer wall.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS455
Black clad guards surround the building.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS456
SOMEONE walks out followed by two of his masked men.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS457
SOMEONE steps out of the ambulance and shuts the driver's door.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS458
SOMEONE opens the ambulance's back door.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS459
He pulls out SOMEONE, bound to a stretcher.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS460
SOMEONE strolls over as his guards untie the boy.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS461
SOMEONE eyes him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS462
SOMEONE's smile diminishes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS463
SOMEONE chuckles to himself.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS464
Now SOMEONE leads SOMEONE and SOMEONE through a passage.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS465
He brings them to a vast armory.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS466
SOMEONE peers through a scope.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS467
She takes the sniper rifle. In a corridor, SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS468
The boy gazes up at him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS469
SOMEONE envisions Ghost Rider urinating fire from left to right.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS470
He doubles over.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS471
He sits up straight and SOMEONE nods.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS472
SOMEONE meets his devilish gaze.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS474
SOMEONE faces forward.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS475
SOMEONE nods for one of guards to bring him a small case.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS476
He takes out a syringe then turns to his son.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS477
As a guard restrains the boy, SOMEONE injects SOMEONE through the neck.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS478
SOMEONE smiles as the child loses consciousness. He stands upright.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS479
He returns the syringe to its case.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS480
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE follow SOMEONE, climbing to the top of an ancient structure
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS481
which overlooks the amphitheater in the surrounding ruins. SOMEONE peers through a binocular, spying on arriving guests. SOMEONE takes a knee.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS482
They watch the guests convene outside.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS483
At dusk above the darkened horizon, scattered clouds roll across the sky.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS484
At night, spotlights illuminate the ancient amphitheater as SOMEONE's guards walk SOMEONE out on stage.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS485
The guards leave the boy kneeling before the guests who sit in six uniform sections, all wearing black robes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS486
SOMEONE faces his acolytes then raises both arms, gesturing for them to rise from their seats.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS487
SOMEONE lowers his arms and sets his maniacal gaze on SOMEONE who remains on his knees rocking side to side with his head down.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS488
Meanwhile, the cross hairs of a night vision sniper scope move from one guard to the next.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS489
SOMEONE lowers her worried gaze, sets down her rifle, and heads off.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS490
As SOMEONE follows her, SOMEONE returns his gaze to the amphitheater and knocks on a rock wall.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS491
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE out among the ruins.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS492
He lays his hand on her shoulder and she meets his gaze, fidgeting anxiously.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS493
SOMEONE faces her.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS494
He rests his hand on her shoulder.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS495
She glances down then heads off and he turns to watch her go.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS496
Now a half moon shines in the night sky.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS497
SOMEONE's black robed acolytes sway as they chant.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS498
On stage, SOMEONE kneels a few feet away from SOMEONE,
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS499
both swaying in unison as though under a spell. We glimpse a few chanting mouths. Meanwhile, the sniper scope targets a guard.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS500
He collapses.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS501
Another goes down.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS502
SOMEONE reloads and takes aim at a third.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS503
She glances up from her green tinted night vision scope then spots four men in a brawl.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS504
She glances up once more then recognizes SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they leave their fallen enemies behind.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS505
Now SOMEONE leads SOMEONE past a wall. He peeks around a corner then crouches with his partner.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS506
He takes a swig of 2000 year old wine.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS507
He hands the bottle to SOMEONE who takes a sip as well.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS508
SOMEONE hands it back.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS509
SOMEONE kisses his friend on each cheek.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS510
He grins.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS511
He grabs his bag and leaves. SOMEONE heads off as well. Now SOMEONE reaches an entryway and chugs his wine.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS512
Two guards trade a look.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS513
He tosses the bottle and shoots them both down.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS515
He kicks a guard.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS516
He reloads then runs up a staircase.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS517
Now SOMEONE darts furtively through a passage in the amphitheater.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS518
He hurdles the low edge of a stone window and peers around a column.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS519
He finds SOMEONE and SOMEONE swaying on their knees before the chanting acolytes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS520
SOMEONE and SOMEONE slump forward.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS521
The boy raises his head, his eyes bloodshot with black irises.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS522
SOMEONE opens his black bloodshot eyes. SOMEONE creeps closer and shakes his head wrathfully. SOMEONE's lips move.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS523
SOMEONE chants as well. His acolytes tilt their eyes back.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS524
Gazing down on the stage, we find a shadow extending from SOMEONE's body as if reaching for SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS525
SOMEONE runs out in the stands.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS526
He shoots down a guard.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS527
SOMEONE turns and looks up, his eyes returning to normal. As he watches SOMEONE shooting his guards and acolytes, SOMEONE runs onto the stage and punches him out.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS528
SOMEONE runs through the stands shooting more acolytes. He pauses, spreading his arms exultantly. SOMEONE reaches a gloved hand out to SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS529
An unseen force halts it.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS530
SOMEONE stares coldly at SOMEONE through blackened eyes. SOMEONE tries again to reach for him but stops, his neck crooking convulsively. In the stands, SOMEONE arrives and grabs SOMEONE's gun hand. His glove and weapon decay.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS531
SOMEONE sits up.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS532
With a swipe of his hand, he sends SOMEONE flying off the stage. He lands hard in a gravel pit below. In a ring of darkness, SOMEONE decays the priest's right arm in his grasp.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS533
The right side of SOMEONE's head decomposes as he swings his left fist at the demon. SOMEONE catches it easily and forces it down.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS534
SOMEONE sees them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS535
Darkness closes in around the priest as SOMEONE's grasp decomposes him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS536
His back arches as the demon snarls. His face a mess of rotten flesh, SOMEONE smashes his head against SOMEONE's. SOMEONE looks on as SOMEONE shakes the rot off his face and out of his hair and mouth.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS538
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch the acolytes surround SOMEONE who struggles to stand in the gravel pit.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS539
SOMEONE's hand creeps over his shoulder bringing him back to his knees.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS540
He brings the other hand around to his cheek and holds him by the head. As SOMEONE looks on with a bitter twisted scowl, SOMEONE draws a line of decay across SOMEONE's high forehead. The devil turns and his minion looks up. The acolytes somberly part to reveal SOMEONE walking toward SOMEONE and the weakened SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS541
The demon wrenches his victim's head to face the boy then grins at SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS542
The devil smiles eagerly.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS543
The boy regards him with a knitted brow.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS544
SOMEONE kneels on one knee with the other leg crooked out awkwardly. SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS545
SOMEONE gives a puzzled scowl.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS546
SOMEONE returns his somber gaze to SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS547
He looks back and forth between the boy and his evil father.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS548
He remember smashing the bottle with his fist and the contract pages flipping by themselves. SOMEONE gives a defeated nod as he recalls signing the contract with his blood. He looks up at SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS549
SOMEONE bares his gritted teeth. SOMEONE runs up to him, seizes him by the shoulders and spews a jet of fire at him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS550
SOMEONE releases his victim and staggers back, looking on. The flames jetting from SOMEONE's mouth engulf SOMEONE's face. The cursed man accepts the fire with a wide open mouth.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS551
Falling back, SOMEONE lies motionless on the gravel.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS552
On his feet, SOMEONE staggers around as black smoke plumes from his head. The surrounding acolytes recoil as he draws near, his face a swirl of flames. Staring slack jawed, SOMEONE darts away. As SOMEONE halts and doubles over, the acolytes surround him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS553
SOMEONE helps up SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS555
At her post, SOMEONE turns to find SOMEONE's motorcycle erupting flames as the engine starts by itself.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS556
In the gravel pit, the acolytes close in on SOMEONE. In the sky, a rising sun breaks over a rapid swirl of clouds. Ghost Rider rises, taking out the acolytes with a circular sweep of his red hot chain. All around the amphitheater, posted floodlights explode. Outside, SOMEONE loads a limp SOMEONE into an SUV. Armed men in full body armor rush to surrounding SUVs and trucks. SOMEONE's vehicle speeds away followed by the armed convoy. In the gravel pit, Ghost Rider jerks his head side to side.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS557
He stares at his own gloved hands.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS558
His skeleton head snaps to one side attentively and he marches off. In SOMEONE's SUV, SOMEONE's head slumps forward. His father regards him with a bitter scowl as he leads the convoy at high speed away from ruins. Meanwhile, Ghost Rider marches from the amphitheater to find his flaming motorcycle approaching. It skids to a half before and he climbs on.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS559
The rider speeds off, his chopper trailing thick plumes of black smoke.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS560
Now SOMEONE's convoy travels through a desert on an isolated two-lane highway.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS561
Ghost Rider quickly gains on the trucks.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS562
The rear driver spots him and swerves left, blocking his path. The rider deftly weaves around the truck. A gunman ahead fires rounds from a mounted cannon. They blast holes in the asphalt around the flaming motorcycle but fail to impede it. At the lead, SOMEONE spies the rider in his side mirror and snarls resentfully.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS563
Ghost Rider pulls up beside a ruthless truck as its driver barks into a radio.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS564
He leaps from his motorcycle onto to the driver's side of the cab and shrieks in his face. The driver flies from the truck, landing in the dirt. Ghost Rider leaps onto the driver's seat and takes the wheel. Flames erupt throughout the engine and blaze around the tires.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS565
Meanwhile, SOMEONE drives after the convoy in a dusty SUV, her chin lowered in a determined stare. At the wheel of the flaming truck, the rider thrusts one hand out to the side and gives a taunting shriek. The cannon truck swerves before it, the shooter firing relentlessly. Ghost Rider rear ends it and it explodes. The SUV ahead of it spins out of control, threatening to cut off SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS566
She weaves around it without breaking speed. From below, SOMEONE climbs up on her hood. Crouching playfully, he touches a fingertip to her windshield. A web-like network of cracks spreads across the glass. He drives his fist through the cracks, shattering the windshield. SOMEONE shields her face from the flying glass shards. Ahead, an SUV carrying gunmen pulls up beside Ghost Rider's truck. The flaming vehicle knocks it off the road. The rider turns. Behind him, SOMEONE reaches a hand toward SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS567
Ghost Rider slings his chain. SOMEONE lurches. With a tug, the rider yanks him off SOMEONE's hood and onto the bed of his possessed truck. SOMEONE grabs the chains which start to rot in his grasp.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS568
His smug grin vanishes. The rider tugs the chain, pulling him down and leaps over him. Recovering, SOMEONE grabs him from behind.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS569
The rider elbows him then knocks him back.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS570
His chain rises by itself, winding around the demon.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS571
SOMEONE dances away from it and meets the rider in a grappling hold.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS573
The mad angel leaps from the bed and together they fly through darkness. Twin lights flare below them.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS574
They're SOMEONE's headlights. The grappling foes land on her SUV's hood. SOMEONE head butts the rider who punches him. The demon rolls over on top of him but the angel throws him into the air. As SOMEONE lands back on the hood, his foe flings him off. The rider peers toward the road, looking for his enemy. SOMEONE climbs up the SUVs rear and over the roof. The foes reconverge in a wrestling grasp on the hood. Shifting gears, SOMEONE accelerates and rear ends an SUV knocking it off the road. SOMEONE bends the rider over the side of the hood.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS575
Darkness fills the sky and Ghost Rider's flames sputter weakly.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS576
His flames reignite in a wild blaze as he lifts his skull. He seizes SOMEONE by the head and brings his face close, his jaw opening wide. His cocky smirk gone, SOMEONE stares fearfully through glistening bloodshot eyes. The rider's flames catch on his long stringy hair. The vengeful creature flings SOMEONE to the road where he decomposes instantly.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS577
Ghost Rider's skull snaps around, catching sight of SOMEONE's SUV ahead. His flaming motorcycle pulls up alongside SOMEONE's vehicle then creeps ahead. The gypsy woman shifts gears and accelerates. Ghost Rider leaps from her hood, landing on his motorcycle. Its thick trails of black smoke obscure our view as we follow him up the highway. SOMEONE's side mirrors show Ghost Rider gaining.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS578
As he draws closer, he slings his glowing chain forward. It lashes around the undercarriage's central rod. Ghost Rider gives his chain a tug.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS579
SOMEONE lurches and the auto part flies past the rider.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS580
The SUV swerves off the road then flips end over end.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS581
It lands on its roof in a flaming wreck.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS582
Ghost Rider pulls up beside it, dismounts from his motorcycle and marches toward the vehicle with a steady purposeful gait.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS583
He finds SOMEONE crawling laboriously from the wreck.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS584
His aging wounded vessel limp from the chest down, the devil drags himself across the sand.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS585
Ghost Rider's gloved hand snatches him by the shoulder then hauls him to his feet.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS586
SOMEONE's twisted features scowl bitterly as the rider shrieks in his face.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS588
Ghost Rider throws him down then slings him skyward with a chain around his chest. SOMEONE hovers helplessly in his bonds high above the earth.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS589
The rider snaps the chains, slinging the devil into the ground.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS590
Our view zooms down the chain to a seemingly bottomless pit.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS591
Following the chain, we find SOMEONE plunging into a sea of fire.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS592
His limbs flailing, he steers helplessly as the flames eat away at his flesh.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS593
The hell fires flare, their light overwhelming our view.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS594
In the light of a high bright sun, Ghost Rider crosses his arms over his chest. He spreads them wide, lifting his palms and skeleton face exultingly toward the heavens. He sways side to side, his fleshless mouth working in a growing roar.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS595
Ghost Rider doubles over then arches back triumphantly. He slumps forward and lingers in stillness.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS596
He turns his head.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS597
Several yards away, SOMEONE crests a ridge at dogged run.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS598
She lurches to halt at the sight of Ghost Rider standing beside the overturned flaming SUV.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS599
The creature's skull turns toward the wreckage. As SOMEONE watches, Ghost Rider circles the vehicle, looking down.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS601
He halts.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS602
He glances back toward SOMEONE and lowers his gaze again.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS603
His gloved hands reach out uncertainly and he lowers out of view. SOMEONE wavers on her feet, her breath coming in ragged gasps. She steps forward as Ghost Rider stands, cradling SOMEONE's limp form in his arms.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS607
Ghost Rider carries the boy to his mother.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS609
SOMEONE staggers woefully as he nears then sinks to her knees.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS612
The rider bends down, laying SOMEONE in her arms.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS613
She tilts the boy's head back gently.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS615
SOMEONE raises a skeletal hand enveloped in blue flames.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS616
SOMEONE eyes him uncertainly.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS617
SOMEONE extends his mystical burning skeletal hand toward SOMEONE.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS618
SOMEONE crosses a protective arm over her son.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS619
Reaching past it, SOMEONE caresses the boy's cheek.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS620
SOMEONE wakes, his color returning.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS621
SOMEONE smiles joyfully through his tears. SOMEONE and his mother face him.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS622
SOMEONE lowers his chin and narrows his eyes.
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS624
On a nighttime highway,
GHOST_RIDER_SPIRIT_OF_VENGEANCE_DVS625
a skeletal biker blazes with blue flame.