SOMEONE leads four men down the alley
GREEN_ZONE_DVS18
The outside group charges past a donkey cart. In the warehouse, the others run away and take cover beside an exit.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS20
Meanwhile, SOMEONE peers up through an awning and sees a figure dash past an open-air window in the tower.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS21
A solider peeks out from the warehouse.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS22
SOMEONE fires a few bursts at the fifth floor of the tower then sees the sniper's head.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS24
SOMEONE looks on.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS25
The warehouse and cross over to the alley.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS26
They race past looters dismantling light fixtures.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS27
A soldier stands guard at a corner as his teammates enter an unlit building.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS29
Another soldier uses a mirror on the top of a closed thick metal door.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS30
The soldiers put on protective gloves and masks.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS32
Beams of light lead the way into a pitch black chamber. We catch glimpses of a dusty floor and machinery.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS33
The soldiers' flashlights glow from underneath the muzzles of their rifles.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS34
And holds out a device pointed toward the floor.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS35
Another soldier's light beam travels up the camouflage of a teammate's uniform.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS36
SOMEONE removes his mask as two men open a pair of tall doors, letting sunlight flood into the room. The chief scans a rusted metal girder and other SOMEONE littering the floor. His men inspect the room.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS37
SOMEONE eyes stains on the girder.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS38
One guy checks out a stack of crates.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS39
Now outside, a soldier smokes a cigarette as he lounges near a Humvee.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS40
At the other side of the vehicle.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS41
Mobile computer. SOMEONE returns.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS42
He squints down at his intel report,
GREEN_ZONE_DVS43
folds it up, and heads off.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS44
The soldiers load their equipment.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS45
Choppers swoop down toward
GREEN_ZONE_DVS46
the International Airport.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS47
In a white suit and sunglasses.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS48
A petite blonde woman watches two cars approach.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS49
He gets off the car.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS51
An Arabic man exits a plane.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS52
Mr. SOMEONE shakes hands.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS53
Now the convoy arrives.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS54
Techs work at computer stations on a
GREEN_ZONE_DVS55
screen filled with multiple satellites.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS56
SOMEONE walks with a balding mustached officer.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS57
Bethel leaves SOMEONE behind in a briefing room.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS58
Into detention as an officer with salt and pepper hair enters.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS59
As the personnel sit, SOMEONE scans the file.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS60
A stout captain steps up.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS61
A site named SOMEONE Monsieur.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS62
SOMEONE frowns and raises his hand.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS63
Bethel glowers disapprovingly.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS64
He glances away.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS65
SOMEONE stares earnestly at the soldier.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS67
Sign reading Baghdad
GREEN_ZONE_DVS68
In big text. Now pedestrians in traffic crowd as
GREEN_ZONE_DVS70
Pots drops a bottle drop on him.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS72
There's a parked car sitting blocking the road.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS74
Now we soar over the city's crowded buildings to an area lush with vegetation. As we reach a palatial building, words appear - Coalition Provisional Authority
GREEN_ZONE_DVS75
Dom's Republican Palace. Inside, Clark addresses high ranking soldiers and officials in a video conference.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS76
A staffer shifts her uncomfortable gaze from SOMEONE to Clark.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS77
Clark coldly shuffles his paperwork.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS78
Now in a quiet residential neighborhood, an Iraqi man in a taupe suit patrols the sidewalk with an assault rifle.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS79
Guard at an intersection. A fourth keeps lookout from a building's rooftop. A white SUV charges up the street then breaks by the man in the taupe suit. Nearby, a thin balding Iraqi with a mustache beneath his aquiline nose limps to a dusty grey car. Glancing across the street, he spots the guards escorting a cluster of well-dressed men away from the white SUV. The bystander gets in his dusty car, keeping an eye on the group as General SOMEONE leads them through a gate. Staring with parted lips, the bystander discreetly drives away. Inside a crowded living room, a middle-aged man lights a cigarette. SOMEONE enters the home and his host extends a hand.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS80
They kiss cheeks and SOMEONE joins the other men in the living room.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS81
They get to their feet. An older bald gentleman respectfully kisses SOMEONE's cheeks.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS82
Another older man offers him the same greeting. SOMEONE accepts it then holds his hands up in a polite refusal to others as they edge toward him. The general sits and the others follow suit.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS91
SOMEONE notices a crowd.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS92
Villagers hold off the predominately male army.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS93
A soldier pins the mustached man.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS94
He attempts to help him stand.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS95
He bats SOMEONE away.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS96
As SOMEONE stares at him, he glances aside.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS97
The chief maintains eye contact with the mustached local.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS98
As SOMEONE stalks off, Wilkins catches up with him.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS99
SOMEONE looks back at Conway.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS100
SOMEONE faces him.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS102
The boyish soldier nods.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS103
Two assigned soldiers get into the dusty sedan.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS105
Now at a safe house
GREEN_ZONE_DVS107
SOMEONE raises his hand, capturing the group's attention.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS115
Sitting beside the general, SOMEONE lowers his gaze. The official glances to a comrade then nods. Now SOMEONE stands, prompting the others. He nods to the official's opponent who leaves. A man with a briefcase shakes the general's hand. Outside, the departing Baptists get into a sedan and drive off.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS116
A car cruises down a street followed by the white truck.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS117
The official shakes hands with SOMEONE, then outside, he chats with a comrade as they get into a car. SOMEONE's attachment approaches.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS118
left. The pickup crosses to a dirty
GREEN_ZONE_DVS119
SOMEONE's sedan stops.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS120
They peer across the now empty street.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS121
They watch two men in suits head down the sidewalk.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS122
The truck parks.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS123
SOMEONE watches the men get in their car.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS125
Three soldiers run to the outer wall.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS127
Soldiers signal and another kicks open door.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS128
They storms indoors.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS130
SOMEONE looks up a staircase. At the patio door, an aide gestures.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS131
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE down a staircase.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS132
The chief peers across the lower window and sees SOMEONE's bald head.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS133
They cross into a kitchen where the dead gunman lies on his back. They approach the open patio door.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS134
Outside, they ascend a staircase to see an SUV drive away down the street. SOMEONE lowers his weapon.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS135
The fallen Iraqi bleeds out on the floor.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS136
SOMEONE and SOMEONE go upstairs to find SOMEONE with the women and children.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS138
SOMEONE finds the little black notebook.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS139
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS140
SOMEONE grabs the notebook.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS141
Now SOMEONE's car and the white pickup truck return.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS142
SOMEONE to the wall.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS143
SOMEONE fidgets then looks at SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS144
He takes out the black notebook.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS146
SOMEONE hurries off at a limp.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS148
He scans the pages.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS149
He hops on one leg.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS150
SOMEONE starts off.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS151
He hops in place, turning away from them. SOMEONE glances at Pots, then walks over to the prosthetic leg, picks it up and hands it to SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS152
SOMEONE holds his earnest gaze. Now our view orbits a massive bust of Saddam Hussein wearing a helmet.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS154
Republican Palace. Inside, SOMEONE answers his phone while passing through a metal detector.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS155
SOMEONE hangs up.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS156
His stubble faced peer frowns.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS157
They part company. SOMEONE gets in a Humvee.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS159
skimming a file. SOMEONE approaches and walks with him down a staircase.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS161
It shows a road leading to an archway.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS164
He undoes his chinstrap and takes off his helmet and eyes the palace.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS165
Now SOMEONE dons his sunglasses as he leads his men onto a patio surrounds a luxurious pool. Sunbathers lounge in deck chairs and waiters bustle. The soldier stare as two bikini clad women saunter by.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS166
SOMEONE spots SOMEONE and a colleague at a table.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS167
As SOMEONE makes his way around the pool, two guys in board shorts amble past, both casually toting semi-automatics. The soldier heads to SOMEONE's small patio table and takes a seat.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS168
Meanwhile, SOMEONE strolls around the patio. Back at the table, SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the little black book.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS169
SOMEONE examines its contents.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS170
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE then returns his attention to the book.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS171
He lifts his gaze to the soldier's face.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS172
SOMEONE tucks the book into his jacket pocket.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS173
SOMEONE rises from the table and trods off.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS174
As SOMEONE stands, SOMEONE weaves toward him.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS175
She comes up behind him as he heads around the pool.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS176
SOMEONE gives a bashful smile.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS177
He glances over his shoulder.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS178
SOMEONE's smile fades.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS179
She holds SOMEONE's gaze then reaches into her bag.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS180
She hands him her contact info and he nods.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS181
He strides off. Later, the chief faces a laptop and types, SOMEONE Dayne Wall Street Journal WMD into a Google search field. On a results page, the top link reads, Iraqi WMD program still active.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS182
Scanning down the page, SOMEONE finds links to more of SOMEONE's articles. Sulochana Security Review, Iraqi chemical weapons programs, evidence of toxins at WMD sites, and IO agents and gas at an Iraqi university.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS183
Focusing intently on the screen, SOMEONE reads an article entitled, News Source Confirms Iraq WMD Program. As his eyes scan the text, he takes note of specific phrases. A high ranking Iraqi official code named Magellan gave compelling information about Iraq's WMD program. Magellan identified specific site locations. The soldier blinks thoughtfully at the article's mention of botulin toxin at a facility at Diwaniya, an underground storage network at SOMEONE Monsieur.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS187
while driving onto a compound, passes a departing military convoy. SOMEONE rides in the passenger seat.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS188
SOMEONE rides in the passenger seat.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS190
Now the white Jeep splashes through a puddle as it drives down a desolate road.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS191
It pulls up in front of an abandoned mansion surrounded by rubble and SOMEONE climbs out of the passenger seat. In the mansion's debris-strewn foyer, he finds a dolphin statue and two soldiers.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS192
SOMEONE jogs upstairs. In a neglected, once luxurious bedroom, SOMEONE slings a backpack over his shoulder, closes the laptop, and grabs his gun from the bed.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS193
Standing beside a Humvee, they lock eyes.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS194
SOMEONE studies him skeptically then glances away.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS195
SOMEONE strolls off.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS196
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk into a CIA compound.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS197
SOMEONE sits in a cubicle.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS198
SOMEONE blinks thoughtfully.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS199
He shifts his gaze to SOMEONE and offers a firm nod.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS200
SOMEONE hands him a folder.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS201
He opens a safe.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS202
SOMEONE gawks disbelievingly.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS203
SOMEONE steadily holds his gaze. SOMEONE slings the money filled backpack over his shoulder and leaves. Outside, SOMEONE waits by his sedan.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS204
As SOMEONE exits the building, the white Jeep
GREEN_ZONE_DVS205
and the SUV speed into
GREEN_ZONE_DVS207
He strides past SOMEONE then glances back at him.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS208
SOMEONE shifts his confused gaze and heads to his Humvee. SOMEONE loiters nearby, his car now tagged with the letters US on its door.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS210
A colleague makes a call.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS211
As SOMEONE unfolds it and skims its contents, more pentagon agents filter into the control room. He lifts his eyes to SOMEONE's.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS212
SOMEONE glares angrily.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS213
SOMEONE smugly tilts his head.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS214
A pentagon agent hurries over with the black book in hand and passes it to SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS215
As SOMEONE and his agents leave, SOMEONE watches with narrowed eyes. SOMEONE heads into a lobby.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS216
the special forces leader and hands him the black book. The soldier pockets it.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS223
SOMEONE eyes them expressionlessly.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS224
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE through a gate. A sign reads, Camp Cropper, Theater Internment Facility. In a front office,
GREEN_ZONE_DVS225
SOMEONE presents some paperwork.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS226
opens his backpack and a guard approaches SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS227
He pats the civilian down. Beside them, a guard seated at a desk watches a basketball game on TV. The soldier inspecting SOMEONE's backpack finds plastic wrapped stacks of bills inside. He shows the sergeant.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS228
The guard inspects SOMEONE's belongings.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS229
They head into a narrow hallway where doors with padlocked bolts line the walls every five feet. A man hangs his hands into the hall through a slot at the bottom of his door. He reaches out as SOMEONE passes.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS230
The guide stops a few doors down.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS232
He secures his leg irons to a ring in the floor.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS233
The guard removes the man's hood and tosses it on the table then posts himself in the corner of the room. SOMEONE stares at him.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS234
He exits. Facing the detainee,
GREEN_ZONE_DVS235
SOMEONE checks his watch. The prisoner's chest heaves, streaks of blood staining his cheek.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS236
He glances uneasily at SOMEONE who waits with his hands on his hips. As the civilian averts his gaze and fidgets, the detainee eyes them nervously.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS237
SOMEONE stoically checks his watch again.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS244
They head down a corridor.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS245
A guard opens a chain-linked gate for them and they turn a corner. As the strapping guard unlocks a cell, SOMEONE eyes two guards in a comfy caged in office.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS246
In the cell, SOMEONE lies prostrate on the floor, his back to the door. SOMEONE nudges him with his foot and SOMEONE's chest heaves.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS247
The strapping guard hesitates. SOMEONE props up SOMEONE's head.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS248
The battered SOMEONE murmurs.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS249
Blood and bruises mar his face.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS250
SOMEONE's body.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS251
SOMEONE leans close and the prisoner winces.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS252
SOMEONE enters.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS253
SOMEONE stands and backs off.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS256
The mustached man and a cohort pull on ski masks and grab guns. Now in a safe house, three aides in business suits
GREEN_ZONE_DVS257
sit on a couch playing cards at a coffee table. A burly man with a trim goatee trudges in.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS258
The burly man nods and ambles off. In a back room, a dignified man assembles a bomb at a well-lit desk. He twists two wires together.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS265
shadowy corridor, he uses a flashlight. SOMEONE passes a room with an open door. Peeking inside, he finds a group of journalists working at computers. The soldier strides onward, brushing past two men in bulletproof vests. SOMEONE faces a door and knocks.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS266
It swings open revealing a stunned SOMEONE on her cellphone.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS267
She angles the receiver toward her mouth.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS268
She hangs up and leads him in.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS269
SOMEONE closes the door behind them.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS270
SOMEONE nervously sweeps a wisp of hair out of her face.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS271
She paces and rifles through some papers.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS272
She summons a breath and drops her gaze.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS273
The journalist shifts uneasily from foot to foot.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS274
SOMEONE turns away and wanders to a wall papered with photos and notes then fearfully locks eyes with the soldier.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS275
She wearily touches her forehead.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS276
SOMEONE freezes. Facing SOMEONE earnestly, she starts to bite her lip then stifles the action.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS277
The chief stares incredulously. SOMEONE whirls away.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS278
SOMEONE paces again to the wall serving as her makeshift bulletin board and faces him.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS279
SOMEONE stares with an arched brow then strides out. The journalist's sheepish gaze drifts after him. Now, SOMEONE storms through CIA offices.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS280
He finds SOMEONE in a computer analysis room.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS281
He slings down his backpack.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS282
SOMEONE gapes then glances at a technician as he heads out.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS283
SOMEONE follows.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS284
The two men lock eyes. SOMEONE's gaze drifts and he marches into the control room.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS285
He types at his computer.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS286
SOMEONE stalks around a central desk.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS287
He halts, facing the young soldier.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS288
SOMEONE's lips stutter thoughtfully.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS289
Another tech works at a computer. SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS290
Now, SOMEONE's car speeds.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS291
Two of SOMEONE's men descend a stairwell. At the bottom, the lean man opens a door and peeks outside into a motionless alley.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS292
He and his stocky companion stride out. Nearby, the masked assassins prowl after them through the shadows.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS293
SOMEONE's men near their car, the lean man toting a gun. The assassins hurry closer.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS294
Where is he? He bashes the man against a wall. Tell me!
GREEN_ZONE_DVS295
knew, I would not tell you.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS296
He gets shot. A Met-D soldier stalks into the alley behind him, his gun smoking.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS297
He kicks the assassin's
GREEN_ZONE_DVS298
gun away. SOMEONE arrives.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS299
SOMEONE faces the stocky man as the other soldier unmasks the dead assassin.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS300
Now, agents and techs bustle around the CIA control room. A spiky haired tech speaks up.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS301
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS302
SOMEONE faces his team.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS303
members disperse. SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS304
The civilian stares imploringly. Seated in the Humvee, SOMEONE glances away and licks his lips.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS305
SOMEONE shakes his head and backs away, summoning a quavering breath. He storms to his car.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS306
The Humvee pulls out, followed by SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS308
up and down the street, then jogs across it.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS309
Now, in a safe house, he runs upstairs and knocks at a door.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS310
An aide opens up and al-Malik enters. SOMEONE stares out a window inside.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS311
He faces his commander.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS313
The general blinks.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS317
The bald general stares inscrutably.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS318
Green zone, street lights glow around the domed palace. In a ballroom mess hall, a 20 foot American flag drapes a wall above hundreds of soldiers and civilians.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS319
SOMEONE eyes a large screen showing President Bush.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS320
He answers his satellite phone.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS321
SOMEONE enters a control room.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS322
In the mess hall, SOMEONE rises from the table.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS323
SOMEONE whirls toward a screen. A bar highlights the words, Met-Delta on a list and a satellite map shows a moving icon. SOMEONE sneers and lifts his phone.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS324
SOMEONE exits the palace.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS327
In a control room, a grey haired tech answers a phone.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS328
He hangs up and strides into SOMEONE's cubicle.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS330
Headlights flicker then turn off. Behind him, the Humvee cuts its headlights as well. The vehicles drive onward through the shadows then slow to a stop. SOMEONE and his squad climb out.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS331
As an armed soldier mounts the roof of the Humvee, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE on foot to the mouth of the alley.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS332
He falls back behind the chief. Creeping along a wall, SOMEONE peeks out at compound across the street where several busses sit parked. The soldier studies them carefully then faces his men.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS333
Leaving his men behind, SOMEONE strides out into the street and heads for the bus station. Scanning his desolate surroundings, he passes an abandoned hatchback.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS334
Back at the alley, SOMEONE peeks around the corner and watches the chief pass a tall boxy bus. SOMEONE glances at it then arrives at the two-story cement ticketing kiosk. Graffiti covers its walls and bars protect its windows. The chief slows then wearily circles to the back of the building and halts.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS335
A dog trots across a street and takes cover under a parked bus.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS336
SOMEONE looks over his shoulder and spots one of his men stalking out the alley and across the street following his path. Clutching his weapon, the soldier ducks into a shadow and vanishes. SOMEONE strolls forward uneasily.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS337
A man stands behind a bus.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS338
The chief studies him quizzically then uses his radio.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS339
Now, journalists crowd a press conference. As a camera flashes, a pentagon official struts in and takes his place.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS340
Meanwhile, SOMEONE hurries down a stairwell. At the bus station, SOMEONE prowls behind a row of parked buses. Halting, he gazes down a narrow passage between two of the hulking vehicles then treads through it. Nearby, three of his men take positions around other buses, all hold their weapons at the ready. SOMEONE reaches the end of a bus and peeks around it. Up ahead of it, SOMEONE 's envoy paces down a street then expectantly glances over his shoulder at SOMEONE. As the chief heads after him, the envoy turns a corner. SOMEONE radios in.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS341
SOMEONE's men skulk onward and he pads down the alley, glances up at the bleak apartments looming above him.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS342
SOMEONE sits among the assembled journalists.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS343
SOMEONE watches smugly.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS344
Now, SOMEONE watches on TV.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS346
Now, SOMEONE emerges from an alley and spies SOMEONE's envoy yard ahead, maintaining a steady pace. SOMEONE follows, matching his gait.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS347
He glances at an Iraqi woman in an upper window, then radios in.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS348
Now, his four team members emerge from the alley and take up positions. Scant light and shadows crisscrossing the street play across SOMEONE's face as he advances. Ahead, SOMEONE's envoy breaks into a run and disappears around a corner. SOMEONE crosses another intersection, his gaze searching for a visual on the stranger. A block or so behind, one of his men scopes the street with a night vision lens.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS349
SOMEONE radios his team.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS351
and barricade him in.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS353
SOMEONE grabs a pistol from under his sedan's backseat and hustles off.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS357
Outside, the helicopters pass overhead. On the ground, SOMEONE peeks around a corner then hustles.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS358
He jabs a pistol into SOMEONE's shoulder.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS359
away from the landing zone. Back in the sitting room, SOMEONE leans close to SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS361
SOMEONE enters the room as SOMEONE winces away from his tormentor.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS362
Under the general's solemn care-worn gaze, the young militant straightens. As he stares at his imposing superior, SOMEONE nods him toward the door. SOMEONE shuffles out.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS363
A gunman's rifle hovers at a relaxed angle by SOMEONE's face. The American looks to SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS364
Outside, SOMEONE and his men advance down an alley. Elsewhere, the Iraqi in street clothes keeps running.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS365
The night sky camouflages his shadowy form. Back with SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS366
The two officers stare intently at each other.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS367
SOMEONE steps closer, studying his captive.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS368
Outside, in the Adaiah district, two of SOMEONE's armed followers guard the gated garage door. A green night vision view shows them clearly.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS369
As a crouched sniper keeps a bead on the Iraqi men from 100 yards off, fellow soldiers creep across the street. The sniper is SOMEONE. He relaxes his aim and radios the Humvee convoy.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS370
SOMEONE seizes SOMEONE by the collar.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS371
SOMEONE's calm harsh gaze glares at SOMEONE who searches the general's eyes. The high ranking Iraqi lets go and nods to his gunman who rifle butts SOMEONE in the face.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS372
Now, theIraqi in street clothes pounds on a metal door.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS373
As the Special Forces infiltrate an alley, an SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS375
kept positions near the rooftop water tower. On the ground, SOMEONE and his men stick to the shadows and post themselves.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS377
The American reels on the floor holding his head.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS379
They park, lights out.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS380
SOMEONE keeps an eye on the garage door guards. The Humvee commander watches the water tower.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS381
The Humvee lies in wait. Now, on the hideout's roof.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS383
throws down a grenade.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS384
The blast erupts outside, dust.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS387
out of reach. Outside, SOMEONE and his team shoot at a side door.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS388
then a grenade.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS390
his foe, both grab the gun.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS391
he's hit a wall and they drop it again. Now, the special forces encounter armed Iraqi.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS392
SOMEONE pins his attacker
GREEN_ZONE_DVS393
and duck and hurls him
GREEN_ZONE_DVS394
spraying the wall with bullets and blood.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS396
commandeered rifle and moves.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS400
He and his aide head upstairs. Now, SOMEONE reaches the same junction and starts for the hall.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS402
Now, SOMEONE and his attachment reach the sitting room.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS403
The leader eyes the fallen Iraqi bleeding out on the floor.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS404
Upstairs, SOMEONE rounds a corner, gets a glimpse of them, and sprints faster.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS405
As SOMEONE takes the stairs, SOMEONE and his aide exit.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS406
fire peppers the alley.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS407
SOMEONE veers right after
GREEN_ZONE_DVS408
his man near the building exit.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS412
SOMEONE heads off. Now, SOMEONE runs under a clothesline.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS415
the apartment, shuts the door, but SOMEONE immediately bursts through it.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS416
The general and his aide cross a dim alcove and disappear through a bead curtain doorway. SOMEONE follows, only steps behind.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS417
Now, as SOMEONE and his aide move on, fiery blasts.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS418
He kicks in a door, upsetting three Iraqi women and one young kid.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS419
in a doorway and peers up at the passing surveillance chopper.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS420
SOMEONE's aide points out a window.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS421
in a room, the aide uses a radio.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS423
SOMEONE's aide confers with the general.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS425
Across a courtyard, they show up on the chopper's monitor.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS426
He ducks aside with his rifle and covers SOMEONE's advance. The general runs, gripping a pistol.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS428
SOMEONE stares, his features awash in a fiery glow.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS430
Return fire kills.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS434
in a clearing at the market's end, separated by a row of ruined stalls.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS435
the general.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS437
SOMEONE runs.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS438
SOMEONE aims at his fellow American then at the fleeing general.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS439
fire as SOMEONE's aide shoots him.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS440
gets to his feet and shoots the bodyguard. Turning, he trains his weapon on SOMEONE. Still holding a pistol, the general raises his hands. He gently tosses his weapon away. Edging closer, SOMEONE glances back at SOMEONE and finds him staring lifelessly. He faces SOMEONE and extends a pointing finger.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS441
His sweat-soaked chest heaving, the general obeys. As an explosion yards away rains sparks, SOMEONE sidesteps on a path parallel to SOMEONE's.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS442
Stepping out from behind a low pile of rubble, SOMEONE plants his feet and gazes steadily at SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS443
SOMEONE's brow knits. A flash of light briefly illuminates SOMEONE's steady undaunted stare the other side. The general falls and SOMEONE aims at the civilian.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS445
SOMEONE stands motionless.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS446
Turning, he briefly meets SOMEONE's gaze. He looks back down at the fallen general then tosses his weapon aside.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS447
His features mostly hidden in shadow, SOMEONE stares at the American with a knitted brow.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS448
His chest heaves. SOMEONE's glare softens into a stunned gape and he lowers his weapon. The battle scarred local presses his lips closed.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS449
SOMEONE turns, peering into the shadows at the other end of the market. He faces SOMEONE who firmly stands his ground, hands at his sides.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS450
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a parting look then lumbers away.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS451
SOMEONE grimly regards the fallen general, lowers his rifle, and heads back through the marketplace. Small fires burn here and there amid the tattered stalls. As our view drifts above the surrounding buildings, a passing Humvee's headlights sweep over a nearby wall. We peer out over the nighttime city as explosions flash.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS452
gilded bed in his neglected room, SOMEONE works at a laptop. Key phrases show as he types - under the auspices of the office of, capricious at best and at worst, intentional distortions and false assertions of high ranking officials, spanning all four mobile exploitations, total mission failure, unavoidable suspicion, manufactured intelligence, evidence that a senior civilian, knowingly promoted.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS453
palace, reports swarm SOMEONE as he arrives.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS454
Near the entrance, he gravely takes in the crowd of journalists.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS455
They haul out a load of hard framed trunks and cases. By the bed, the chief adjusts his battle vest and shoulders his backpack. Later, he leaves with his helmet in hand. Now, inside the palace.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS456
As he and others reach a meeting room, SOMEONE welcomes them. SOMEONE grins at the pentagon official.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS458
In the sunlit room, local officials stand waiting, some in long Arabic scarves, others in business suits. SOMEONE addresses his new associates.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS459
In the hall with the press, SOMEONE's smile fades as she spies SOMEONE.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS460
He sees her staring.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS461
Elsewhere, SOMEONE climbs a stairway. He reaches a landing where a giant American flag covers one of the walls. Through a doorway, he finds SOMEONE giving an interview.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS462
The Washington official notices the approaching soldier.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS463
He steps away, intercepting SOMEONE in the adjoining room.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS464
SOMEONE stares then musters a nod.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS465
As he peruses the report, SOMEONE watches him coldly. SOMEONE's jaw tightens in a repressed scowl. Looking up from the file, he glances around then lifts his brow.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS466
SOMEONE bridles then draws himself up.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS467
He allows a brief smirk.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS468
SOMEONE backs off, seething at the corrupt official.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS469
He rejoins his staff.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS470
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE watching him from a doorway. They share a grim knowing look. Turning away, the soldier lumbers out. SOMEONE bites her lower lip as she stares after him.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS471
an oscillating fan swivels behind her as other journalists bustle. SOMEONE sets a notepad beside her computer.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS472
She finds an untitled message from SOMEONE in her email inbox.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS473
She opens the email which reads, Let's get this story right this time. See attached. SOMEONE glances down, working her laptop touchpad and leans toward her screen. It displays a document titled, Falsification of WMD intel, the truth about Magellan. SOMEONE scans the text. A signature reads, Respectfully, Roy R. SOMEONE, Chief Warrant Officer, US Army. Underneath, a distribution list includes email addresses for virtually every prominent American newspaper, news magazine, and broadcaster. SOMEONE's jaw drops. The list of addresses goes on and on. Summoning a breath, SOMEONE smiles. Now, SOMEONE strides outside through a doorway framed by stained glass panels.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS474
rolls down a highway. SOMEONE rides shotgun aboard one vehicle.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS475
and a headset microphone.
GREEN_ZONE_DVS476
An aerial view of the parched landscape shows the convoy churning up dust on the
GREEN_ZONE_DVS477
forward to the horizon past two enormous oil tanks and other structures in the distance.