In a mansion
GROWN_UPS_DVS14
Outside a car rolls across the lawn.
GROWN_UPS_DVS15
The family runs outside. A young girl exits the car.
GROWN_UPS_DVS20
At another house a photo shows the five boys with their coach, Outside, a husky guy plays with two kids in an above ground pool.
GROWN_UPS_DVS21
As his busty wife brings the phone, he tries to climb out. The pool breaks and
GROWN_UPS_DVS22
takes the phone.
GROWN_UPS_DVS24
a man ends a call.
GROWN_UPS_DVS26
As he storms off, his mother-in-law speaks up.
GROWN_UPS_DVS27
In a studio apartment
GROWN_UPS_DVS28
a guy with a blond SOMEONE uses the phone.
GROWN_UPS_DVS29
A woman in bed kicks him.
GROWN_UPS_DVS30
He eyes a tattoo of O. J. Simpson on her calf.
GROWN_UPS_DVS31
With a poufy-haired man
GROWN_UPS_DVS32
A heavy-set blond on a massage table looks up, her hair hiding her face.
GROWN_UPS_DVS34
She's an old woman!
GROWN_UPS_DVS38
Words appear. New England. A luxury SUV parks in front of a white-steepled church. Inside, the lanky SOMEONE sits behind the wheel. Beside him, his exotic wife wears
GROWN_UPS_DVS39
SOMEONE gives a horrified gape.
GROWN_UPS_DVS40
Her mother wears a hat.
GROWN_UPS_DVS41
She aims for his lips.
GROWN_UPS_DVS42
SOMEONE checks his cellphone.
GROWN_UPS_DVS43
The guys notice that
GROWN_UPS_DVS44
they flick their tongues at each other.
GROWN_UPS_DVS45
Wind lifts SOMEONE's poufy toupee.
GROWN_UPS_DVS46
into the church.
GROWN_UPS_DVS48
A burly man turns and taps a friend with a wonky eye.
GROWN_UPS_DVS49
SOMEONE leans close to SOMEONE.
GROWN_UPS_DVS50
Nearby, Mama Ronzoni sits on her grandson's handheld video game.
GROWN_UPS_DVS54
SOMEONE stands nervously. He makes his way down the aisle of packed pews, then steps up in front of the flower-adorned casket.
GROWN_UPS_DVS57
Later, SOMEONE sings.
GROWN_UPS_DVS61
The pastor stares, aghast. In the pews, SOMEONE and SOMEONE crack
GROWN_UPS_DVS62
SOMEONE sinks down on one knee. SOMEONE shakes his head.
GROWN_UPS_DVS63
a five-dollar SOMEONE
GROWN_UPS_DVS64
SOMEONE cups a hand to his mouth.
GROWN_UPS_DVS65
Later, at an outdoor reception
GROWN_UPS_DVS68
SOMEONE's son runs up to an arbor.
GROWN_UPS_DVS69
She breastfeeds him. SOMEONE covers SOMEONE's eyes.
GROWN_UPS_DVS70
Seated next to her, SOMEONE stares and slides away.
GROWN_UPS_DVS71
angrily throws a piece of
GROWN_UPS_DVS72
SOMEONE laughs.
GROWN_UPS_DVS74
He tosses a limp
GROWN_UPS_DVS75
SOMEONE pinches SOMEONE.
GROWN_UPS_DVS76
She crosses the porch. SOMEONE opens the door.
GROWN_UPS_DVS79
SOMEONE smiles tightly. Exploring the room, SOMEONE and SOMEONE find an old TV set and knock on its bulky casing.
GROWN_UPS_DVS83
He stands.
GROWN_UPS_DVS84
Now outside, SOMEONE and his boyhood friends eye SOMEONE's shaggy blond dog.
GROWN_UPS_DVS87
He carries his sons out.
GROWN_UPS_DVS90
Small brown bird flaps feebly.
GROWN_UPS_DVS94
His wife breastfeeds their son.
GROWN_UPS_DVS96
SOMEONE shifts her confused gaze.
GROWN_UPS_DVS99
Everyone looks over.
GROWN_UPS_DVS100
His wife gives him a look.
GROWN_UPS_DVS101
She throws down her napkin and storms off.
GROWN_UPS_DVS102
Outside a restroom,
GROWN_UPS_DVS107
SOMEONE carries a shoebox.
GROWN_UPS_DVS109
SOMEONE wears stylish heels.
GROWN_UPS_DVS110
SOMEONE leaves confusedly.
GROWN_UPS_DVS113
From the porch, Mama Ronzoni looks in at the dog.
GROWN_UPS_DVS114
Now sitting outside on the porch, SOMEONE places a strip of bacon on the bug zapper.
GROWN_UPS_DVS115
He sets down another strip.
GROWN_UPS_DVS116
He spots SOMEONE picking up a rock near the lake.
GROWN_UPS_DVS117
He just stares at it.
GROWN_UPS_DVS118
SOMEONE drops the rock back on the ground.
GROWN_UPS_DVS119
SOMEONE wears pantaloons.
GROWN_UPS_DVS120
He sulks off.
GROWN_UPS_DVS122
SOMEONE stops chewing.
GROWN_UPS_DVS123
He pulls a moth from his mouth.
GROWN_UPS_DVS125
and SOMEONE rows alone.
GROWN_UPS_DVS127
SOMEONE stands facing the water and wrinkles his brow.
GROWN_UPS_DVS129
the island, SOMEONE carries a bucket of KFC and SOMEONE totes a boom box.
GROWN_UPS_DVS133
Holding the basketball net around the urn, SOMEONE removes its lid.
GROWN_UPS_DVS134
He takes a handful of ashes and tosses them.
GROWN_UPS_DVS135
He retrieves more and scatters it into the air with an underhand throw.
GROWN_UPS_DVS136
Stifling a grin, SOMEONE exchanges a glance with SOMEONE. SOMEONE closes the urn and bows his head.
GROWN_UPS_DVS139
in denim short-shorts and a midriff
GROWN_UPS_DVS140
The young woman eyes them.
GROWN_UPS_DVS141
SOMEONE steps past his friends and heads over.
GROWN_UPS_DVS142
He hugs her.
GROWN_UPS_DVS144
Andre and SOMEONE watch from inside SOMEONE's car.
GROWN_UPS_DVS145
Later, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE sit in chairs watching as SOMEONE leans over her car to fix it.
GROWN_UPS_DVS146
They ogle SOMEONE's long legs and butt.
GROWN_UPS_DVS147
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare at SOMEONE while the other two look away.
GROWN_UPS_DVS148
They switch.
GROWN_UPS_DVS149
They stare in the same direction.
GROWN_UPS_DVS151
Gloria hugs her.
GROWN_UPS_DVS152
She dons her glasses and peers under the hood.
GROWN_UPS_DVS153
Using pliers, she removes a lid
GROWN_UPS_DVS154
out. Her hair blows backwards
GROWN_UPS_DVS155
and forward. SOMEONE watches
GROWN_UPS_DVS156
flapping in the breeze. They playfully fight over
GROWN_UPS_DVS157
in a churning motion
GROWN_UPS_DVS158
They turn their chairs away.
GROWN_UPS_DVS159
They fish from the boathouse.
GROWN_UPS_DVS165
now in the woods
GROWN_UPS_DVS166
In slow motion, SOMEONE sprints with wide eyes, his mouth agape, while SOMEONE runs with his hands over his head.
GROWN_UPS_DVS168
and drops to his knees.
GROWN_UPS_DVS170
terrified eyes fixed on the sky, a tree branch clotheslines him.
GROWN_UPS_DVS171
Holding his cramped leg, SOMEONE looks
GROWN_UPS_DVS172
and he races over to the dog as the arrow plummets to the ground.
GROWN_UPS_DVS173
He throws the dog over his shoulder.
GROWN_UPS_DVS174
The lanky hero steps on SOMEONE as he runs
GROWN_UPS_DVS175
The arrow lands in SOMEONE's foot!
GROWN_UPS_DVS176
Now in a bedroom, SOMEONE sits studying in a
GROWN_UPS_DVS177
SOMEONE packs a suitcase. She faces SOMEONE with a wide-eyed glare.
GROWN_UPS_DVS180
SOMEONE freezes, her eyes widening.
GROWN_UPS_DVS181
With a guilty stare, she takes a deep breath.
GROWN_UPS_DVS182
SOMEONE runs from the room. SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE who hurries out after her. With a remorseful gaze.
GROWN_UPS_DVS183
She sits down on a bench at the foot of the bed.
GROWN_UPS_DVS184
Later, she sits up in bed while SOMEONE packs.
GROWN_UPS_DVS187
She buries herself under the covers.
GROWN_UPS_DVS188
using cups and string
GROWN_UPS_DVS190
SOMEONE frowns at the cup in his hand, then puts it to his ear.
GROWN_UPS_DVS191
He quickly lowers it. Smiling bemusedly, he follows the out another door and down a hallway. He peeks around a corner. The string leads to a chair where Mama Ronzoni sits knitting.
GROWN_UPS_DVS192
Now in bed, SOMEONE uses a cup phone.
GROWN_UPS_DVS197
The next morning at a kitchen table, SOMEONE feeds the injured bird with liquid from a narrow tube. It leads to a pump on SOMEONE's breast. SOMEONE watches.
GROWN_UPS_DVS199
Now SOMEONE stands by the SUV composing a text message as SOMEONE sits buried inside
GROWN_UPS_DVS201
The mother pauses and looks to the lake shore where her kids skep stones with their
GROWN_UPS_DVS202
SOMEONE heads over.
GROWN_UPS_DVS203
Donna skips the stone across the water.
GROWN_UPS_DVS205
In the house,
GROWN_UPS_DVS206
SOMEONE crosses to his beaming wife.
GROWN_UPS_DVS208
SOMEONE stoically spits some out.
GROWN_UPS_DVS209
cones in their hands as they walk.
GROWN_UPS_DVS210
SOMEONE arrives.
GROWN_UPS_DVS211
It's an unrevealing one-piece
GROWN_UPS_DVS212
slinky bathing suit, SOMEONE quick
GROWN_UPS_DVS213
The others follow her gaze.
GROWN_UPS_DVS216
SOMEONE sips from the carton.
GROWN_UPS_DVS220
They gape lustfully.
GROWN_UPS_DVS221
He has dazzling smile.
GROWN_UPS_DVS224
He zip line across the park.
GROWN_UPS_DVS226
He steps up to the platform and grabs the handles.
GROWN_UPS_DVS227
Now at the lake house, the fathers and sons play
GROWN_UPS_DVS228
SOMEONE to throw horseshoes.
GROWN_UPS_DVS230
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE gesture to her breasts.
GROWN_UPS_DVS232
SOMEONE stares at Amber and Jan
GROWN_UPS_DVS233
stares, too. SOMEONE catches
GROWN_UPS_DVS234
She spots her husband wading in the lake with SOMEONE as she catches guppies in a jar.
GROWN_UPS_DVS235
lake lodge. Inside, the adults toast marshmallows.
GROWN_UPS_DVS241
each other gracefully
GROWN_UPS_DVS243
Later at the lake house, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE asleep on the couch and slaps him on the forehead.
GROWN_UPS_DVS244
SOMEONE stands in the kitchen with a jug of water.
GROWN_UPS_DVS247
SOMEONE gets another jug from the fridge and both men guzzle their water.
GROWN_UPS_DVS250
They gulp some more.
GROWN_UPS_DVS251
They guzzle again.
GROWN_UPS_DVS256
SOMEONE's forehead.
GROWN_UPS_DVS257
He flutters his hands against SOMEONE's face. SOMEONE
GROWN_UPS_DVS259
He walks his fingers over SOMEONE's forehead.
GROWN_UPS_DVS261
morning, the families raise the American flag on the boathouse's rooftop patio.
GROWN_UPS_DVS262
Later in the lake house, SOMEONE works
GROWN_UPS_DVS264
SOMEONE staggers out of the closet.
GROWN_UPS_DVS265
Mama Ronzoni's funeral hat. He finds the breast pump on his nipple.
GROWN_UPS_DVS266
Curly steps out of the closet and stands beside him.
GROWN_UPS_DVS269
He lowers the ice, revealing a cut.
GROWN_UPS_DVS271
SOMEONE and Andre duck behind the stairs.
GROWN_UPS_DVS273
SOMEONE eyes him.
GROWN_UPS_DVS281
SOMEONE and Donna climb the
GROWN_UPS_DVS282
stop. Later on a basketball court,
GROWN_UPS_DVS284
SOMEONE stands and limps forward.
GROWN_UPS_DVS286
Now, SOMEONE points.
GROWN_UPS_DVS287
of a hill, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE
GROWN_UPS_DVS289
He eats his daughter's dessert instead.
GROWN_UPS_DVS291
Bending over, Riley lowers his raised arms. His hand rubs SOMEONE's breast!
GROWN_UPS_DVS292
some spectators
GROWN_UPS_DVS293
In slow motion, SOMEONE eyes the open basket then looks at Bailey's disheartened expression. Pressing his lips together, he shifts his gaze to Bailey's wife, who watches hopefully. SOMEONE turns back to the basket and shoots. The ball arcs into the
GROWN_UPS_DVS294
air. Hitting the backboard, it drops onto the basket's rim then bounces away from the net. The
GROWN_UPS_DVS295
hugs his teammates and the crowd rushes over.
GROWN_UPS_DVS297
He produces a bow and arrow.
GROWN_UPS_DVS298
He looks up.
GROWN_UPS_DVS299
He grins.
GROWN_UPS_DVS300
His eyes roll back and he faints.