He jogs up a corridor then kicks open a coal door and slides down a spiraling chute.
HUGO_DVS23
At the bottom, he runs past damp brick walls then scurries through a labyrinth of pipes and machinery.
HUGO_DVS24
He ducks through a large gear with thick spokes then races up a spiral staircase.
HUGO_DVS25
Turning down another narrow hallway with steam rising through the grating, the boy reaches another clock powered by a complex mechanism of spinning gears.
HUGO_DVS26
He peers through the clock's open numbers at a toy shop below. Surrounded by dolls, rocking horses, musical instruments, and other items, a bearded white-haired man sits behind the counter with his chin propped on one hand.
HUGO_DVS27
The man glances sideways and narrows his eyes as he studies the clock.
HUGO_DVS28
The boy stares back through the number four.
HUGO_DVS30
The man releases a wind-up mouse, watches it scoot across the counter,
HUGO_DVS31
then retrieves it.
HUGO_DVS32
A brown-haired girl wearing a beret steps up beside the man and sets down a loaf of bread.
HUGO_DVS33
He gestures towards the back of the shop.
HUGO_DVS35
The girl stands and smiles at the man. Looking at her, he shrugs then nods emphatically.
HUGO_DVS36
Slowly, she turns and walks away with the bread. The boy watches as the man lowers his head and shuts his eyes.
HUGO_DVS38
His hands rest on the counter, a few inches from the wind-up mouse. Crouching, the boy leaves the clock and scuttles along a crawlspace beneath the walkway.
HUGO_DVS39
He swings open a small metal grate then steps into a tiled corridor, opposite the shop.
HUGO_DVS41
Confiserie et Juet, or candy and toy shop.
HUGO_DVS42
Wearing a tattered coat, shorts, and sweater, the boy creeps toward the store.
HUGO_DVS43
The white-haired man dozes behind the counter. As the boy reaches the toy shop, he reaches one hand toward the wind-up mouse.
HUGO_DVS44
The man suddenly snatches his arm.
HUGO_DVS45
The mouse falls and breaks.
HUGO_DVS46
The boy reaches into his coat pocket then sets items onto the counter: a pocketknife, bundle of string, and a piece of cloth filled with small sprockets, gears, and springs.
HUGO_DVS47
The boy glances over his shoulder then reaches into his other pocket. Glaring at the man, he takes out a small notebook and slaps it onto the counter.
HUGO_DVS48
The man releases the boy's arm then opens the notebook.
HUGO_DVS49
He frowns as he flips through the pages.
HUGO_DVS50
Handwritten notes, mathematical equations, and schematic drawings fill the pages.
HUGO_DVS51
The man inhales sharply as he flips to drawings of a mechanical man's head and torso.
HUGO_DVS52
The shopkeeper squeezes his eyes shut. As he rapidly flips the pages, the drawings become an animation of the automaton turning its head.
HUGO_DVS53
The man shakes the notebook in the boy's face then frowns and slaps it onto the counter.
HUGO_DVS54
Across the station, the station inspector lifts his head.
HUGO_DVS55
The station inspector removes the leash from his dog, who then runs off. The inspector limps through the crowd after him.
HUGO_DVS57
The dog skids across the polished floor as he runs up the hallway opposite the toyshop. The boy spins around then takes off into the crowd.
HUGO_DVS58
Swinging out his unbending left leg as he runs, the inspector follows after them.
HUGO_DVS59
He slams into a woman, spins, then falls on top of her. The five-piece band plays in the cafe as the boy leaps over a bench and upsets a dining table.
HUGO_DVS60
The boy zips through the cafe, then weaves his way through tables out front.
HUGO_DVS61
A woman clutches a small little dog to her chest as the Doberman skids past a large tiered cake, races past the band, then runs out of the other side of the cafe. The station inspector dashes into the cafe.
HUGO_DVS63
Hurtling toward the cake, the inspector turns and crashes into the band. He puts his foot through a bass guitar and falls into the band members. The inspector struggles to his feet.
HUGO_DVS64
Gripping a SOMEONE club, the inspector runs out the other end of the cafe.
HUGO_DVS65
Up ahead, the boy dashes through the crowd then slides under a newspaper vendor's legs.
HUGO_DVS66
The inspector shoves past the man, then pushes his way into a throng of travelers standing on a train platform.
HUGO_DVS67
He limps up the platform along the edge of the tracks, pushing people out of the way as he goes.
HUGO_DVS68
The inspector reaches the end of the platform and gazes around himself.
HUGO_DVS69
His dog paces in a circle. Above them, the boy paces along a narrow catwalk, running across the tracks as a train leaves the station.
HUGO_DVS70
The inspector throws down his club.
HUGO_DVS71
The passing train snags the inspector's leg brace.
HUGO_DVS72
He falls and the train drags him along the platform.
HUGO_DVS73
He slides into a suitcase, which strikes him in the crotch. The dog lies down and lowers his head. Meanwhile, the boy jogs up a grimy corridor filled with gears and steaming pipes. He crawls through a gap in a mesh screen then hops through the spokes of a large gear as it spins. The boy turns down a hallway then opens a metal door.
HUGO_DVS74
He peeks inside.
HUGO_DVS75
Reaching into a pocket, the boy takes out a set of keys as he approaches another metal door.
HUGO_DVS76
He slides a latch then shoves open the heavy door.
HUGO_DVS77
The boy enters an attic with a wood-plank floor and shuts the door behind him.
HUGO_DVS78
Light shines in through narrow windows along the slanted ceiling and illuminates spinning gears and exposed steel girders.
HUGO_DVS79
The boy crosses to a small area in front of three large windows which has been swept clean.
HUGO_DVS80
He steps to a worktable covered in gears, sprockets, and schematic drawings.
HUGO_DVS81
He picks up one gear and compares it to a drawing,
HUGO_DVS82
then tosses it aside.
HUGO_DVS83
Setting his jaw, the boy leaves.
HUGO_DVS84
He climbs down a metal ladder to a large square clock suspended over train station platforms.
HUGO_DVS85
Inside, the boy attaches a handle to the clockwork mechanism and cranks it.
HUGO_DVS86
He oils a gear then stares down at the crowd below.
HUGO_DVS87
Outside the cafe, the brown-haired woman still holds her little dog to her chest.
HUGO_DVS88
The news vendor - a rotund man wearing glasses and a beret - approaches the woman.
HUGO_DVS89
She nods and the man reaches his hand toward her dog.
HUGO_DVS90
The boy smiles.
HUGO_DVS91
Later, he trudges up a metal staircase inside a square tower. Clouds of steam rise up the lofty tower and drift past an enormous pendulum swinging back and forth.
HUGO_DVS92
At the top, large clocks face out from every side. Each controlled by a single mechanism with immense gears. Inching around some stray pigeons, the boy climbs a stepladder beside the mechanism and switches on a lightbulb hanging from a chain.
HUGO_DVS93
He cranks a thick handle protruding from the side of the mechanism.
HUGO_DVS94
Stopping his efforts, the boy gazes out the center of a clock face.
HUGO_DVS95
The sun sets behind the Eiffel Tower in the distance.
HUGO_DVS96
Slowly, he creeps forward and stares out through the clear glass.
HUGO_DVS97
He stands motionless at the top of the clock tower, as the setting sun casts long shadows over the train station and the rest of the sprawling city.
HUGO_DVS98
The white-haired man pulls down a gate as he closes his shop.
HUGO_DVS99
The man turns and faces the boy.
HUGO_DVS101
The man strides off.
HUGO_DVS102
SOMEONE stares after him, then follows through the mostly deserted train station.
HUGO_DVS103
SOMEONE strides closer as they reach the front entrance.
HUGO_DVS104
The shopkeeper turns his back on SOMEONE and walks out.
HUGO_DVS105
SOMEONE stands rooted to the floor, gazing out at the snowy Paris streets beyond.
HUGO_DVS106
SOMEONE throws open the doors and steps outside.
HUGO_DVS107
Shivering against the cold, SOMEONE follows several paces behind the shopkeeper as he crosses a wide brick street.
HUGO_DVS108
SOMEONE rubs his hands together as the man trudges up stone steps then turns down a street lined with tall tenements.
HUGO_DVS109
The twin towers of Notre Dame loom in the distance.
HUGO_DVS110
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder as he trails the man into an alley.
HUGO_DVS111
Hurrying his pace, he falls in step beside the man - who doesn't acknowledge SOMEONE's presence.
HUGO_DVS112
They approach a gate leading to a cemetery filled with snow dusted statues of hooded figures standing with their hands clasped and their heads bowed.
HUGO_DVS113
SOMEONE stares up at the statues as he passes.
HUGO_DVS114
The man walks out of a gate on the opposite side then enters a building's front door- which he shuts in SOMEONE's face.
HUGO_DVS115
SOMEONE furrows his brow.
HUGO_DVS116
He steps back and stares up at the building as a train passes along an elevated track nearby.
HUGO_DVS117
The girl who visited the shopkeeper earlier is visible in an upper window.
HUGO_DVS118
In the window beside it, the shopkeeper steps beside a curly-haired woman.
HUGO_DVS119
SOMEONE tosses a pebble at the girl's window.
HUGO_DVS120
She stands and looks down at him.
HUGO_DVS121
SOMEONE motions for her to come outside then presses his palms together and pleads.
HUGO_DVS122
Frowning, the girl glances over her shoulder.
HUGO_DVS123
A moment later, she opens the front door and steps outside.
HUGO_DVS124
The girl stares at SOMEONE with her arms crossed.
HUGO_DVS125
She steps toward him.
HUGO_DVS126
SOMEONE plants his feet and folds his arms.
HUGO_DVS127
Smiling, the girl nods.
HUGO_DVS128
SOMEONE nods back then turns and runs through the small cemetery.
HUGO_DVS129
Back in the attic, SOMEONE lights a candle and sets it onto a chair seat.
HUGO_DVS130
He turns and yanks a sheet off a doll-sized mechanical man - or automaton - sitting at a small table.
HUGO_DVS131
The automaton's head and hands are solid,
HUGO_DVS132
while it's arms and torso are an open metal framework.
HUGO_DVS133
Gears and sprockets fill the automaton's chest cavity.
HUGO_DVS134
SOMEONE sits across from the automaton and stares at its solid black eyes.
HUGO_DVS135
As the light flickers, clothes materialize on the metallic man.
HUGO_DVS136
Now well dressed and clean, SOMEONE stands with a blonde man with glasses.
HUGO_DVS137
The man sets a small table in front of the automaton.
HUGO_DVS138
SOMEONE's father opens the automaton's shirt and exposes its interior mechanism.
HUGO_DVS139
SOMEONE's father shrugs, then smiles, and hugs him.
HUGO_DVS140
SOMEONE watches his father place a gear assembly into the automaton's chest.
HUGO_DVS141
Later, his father repairs a clock in his shop, which is filled with various gears and mechanisms.
HUGO_DVS142
SOMEONE sweeps nearby.
HUGO_DVS143
At night, his father runs a finger over a heart-shaped keyhole in the automaton's back.
HUGO_DVS144
He flips through his notebook to a page with drawings of a heart-shaped key.
HUGO_DVS145
SOMEONE watches him add another sketch.
HUGO_DVS146
Back in the train station, tears well in SOMEONE's eyes.
HUGO_DVS147
In a museum, SOMEONE's father furrows his brow as he studies a mechanical model of a large sphere with orbiting satellites.
HUGO_DVS148
Standing by a rotating film reel, he glances back over his shoulder and frowns.
HUGO_DVS149
SOMEONE's father walks through the museum,
HUGO_DVS150
passing a sarcophagus adorned with the figure of a pope.
HUGO_DVS151
He steps slowly past marble statues and other works of antiquity and gazes at a pair of closed doors.
HUGO_DVS152
As he throws open the doors, flames twist up a staircase and engulf him.
HUGO_DVS153
Back in the shop, SOMEONE polishes the automaton with a strip of cloth.
HUGO_DVS154
A mustached man wearing a bowler staggers into the room.
HUGO_DVS155
Claude takes a drag from his cigarette, burns his finger, and drops it.
HUGO_DVS156
SOMEONE stares at his uncle then lowers his eyes.
HUGO_DVS157
SOMEONE's eyes flip from side to side as he stares downward.
HUGO_DVS158
SOMEONE recoils as Claude sways into a grandfather clock.
HUGO_DVS159
Claude palms a nearby pocket watch and places it into his coat.
HUGO_DVS160
Later, SOMEONE carries the automaton.
HUGO_DVS161
Claude takes a swig from a flask, as he leads SOMEONE to the station.
HUGO_DVS162
They walk into the attic storeroom.
HUGO_DVS163
SOMEONE unwraps the automaton.
HUGO_DVS164
Claude and SOMEONE visit a grave site.
HUGO_DVS165
Alone with the automaton, SOMEONE blinks away tears.
HUGO_DVS167
In the station, the brown-haired woman walks her little dog to the cafe and opens the door.
HUGO_DVS168
SOMEONE peers through the vent at a tray of steaming croissants.
HUGO_DVS169
The news vendor smiles as he approaches the woman and her dog.
HUGO_DVS170
As he offers the woman a paper, her dog bites him.
HUGO_DVS171
Her dog pulls her away from the cafe.
HUGO_DVS172
As station agents rush to her aide, SOMEONE sneaks out of the vent and creeps toward the tray of croissants.
HUGO_DVS173
Glancing around himself, he steals a roll and a bottle of milk then walks off.
HUGO_DVS174
Wearing his leg brace, the station inspector paces down a staircase and surveys the crowd.
HUGO_DVS175
He leans back against a pillar.
HUGO_DVS176
Still chewing, SOMEONE stands on the other side of the pillar.
HUGO_DVS177
He freezes as the inspector takes out a pocket watch and checks the time.
HUGO_DVS178
SOMEONE ducks as the inspector stretches back his arms, then hides behind the pillar as the inspector turns his head.
HUGO_DVS179
SOMEONE flees in the opposite direction.
HUGO_DVS180
Nearby, the brown-haired flower seller smiles as she pushes her cart through the station.
HUGO_DVS181
Straightening his hat, the inspector walks stiffly towards the woman as she sets up shop.
HUGO_DVS182
Grimacing, the inspector reaches down and unlocks his leg brace.
HUGO_DVS183
He glances toward the flower seller then turns and limps off in the other direction.
HUGO_DVS184
Meanwhile, SOMEONE opens the toyshop.
HUGO_DVS185
He turns and faces SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS186
Staring at SOMEONE, SOMEONE steps forward and hands him a small parcel wrapped in cloth.
HUGO_DVS187
As SOMEONE opens it, ashes and flakes of charred paper spill onto the floor.
HUGO_DVS188
Sobs shake SOMEONE's shoulders.
HUGO_DVS189
He looks up at SOMEONE
HUGO_DVS190
with tears streaming down his cheeks.
HUGO_DVS191
SOMEONE presses his lips together
HUGO_DVS192
then jerks his head to one side.
HUGO_DVS193
SOMEONE wipes his face with a sooty hand then runs off.
HUGO_DVS194
Turning the corner, he barrels into the brown-haired girl.
HUGO_DVS195
She cleans his face with a handkerchief.
HUGO_DVS196
The white-haired bookseller raises his eyebrows as he examines SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS197
SOMEONE stares at the bookseller as he follows SOMEONE to the back of the shop.
HUGO_DVS198
SOMEONE blinks and looks down.
HUGO_DVS199
She glances at SOMEONE and grins.
HUGO_DVS200
SOMEONE selects a book.
HUGO_DVS201
SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's shoulder, smiles, and leaves.
HUGO_DVS202
Scowling, he marches off.
HUGO_DVS203
SOMEONE stands in front of the toyshop and stares at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS204
SOMEONE narrows his eyes.
HUGO_DVS205
Without glancing away from the boy, he reaches under the counter then drops the broken wind-up mouse in front of SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS206
SOMEONE looks down then back at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS207
SOMEONE remains standing with his arms at his sides.
HUGO_DVS208
SOMEONE sets down a cup of small hand tools then folds his arms.
HUGO_DVS209
Stepping forward, SOMEONE picks up a screwdriver and adjusts the toy's wind-up mechanism.
HUGO_DVS210
He takes off the toy' outer shell and uses a small hammer to pound it back into shape.
HUGO_DVS212
He snaps the shell back onto the mechanism,
HUGO_DVS213
tightens it on with screws, then places the repaired mouse back onto the counter.
HUGO_DVS214
SOMEONE picks up the mouse, inserts a key, and winds it up.
HUGO_DVS215
The mouse scuttles over the counter in a figure-eight, rears up on a spring and peers at SOMEONE, forms another figure-eight, and peers at SOMEONE,
HUGO_DVS216
then falls still.
HUGO_DVS217
SOMEONE waves his hand dismissively.
HUGO_DVS218
SOMEONE walks into the shop, then reaches for a broom.
HUGO_DVS219
In the cafe, a musician with a pencil-thin moustache strums a guitar in front of the band.
HUGO_DVS220
People dance or tap their toes as clouds of cigarette smoke fill the air.
HUGO_DVS221
In the toy store, SOMEONE squirts oil onto a model house.
HUGO_DVS222
People are dancing.
HUGO_DVS223
He glances up at SOMEONE, who holds a deck of playing cards topped by the eight of spades.
HUGO_DVS224
As he waves one hand, the eight of diamonds rises from the middle of the deck.
HUGO_DVS225
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, who quickly returns to his work.
HUGO_DVS226
SOMEONE shuffles the cards as he stares at the boy.
HUGO_DVS227
Later, he demonstrates how to fan out a deck of cards.
HUGO_DVS228
SOMEONE attempts it with a deck of his own but fumbles and drops the cards.
HUGO_DVS229
Alone in the attic, kneeling across from the automaton, SOMEONE waves one hand over a deck of cards.
HUGO_DVS230
The king of hearts card floats up into his hand.
HUGO_DVS231
He presents it to the automaton.
HUGO_DVS232
SOMEONE grins.
HUGO_DVS233
In the shop, he paints coat buttons onto a tin soldier.
HUGO_DVS234
In the steamy attic, he reattaches the automatons left arm.
HUGO_DVS235
In the shop, SOMEONE looks up from his work at SOMEONE, who demonstrates dance steps for a group of girls.
HUGO_DVS236
In the attic, he pushes a mechanism's gear with his thumb, spinning a tiny propeller.
HUGO_DVS237
In the main station, SOMEONE stares at her feet as she dances with another girl. She looks up and smiles at SOMEONE, who gasps and turns away.
HUGO_DVS238
In the attic, SOMEONE inserts the repaired mechanism into the automaton's chest cavity and locks it into place.
HUGO_DVS239
Later, the reassembled automaton sits at the small table with a sheet of blank paper and a pen in its right hand.
HUGO_DVS241
SOMEONE winds a crank on the automaton's back.
HUGO_DVS243
Smiling, SOMEONE leaps in front of the automaton and watches.
HUGO_DVS244
A few more gears within the complicated mechanism begin to spin.
HUGO_DVS245
The automaton sits motionless.
HUGO_DVS246
The pen in its hand never moving.
HUGO_DVS247
SOMEONE's smile fades.
HUGO_DVS248
He steps forward and lightly shoves the automaton, then flicks the tiny propeller.
HUGO_DVS249
He forces it to turn, but still nothing happens.
HUGO_DVS250
SOMEONE walks to the back of the automaton and rubs one finger over the heart shaped keyhole.
HUGO_DVS251
SOMEONE pulls off a thin metal rod and drops it onto his worktable.
HUGO_DVS252
In the train station, a dirty boy with ratty hair and clothing glances at SOMEONE as he strolls past the toyshop.
HUGO_DVS253
Holding his dog on a leash, the station inspector stares intently at the boy as he follows him.
HUGO_DVS254
SOMEONE ducks behind the toyshop counter until they pass.
HUGO_DVS255
A businessman reading a newspaper vacates a bench, leaving behind a crumpled paper bag.
HUGO_DVS256
The unwashed boy examines the contents of the bag then peers into an empty glass bottle.
HUGO_DVS257
The station inspector steps up to him.
HUGO_DVS258
The boy tries to run but the dog blocks his retreat. The inspector whips the leash around the boy's ankle.
HUGO_DVS259
The boy now stands in a cage in the inspector's office.
HUGO_DVS260
SOMEONE peers down from a wall clock.
HUGO_DVS261
SOMEONE watches the boy being lead to a policeman's paddy wagon.
HUGO_DVS262
The boy struggles but they toss him into the wagon with a group of other orphans.
HUGO_DVS263
The policeman gives the inspector a photo.
HUGO_DVS264
SOMEONE scurries to another vent and watches SOMEONE give dance lessons.
HUGO_DVS265
Later, SOMEONE explores the bookstore with SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS266
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE then smiles and takes his hand as they walk around a giant stack of books.
HUGO_DVS267
SOMEONE grins.
HUGO_DVS268
SOMEONE smiles back.
HUGO_DVS269
Later, they stand in a street gazing up at a glowing theatre sign - Le Cinema.
HUGO_DVS270
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE then jerks his head to one side.
HUGO_DVS271
They tiptoe around the corner together to a side entrance.
HUGO_DVS272
Taking out a set of small tools, SOMEONE picks the lock.
HUGO_DVS273
He opens the door. Inside the darkened theatre, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit together.
HUGO_DVS274
On the movie screen, Harold SOMEONE dangles from the side of a building by his fingertips.
HUGO_DVS275
He regains his footing and climbs up the corner of the building.
HUGO_DVS276
SOMEONE glances sideways at SOMEONE and smiles.
HUGO_DVS277
As SOMEONE slips, SOMEONE gasps and grabs SOMEONE's arm.
HUGO_DVS278
SOMEONE stands on a window ledge.
HUGO_DVS279
In an apartment, a man swings out the bottom of his window, forcing SOMEONE to grab onto the hands of a nearby clock.
HUGO_DVS280
The clock face starts to detach from the building.
HUGO_DVS281
SOMEONE's legs kick wildly as he hangs by only a few springs.
HUGO_DVS282
A mustached man sneaks up behind SOMEONE and SOMEONE and grabs their shoulders.
HUGO_DVS283
He wrestles them out of their seats and marches them out of the front door.
HUGO_DVS284
SOMEONE and SOMEONE flee up a sidewalk.
HUGO_DVS285
Standing on a bridge, SOMEONE stares at her.
HUGO_DVS286
He takes a step forward then turns and points into the distance.
HUGO_DVS287
The train station's clock tower rises on the other side of the river.
HUGO_DVS288
They walk into the station.
HUGO_DVS289
Brow furrowed the station inspector strides toward them.
HUGO_DVS290
SOMEONE takes off SOMEONE's beret and places it over his own head.
HUGO_DVS291
The station inspector passes them then pauses and turns.
HUGO_DVS292
SOMEONE and SOMEONE freeze.
HUGO_DVS293
SOMEONE starts to slide away but SOMEONE grabs the hem of his coat.
HUGO_DVS294
The station inspector frowns at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS295
His dog sniffs SOMEONE's leg.
HUGO_DVS296
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk off together then glance over their shoulders.
HUGO_DVS297
Across the station, the inspector climbs a series of pegs sticking out of a wall, using only his hands.
HUGO_DVS298
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder then gives SOMEONE her beret back.
HUGO_DVS299
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS300
SOMEONE shoves his way through a crowd of people walking in the opposite direction.
HUGO_DVS301
SOMEONE pushes her way through the crowd after him.
HUGO_DVS302
SOMEONE falls.
HUGO_DVS303
She curls up and covers her head as people step over and around her.
HUGO_DVS304
SOMEONE turns and fights his way back to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS305
Reaching out his hand, he pulls her up off the floor.
HUGO_DVS306
They smile at one another.
HUGO_DVS307
SOMEONE's mouth drops open.
HUGO_DVS308
A heart-shaped key dangles from a cord around SOMEONE's neck.
HUGO_DVS309
SOMEONE stares into SOMEONE's eyes.
HUGO_DVS310
SOMEONE leads her through a back corridor filled with steam and dripping pipes.
HUGO_DVS311
They step into SOMEONE's attic workshop.
HUGO_DVS312
SOMEONE twirls as she gazes around herself.
HUGO_DVS313
SOMEONE yanks the sheet off the automaton.
HUGO_DVS314
SOMEONE peers closely at the automaton then strokes its metal face.
HUGO_DVS315
SOMEONE takes off the key from around her neck
HUGO_DVS316
and hands it to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS317
He looks down at it.
HUGO_DVS318
They stare at one another then both face the automaton.
HUGO_DVS319
SOMEONE walks behind it and turns the crank attached to its back.
HUGO_DVS320
He inserts the heart-shaped key into the lock.
HUGO_DVS321
It fits perfectly.
HUGO_DVS322
He turns the key, steps back beside SOMEONE, and smiles at her.
HUGO_DVS323
Gears and sprockets inside the automaton's chest whirr to life.
HUGO_DVS324
A tumbler of notched plates rotates into a new configuration then drops slightly.
HUGO_DVS325
The teeth of gears mesh together and power various parts of the mechanism. Tiny hammers rise and fall as a patterned cylinder rotates under them.
HUGO_DVS327
Holding a pen above a blank page, The automaton's right arm moves slightly then stops.
HUGO_DVS328
SOMEONE frowns.
HUGO_DVS329
He smiles again as the automaton slides its hand across the desk
HUGO_DVS330
and dips the pen into an ink well.
HUGO_DVS331
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lean forward.
HUGO_DVS332
The automaton moves its hand across the length of the page then makes a small SOMEONE, resembling the letter "J."
HUGO_DVS333
The automaton's head moves up and down and side to side as it writes.
HUGO_DVS334
SOMEONE and SOMEONE smile at one another.
HUGO_DVS336
The automaton moves its hand and makes another scribble, then another, seemingly at random.
HUGO_DVS337
SOMEONE furrows her brow and cocks her head to one side.
HUGO_DVS338
SOMEONE sidles beside the automaton and tilts his head.
HUGO_DVS339
The automaton writes a character resembling a half-formed letter "B"
HUGO_DVS340
then draws a series of short diagonal lines.
HUGO_DVS341
The automaton's head droops as it winds down to a stop.
HUGO_DVS342
SOMEONE stares at the illegible characters then pushes himself away from the table.
HUGO_DVS343
SOMEONE wrings her hands as she watches SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS344
SOMEONE punches a stuffed chair then drops into it and sobs.
HUGO_DVS345
SOMEONE kneels beside him.
HUGO_DVS346
They rush back to the table as the automaton begins writing again.
HUGO_DVS347
Moving its hand, it begins connecting the various shapes and scribbles together with lines.
HUGO_DVS348
SOMEONE smiles.
HUGO_DVS349
He and SOMEONE step on either side of the automaton to get a better view.
HUGO_DVS350
The automaton draws a five-pointed star then a series of curved lines.
HUGO_DVS351
Its metal hands move quicker and quicker across the page.
HUGO_DVS352
It draws circles within circles and a series of overlapping checkmarks.
HUGO_DVS353
The automaton completes the drawing
HUGO_DVS354
and withdraws its hand.
HUGO_DVS355
On the page, a sketch of a rocket ship striking one eye of the Man in the Moon.
HUGO_DVS356
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE and smiles.
HUGO_DVS357
The automaton reaches out its hand and signs a name in cursive at the bottom of the page.
HUGO_DVS359
The automaton's head returns to its normal posing as it stops.
HUGO_DVS360
SOMEONE picks up the drawing and stares at it.
HUGO_DVS361
He glances sideways at the automaton and grins.
HUGO_DVS362
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step through the cemetery then through an iron gate. SOMEONE gazes up at SOMEONE's flat as she unlocks the front door.
HUGO_DVS363
SOMEONE holds the door open as SOMEONE steps inside.
HUGO_DVS364
SOMEONE steps down a hallway then turns into a sitting room.
HUGO_DVS365
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE, who sits and sews.
HUGO_DVS366
SOMEONE stands as SOMEONE steps into the room.
HUGO_DVS367
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE then drops her sewing onto a chair.
HUGO_DVS368
SOMEONE steps toward SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS369
She inspects him intently then turns to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS370
They look at SOMEONE, who pulls a folded piece of paper from an inner-jacket pocket.
HUGO_DVS371
He partially unfolds the paper then holds it out to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS372
She opens it and gazes down at the drawing of the rocket striking the eye of the Man in the Moon.
HUGO_DVS373
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE then looks back at the drawing.
HUGO_DVS374
Still staring at the drawing, SOMEONE slowly sits.
HUGO_DVS375
She glances at SOMEONE then back at the drawing, while raising one hand to her mouth.
HUGO_DVS376
SOMEONE raises her hand toward her own neck then looks at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS377
SOMEONE removes the key from around her own neck.
HUGO_DVS378
SOMEONE holds up the drawing then stands.
HUGO_DVS379
SOMEONE takes the drawing.
HUGO_DVS380
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS381
She places her hand on the side of his head.
HUGO_DVS382
SOMEONE withdraws her hand. She opens the door then immediately closes it.
HUGO_DVS383
SOMEONE turns SOMEONE and SOMEONE around then herds them into another room.
HUGO_DVS384
SOMEONE pulls the door almost shut but immediately opens it.
HUGO_DVS385
She shuts the door.
HUGO_DVS386
SOMEONE turns and eyes an armoire standing against a wall.
HUGO_DVS387
SOMEONE opens the armoire as SOMEONE places her ear against the door.
HUGO_DVS388
SOMEONE searches through stacks of towels, while SOMEONE helps SOMEONE take off his coat in the next room.
HUGO_DVS389
SOMEONE crouches and peeks through a keyhole.
HUGO_DVS390
SOMEONE searches a container then shuts a drawer in the armoire.
HUGO_DVS391
SOMEONE looks up at SOMEONE as she turns her gaze toward the hallway.
HUGO_DVS392
SOMEONE closes the armoire, steps back, then peers at a small panel near the top which juts out slightly.
HUGO_DVS393
He points toward the panel.
HUGO_DVS394
SOMEONE sets a chair in front of the armoire and begins to climb onto it.
HUGO_DVS395
SOMEONE steps onto the chair then inspects the panel.
HUGO_DVS396
In the next room, SOMEONE glances toward the hallway.
HUGO_DVS397
SOMEONE presses the panel flush
HUGO_DVS398
then turns and smiles at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS399
SOMEONE raps lightly on the wood.
HUGO_DVS400
SOMEONE smiles. SOMEONE glances behind herself then reaches up with both hands and removes the panel.
HUGO_DVS401
Smiling, she hands the panel to SOMEONE then turns toward a wooden box sitting in the exposed space.
HUGO_DVS402
SOMEONE grabs the box with both hands and pulls it forward.
HUGO_DVS403
The chair teeters under her.
HUGO_DVS404
SOMEONE glances over her shoulder then drags the box forward several inches.
HUGO_DVS405
Suddenly, the box falls but SOMEONE holds on, hugging it to her chest.
HUGO_DVS406
Wide-eyed, SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE turns toward him.
HUGO_DVS407
They smile.
HUGO_DVS408
The chair's legs snap and collapse.
HUGO_DVS409
The box falls to the floor and springs open.
HUGO_DVS410
Papers fly out and swirl around the room.
HUGO_DVS411
A sketch of a disembodied face floats past then another of a man peeking out from a ringed planet.
HUGO_DVS412
Several drawings of a dragon peel away in sequence. The flipping pages become an animation of the dragon breathing fire.
HUGO_DVS413
Sketches twist and twirl as they sail about the room.
HUGO_DVS414
SOMEONE's mouth opens as a drawing of the rocket crashing into the Man in the Moon drifts past.
HUGO_DVS416
As the drawings float to the floor, SOMEONE glares in from the doorway, SOMEONE stands behind him.
HUGO_DVS417
SOMEONE steps closer to SOMEONE, who licks his lips and swallows.
HUGO_DVS418
SOMEONE gazes around the room then steps inside.
HUGO_DVS419
Drawings litter the floor.
HUGO_DVS420
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE, who shakes her head.
HUGO_DVS421
SOMEONE scoops up several drawings with both hands.
HUGO_DVS422
He stares at SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS423
SOMEONE furiously crumples the drawings as SOMEONE tries to grab his hands.
HUGO_DVS424
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS425
SOMEONE sits on a bed. SOMEONE grasps his arm then sits next to him.
HUGO_DVS426
SOMEONE shakes his head and shrugs.
HUGO_DVS427
SOMEONE blinks back tears.
HUGO_DVS428
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE as he draws a deep breath then drops his head and covers his face with his hand.
HUGO_DVS429
SOMEONE wraps her arm around SOMEONE's shoulder as he gently sobs.
HUGO_DVS430
SOMEONE turns toward SOMEONE, nods, then they both walk out of the room, gazing over their shoulders at SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS431
At the front door, SOMEONE stands on the landing as SOMEONE faces him from the doorway.
HUGO_DVS432
SOMEONE nods slightly as he meets SOMEONE's gaze.
HUGO_DVS433
They peer into each other's eyes.
HUGO_DVS434
SOMEONE looks downward.
HUGO_DVS435
SOMEONE grasps her hand then turns and walks off.
HUGO_DVS436
Facing SOMEONE, SOMEONE nods then turns and walks away.
HUGO_DVS437
Later, he crosses a cobble-stoned street near a statue of a lion.
HUGO_DVS438
He pushes open a door to the train station, steps inside, then collides with the bookseller.
HUGO_DVS439
He drops several books.
HUGO_DVS440
Crouching, SOMEONE quickly picks up the books then stands and faces the bearded bookseller.
HUGO_DVS441
SOMEONE runs his hand across the cover of the top book.
HUGO_DVS442
SOMEONE Hood.
HUGO_DVS443
SOMEONE returns the books.
HUGO_DVS444
SOMEONE stares at the floor.
HUGO_DVS445
SOMEONE smiles as the bookseller hands him the thick volume then walks off.
HUGO_DVS446
Holding the book in both hands, SOMEONE walks deeper into the station.
HUGO_DVS447
Outside the cafe, the station inspector sips from a cup.
HUGO_DVS448
SOMEONE freezes then turns and walks in the opposite direction.
HUGO_DVS449
The inspector stares at the flower seller.
HUGO_DVS450
He turns to the brown-haired cafe owner.
HUGO_DVS451
The inspector smiles weakly.
HUGO_DVS452
He raises his eyebrows and bares his teeth.
HUGO_DVS453
A curly-haired woman walks up with a tray.
HUGO_DVS454
She hands the inspector a new cup and saucer.
HUGO_DVS455
Still smiling, he steps forward then glances down at the two cups in his hands.
HUGO_DVS456
He returns them to the brown-haired woman then approaches the flower seller, who arranges bouquets for display.
HUGO_DVS457
He waves his hands in front of himself.
HUGO_DVS458
The inspector bends over a large bouquet of blue flowers.
HUGO_DVS459
He lurches forward, SOMEONE gasps and turns away.
HUGO_DVS460
The inspector adjusts his leg brace then glances at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS461
Standing, he gazes at the floor, his shoulders hunched.
HUGO_DVS462
The inspector straightens then faces SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS463
The inspector bows slightly then turns and walks off.
HUGO_DVS464
He stops and glances back.
HUGO_DVS465
The inspector turns toward SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS466
She smiles at him then snaps off the tops of a handful of posies. SOMEONE slides one of the flowers beneath a silver button of the inspector's jacket.
HUGO_DVS467
He smiles at the flower then nods to SOMEONE. He touches the brim of his cap.
HUGO_DVS468
Then he turns and walks off. SOMEONE glances over her shoulder at him as she returns to her work.
HUGO_DVS470
Elsewhere, in a cavernous library lined with long tables and reading lamps, sunlight filters in through tall arched windows.
HUGO_DVS471
SOMEONE and SOMEONE inspect book titles as they stroll past shelves.
HUGO_DVS472
SOMEONE pulls a tall, thick book from a shelf.
HUGO_DVS473
SOMEONE sets the volume onto a table.
HUGO_DVS474
He and SOMEONE gaze at the book's cover.
HUGO_DVS475
SOMEONE opens it.
HUGO_DVS476
A photograph of a train.
HUGO_DVS477
In black and white footage, a train rolls into a station. People watching the movie duck or turn away.
HUGO_DVS478
SOMEONE gazes up at a mural of a celestial figure shooting wind from his finger.
HUGO_DVS479
Shafts of light shine from the man's finger then turn into a movie projector's diffused beam. A curtain parts in front of a movie screen.
HUGO_DVS480
Onscreen a mustached man kisses a woman. A cowboy points his revolver and fires. Crowds gather before an ancient temple of large columns and statues.
HUGO_DVS481
SOMEONE turns a page. Buster Keaton sits on the coupling rod of a locomotive's wheels. As the train moves forward, the rod lifts Keaton's body in a circular motion. On another page a woman ties a feathered headdress to her head. A man in evening dress stares at her.
HUGO_DVS482
The book's pages flip quickly. A woman in white leaps backwards. A cowboy turns his head. People watch a movie. SOMEONE looks up from a sleeping boy. As SOMEONE turns the book's pages, more movie images appear. On a final page a rocket sticks out of the Man in the Moon's eye.
HUGO_DVS483
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange glances.
HUGO_DVS484
A bearded bespectacled man stand behind them.
HUGO_DVS485
The man raises his eyebrows as he stares down at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS486
As SOMEONE and the man stare at each other, SOMEONE glances at the open book.
HUGO_DVS487
SOMEONE nudges SOMEONE and points to a photograph of the author.
HUGO_DVS488
Same man standing behind them.
HUGO_DVS489
SOMEONE's mouth opens.
HUGO_DVS490
She looks up at the man.
HUGO_DVS491
The man, Rene SOMEONE,
HUGO_DVS492
bends forward.
HUGO_DVS493
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS494
SOMEONE nods.
HUGO_DVS495
SOMEONE looks around himself.
HUGO_DVS496
Elsewhere, two wooden doors swing open, revealing a large room filled with dark furniture and framed photographs.
HUGO_DVS497
An old photo.
HUGO_DVS498
SOMEONE holds up an old playbill.
HUGO_DVS499
A clock with a clear face.
HUGO_DVS500
SOMEONE touches a large movie camera.
HUGO_DVS501
Ina photograph, people wear elaborate costumes.
HUGO_DVS502
SOMEONE gazes at a photo of a bearded man.
HUGO_DVS503
A young boy in a tweed suit gapes.
HUGO_DVS504
Young SOMEONE and his brother step into a glass house.
HUGO_DVS505
Beyond slowly swimming fish, a mermaid with hair flowing over her shoulders carries a staff.
HUGO_DVS506
People dressed as lobsters march with tall spears.
HUGO_DVS507
They stop before three women sitting on a seashell throne.
HUGO_DVS508
Real lobsters float downward.
HUGO_DVS509
A stagehand wearing a cap drops lobsters into a tank.
HUGO_DVS510
SOMEONE and his brother walk past an actor putting on a lobster costume. Two men adjust a camera on a tripod. On set, the three women hold perfectly still as lobstermen rush around them.
HUGO_DVS511
Wearing a shiny breastplate, a young SOMEONE trots onto the set. A man slides a fake sword into his belt.
HUGO_DVS512
The young SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE, who slips on a fake beard then gestures with his finger.
HUGO_DVS513
SOMEONE steps up to him.
HUGO_DVS514
SOMEONE puts on a plumed helmet.
HUGO_DVS515
SOMEONE smiles.
HUGO_DVS516
SOMEONE strides toward the other actors.
HUGO_DVS517
The mermaid carrying a staff strolls past the three women. Knights wearing helmets hold their arms out to a man with a long white beard holding a trident, who sits above the seashell throne.
HUGO_DVS518
SOMEONE slides open a drawer and takes out a film canister.
HUGO_DVS519
Back at the station, SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb down into the suspended clock.
HUGO_DVS520
SOMEONE adjusts a screw in a clock's mechanism.
HUGO_DVS521
Below, the inspector looks at the clock then checks his watch.
HUGO_DVS522
Bending toward the clock's gears, SOMEONE drops a wrench through an opening. It lands on the station floor, behind the inspector and SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS523
The inspector turns and picks up the wrench then stares up at the clock.
HUGO_DVS524
SOMEONE holds one finger over his mouth.
HUGO_DVS525
He turns to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS526
The inspector walks off.
HUGO_DVS527
Smiling, SOMEONE climbs a ladder toward SOMEONE. Later she sits against a wall as SOMEONE rotates a large crank.
HUGO_DVS529
Inside another clock, SOMEONE adjusts a small pendulum. In another, he turns a gear as he checks his pocket watch.
HUGO_DVS530
Below, the bookseller talks with a man wearing a cap.
HUGO_DVS531
SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze at each other.
HUGO_DVS532
She shrugs.
HUGO_DVS533
At night, lights stream along the streets and boulevards of Paris.
HUGO_DVS534
Inside the clock tower, SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze down upon the city.
HUGO_DVS535
A full moon hangs above the Eiffel Tower.
HUGO_DVS536
SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze into each other's eyes. SOMEONE smiles slightly.
HUGO_DVS537
They hold hands as they look out over Paris.
HUGO_DVS538
Behind them, the clockwork's gears turn smoothly.
HUGO_DVS539
Later, SOMEONE pulls a metal grate over the front of his shop.
HUGO_DVS540
Steam floats through the empty train station.
HUGO_DVS541
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hide behind a kiosk.
HUGO_DVS543
SOMEONE nods then grins.
HUGO_DVS544
SOMEONE breaks into a broad smile.
HUGO_DVS545
She leans forward and kisses SOMEONE on the cheek
HUGO_DVS546
then walks off.
HUGO_DVS547
SOMEONE watches her walk past an empty bench towards SOMEONE
HUGO_DVS548
who trudges slowly along a wall.
HUGO_DVS549
SOMEONE stops and takes SOMEONE's briefcase from him. They walk arm-in-arm.
HUGO_DVS550
SOMEONE slowly backs up behind the kiosk as he watches them leave.
HUGO_DVS551
In the attic, he winds a pocket watch then hangs it from a post near his bed.
HUGO_DVS552
Wearing a nightgown, SOMEONE gazes at the automaton, which sits across the room from him.
HUGO_DVS553
Steam swirls around the motionless figure.
HUGO_DVS554
Lying down, SOMEONE stares at his watch, which reads five until ten.
HUGO_DVS555
Later, he lies on his back, his eyes still open.
HUGO_DVS556
Morning. People walk along train station platforms.
HUGO_DVS557
SOMEONE steals an apple from a passing cart and slips it into his pocket.
HUGO_DVS558
SOMEONE glances toward the railroad track as he walks near the edge of the platform.
HUGO_DVS559
He slows then stops.
HUGO_DVS560
A key sticks out of the gravel next to a railroad tie. SOMEONE glances down the platform then creeps toward the edge.
HUGO_DVS561
Glancing in both directions, SOMEONE hops down to the tracks, steps over a rail, then crouches on a tie.
HUGO_DVS562
He picks up the key and examines it.
HUGO_DVS563
It resembles SOMEONE's key with a heart at each end.
HUGO_DVS564
SOMEONE turns the key in his hand.
HUGO_DVS565
Inscribed around one heart,
HUGO_DVS566
Cabret et Fils Horloge, or Cabret and Son Clock Makers.
HUGO_DVS567
One rail begins to vibrate. A train steams toward the station.
HUGO_DVS568
The train's engineer, wearing goggles and covered in soot, leans out of the engine car.
HUGO_DVS569
The engineer furiously turns a wheel then shoves a lever. SOMEONE stares at the key then looks around at the vibrating ground.
HUGO_DVS570
Black smoke pours from the train's stack. Sparks shoot from between the train's wheels. SOMEONE's eyes widen.
HUGO_DVS571
The train roars toward SOMEONE, who holds out one hand as he falls backward onto the tracks.
HUGO_DVS573
The engineer and stoker cover their faces. The train veers onto the platform and crashes through the station.
HUGO_DVS574
People flee as the locomotive plows through luggage and benches. Inside the cafe, customers duck as the windows blow out.
HUGO_DVS576
One man knocks another man out of the train's path as it crashes through a newsstand.
HUGO_DVS577
The runaway train smashes through the station's huge front windows and falls into the street one story below.
HUGO_DVS580
SOMEONE awakes and sits up in bed.
HUGO_DVS581
Sweating, he looks around himself.
HUGO_DVS582
The automaton's face is turned in his direction.
HUGO_DVS583
SOMEONE gazes toward the dangling strap that held his watch,
HUGO_DVS584
but the watch is gone.
HUGO_DVS585
The automaton stares at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS586
SOMEONE glances around himself, feels his own chest, then unbuttons his shirt.
HUGO_DVS587
Pulling his shirt open with both hands, SOMEONE looks down at his torso, which is now a metallic framework filled with pistons and moving parts.
HUGO_DVS588
He stands quickly on mechanical legs.
HUGO_DVS589
SOMEONE glances up as the huge gears of a clock close in around him.
HUGO_DVS590
He holds his robotic hands to his face,
HUGO_DVS591
which turns into the automaton's face and then back to his own again.
HUGO_DVS592
Again, SOMEONE awakes and sits up in bed. His watch hangs from the strap where he left it.
HUGO_DVS593
Across the room, the automaton faces toward SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS594
Sitting on his bed, staring back at the automaton, SOMEONE holds a small oil lamp.
HUGO_DVS595
Above him, a large gear slowly rotates.
HUGO_DVS596
Outside, a man lies on his back on a riverside. A gloved hand pushes open the man's coat revealing a flask in a vest pocket.
HUGO_DVS597
A policeman grabs the flask and turns it upside down. Engraved on the bottom,
HUGO_DVS598
"Claude Cabret, 1925."
HUGO_DVS599
The policeman holds out the flask to another policeman. In the station inspector's office, a phone rings.
HUGO_DVS600
Wearing leather gloves and long johns, the inspector soaks in a bathtub as he uses the phone.
HUGO_DVS601
The inspector hangs up the phone then stares intently at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS602
SOMEONE's ears stand straight up as he stares at the inspector.
HUGO_DVS603
Standing in the cemetery beneath a statue of a hooded figure, SOMEONE checks his pocket watch.
HUGO_DVS604
He steps through the arched gate and crosses a narrow street, where he meets Rene SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS605
SOMEONE steps up to SOMEONE front door.
HUGO_DVS606
Inside, SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS607
SOMEONE closes a large book, then walks down the hallway.
HUGO_DVS608
She opens the front door.
HUGO_DVS609
Carrying cases, SOMEONE and SOMEONE step inside.
HUGO_DVS610
SOMEONE looks from SOMEONE to the others.
HUGO_DVS611
SOMEONE removes his hat.
HUGO_DVS612
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE then at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS613
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS614
SOMEONE glances over her shoulder at her godmother. Smiling, SOMEONE steps up to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS615
SOMEONE's eyes glisten as she smiles and turns away.
HUGO_DVS616
SOMEONE dons his hat.
HUGO_DVS617
SOMEONE jerks her head.
HUGO_DVS618
SOMEONE glances over her shoulder at a closed door.
HUGO_DVS619
She leads them into the sitting room where SOMEONE sets up a projector.
HUGO_DVS620
The others sit as SOMEONE threads a film through the projector.
HUGO_DVS621
SOMEONE smiles.
HUGO_DVS622
SOMEONE pulls his chair closer to a screen.
HUGO_DVS623
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE then nods.
HUGO_DVS624
He smiles and turns a crank on his film projector as the lights dim.
HUGO_DVS625
Everyone smiles as a black and white movie flickers on a screen.
HUGO_DVS626
A group of female sailors push a bullet-shaped capsule into a giant cannon.
HUGO_DVS627
The women wave their sailor's caps.
HUGO_DVS628
SOMEONE holds one hand to her chest as she watches.
HUGO_DVS629
On screen, a military officer swings his sabre. A gunner lights a fuse on the cannon, which fires the capsule into outer space.
HUGO_DVS630
It lodges in the left eye of a man wearing a mask of the moon.
HUGO_DVS631
SOMEONE smiles. As the capsule lands on the moon's surface and people step out, the capsule turns red.
HUGO_DVS632
The people jump and wave as the distant Earth rises above the horizon. Later, as the explorers sleep on the moon's surface,
HUGO_DVS633
people appear in the sky. A bearded man peers out of the planet Saturn.
HUGO_DVS634
A woman sits on a crescent moon.
HUGO_DVS635
A young SOMEONE sits on the crescent moon as snow falls on the sleepers.
HUGO_DVS636
SOMEONE smiles and places one hand on SOMEONE's shoulder.
HUGO_DVS637
On screen, the explorers flee as an alien with a man's body and a lizard's head chases them. One man uses an umbrella to hit the alien, who vanishes in a puff of red smoke.
HUGO_DVS638
The explorers return to their capsule and huddle inside.
HUGO_DVS639
Another alien leaps onto it sending the capsule over a cliff.
HUGO_DVS640
It drops into the ocean and sinks to the bottom of the sea.
HUGO_DVS641
The explorers escape and swim back to the surface.
HUGO_DVS642
Later, people celebrate the explorers with a parade and a statue in their honor.
HUGO_DVS643
SOMEONE smiles as the film ends.
HUGO_DVS644
He stops turning the crank.
HUGO_DVS645
Tears well in SOMEONE's eyes.
HUGO_DVS646
SOMEONE sits with her mouth open then shakes her head and smiles.
HUGO_DVS647
Everyone turns toward SOMEONE
HUGO_DVS648
who stands in the doorway.
HUGO_DVS649
SOMEONE stands then walks to SOMEONE and takes his hand.
HUGO_DVS650
He steps into the room
HUGO_DVS651
and walks up to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS652
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's other hand and the women lead him to a sofa.
HUGO_DVS653
SOMEONE raises SOMEONE's hands to his lips and kisses it.
HUGO_DVS654
SOMEONE nods.
HUGO_DVS655
SOMEONE's moustache and beard darken. As a younger man, he stands on a stage in a packed theatre.
HUGO_DVS656
SOMEONE floats horizontally above the stage with her elbow resting atop a thin pole.
HUGO_DVS657
SOMEONE waves his hand in front of SOMEONE's face.
HUGO_DVS658
He picks up a metal hoop, then slides it up the pole, and over SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS659
People ride a carousel near a stage with strongman and a fire juggler.
HUGO_DVS660
Carnival SOMEONE stands outside a cinematograph.
HUGO_DVS661
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step into a tent
HUGO_DVS662
where a man cranks a movie projector.
HUGO_DVS663
SOMEONE's mouth drops open as he watches the screen.
HUGO_DVS664
The audience cowers as an oncoming train passes.
HUGO_DVS665
SOMEONE slides up to the projectionist and studies his contraption.
HUGO_DVS666
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pose in front of a glass building as a photographer takes their picture inside a set of a smoking cave.
HUGO_DVS667
Wearing a bathing suit and cape, SOMEONE twirls for SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS668
Wearing a devil costume, SOMEONE sinks beneath the floor of the cave in a cloud of smoke.
HUGO_DVS669
Cameramen record the scene.
HUGO_DVS670
A platform raises him up again.
HUGO_DVS671
SOMEONE brushes his face with powder. Later, actors wearing robes and
HUGO_DVS672
turbans march with spears and scimitars through a surrealistic ruin.
HUGO_DVS673
They retreat as a large dragon puppet slides onto the set.
HUGO_DVS674
Flames shoot from the dragon's nostrils.
HUGO_DVS675
Its head sags to the floor.
HUGO_DVS676
SOMEONE runs to the puppeteers.
HUGO_DVS677
He demonstrates a sword thrust for one of the actors.
HUGO_DVS678
The dragon breathes smoke and fire.
HUGO_DVS679
Weapons raised, the actors creep across the set.
HUGO_DVS680
They hide behind a panel of scenery then retreat as men push the dragon puppet along on a track.
HUGO_DVS681
Flames leap from the dragon's nostrils.
HUGO_DVS682
The actors jab at the dragon with their prop weapons.
HUGO_DVS683
Later, they surround a group of dancers wearing skeleton costumes.
HUGO_DVS684
As the skeletons cartwheel and dance in place, the warriors raise their weapons.
HUGO_DVS685
The camera stops while the skeletons hurry off the set.
HUGO_DVS686
A man places a smoke bomb where they stood.
HUGO_DVS687
A smoke bomb detonates as the warriors swing their weapons. Later, SOMEONE cuts a film strip with scissors.
HUGO_DVS688
In the edited movie, the skeletons appear to vanish in a puff of smoke as the warriors chop through them. Later SOMEONE poses SOMEONE on a movie set.
HUGO_DVS689
Sparks shoot in front of SOMEONE as she reclined in front of a painting of a shooting star.
HUGO_DVS690
Artillery explodes in a field. A cannon fires. SOMEONE throws pieces of set onto a bonfire.
HUGO_DVS691
In old film footage, soldiers run out of a trench onto a smoky battlefield.
HUGO_DVS692
A rain-soaked movie poster peels off a brick wall.
HUGO_DVS693
SOMEONE picks up a prop of the Man in the Moon and throws it onto the bonfire. He watches as flames erupt through the props open mouth and consume it.
HUGO_DVS694
Film strips melt in a bucket.
HUGO_DVS695
A woman wearing high-heeled shoes walks past SOMEONE's toyshop.
HUGO_DVS696
SOMEONE grins at SOMEONE then stands.
HUGO_DVS697
He runs out of the room. SOMEONE smiles broadly. Outside, SOMEONE pushes past pedestrians as he races toward the train station.
HUGO_DVS698
Inside, he grins as he strides through a sea of people.
HUGO_DVS699
Nearby, the news vendor carries a wicker basket toward the cafe where the owner sits outside with her small dog in her lap.
HUGO_DVS700
Frick sets down his basket.
HUGO_DVS701
A small brown dog peeks out of the basket.
HUGO_DVS702
The two dogs stare at one another.
HUGO_DVS703
The cafe owner sets her dog on the floor.
HUGO_DVS704
The two dogs wag their tails as they sniff one another.
HUGO_DVS705
He glances at the cafe owner who presses her hands over her heart.
HUGO_DVS706
Smiling, he steps forward and kisses her hands.
HUGO_DVS707
SOMEONE glances at them as he passes.
HUGO_DVS708
SOMEONE stops.
HUGO_DVS709
A few paces ahead, SOMEONE sits attentively beside the station inspector who checks a pocket watch.
HUGO_DVS710
SOMEONE dives under some nearby cafe tables as the inspector turns and approaches Frick and the cafe owner.
HUGO_DVS711
The dogs run over to SOMEONE who tries to shoo them away.
HUGO_DVS712
The inspector grabs SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS713
SOMEONE reaches out toward SOMEONE who stares at the inspector.
HUGO_DVS714
SOMEONE struggles as the inspector drags him to his office.
HUGO_DVS716
The inspector locks SOMEONE in a metal cage.
HUGO_DVS717
The inspector stands with his back to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS718
SOMEONE picks the cages lock with a tool.
HUGO_DVS719
SOMEONE opens the cage and sneaks out.
HUGO_DVS720
The inspector rushes out of his office.
HUGO_DVS721
Below, SOMEONE runs across the station. The inspector hurries back into his office and slides down a fireman's pole.
HUGO_DVS722
The Doberman follows the inspector as he chases SOMEONE through the crowd. SOMEONE runs around a corner and slides beneath a staircase. The inspector limps around the corner and stares at the deserted corner.
HUGO_DVS723
A small vent stands ajar.
HUGO_DVS724
Furrowing his brow, the inspector opens the vent and peers inside.
HUGO_DVS725
SOMEONE sticks his head in beside him.
HUGO_DVS726
SOMEONE runs down a steamy corridor filled with pipes.
HUGO_DVS727
He stops and listens.
HUGO_DVS728
SOMEONE hurries up the clock tower staircase.
HUGO_DVS729
A moment later, the inspector runs to the bottom of the stairs and unleashes SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS730
The dog bounds up the stairs after SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS731
The massive pendulum sweeps back and forth as SOMEONE climbs higher.
HUGO_DVS732
Slick with sweat, he reaches the top.
HUGO_DVS733
SOMEONE peers down the stairs then at the large clockwork mechanism as he paces frantically.
HUGO_DVS734
SOMEONE stares through the clear glass panels of one of the giant clocks.
HUGO_DVS735
The Eiffel Tower glows with lights in the distance.
HUGO_DVS736
He pushes open a hinged window pane and stares at the street far below.
HUGO_DVS737
SOMEONE crawls out of the window and twists himself around. He reaches up and grabs onto the clock's giant minute hand - a thin metal beam pointed at the number three.
HUGO_DVS738
He kicks the windows shut with one foot as he dangles.
HUGO_DVS739
Inching sideways, SOMEONE moves toward the far end of the minute hand, out of view of the windows.
HUGO_DVS740
SOMEONE reaches the top of the stairs and sniffs some boxes and rags.
HUGO_DVS741
Standing beside him, the inspector peers up at the clockwork's giant moving gears.
HUGO_DVS742
Tufts of snow fall as SOMEONE slides his fingers along the top of the minute hand.
HUGO_DVS743
As he reaches the end of the bar, one of the clockwork's gears snaps.
HUGO_DVS744
SOMEONE hangs on tightly as the minute hand drops about a foot. SOMEONE's ears prick up.
HUGO_DVS745
SOMEONE lowers himself onto the curved bottom rim of the clock face.
HUGO_DVS746
He peers into a window as SOMEONE and the inspector poke their heads into the clockwork's interior.
HUGO_DVS747
He ducks as the inspector swivels and glances over his shoulder.
HUGO_DVS749
SOMEONE leans his face against the clock as SOMEONE and the inspector head back downstairs.
HUGO_DVS750
SOMEONE sits on the bottom of the clock with his feet resting on a small ledge covered in snow.
HUGO_DVS752
A few cars motor along the street far below.
HUGO_DVS753
He makes his way back to the center of the clock,
HUGO_DVS754
opens the window, and climbs inside.
HUGO_DVS755
SOMEONE dashes down the stairs.
HUGO_DVS756
In the candlelit attic, SOMEONE throws a sheet over the automaton and carries it away. Clutching the automaton to his chest, SOMEONE wades through a river of people exiting a train platform.
HUGO_DVS757
The inspector rushes up behind SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS758
A train door swings open and reflects the inspector in the glass.
HUGO_DVS759
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
HUGO_DVS760
SOMEONE ducks through the train.
HUGO_DVS761
SOMEONE exits onto the opposite platform but is cornered by SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS762
As the inspector yanks SOMEONE, the automaton sails into the air. The inspector gazes up at it.
HUGO_DVS763
SOMEONE kicks the inspector in the shin, causing him to lose his grip. SOMEONE moves under the automaton with his arms outstretched but stops at the edge of the platform.
HUGO_DVS764
The automaton drops onto the tracks.
HUGO_DVS765
SOMEONE glances down the rails at an oncoming train then at the automaton.
HUGO_DVS766
He jumps down onto the tracks.
HUGO_DVS767
The sooty faced engineer sticks his head out of the side of the train.
HUGO_DVS768
SOMEONE crouches as the train approaches.
HUGO_DVS769
The engineers throw on the brakes.
HUGO_DVS770
SOMEONE's hair blows back as he is illuminated by the train's headlight. The inspector reaches down and pulls SOMEONE and the automaton safely onto the platform.
HUGO_DVS771
SOMEONE shakes his head.
HUGO_DVS772
He yanks SOMEONE to his feet.
HUGO_DVS773
He pulls the boy through the crowd.
HUGO_DVS774
The inspector glances down at the brace on his leg.
HUGO_DVS775
SOMEONE takes off his hat as he steps forward with SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS776
The inspector eyes SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS777
He glances at SOMEONE who stands nearby staring at them.
HUGO_DVS778
The inspector releases SOMEONE who carries the automaton to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS780
clasps the automaton to his chest then hugs SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS781
SOMEONE puts one arm around SOMEONE as they all walk off together.
HUGO_DVS782
The inspector stands still and stares at the floor.
HUGO_DVS783
SOMEONE approaches him.
HUGO_DVS784
She strokes his arm
HUGO_DVS785
then slips her arm through his.
HUGO_DVS786
Wearing a tuxedo, SOMEONE sits in a crowded theatre. The inspector sits nearby with SOMEONE and the bookseller, Labisse.
HUGO_DVS787
Sitting with SOMEONE and SOMEONE, SOMEONE smiles as he applauds.
HUGO_DVS788
On stage, SOMEONE steps aside as a spotlight illuminates a curtain.
HUGO_DVS789
The curtain parts and SOMEONE walks out wearing a tuxedo.
HUGO_DVS790
The audience rises to its feet.
HUGO_DVS791
Tears well in SOMEONE's eyes as she stands.
HUGO_DVS792
He nods to the audience then bows to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS793
SOMEONE grins at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS794
SOMEONE places one hand on his heart
HUGO_DVS795
and nods to SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS796
He winks at SOMEONE.
HUGO_DVS797
SOMEONE holds up his arms then bows and steps backward toward a movie screen. He puts on a top hat and places a cigarette in his mouth, then ducks off stage.
HUGO_DVS798
On screen, a young SOMEONE wearing a top hat and smoking a cigarette
HUGO_DVS799
straightens then draws a sketch of Shakespeare on a chalkboard.
HUGO_DVS800
Next, a fleet of airships, dirigibles, and hot air balloons fly across a cloudy sky.
HUGO_DVS801
Wearing a coat and tails, young SOMEONE throws a music clefs.
HUGO_DVS803
onto five telegraph wires running overhead. He takes off his own head and throws it onto the wires where it hovers like a musical note.
HUGO_DVS804
His head reappears on his shoulders but copies remain.
HUGO_DVS805
Standing in the wings, the older SOMEONE chuckles. In other clips, revelers push a chariot across the sky. A magician lifts a giant hat, revealing a woman with butterfly wings.
HUGO_DVS806
A witch rides on a flying broomstick through a thunderstorm.
HUGO_DVS807
A man pulls off a bearded sheik's robes and skin, leaving a skeleton which collapses into a chair.
HUGO_DVS808
Outside a castle, a magician conjures a pair of green imps who twirl batons of fire. A carriage drives into the mouth of a volcano spewing smoke and embers. A train crashes onto a fiery landscape of jagged rocks.