She eyes her arm.
IN_TIME_DVS24
SOMEONE pauses on his way out.
IN_TIME_DVS25
He and his mother clasp each other's forearms, then rotate his over hers.
IN_TIME_DVS26
They watch their clocks tick rapidly on their free arms.
IN_TIME_DVS27
SOMEONE's halts at 1 day and 14 minutes, then resumes its normal countdown.
IN_TIME_DVS28
He kisses her cheek.
IN_TIME_DVS29
His mother beams after him.
IN_TIME_DVS30
Leaving the building, SOMEONE steps out onto a street crowded with pedestrians.
IN_TIME_DVS31
Posted cameras monitor the neighborhood.
IN_TIME_DVS32
A little girl approaches.
IN_TIME_DVS33
Her clock doesn't move.
IN_TIME_DVS34
SOMEONE holds out a hand. She gives him a flat metal box.
IN_TIME_DVS35
He presses its curved receptor to the inside of his wrist. A display ticks up to five minutes.
IN_TIME_DVS36
SOMEONE takes the time with a smile.
IN_TIME_DVS37
Turning a corner, SOMEONE checks his body clock, then breaks into a run.
IN_TIME_DVS38
Arriving outside a factory, SOMEONE goes to a coffee cart with the drink prices listed digitally in minutes and seconds. The prices change abruptly.
IN_TIME_DVS39
SOMEONE sticks his wrist in a scanner that takes minutes off his timer.
IN_TIME_DVS40
Opening a flask, SOMEONE spikes his coffee.
IN_TIME_DVS41
Two men clasp each other's arms.
IN_TIME_DVS42
Now an inky black body clock shows all zeros on a dead man's arm.
IN_TIME_DVS43
A well-dressed man standing over the corpse meets their gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS44
As SOMEONE moves on, SOMEONE lingers, holding the thin man's gaze with narrowed eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS45
Later, he stands at a machine inside the factory.
IN_TIME_DVS46
SOMEONE sets a flat metal box on a platform, then pulls a lever.
IN_TIME_DVS47
As he repeats the process, a complete portable time capsule rolls down a conveyor sporting the curved receptor at one end.
IN_TIME_DVS48
It joins others in a bin.
IN_TIME_DVS49
Now, the factory workers file past a scanner. Each sticking their wrist in as they go.
IN_TIME_DVS50
Heading off, SOMEONE checks his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS51
SOMEONE marches out sullenly.
IN_TIME_DVS52
Now, he arrives at a harshly lit doorway where a sign overhead reads Beer/Wine.
IN_TIME_DVS53
He enters the bar where women in slinky dresses dance before a live band.
IN_TIME_DVS54
One paws at SOMEONE as he passes. Smiling politely, he sidles past and goes to a table where men play cards.
IN_TIME_DVS55
SOMEONE grasps the card player's forearm.
IN_TIME_DVS56
He moves off down the length of the bar, passing a chiseled well-dressed man flanked by beautiful women. SOMEONE sits at the far end.
IN_TIME_DVS57
He points at the well-dressed man.
IN_TIME_DVS58
The well-dressed man waves at a bartender.
IN_TIME_DVS59
Nearby, a man starring at his exposed body clock hangs up a phone.
IN_TIME_DVS60
The women paw at the well-dressed man.
IN_TIME_DVS61
Clad in dark clothes, the stranger glares coldly at him.
IN_TIME_DVS62
Noticing, SOMEONE approaches the wealthy man.
IN_TIME_DVS63
The handsome man sips his drink casually.
IN_TIME_DVS64
The door bursts open and a group of thugs saunter in. As the bar clears, SOMEONE sticks by the rich man's side.
IN_TIME_DVS65
A blonde man with a gun leads the thugs.
IN_TIME_DVS66
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE to a back hall. The rich man stands and faces the thugs.
IN_TIME_DVS67
As SOMEONE leaves, SOMEONE watches the rich stranger and the minutemen. Their leader sets his gun down.
IN_TIME_DVS68
His gaze drifts towards the rich man's clock.
IN_TIME_DVS69
The wealthy man's hand curls into a fist.
IN_TIME_DVS70
He glares at the gangster.
IN_TIME_DVS71
SOMEONE removes his overcoat.
IN_TIME_DVS72
His smooth ageless features give a smirk.
IN_TIME_DVS73
The wealthy man takes a few steps forward, then shifts his uneasy gaze and loosens his tie.
IN_TIME_DVS74
SOMEONE steps out of view as the man backs away.
IN_TIME_DVS75
The stranger bumps a table, then rushes nauseously into the back hall where he pushes his way in to a men's room.
IN_TIME_DVS76
Posted nearby, a thug in a fedora follows him.
IN_TIME_DVS77
Crouching at a toilet, the rich man vomits.
IN_TIME_DVS78
From hiding, SOMEONE swings a stall door, knocking out the thug.
IN_TIME_DVS79
Out front, SOMEONE spies SOMEONE hustling the rich man out.
IN_TIME_DVS80
In an alley.
IN_TIME_DVS81
SOMEONE blocks the exit with a dumpster.
IN_TIME_DVS82
He leads the wealthy man down the alley and out onto a street.
IN_TIME_DVS83
SOMEONE and his men leave the bar through the front exit and get in a waiting car.
IN_TIME_DVS84
The car pursues SOMEONE and the stranger down a deserted street.
IN_TIME_DVS85
The two men reach a gate.
IN_TIME_DVS86
SOMEONE boosts the stranger into climbing it.
IN_TIME_DVS87
Climbing after his companion, SOMEONE drops down on the other side as the car arrives.
IN_TIME_DVS88
As SOMEONE drags the stranger down an alley, the car backs out of view. The two men reach a door and SOMEONE breaks a chain locking it shut. The stranger starts to wander off.
IN_TIME_DVS89
SOMEONE yanks him through the doorway, then uses the chain to pull the door shut behind them.
IN_TIME_DVS90
The car speeds into view.
IN_TIME_DVS91
Hidden in a shadowy space, SOMEONE gets a firm grip on the chain. The gangsters get out of the car and bang against doorways spaced along the long wall.
IN_TIME_DVS92
Wielding a gun, the fedora-wearing thug marches up to SOMEONE's door and kicks the lock.
IN_TIME_DVS93
As he tugs at it, the working man on the other side holds the chain tightly. The thug gives up and moves on.
IN_TIME_DVS94
SOMEONE leads the rich stranger away.
IN_TIME_DVS95
As SOMEONE angrily scans the alley, SOMEONE leads his companion up an abandoned stairway.
IN_TIME_DVS97
the fedora-wearing thug stands behind SOMEONE' shoulder.
IN_TIME_DVS98
A malicious smile flickers across SOMEONE' features.
IN_TIME_DVS99
Now, in a large abandoned space, SOMEONE shoves the stranger onto a leather bench, then crosses to a wall of dirty broken windows.
IN_TIME_DVS100
SOMEONE takes out a flask and unscrews its cap.
IN_TIME_DVS101
He holds it out to his rescuer and nods insistently.
IN_TIME_DVS102
Taking it, SOMEONE sips.
IN_TIME_DVS103
He shuts his eyes and shakes his head.
IN_TIME_DVS104
SOMEONE reluctantly takes another swig.
IN_TIME_DVS105
He shakes his head again.
IN_TIME_DVS106
He returns the flask to his smiling companion.
IN_TIME_DVS107
SOMEONE's smile fades as a car crawls past outside.
IN_TIME_DVS108
Smirking, SOMEONE checks his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS109
It reads 18 hours 58 minutes.
IN_TIME_DVS110
SOMEONE faces the rich man with a bemused frown.
IN_TIME_DVS111
He stalks closer to SOMEONE, sneering bitterly.
IN_TIME_DVS112
The rich man lowers his head.
IN_TIME_DVS113
He meets the working class man's knowing gaze. As SOMEONE turns away, SOMEONE stares ahead with a haunted expression.
IN_TIME_DVS114
SOMEONE faces him, then sinks into a leather armchair positioned opposite the bench.
IN_TIME_DVS115
SOMEONE blinks quizzically and tilts his head.
IN_TIME_DVS116
Under SOMEONE's earnest gaze, SOMEONE blinks heavily and looks away.
IN_TIME_DVS117
The rich man eyes his companion's arm.
IN_TIME_DVS118
SOMEONE pulls up his sleeve and watches his clock seconds tick away.
IN_TIME_DVS119
SOMEONE gives a small nod, his eyes glistening.
IN_TIME_DVS120
He stares off sadly, then meets SOMEONE's stoic gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS121
SOMEONE stares at the glowing clock ticking down his own body's time.
IN_TIME_DVS122
They share a brief wry smile.
IN_TIME_DVS123
SOMEONE leans forward, holding out the flask.
IN_TIME_DVS124
SOMEONE brings it to his lips hesitantly, then swigs at it with increasing enthusiasm.
IN_TIME_DVS125
He returns the flask to its melancholy owner, who tips it in a silent toast and drinks.
IN_TIME_DVS127
Daylight pours in through the windows as SOMEONE lies back on the bench, his head on the meagerly padded armrest.
IN_TIME_DVS128
Facing him, SOMEONE sleeps in the armchair.
IN_TIME_DVS130
The rich man wakes and turn toward his rescuer.
IN_TIME_DVS131
We drift closer to the working class man as he slumbers peacefully,
IN_TIME_DVS132
his arms dangling over their rests.
IN_TIME_DVS133
SOMEONE creeps over to SOMEONE and crouches at his side.
IN_TIME_DVS134
Pulling back his sleeve,
IN_TIME_DVS135
he slips his own wrist under SOMEONE's.
IN_TIME_DVS136
He glances at SOMEONE with wide eyes, then looks down at his body clock
IN_TIME_DVS137
and watches the rapidly decreasing count.
IN_TIME_DVS138
As he reaches a balance of five minutes,
IN_TIME_DVS139
SOMEONE halts the transfer.
IN_TIME_DVS141
SOMEONE wakes with a start.
IN_TIME_DVS142
Getting his bearings, he habitually checks his body clock.
IN_TIME_DVS143
It reads over 116 years.
IN_TIME_DVS144
The working class man looks around, finds himself alone, and sits up.
IN_TIME_DVS145
Facing the windows, he stands abruptly and steps closer.
IN_TIME_DVS146
Letters written in the grime of a glass pane read:
IN_TIME_DVS147
"Don't waste my time."
IN_TIME_DVS148
Peering out a broken pane next to it, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE sitting on the railing of a high stone bridge, his feet dangling over the side.
IN_TIME_DVS149
The melancholy man faces the river and distant mountains as his body clock ticks down under 15 seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS150
He blinks his clear pale eyes in the bright morning sun and his woeful expression grows serene.
IN_TIME_DVS151
His clock ticks out its last three seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS152
SOMEONE's back arches and he grimaces painfully.
IN_TIME_DVS153
His body falls from the railing, tumbles midair, and splashes into the shallow water 50 feet below.
IN_TIME_DVS154
SOMEONE sprints onto the bridge and peers over the railing.
IN_TIME_DVS155
The shallow river's current rushes around SOMEONE as he sprawls motionless on its concrete bed.
IN_TIME_DVS156
A mounted camera lowers its view towards SOMEONE, who wearily hurries away.
IN_TIME_DVS157
Now, at an apartment complex, a smiling woman cradles her baby.
IN_TIME_DVS158
She eyes the baby's clock.
IN_TIME_DVS159
Exiting an apartment, he appears at her side.
IN_TIME_DVS160
SOMEONE gives his friend a conspiring nod.
IN_TIME_DVS161
As he and SOMEONE head down a flight of stairs into a courtyard,
IN_TIME_DVS162
SOMEONE unzips the end of his jacket sleeve.
IN_TIME_DVS163
Glancing around, he pulls it up.
IN_TIME_DVS164
He shows his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS165
Nodding, SOMEONE looks off thoughtfully.
IN_TIME_DVS166
A faint smile touches his lips as he turns to SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS167
Clasping SOMEONE's arm, he holds his gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS168
As SOMEONE releases him, SOMEONE checks his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS169
SOMEONE claps a hand on his shoulder.
IN_TIME_DVS170
SOMEONE nods, then twitches a sad smile.
IN_TIME_DVS171
SOMEONE grabs him into a hug.
IN_TIME_DVS172
Pulling away, he gives his friend an expectant look.
IN_TIME_DVS173
SOMEONE lifts his brow in an encouraging expression,
IN_TIME_DVS174
and SOMEONE heads off.
IN_TIME_DVS175
SOMEONE stares after him, then checks his clock again.
IN_TIME_DVS176
He glances at a bar across the street.
IN_TIME_DVS177
Now, SOMEONE's mom scans her wrist. A sign on the building that reads Weis Time Lenders flashes off as she heads away. The windows go dark. SOMEONE's mother boards a bus.
IN_TIME_DVS178
With a tense look, she jerks her hand away from the scanner.
IN_TIME_DVS180
Sliding her sleeve up, she checks the balance on her clock.
IN_TIME_DVS181
The bus driver shifts his regretful gaze away.
IN_TIME_DVS182
SOMEONE's mother looks at the other passengers who either avoid her gaze or turn away with disengaged expressions.
IN_TIME_DVS183
She hurries off the bus and jogs back towards Weis Time Lenders finding it closed.
IN_TIME_DVS184
The bus pulls away.
IN_TIME_DVS185
SOMEONE's mother glances around, her eyes desperate,
IN_TIME_DVS186
then takes off down a desolate street.
IN_TIME_DVS187
Ahead of her, the bus's taillights glow in the shadows of dingy buildings.
IN_TIME_DVS188
Now, SOMEONE's mother furiously pumps her arms as she runs.
IN_TIME_DVS189
Behind her, a truck's headlights grow brighter as it draws closer.
IN_TIME_DVS190
She waves at the vehicle which speeds right past.
IN_TIME_DVS191
Finding only 20 minutes on her clock, she takes off at a sprint.
IN_TIME_DVS192
As the bus stops in Dayton, SOMEONE steps forward holding a bouquet.
IN_TIME_DVS193
Two passengers climb off and the doors closed behind them.
IN_TIME_DVS194
SOMEONE gazes in at the bus's remaining passengers, then watches the vehicle glide away.
IN_TIME_DVS195
His thoughtful eyes shift to a truck heading in the opposite direction and he drops his flowers taking off after it.
IN_TIME_DVS196
Meanwhile, his mother hurries toward a man entering a building.
IN_TIME_DVS197
He hurries inside and closes the door.
IN_TIME_DVS198
Banging on the door, she sees the man glance back then hurry off.
IN_TIME_DVS199
She checks her clock. Nine minutes.
IN_TIME_DVS200
Now, SOMEONE sprints away from Dayton while his mother races toward it.
IN_TIME_DVS201
She glances at her left forearm as she runs, her face pinched anxiously.
IN_TIME_DVS202
Rounding a corner, she lifts her arm and finds her clock counting down from ten seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS203
She races faster.
IN_TIME_DVS204
SOMEONE sprints furiously toward his mother from the opposite end of the street.
IN_TIME_DVS205
As they draw closer, SOMEONE extends his hand. His mother beams. Three feet before they reach each other, she tumbles forward. He catches her.
IN_TIME_DVS206
Dropping to his knees, he cradles her limp body.
IN_TIME_DVS207
He finds her clock timed out.
IN_TIME_DVS208
His face contorts in anguish.
IN_TIME_DVS209
He presses it to her neck, rocking back and forth.
IN_TIME_DVS210
With his eyes squeezed shut, he tilts his face skyward.
IN_TIME_DVS211
A wide view shows the young man hunched over his mother's body in the barren street,
IN_TIME_DVS212
awash with pale light from nearby buildings.
IN_TIME_DVS214
Two men in all black drag SOMEONE's body from the shallow stream of water in the otherwise dried up canal.
IN_TIME_DVS215
As one checks SOMEONE's clock, a sharp cheek boned man in black approaches.
IN_TIME_DVS216
They circle the body.
IN_TIME_DVS217
Eyeing the body, he chews his gum thoughtfully.
IN_TIME_DVS218
He strides toward his car, his long leather jacket billowing behind him.
IN_TIME_DVS219
Shifting his gaze from the blonde in thigh-highs and miniskirt,
IN_TIME_DVS220
SOMEONE spots the surveillance camera on the bridge.
IN_TIME_DVS221
Now, a luxury sedan stops on a street in Dayton and SOMEONE strides over.
IN_TIME_DVS222
SOMEONE glances around, then slides up the sleeve of his charcoal suit jacket and the black dress shirt underneath, displaying the balance on his clock. The chauffeur nods and unlocks a back door.
IN_TIME_DVS223
With a cautious look, SOMEONE climbs in.
IN_TIME_DVS226
As the sedan glides away, he peers out his widow at the passing city.
IN_TIME_DVS227
The chauffeur shoots him a look in the rear view mirror.
IN_TIME_DVS228
SOMEONE blinks his sullen eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS229
The sedan reaches a booth labeled Time Zone 12 Border.
IN_TIME_DVS230
A concrete barricade blocks their path.
IN_TIME_DVS231
A metal panel cut in at one side to create a C shaped hollow flips up from a console beside SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS232
He slips his wrist into the cuff-like scanner and watches his clock's balance count down.
IN_TIME_DVS233
A green light flashes on the booth
IN_TIME_DVS234
and the concrete barricade lowers into the ground, allowing the sedan to pass.
IN_TIME_DVS235
Later, the vehicle reaches one end of a bridge marked
IN_TIME_DVS236
Time Zone 8 Border.
IN_TIME_DVS237
SOMEONE scans his wrists and a barricade lowers.
IN_TIME_DVS238
As the sedan glides on, he gives a worried look.
IN_TIME_DVS239
They stop at the barricade for Time Zone 4 and the scanner flips up again.
IN_TIME_DVS240
SOMEONE inserts his wrist.
IN_TIME_DVS241
The sedan trundles through the gap in a six-foot high wall. SOMEONE checks his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS242
SOMEONE gives a solemn look.
IN_TIME_DVS243
He stares with hardened eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS244
The chauffeur glances at him.
IN_TIME_DVS245
SOMEONE lowers his vengeful gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS246
As the sedan glides down a concrete passage way,
IN_TIME_DVS247
the time zone barricade rises back up.
IN_TIME_DVS248
Now, the luxury vehicle drives down a street in a clean, well-maintained city with elegant towering skyscrapers. It pulls into a business plaza where luxury vehicles wait a curb.
IN_TIME_DVS249
Suited men in sunglasses escort well-dressed citizens and chauffeurs assist patrons into cars. A porter pushes a luggage cart down a walkway along a skyscraper's facade.
IN_TIME_DVS250
Climbing out of the sedan, SOMEONE sweeps his view around the area.
IN_TIME_DVS251
He starts to jog down the walkway and the people strolling past glance at him.
IN_TIME_DVS252
Stopping by a hotel's front doors, he pulls up his sleeve and checks his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS253
He shifts his thoughtful eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS254
As he strolls to the door, his gaze catches a young woman with chin length auburn hair and large blue eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS255
Standing at a car's open door, she turns as he passes and stares after him.
IN_TIME_DVS256
He glances back at her, then enters the hotel.
IN_TIME_DVS257
A suited man with sunglasses and a two-way radio earpiece leans toward the young woman.
IN_TIME_DVS258
In the hotel, SOMEONE approaches the front desk.
IN_TIME_DVS259
SOMEONE glances at the suited men escorting the hotel's patrons.
IN_TIME_DVS260
He holds out his wrist.
IN_TIME_DVS261
The two front desk clerks exchange a look.
IN_TIME_DVS262
As the female clerk enters information on a computer, her male counterpart puts a time capsule to SOMEONE's wrist.
IN_TIME_DVS263
He hands him a key.
IN_TIME_DVS264
Now, in a stark building, SOMEONE and a blond timekeeper watch surveillance footage of SOMEONE on the bridge, while SOMEONE eyes a continually changing screen displaying time per capita in each zone.
IN_TIME_DVS265
He checks a screen with a map.
IN_TIME_DVS266
His gaze flickers over the map of time circulation.
IN_TIME_DVS267
He strides away.
IN_TIME_DVS268
Now, SOMEONE lies asleep in his elegant suite,
IN_TIME_DVS269
his body covered in a downy white comforter.
IN_TIME_DVS270
Awaking, he sits up and looks around.
IN_TIME_DVS271
He checks his clock which shows over 105 years.
IN_TIME_DVS272
Lying back down, he lets his head drop onto the pillow and closes his eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS273
He opens them again and furrows his brow.
IN_TIME_DVS274
Later, a view through the hotel restaurant's window shows SOMEONE eating alone.
IN_TIME_DVS275
He shoots furtive glances at his surroundings as he devours his French fries.
IN_TIME_DVS276
The auburn-haired young woman watches him from her table on a patio outside.
IN_TIME_DVS277
Swallowing, SOMEONE swigs from a champagne flute.
IN_TIME_DVS278
A waitress strolls up to his table.
IN_TIME_DVS279
Still chewing, SOMEONE holds out his wrist.
IN_TIME_DVS280
As she collects his time in a capsule,
IN_TIME_DVS281
the auburn-haired young woman continues to watch with intrigued eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS282
SOMEONE blinks.
IN_TIME_DVS283
He gazes at her.
IN_TIME_DVS284
She allows a bashful smile.
IN_TIME_DVS285
Eyeing him, she grimaces.
IN_TIME_DVS286
On the patio, the young woman stops staring as a waitress serves her.
IN_TIME_DVS287
Now, at the timekeeper's headquarters.
IN_TIME_DVS288
A female timekeeper displays a photo.
IN_TIME_DVS289
He stares intently.
IN_TIME_DVS290
Nighttime. Inside a palatial mansion, a tuxedoed man greets patrons in black tie. He stops SOMEONE who also wears a tux.
IN_TIME_DVS291
SOMEONE appraises the host.
IN_TIME_DVS292
With a defiant look, SOMEONE holds out his wrist.
IN_TIME_DVS293
As the host collects his time, the newcomer shifts his eyes uncertainly.
IN_TIME_DVS294
They head up a staircase to a mezzanine.
IN_TIME_DVS295
Later, SOMEONE sits at the poker table.
IN_TIME_DVS296
A cube at its center shows 600 years in the pot.
IN_TIME_DVS297
He watches with an indifferent expression as the dealer lays out a fourth card.
IN_TIME_DVS298
The man across from SOMEONE scrutinizes him.
IN_TIME_DVS299
SOMEONE's clock displays over 250 years.
IN_TIME_DVS300
SOMEONE glances at the suited men posted nearby.
IN_TIME_DVS301
SOMEONE grins. Checking his cards, he finds a pair of queens and places his wrist under a scanner.
IN_TIME_DVS302
The cube's balance ticks up to 650.
IN_TIME_DVS303
As SOMEONE shifts his uncertain eyes, SOMEONE gives a knowing smile.
IN_TIME_DVS304
SOMEONE covers his clock with his sleeve.
IN_TIME_DVS305
SOMEONE slides his wrist under a scanner, his eyes fixed on SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS306
The dealer sets a fifth card face up.
IN_TIME_DVS307
Both players lift their gazes as the auburn-haired young woman approaches with her dark-haired guard right behind her.
IN_TIME_DVS308
Sitting beside SOMEONE, she stares at SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS309
His clock shows over 9000 years.
IN_TIME_DVS310
SOMEONE watches the pot tick up to 900 years.
IN_TIME_DVS311
He scans his wrist.
IN_TIME_DVS312
With his eyes fixed on SOMEONE, he reaches for his cards.
IN_TIME_DVS313
Spotting his exposed arm, the auburn-haired woman leans closer.
IN_TIME_DVS314
SOMEONE's jaw drops.
IN_TIME_DVS315
SOMEONE follows their eyes to the 23 seconds remaining on his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS316
He meets SOMEONE's gaze and tossed down his pair of queens.
IN_TIME_DVS317
SOMEONE considers the cards.
IN_TIME_DVS318
Looking down at his own, he flips them over to reveal an eight and a four.
IN_TIME_DVS319
The dealer slides two cards from his five giving SOMEONE a straight.
IN_TIME_DVS320
SOMEONE shoots the auburn-haired woman a sidelong glance.
IN_TIME_DVS321
She lowers her eyes to his clock, which ticks down from five seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS322
SOMEONE casually sets his wrist on a time dispenser.
IN_TIME_DVS323
His clock counts up to 1100 years and one second.
IN_TIME_DVS324
SOMEONE gives a tight smile.
IN_TIME_DVS325
He rises.
IN_TIME_DVS326
The auburn-haired woman and SOMEONE follow suit.
IN_TIME_DVS327
SOMEONE glances at the young woman.
IN_TIME_DVS328
SOMEONE follows his gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS329
SOMEONE gives a nod.
IN_TIME_DVS330
SOMEONE twitches a smile.
IN_TIME_DVS331
SOMEONE looks at her.
IN_TIME_DVS332
She holds his gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS333
SOMEONE casts SOMEONE a fascinated look, then follows her father downstairs. SOMEONE checks his clock which now displays a minute and fifteen seconds less.
IN_TIME_DVS334
Now in an auto showroom, SOMEONE sits in a silver Roadster.
IN_TIME_DVS335
He stares at the sales attendant, then shifts his gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS336
His expression grows resolute and he thrusts out his wrist.
IN_TIME_DVS337
The sales attendant holds a time capsule to it and smiles.
IN_TIME_DVS338
SOMEONE eyes the dashboard admiringly.
IN_TIME_DVS339
At dusk.
IN_TIME_DVS340
The Roadster speeds along a winding road built into a cliff face as ocean waves crash below.
IN_TIME_DVS341
At night, the Roadster turns, pulls through an open gate, and passes a marble statue.
IN_TIME_DVS342
It pulls up to a vast opulent mansion with a column-framed entrance.
IN_TIME_DVS343
Just inside, SOMEONE stands with SOMEONE and two other auburn-haired beauties.
IN_TIME_DVS344
As SOMEONE steps into the party, SOMEONE smirks and SOMEONE gazes discreetly after him.
IN_TIME_DVS345
Now, at a buffet table, SOMEONE scoops up a spoonful of caviar and sniffs it.
IN_TIME_DVS346
Eyeing the food dubiously, he puts it back.
IN_TIME_DVS347
SOMEONE saunters over, trailed closely by her guard.
IN_TIME_DVS348
SOMEONE's guard eyes her uncertainly, then moves off.
IN_TIME_DVS349
SOMEONE smiles briefly and cocks his head.
IN_TIME_DVS350
SOMEONE glances toward a doorway framing her parents.
IN_TIME_DVS351
Now, on a sparsely populated dance floor, SOMEONE twirls into SOMEONE's grasp.
IN_TIME_DVS352
He holds her close as they dance.
IN_TIME_DVS353
SOMEONE adverts his gaze,
IN_TIME_DVS354
but SOMEONE leans her full lips closer.
IN_TIME_DVS355
Her parents watch vigilantly from the doorway.
IN_TIME_DVS356
SOMEONE notices.
IN_TIME_DVS357
SOMEONE regards her incredulously.
IN_TIME_DVS358
SOMEONE stops swaying.
IN_TIME_DVS359
SOMEONE follows suite, lowing her hands.
IN_TIME_DVS360
He abruptly takes one.
IN_TIME_DVS361
As he leads her out, SOMEONE looks on with a seething glare.
IN_TIME_DVS362
SOMEONE glances over her shoulder as SOMEONE leads her out and across a back porch.
IN_TIME_DVS363
At the timekeeper's headquarters, SOMEONE joins his men who watch video footage of SOMEONE's arrival at the party.
IN_TIME_DVS364
The Roadster passes through the open gate.
IN_TIME_DVS365
SOMEONE leads his men out at a march.
IN_TIME_DVS366
Now, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE down marble steps to a sandy beach enclosed within rock formations.
IN_TIME_DVS367
Smiling appreciatively at the ocean, SOMEONE takes his clothes off.
IN_TIME_DVS368
SOMEONE unbuttons his shirt and grins.
IN_TIME_DVS369
SOMEONE starts for the ocean, then pauses and turns back, unbuckling his belt.
IN_TIME_DVS370
She watches him get in the water.
IN_TIME_DVS371
She gazes longingly toward the ocean.
IN_TIME_DVS372
Now, from underwater, we gaze up at the silhouetted naked forms of SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they swim side by side.
IN_TIME_DVS373
The green light from their body clocks glows in the water.
IN_TIME_DVS374
They pause near a rock formation.
IN_TIME_DVS375
As they tread water, they bring their open mouths teasingly close.
IN_TIME_DVS376
SOMEONE soberly paddles back a little.
IN_TIME_DVS377
As she maintains her distances, calm waves splash between them.
IN_TIME_DVS378
SOMEONE comes down the steps.
IN_TIME_DVS379
She leads SOMEONE toward the rock formations.
IN_TIME_DVS380
They swim around behind one and hide.
IN_TIME_DVS381
Sea spray forms a light mist over the water's surface as SOMEONE shifts her gaze between SOMEONE and the mansion.
IN_TIME_DVS382
SOMEONE grins. Beneath the water's surface, SOMEONE's body clock read over a thousand years. He smiles at SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS383
SOMEONE briefly leans closer to him, then swims away.
IN_TIME_DVS384
SOMEONE gazes after her and follows.
IN_TIME_DVS385
Now, SOMEONE walks through the party, shifting his agitated gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS386
He encounters a fully dressed SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS387
SOMEONE arrives behind her father.
IN_TIME_DVS388
Turning, SOMEONE spots her and smiles.
IN_TIME_DVS389
SOMEONE buttons his jacket and accompanies his host into the spacious foyer.
IN_TIME_DVS390
Ahead, the elegant guests scatter as SOMEONE and his men march in.
IN_TIME_DVS391
SOMEONE's cool blue eyes shift to SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS392
SOMEONE nods and steps aside.
IN_TIME_DVS393
SOMEONE and his blonde partner march forward and seize SOMEONE by the arms.
IN_TIME_DVS394
He glances over his shoulder at SOMEONE as they march him to the staircase.
IN_TIME_DVS395
SOMEONE climbs up after them.
IN_TIME_DVS396
Now, in a study, the blond timekeeper plants SOMEONE's arm on a desk and exposes his body clock.
IN_TIME_DVS397
From the far side of the room, SOMEONE strolls over and takes a seat on the other side of the desk.
IN_TIME_DVS398
SOMEONE unknots his tie with a breezy smirk and shrugs his head.
IN_TIME_DVS399
SOMEONE twiddles his thumbs and regards the suspect impassively.
IN_TIME_DVS400
The timekeeper and suspect stare at each other, neither betraying a hint of emotion.
IN_TIME_DVS401
SOMEONE gives a patient, amused smile, then narrows his eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS402
SOMEONE's smirk fades but he maintains steady eye contact with the timekeeper.
IN_TIME_DVS403
SOMEONE stands.
IN_TIME_DVS404
He strolls over to SOMEONE's side of the desk.
IN_TIME_DVS405
SOMEONE coldly turns away and SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS406
He and the blonde extract it from his body clock.
IN_TIME_DVS407
The timekeepers finish and head out of the study.
IN_TIME_DVS408
SOMEONE calmly pauses and turns back.
IN_TIME_DVS409
He marches toward the desk, his lips parted.
IN_TIME_DVS410
Halting, he gives an amazed shake of the head.
IN_TIME_DVS411
SOMEONE gives him a sharp look.
IN_TIME_DVS412
SOMEONE leaves the room, joining SOMEONE and his daughter in the hall. SOMEONE starts to go.
IN_TIME_DVS413
She stalks off.
IN_TIME_DVS414
SOMEONE springs up, grabs a timekeeper's gun and punches both officers flanking him.
IN_TIME_DVS415
As SOMEONE trots down to the foyer, SOMEONE leaves the study and rushes down the other side of the twin stairway.
IN_TIME_DVS416
Halfway down, a timekeeper intercepts him.
IN_TIME_DVS417
He kicks the lawman back and swings over the railing.
IN_TIME_DVS418
SOMEONE flings a guard to the floor, then grabs SOMEONE. Using her as a human shield, he backs out of the foyer and enters a kitchen.
IN_TIME_DVS419
Fighting his way outside, he finds SOMEONE at his Roadster. The guard aims a gun.
IN_TIME_DVS420
He obeys and SOMEONE knocks him out.
IN_TIME_DVS421
He takes the guard's gun and gets in is car. With SOMEONE at his side, he backs through a small courtyard.
IN_TIME_DVS422
Turning, he pulls through a corridor and out onto the front driveway. The Roadster passes several timekeeper cars as the authorities rush out through the front door.
IN_TIME_DVS423
As SOMEONE and his hostage speed away, the timekeeper cars follow.
IN_TIME_DVS424
As their sirens sound, white bars of light repeatedly extend across their grills and upper windshields.
IN_TIME_DVS425
The Roadster turns out to a quiet road, forcing an arriving timekeeper car to veer to one side.
IN_TIME_DVS426
The others pass it in their pursuit.
IN_TIME_DVS427
Now, as they chase SOMEONE's car across an overpass, SOMEONE looks over her shoulder.
IN_TIME_DVS428
One of the pursuing cars moves to the front and tails them aggressively.
IN_TIME_DVS429
SOMEONE weaves the Roadster through the traffic.
IN_TIME_DVS430
The car stays on his tail.
IN_TIME_DVS431
At the wheel, SOMEONE drives with narrowed eyes and pursed lips.
IN_TIME_DVS432
Lowering his chin, he braces himself and rams the Roadster's rear bumper.
IN_TIME_DVS433
The small convertible spins out and stops, facing SOMEONE's front end. SOMEONE jerks the gearshift and reverses down the street at high speed.
IN_TIME_DVS434
SOMEONE veers into the oncoming lane and swerves around the approaching cars. Maintaining a close pursuit, SOMEONE blinks his large eyes and sets his jaw tight. SOMEONE's auburn hair blows across her face as she stares slack-jawed at the oncoming traffic.
IN_TIME_DVS435
A huge truck heads straight for them. SOMEONE wrenches the wheel, spinning the Roadster out of its path and back in the right direction.
IN_TIME_DVS436
SOMEONE tries to turn his car out of the way but the truck crashes through its rear half.
IN_TIME_DVS437
As SOMEONE makes his escape with SOMEONE, the timekeeper catches his breath and glares after them with gritted teeth.
IN_TIME_DVS438
SOMEONE glances at his hostage, looks over his shoulder, and smirks.
IN_TIME_DVS439
Now in a deserted area, two timekeeper cars speed across another overpass. Below, the Roadster turns in beneath the structure.
IN_TIME_DVS440
SOMEONE checks his body clock which shows an hour and ten minutes.
IN_TIME_DVS441
SOMEONE smacks his hand away and avoids his gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS442
SOMEONE looks down.
IN_TIME_DVS443
She pulls up her long glove.
IN_TIME_DVS444
Now, in bright sunlight, the Roadster speeds along a multilevel network of roads by the river basin.
IN_TIME_DVS445
At the wheel, SOMEONE looks up at a posted video camera trained on the road.
IN_TIME_DVS446
As he turns his head to stare at it, the Roadster approaches a spike strip laid across the street.
IN_TIME_DVS447
It blows out the car's tires.
IN_TIME_DVS448
Losing control, SOMEONE leans forward and protectively pushes SOMEONE's head down. The car careens off the road and tumbles end over end into the basin.
IN_TIME_DVS449
It settles on its wheels, both occupants slumped and motionless.
IN_TIME_DVS450
SOMEONE and his men arrive.
IN_TIME_DVS451
As his men surround the car, SOMEONE leans over SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS452
A young thug checks her.
IN_TIME_DVS453
SOMEONE pushes past his men and grabs SOMEONE's arm. He faces his underlings defensively.
IN_TIME_DVS454
A timekeeper car drives past.
IN_TIME_DVS455
As his thugs head for their car, SOMEONE lingers.
IN_TIME_DVS456
He releases the heiress, pounds the car with his fist, and joins his men.
IN_TIME_DVS457
SOMEONE's head twitches groggily.
IN_TIME_DVS458
The gangster's car speeds off down the depleted river basin.
IN_TIME_DVS459
In the Roadster, SOMEONE stirs weakly then wakes.
IN_TIME_DVS460
She eyes her body clock which ticks down under 32 minutes.
IN_TIME_DVS461
Beside her, SOMEONE sits up clutching his head painfully.
IN_TIME_DVS462
He faces his companion and gently turns her face with his hand.
IN_TIME_DVS463
She leaves the car.
IN_TIME_DVS464
SOMEONE climbs out through his mangled door.
IN_TIME_DVS465
He grabs her forearm and gives her a few minutes.
IN_TIME_DVS466
She flings his hand away.
IN_TIME_DVS467
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's gloved hand and they run off down the basin.
IN_TIME_DVS468
Now, on the road adjacent to its slope, a timekeeper's cruiser breaks hard, its tires smoking.
IN_TIME_DVS469
It backs up quickly and lurches to a halt.
IN_TIME_DVS470
At the wheel, SOMEONE gazes down at the wrecked Roadster.
IN_TIME_DVS471
Later, he raises a scanner by his seat and sticks his wrist through it.
IN_TIME_DVS472
His body clock indicates a transfer of time into his body and he leaves the car.
IN_TIME_DVS473
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and their blond colleague surround the mangled Roadster.
IN_TIME_DVS474
SOMEONE perches serenely on the Roadster's hood.
IN_TIME_DVS475
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE run hand in hand through the ghetto.
IN_TIME_DVS476
Reaching SOMEONE's apartment complex, they dash up the steps to his unit.
IN_TIME_DVS477
SOMEONE stands by as SOMEONE raises a fist to a screen door fitted with protective iron bars.
IN_TIME_DVS478
SOMEONE's clock shows three and a half minutes left.
IN_TIME_DVS479
The inner door opens and SOMEONE's wife stares out.
IN_TIME_DVS480
She vacantly opens the screen door.
IN_TIME_DVS481
Greta averts her tearful gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS482
She withdraws into the apartment, shutting the doors. As SOMEONE beats the screen door, SOMEONE notes two and a half minutes left on her clock.
IN_TIME_DVS483
SOMEONE paces, then faces SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS484
Brushing her hair back, he finds a sizable diamond stud on her earlobe.
IN_TIME_DVS485
He grabs her hand and leads her down the steps. They race down a deserted road and approach a building with a sign over the entrance reading simply Pawn.
IN_TIME_DVS486
Its metal security gate lowers.
IN_TIME_DVS487
SOMEONE sticks his foot under the gate.
IN_TIME_DVS488
SOMEONE's clock reads less than a minute. SOMEONE removes her earrings.
IN_TIME_DVS489
She tosses them under the gate.
IN_TIME_DVS490
It rises, revealing an additional grated gate behind it.
IN_TIME_DVS491
From the other side, a woman trains a shotgun on the pair while a man with long bangs examines the earrings.
IN_TIME_DVS492
He notices less than a minute on SOMEONE's clock.
IN_TIME_DVS493
SOMEONE sticks his hand through the gate.
IN_TIME_DVS494
The broker transfers the time to him, then yanks his hand back.
IN_TIME_DVS495
The gate lowers.
IN_TIME_DVS496
SOMEONE clamps a hand over SOMEONE's mouth. Later, they hide.
IN_TIME_DVS497
As a timekeeper's car passes, SOMEONE transfers half his time to SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS498
They watch their own clocks, then release each other.
IN_TIME_DVS499
On the street.
IN_TIME_DVS500
They pass a Weis Time Lenders.
IN_TIME_DVS501
He guides her to a bank of pay phones and picks up a receiver.
IN_TIME_DVS502
He scans his wrist.
IN_TIME_DVS503
SOMEONE gives him a stubborn look
IN_TIME_DVS504
and he turns his head toward the keypad.
IN_TIME_DVS505
She dials sulkily.
IN_TIME_DVS506
SOMEONE corners her against a wall as he listens.
IN_TIME_DVS507
Meanwhile, in SOMEONE's study.
IN_TIME_DVS508
SOMEONE gives a nod and SOMEONE answers.
IN_TIME_DVS509
SOMEONE holds out the phone.
IN_TIME_DVS510
Taking it, SOMEONE casually leans against SOMEONE's desk.
IN_TIME_DVS511
SOMEONE gazes at a building's neon sign which reads Mission Out of Time.
IN_TIME_DVS512
Shaking his head, SOMEONE moves away from SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS513
With a puzzled look, SOMEONE lowers the receiver and hangs it up.
IN_TIME_DVS514
The blond timekeeper traces the call.
IN_TIME_DVS515
He returns the phone to SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS516
He stares off. Michele eyes him.
IN_TIME_DVS517
Back in Dayton.
IN_TIME_DVS518
With his gun at her back, he shuffles her past a timed out woman lying in the street.
IN_TIME_DVS520
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE up a fire escape to a balcony.
IN_TIME_DVS521
Opening a window, he climbs into the building where he lived with his mother.
IN_TIME_DVS522
SOMEONE climbs in after him.
IN_TIME_DVS523
He turns on a light over a sink and runs water over his bloody knuckles. SOMEONE looks around.
IN_TIME_DVS524
SOMEONE drinks from the tap, wipes his mouth, then shuts off the faucet.
IN_TIME_DVS525
Now, in the bathroom, SOMEONE zips herself into a modest short-sleeved dress.
IN_TIME_DVS526
On her left arm, she wears an evening glove with its fingers cut off.
IN_TIME_DVS527
Gazing at herself in a small mirror, she adjusts her straight auburn hair.
IN_TIME_DVS528
In the adjacent room, SOMEONE puts on a long-sleeved shirt.
IN_TIME_DVS529
Later, he gazes out a window at the Mission's neon sign.
IN_TIME_DVS530
Its status still reads Out of time.
IN_TIME_DVS531
He turns from the window as SOMEONE joins him in the living room.
IN_TIME_DVS532
SOMEONE drops her gaze to her outfit.
IN_TIME_DVS533
He sets the gun on a table, then pours the champagne from his mother's birthday.
IN_TIME_DVS534
SOMEONE sits on the edge of the couch.
IN_TIME_DVS535
She gazes up at him.
IN_TIME_DVS536
Setting down his drink, SOMEONE sits on the couch and faces her.
IN_TIME_DVS537
As he rolls up his sleeve, SOMEONE puts her drink on the floor.
IN_TIME_DVS538
She gives him an uneasy look, then extends her arm.
IN_TIME_DVS539
They clasp each other's wrists.
IN_TIME_DVS540
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE's clock which counts down from seven seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS541
He gently twists her arm until his hand is on top.
IN_TIME_DVS542
She watches as his balance ticks back up to 16 hours, 9 minutes, and 59 seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS543
Lifting her gaze to SOMEONE's, she holds
IN_TIME_DVS544
it intently,
IN_TIME_DVS545
then releases his wrist and slides hers out of his grasp.
IN_TIME_DVS546
She slides the glove over her clock. SOMEONE lowers his sleeve.
IN_TIME_DVS548
he sips from his mug of champagne. SOMEONE considers him.
IN_TIME_DVS549
She stares with inviting eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS550
He twitches a smile.
IN_TIME_DVS551
In a flashback, SOMEONE trips forward as he walks.
IN_TIME_DVS552
SOMEONE stares sadly.
IN_TIME_DVS553
A flashback shows her in bed.
IN_TIME_DVS554
She shudders.
IN_TIME_DVS555
As her clock begins to count down, SOMEONE lifts her head off the pillow and gazes at it.
IN_TIME_DVS556
She runs her finger over the glowing numbers.
IN_TIME_DVS557
Touching her face, she examines it.
IN_TIME_DVS558
In the present.
IN_TIME_DVS559
She averts her eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS560
SOMEONE gives a surprised look.
IN_TIME_DVS561
He grabs two guns off the table, tucking one into the back of his waistband as he strides out of the room.
IN_TIME_DVS562
SOMEONE stares off with woeful eyes. Morning.
IN_TIME_DVS563
Standing at the window facing the Mission,
IN_TIME_DVS564
SOMEONE sees a line gathering outside.
IN_TIME_DVS565
He turns to SOMEONE, who sleeps on the couch, and loads his gun.
IN_TIME_DVS566
She wakes.
IN_TIME_DVS567
He returns his gaze to the window.
IN_TIME_DVS568
SOMEONE joins him.
IN_TIME_DVS569
As the Mission's door opens and a man emerges, she sucks in an anxious breath.
IN_TIME_DVS570
The neon letters on the sign flicker, then glow steadily.
IN_TIME_DVS571
Out of time.
IN_TIME_DVS572
The crowd outside disperses and the Mission proprietor heads back inside.
IN_TIME_DVS573
SOMEONE lowers his gaze and clenches his jaw.
IN_TIME_DVS574
He glances at SOMEONE, who gives him a sidelong look then shifts away her crestfallen eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS575
His expression softens.
IN_TIME_DVS576
SOMEONE considers her, then turns back to the window.
IN_TIME_DVS577
He shrugs his brow.
IN_TIME_DVS578
She checks her clock.
IN_TIME_DVS579
They move from the window.
IN_TIME_DVS580
Now, SOMEONE holds SOMEONE's arm as he escorts her down a sidewalk.
IN_TIME_DVS581
His other hand rests on a gun at the front of his waistband.
IN_TIME_DVS582
She holds his gaze with solemn eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS583
He takes the gun hidden at his back and places her hand around it.
IN_TIME_DVS584
She gives him a tender look,
IN_TIME_DVS585
then takes a few steps toward the pay phone across the street.
IN_TIME_DVS586
Turning back, she places her hand against SOMEONE's neck and pulls him into a kiss.
IN_TIME_DVS587
He slides his arm around her waist and she clutches the front of his shirt.
IN_TIME_DVS588
As their kiss ends, SOMEONE lets her lips graze against his, then strides away.
IN_TIME_DVS589
With his gun in one hand, SOMEONE sits on a street corner's curb, scanning the area as SOMEONE dials at a pay phone.
IN_TIME_DVS590
A timekeeper's cruiser rolls up behind SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS591
Meanwhile, SOMEONE answers his phone.
IN_TIME_DVS592
Climbing out of the cruiser, SOMEONE approaches the oblivious SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS593
He raises a gun.
IN_TIME_DVS594
She spots SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS595
She fires her gun. SOMEONE releases his weapon as he falls back. SOMEONE lowers his phone from his ear and gazes at it.
IN_TIME_DVS596
Striding up to SOMEONE, SOMEONE kicks the timekeeper's gun aside. SOMEONE retrieves it as SOMEONE holds SOMEONE down with one knee and presses his gun to his chest. He checks the timekeeper's clock.
IN_TIME_DVS597
Grinning, SOMEONE clasps SOMEONE's right wrist and twists it into receiving position.
IN_TIME_DVS598
He stands.
IN_TIME_DVS599
SOMEONE checks his balance and finds 4 hours and 45 minutes. Tucking his gun into his waistband, SOMEONE climbs into the cruiser's driving seat. As the vehicle peels out, SOMEONE gets to his feet and watches it speed past.
IN_TIME_DVS600
Clutching his arm, he heads toward the pay phone.
IN_TIME_DVS601
Two Dayton residents spot him
IN_TIME_DVS602
and one rips out the phone's receiver.
IN_TIME_DVS604
She checks her clock.
IN_TIME_DVS605
SOMEONE meets her gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS606
With SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS607
SOMEONE pushes past the disgruntled Dayton residents gathering around him.
IN_TIME_DVS608
Now, SOMEONE totes a gun as he approaches the group surrounding SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS609
The injured timekeeper emerges.
IN_TIME_DVS610
He sees SOMEONE's extra time.
IN_TIME_DVS611
Ignoring him, SOMEONE heads to the passenger side of SOMEONE's cruiser.
IN_TIME_DVS612
They get in and SOMEONE backs away from the crowd.
IN_TIME_DVS613
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE wait in their stolen vehicle which sits parked on a side street.
IN_TIME_DVS614
SOMEONE gives a thoughtful look.
IN_TIME_DVS615
He swerves around a corner onto a main road and halts the cruiser directly across a limousine's path.
IN_TIME_DVS616
The luxury vehicle rolls to a stop.
IN_TIME_DVS617
Toting his gun, SOMEONE climbs out of the cruiser and strides to the limo driver's side.
IN_TIME_DVS618
He taps his weapon on the window.
IN_TIME_DVS619
The chauffeur rolls it down and gazes out.
IN_TIME_DVS620
He points the gun inside.
IN_TIME_DVS621
The chauffeur shakes his head.
IN_TIME_DVS622
SOMEONE shoots at the vehicle.
IN_TIME_DVS623
SOMEONE ducks and glares at his partner.
IN_TIME_DVS624
With a fearful look, the chauffeur pops open a back door.
IN_TIME_DVS625
SOMEONE holds it open as a blond woman steps out.
IN_TIME_DVS626
She wears a fur coat over her black dress.
IN_TIME_DVS627
He glances at SOMEONE, then eyes the woman's earrings.
IN_TIME_DVS628
She gives them to him.
IN_TIME_DVS629
He moves to SOMEONE, who keeps her gun aimed at the blond and sets the earrings in her palm.
IN_TIME_DVS630
He aims his gun at the chauffeur.
IN_TIME_DVS631
Later, he and SOMEONE take off in the limo.
IN_TIME_DVS632
Now parked, they watch a news report.
IN_TIME_DVS633
SOMEONE turns off the TV. SOMEONE shoots him a glance.
IN_TIME_DVS634
SOMEONE gestures at the television.
IN_TIME_DVS635
SOMEONE allows a smile.
IN_TIME_DVS636
Looking out her window, she suppresses a smile.
IN_TIME_DVS637
She meets his gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS638
She turns away.
IN_TIME_DVS639
As he gazes at her, she lifts her eyes to his with a meaningful look.
IN_TIME_DVS640
He leans closer and presses his lips to hers.
IN_TIME_DVS641
Outside, a willow's canopy rustles in a gentle breeze as it shelters the stolen car.
IN_TIME_DVS642
Now, in his office,
IN_TIME_DVS643
SOMEONE eyes a wall-sized digital map which displays the world's time zones.
IN_TIME_DVS644
He talks on a speaker phone.
IN_TIME_DVS645
As SOMEONE enters, SOMEONE takes the phone off speaker.
IN_TIME_DVS646
He hangs up, then shifts his gaze to SOMEONE, who examines the data tables on the digital map.
IN_TIME_DVS647
He turns to SOMEONE, who shrugs his hands.
IN_TIME_DVS648
SOMEONE blinks at the businessman, his face relaxed in a deadpan expression.
IN_TIME_DVS649
SOMEONE unbuttons a cuff and adjusts his sleeve.
IN_TIME_DVS650
Shrugging his lips, SOMEONE nods.
IN_TIME_DVS651
SOMEONE lowers his gaze from the timekeeper,
IN_TIME_DVS652
then pushes his chair out from his desk and stands.
IN_TIME_DVS653
He smirks.
IN_TIME_DVS654
SOMEONE's stare remains firm.
IN_TIME_DVS655
SOMEONE strolls off.
IN_TIME_DVS656
Now, SOMEONE teaches SOMEONE how to shoot.
IN_TIME_DVS657
With SOMEONE behind her, SOMEONE aims the gun,
IN_TIME_DVS658
cringes as it goes off. SOMEONE gently takes the gun from her.
IN_TIME_DVS659
SOMEONE faces him and lingers close, her gaze lowered coyly.
IN_TIME_DVS660
SOMEONE gazes off thoughtfully.
IN_TIME_DVS661
SOMEONE lifts her gaze to meet his.
IN_TIME_DVS662
Bending one leg, she plants the toe of her shoe in the dirt.
IN_TIME_DVS663
The heiress smiles briefly,
IN_TIME_DVS664
then steps back and shifts on her feet.
IN_TIME_DVS665
SOMEONE's lips curl into a curious smirk
IN_TIME_DVS666
and SOMEONE beams mischievously.
IN_TIME_DVS667
Now, at Weis Time Lenders, a pretty woman faces a teller.
IN_TIME_DVS668
He cocks an eyebrow.
IN_TIME_DVS669
The customers scatter as a truck barrels through the bank's glass walls. It smashes through the glass barriers inside and stops at an open vault.
IN_TIME_DVS670
Drawing their guns, SOMEONE and SOMEONE get out of the truck and hurry into the vault.
IN_TIME_DVS671
SOMEONE opens a large suitcase on the floor and they hurriedly fill it with time capsules from the surrounding shelves.
IN_TIME_DVS672
Crouching, SOMEONE shuts the sizable case.
IN_TIME_DVS673
They pause and face the staring customers.
IN_TIME_DVS674
As the pair leaves, the customers rush into the vault and clean it out.
IN_TIME_DVS675
Now, capsules fall onto pavement littered with broken glass as the ghetto citizens drain the capsule's time into their bodies.
IN_TIME_DVS676
At the arrival of two timekeeper cruisers, a few drop their empty capsules and stroll off with affected nonchalance.
IN_TIME_DVS677
Many others linger on the spot staring at the authorities.
IN_TIME_DVS678
SOMEONE' car drives by.
IN_TIME_DVS679
Riding shotgun, the gang leader stares wide-eyed at the newly-empowered citizens.
IN_TIME_DVS680
SOMEONE gets out of his car, faces the plundered vault, and addresses the staring crowd.
IN_TIME_DVS681
The citizens by the building step away but the crowd lingers. SOMEONE approaches the destroyed window trailed by his men.
IN_TIME_DVS682
Now, in her complex's courtyard, Greta hangs laundry to dry on a line.
IN_TIME_DVS683
Taking a garment from her basket, she pauses and stares inside.
IN_TIME_DVS684
She pulls out a time capsule and looks around.
IN_TIME_DVS685
As she reads the display, her breath quickens and her brow furrows.
IN_TIME_DVS687
as SOMEONE sleeps in a large concrete pipe,
IN_TIME_DVS688
SOMEONE arrives and takes her capsule.
IN_TIME_DVS689
He deposits time from his own body,
IN_TIME_DVS690
then returns it to the sleeping child and slips away.
IN_TIME_DVS691
Now, at the Mission,
IN_TIME_DVS692
a masked SOMEONE holds up its young, long-haired proprietor.
IN_TIME_DVS693
Holding him at gunpoint, SOMEONE transfers time into his body.
IN_TIME_DVS694
The proprietor stares slack-jawed at his clock
IN_TIME_DVS695
and smiles faintly as his balance ticks past a century.
IN_TIME_DVS696
Now, the words Out Of blink of on his neon sign, leaving only Time illuminated.
IN_TIME_DVS697
Citizens hurry over and line up as the proprietor doles out his newly acquired wealth.
IN_TIME_DVS698
At the timekeeper's headquarters.
IN_TIME_DVS699
Using a phone, SOMEONE faces the time map.
IN_TIME_DVS700
Zone 12 shines in amber amidst the surrounding green zones.
IN_TIME_DVS701
SOMEONE ends the call and faces SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS702
In the ghetto, a tall young man with deep-set eyes walks down a deserted street.
IN_TIME_DVS703
He stops and smirks fearlessly as the minutemen's car stops in his path.
IN_TIME_DVS704
Boasting over four weeks, the man draws a gun.
IN_TIME_DVS705
As SOMEONE backs off, the young man smiles triumphantly and nods.
IN_TIME_DVS706
The minutemen get in their car and drive past him.
IN_TIME_DVS707
As the man moves on, the car halts and backs up.
IN_TIME_DVS708
As it heads back toward the defiant young man,
IN_TIME_DVS710
SOMEONE leans out the passenger window and aims a gun at his back. The man collapses.
IN_TIME_DVS711
The man collapses.
IN_TIME_DVS712
SOMEONE gets out, approaches him, and aims again.
IN_TIME_DVS713
Finding his victim's clock frozen in inky numbers, SOMEONE lowers his weapon.
IN_TIME_DVS714
Looking up, he spots a billboard featuring SOMEONE and SOMEONE advertising a reward of ten years.
IN_TIME_DVS715
Now, SOMEONE watches the news.
IN_TIME_DVS716
He turns off the TV. SOMEONE faces him from a doorway.
IN_TIME_DVS717
Now, a sign reads No Tell Hotel. Five hours per night. In a seedy room.
IN_TIME_DVS718
Now, a sign reads No Tell Hotel. Five hours per night. In a seedy room. Seated facing SOMEONE on a bed.
IN_TIME_DVS719
SOMEONE shows a hand of cards. He smiles and she throws them down at her side.
IN_TIME_DVS720
He shows his hand.
IN_TIME_DVS721
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's blouse off, lays her down, and leans over her.
IN_TIME_DVS722
Outside, timekeepers approach SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS723
SOMEONE readies his gun. In the room, SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE's neck.
IN_TIME_DVS725
He pauses, pushes himself up, and looks to the window. He faces his companion gravely.
IN_TIME_DVS726
Peering through blinds, he sees timekeepers approaching.
IN_TIME_DVS727
IN_TIME_DVS728
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE leave the room, a few arrive in the hall.
IN_TIME_DVS729
The break into a nearby room. SOMEONE throws a chair through a window.
IN_TIME_DVS730
They land safely on a car below, and race across the deserted back street. They leap from the second story window.
IN_TIME_DVS731
The run around the corner of a chain link fence and continue behind a solid wall.
IN_TIME_DVS733
SOMEONE and his blond partner watch from the window.
IN_TIME_DVS734
The two outlaws peek back at them.
IN_TIME_DVS735
SOMEONE squeezes past his men and jumps from the window.
IN_TIME_DVS736
IN_TIME_DVS738
The couple takes off running. SOMEONE hops down from the car and sprints after them with a methodical gait.
IN_TIME_DVS739
SOMEONE and SOMEONE reach a more populated area where they pass men in jumpsuits heading to the factory.
IN_TIME_DVS740
SOMEONE arrives as well.
IN_TIME_DVS741
The outlaws dash down a narrow alley.
IN_TIME_DVS743
They climb a fire escape. Behind them, SOMEONE draws his gun.
IN_TIME_DVS745
Now, the two outlaws hurry over a tightly-packed network of rooftops. A few buildings behind them, SOMEONE climbs up and resumes his sprint.
IN_TIME_DVS746
SOMEONE and SOMEONE scurry down a slanted roof.
IN_TIME_DVS747
Gaining on them, SOMEONE fires.
IN_TIME_DVS748
As SOMEONE races on, SOMEONE shoots back at their pursuer, then follows her. Without breaking his stride, SOMEONE leaps from one rooftop to another.
IN_TIME_DVS749
SOMEONE and SOMEONE reach the end of the network and face a broad gap at their feet. Drawing near, SOMEONE takes cover and fires at them.
IN_TIME_DVS750
SOMEONE shoots back.
IN_TIME_DVS752
SOMEONE fires at SOMEONE, who ducks behind a domed bench.
IN_TIME_DVS753
SOMEONE slides down a pipe along the building, followed by her partner in crime. Lunging out to shoot, SOMEONE finds them gone.
IN_TIME_DVS754
The two outlaws hit the ground and dash hand in hand to a bus. They board and pay their fares. The driver faces a sign picturing them.
IN_TIME_DVS755
His side mirror shows SOMEONE sprinting toward the bus.
IN_TIME_DVS756
SOMEONE thrusts out his upturned wrist. The driver puts his own on top of it, watches his body clock tally the transfer of time, and welcomes them with a terse nod.
IN_TIME_DVS757
The bus pulls away, revealing SOMEONE as he arrives at the curb.
IN_TIME_DVS758
On board, SOMEONE and SOMEONE fall into a pair of unoccupied seats and catch their breath.
IN_TIME_DVS759
SOMEONE stares after the bus stoically,
IN_TIME_DVS760
then turns away.
IN_TIME_DVS761
Now, the two outlaws enter a sunlit hotel lobby and approach the desk.
IN_TIME_DVS762
He shows his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS763
The clerk smiles. A lanky man enters with a suitcase as the outlaws head upstairs.
IN_TIME_DVS764
Behind the desk, the clerk pulls her sleeve down over her clock.
IN_TIME_DVS765
The traveler gazes after the outlaws.
IN_TIME_DVS766
He leaves with a sneer.
IN_TIME_DVS767
At night.
IN_TIME_DVS768
The minutemen's car pulls up next to a group of guys who scatter.
IN_TIME_DVS769
SOMEONE' thugs herd the people into a line with their backs against a fence.
IN_TIME_DVS770
Among them, the lanky traveler shifts his angry gaze.
IN_TIME_DVS771
SOMEONE holds up a man's body clock.
IN_TIME_DVS772
His thugs hold the citizens at gunpoint.
IN_TIME_DVS773
SOMEONE steps forward and bends his ear with his finger, then glares at the people.
IN_TIME_DVS774
His gaze falls on the man with a month.
IN_TIME_DVS775
Shaking his head, SOMEONE turns away.
IN_TIME_DVS776
The fedora-wearing thug advances.
IN_TIME_DVS777
He depletes the man with a month.
IN_TIME_DVS778
His time runs out.
IN_TIME_DVS779
As he collapses, SOMEONE tilts his head with a smirk.
IN_TIME_DVS780
He faces the man next to the traveler and skips up to him.
IN_TIME_DVS781
The traveler steps forward.
IN_TIME_DVS782
SOMEONE looks back at the fedora-wearing thug, who lowers his gun.
IN_TIME_DVS783
The gang leader steps in close to the traveler and lazily caresses his lapel.
IN_TIME_DVS784
He brushes off his shoulder and smirks.
IN_TIME_DVS785
Now, on a billboard featuring SOMEONE and SOMEONE, a flickering footer reads Reward: Ten Years.
IN_TIME_DVS786
SOMEONE gazes at it through a hotel window.
IN_TIME_DVS787
He joins SOMEONE, wrapping an arm around her as she leans against him.
IN_TIME_DVS788
Their smiles fade and they gaze off thoughtfully in different directions.
IN_TIME_DVS789
SOMEONE's eyes widen and he shakes his head.
IN_TIME_DVS790
Smiling faintly, he nuzzles her auburn hair, then shrugs his head.
IN_TIME_DVS791
SOMEONE smirks flirtatiously and her companion grins.
IN_TIME_DVS793
She turns to face him and they share a tender kiss.
IN_TIME_DVS794
The minutemen burst in. Led by the fedora-wearing man, the thugs back SOMEONE up to a wall at gunpoint.
IN_TIME_DVS795
SOMEONE sits by SOMEONE and forcefully holds her close.
IN_TIME_DVS796
SOMEONE drags SOMEONE across the suite.
IN_TIME_DVS797
The fedora-wearing thug pulls SOMEONE along.
IN_TIME_DVS798
The minutemen force the couple to sit at a table.
IN_TIME_DVS799
SOMEONE hands his gun off to an underling.
IN_TIME_DVS800
SOMEONE removes his overcoat then his jacket.
IN_TIME_DVS801
Rolling up his shirt sleeve, he sits facing SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS802
He rests his arms on the table and leans forward.
IN_TIME_DVS803
SOMEONE maintains a stoic gaze as the gangster reaches a hand across the table, his palm turned upward.
IN_TIME_DVS804
SOMEONE reaches for SOMEONE's leg but she smacks his hand away.
IN_TIME_DVS805
He gives a cocky grin.
IN_TIME_DVS806
SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE, who shakes her head with wide eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS807
He rolls up his sleeve and lays his arm on the table, showing his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS808
As he reaches his other hand out, SOMEONE takes a deep breath.
IN_TIME_DVS809
SOMEONE and SOMEONE clasp each other's forearms. The gang leader wrenches his arm over SOMEONE's, quickly depleting his time.
IN_TIME_DVS810
SOMEONE stares at the men's clocks.
IN_TIME_DVS811
SOMEONE gazes steadily at his foe and breathes deeply through flared nostrils. He starts to rotate his arm over the gangster's.
IN_TIME_DVS812
SOMEONE lets him teasingly, then wrenches himself back into the upper handed position.
IN_TIME_DVS813
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE's clock. Its balance ticks toward 15 seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS814
SOMEONE lifts his chin, smirking triumphantly as he maintains eye contact with his rival.
IN_TIME_DVS815
SOMEONE's clock ticks under ten seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS816
SOMEONE' eyes dart downward. SOMEONE cocks his head, then claims the upper hand, pinning his opponent's wrist to the table. SOMEONE struggles futilely to free himself, then eyes his rapidly depleting balance. SOMEONE and the thugs lean forward, watching intently. SOMEONE scowls desperately. He watches his clock tick down to ten seconds. Without breaking eye contact with SOMEONE, SOMEONE draws a gun from his boot and shoots the underlings.
IN_TIME_DVS817
He aims at SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS818
The gangster flies back in his chair and falls to the floor.
IN_TIME_DVS819
SOMEONE and SOMEONE join hands and escape to a dimly lit hallway.
IN_TIME_DVS820
They hurry up a stairwell.
IN_TIME_DVS821
Now, SOMEONE gazes at the four dead minutemen who lie face down on a sidewalk.
IN_TIME_DVS822
SOMEONE blinks, his back to SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS823
With his hands clasped calmly behind his back,
IN_TIME_DVS824
he steps up to SOMEONE, his face mere inches from the other timekeeper's.
IN_TIME_DVS825
His cold eyes hold SOMEONE's.
IN_TIME_DVS826
He backs off.
IN_TIME_DVS827
With his displeased gaze still on SOMEONE, SOMEONE rumples his lips, then turns away.
IN_TIME_DVS828
As he and the blond timekeeper stride off,
IN_TIME_DVS829
SOMEONE shifts his attention to the bystanders gathered in a wide circle around him.
IN_TIME_DVS830
He strolls up to a group of them.
IN_TIME_DVS832
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE by the hand across a roof.
IN_TIME_DVS833
Reaching a chest-high wall at its edge, they peer down at the street
IN_TIME_DVS834
where a digital sign on a storefront displays the time lender's loan rate.
IN_TIME_DVS835
They watch it as it ticks up from 33% to 37%.
IN_TIME_DVS836
SOMEONE turns away.
IN_TIME_DVS837
He stands with his back to SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS838
She gives him an exasperated look.
IN_TIME_DVS839
She stares off thoughtfully, then shifts her eyes back to him.
IN_TIME_DVS840
SOMEONE shoots her a questioning glance.
IN_TIME_DVS842
Three limos pulled into the semi-circular driveway in front of a towering skyscraper.
IN_TIME_DVS843
A cluster of guards waits outside one as SOMEONE climbs out.
IN_TIME_DVS844
The suited men surround their charge and the group heads up a broad flight of stairs in the building's lobby.
IN_TIME_DVS845
Toting a gun in one hand, SOMEONE strides in after them.
IN_TIME_DVS846
SOMEONE spots her.
IN_TIME_DVS847
He raises his weapon. The other guards aim at her as well.
IN_TIME_DVS848
Pushing aside two guards, SOMEONE emerges from behind their protective wall.
IN_TIME_DVS849
She sets her gun on the floor.
IN_TIME_DVS850
He stares with wide eyes. She steps closer.
IN_TIME_DVS851
She smiles.
IN_TIME_DVS852
Among them, SOMEONE aims a gun at SOMEONE's head.
IN_TIME_DVS853
SOMEONE gives a shocked look.
IN_TIME_DVS854
As the guards set their weapons on the floor, SOMEONE removes his sunglasses. SOMEONE picks up her gun and strides up to her father.
IN_TIME_DVS855
Smiling, SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE closer.
IN_TIME_DVS857
he emerges from an elevator with SOMEONE at gunpoint.
IN_TIME_DVS858
SOMEONE follows. At her father's office, she enters a pass code.
IN_TIME_DVS859
SOMEONE guides the businessman inside.
IN_TIME_DVS860
He glances at the digital map and data tables as SOMEONE leads them past.
IN_TIME_DVS861
Reaching a vault in an adjacent room, he releases SOMEONE and moves to the metal door.
IN_TIME_DVS862
SOMEONE trains her gun on her father.
IN_TIME_DVS863
SOMEONE turns the vault's dial.
IN_TIME_DVS864
SOMEONE looks away.
IN_TIME_DVS865
He turns the vault's wheel and heaves the door open.
IN_TIME_DVS866
Inside, he finds a lone time capsule on a pedestal.
IN_TIME_DVS867
Its time balance reads
IN_TIME_DVS868
one million years.
IN_TIME_DVS869
SOMEONE stares disbelievingly.
IN_TIME_DVS870
SOMEONE watches as he exits the vault with the capsule and shakes his head.
IN_TIME_DVS871
He hands the capsule to her.
IN_TIME_DVS872
SOMEONE strides forward,
IN_TIME_DVS873
his gun aimed at SOMEONE's head.
IN_TIME_DVS874
The businessman backs up a few steps,
IN_TIME_DVS875
leaning away from the weapon only inches from his brow.
IN_TIME_DVS876
SOMEONE glares at him, then lowers his gun.
IN_TIME_DVS877
SOMEONE takes a shaky breath as she watches from a doorway.
IN_TIME_DVS878
He strides out of the office and SOMEONE punches a code into the keypad.
IN_TIME_DVS879
As the doors slide shut, closing SOMEONE inside,
IN_TIME_DVS880
she stares at him through their diminishing gap.
IN_TIME_DVS881
SOMEONE aims his gun at the keypad.
IN_TIME_DVS882
At the timekeeper's headquarters.
IN_TIME_DVS883
SOMEONE eyes the circulation map and per capita table.
IN_TIME_DVS884
SOMEONE's brow furrows.
IN_TIME_DVS885
SOMEONE sprints out of the building.
IN_TIME_DVS886
In a parking garage, SOMEONE pays an attendant.
IN_TIME_DVS887
A security gate at the parking booth lifts and SOMEONE drives a limo out of the garage.
IN_TIME_DVS888
Meanwhile, SOMEONE distractedly chews gum as he steers a cruiser through New Greenwich.
IN_TIME_DVS889
His alert eyes scan his surroundings.
IN_TIME_DVS890
Riding beside SOMEONE, SOMEONE eyes the capsule.
IN_TIME_DVS891
SOMEONE finds 44 minutes on his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS892
Spinning the wheel, he skids around a grassy island dividing the two directions of traffic and speeds after the limo.
IN_TIME_DVS893
At one end of a bridge, timekeeper vehicles line up along the zone's border.
IN_TIME_DVS894
Taking shelter behind them, timekeepers aim their weapons over the hoods.
IN_TIME_DVS895
SOMEONE stares with determined eyes as he speeds toward the barricade.
IN_TIME_DVS896
SOMEONE glances over her shoulder at SOMEONE's cruiser, which closes in.
IN_TIME_DVS897
A barrage of bullets hits the limo, sending sparks off the vehicle's armored body.
IN_TIME_DVS898
SOMEONE and SOMEONE flinch as shots hit the windshield, leaving dents in the bulletproof glass.
IN_TIME_DVS899
SOMEONE briefly takes SOMEONE's hand.
IN_TIME_DVS900
He weaves the limo between the cruisers and crashes straight through the border's security booth.
IN_TIME_DVS901
The concrete barricades lower and SOMEONE drives over.
IN_TIME_DVS903
The limo speeds down a street in the ghetto.
IN_TIME_DVS904
Following close behind, SOMEONE's cruiser turns a corner.
IN_TIME_DVS905
Meanwhile, outside the Mission, SOMEONE waits with the young proprietor. She blinks her anxious eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS906
As they speed through an intersection one block from the Mission, SOMEONE's cruiser emerges from the cross street and smashes into them.
IN_TIME_DVS907
Both vehicles skid to a stop, billowing smoke.
IN_TIME_DVS908
SOMEONE runs over as SOMEONE climbs out of the limo.
IN_TIME_DVS909
He glances at the cruiser but sees no movement.
IN_TIME_DVS910
He hands her the capsule and her jaw drops.
IN_TIME_DVS911
She races off.
IN_TIME_DVS912
He's got an hour.
IN_TIME_DVS913
SOMEONE gets out of his car. As he aims his gun at SOMEONE and SOMEONE, Dayton residents crowd closer.
IN_TIME_DVS914
On the Mission's sign, the words Out Of turn off.
IN_TIME_DVS915
Grabbing SOMEONE's hand, SOMEONE pulls her against the flow of the crowd which now hurries toward the Mission.
IN_TIME_DVS916
He glances over his shoulder. Behind him, SOMEONE shoves his way past the flood of Dayton residents. With his gun in one hand, he pumps his arms as he sprints furiously.
IN_TIME_DVS917
He finds a timekeeper parked on a corner with his driver's side door open.
IN_TIME_DVS918
Grabbing him, he hurls him to the ground, climbs into the cruiser, and speeds off.
IN_TIME_DVS919
Outside the Mission, the crowd converges around the proprietor, who dispenses time from the stolen cartridge.
IN_TIME_DVS920
Meanwhile, SOMEONE and SOMEONE flee down a street, still holding hands.
IN_TIME_DVS921
He checks his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS922
From the cruiser, SOMEONE spots the couple running down a road amid rolling grassy hills.
IN_TIME_DVS923
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, noting her pained expression.
IN_TIME_DVS924
She nods. Meanwhile, the cruiser speeds down a nearby road.
IN_TIME_DVS925
A wide view shows SOMEONE and SOMEONE running on cracked pavement.
IN_TIME_DVS926
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder.
IN_TIME_DVS927
At the top of a hill, SOMEONE parks behind a
IN_TIME_DVS928
barricade of concrete blocks across the road which SOMEONE the time zone border.
IN_TIME_DVS929
Clutching his gun, he sprints between the blocks and follows the road down the hill.
IN_TIME_DVS930
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE close in on the border, SOMEONE cuts them off, his gun raised.
IN_TIME_DVS931
They halt in front of him and he gives a relieved look.
IN_TIME_DVS932
He allows an impressed smile.
IN_TIME_DVS933
SOMEONE scrutinizes him.
IN_TIME_DVS934
SOMEONE wipes his brow, then nods.
IN_TIME_DVS935
Shaking his head, SOMEONE gives an outraged smile. He glances at SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS936
SOMEONE's clock shows 1 minute, 26 seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS937
SOMEONE nods.
IN_TIME_DVS938
A look of realization crosses his face and he shifts his worried eyes.
IN_TIME_DVS939
Lowering his gun, he checks his own clock, which counts down from five seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS940
His lips part in a shocked expression.
IN_TIME_DVS941
He convulses, then falls back with his arms and legs sprawled.
IN_TIME_DVS942
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange a fearful glance.
IN_TIME_DVS943
Facing a city on the horizon, SOMEONE checks his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS944
58 seconds remain.
IN_TIME_DVS945
SOMEONE watches her own clock dip under one minute.
IN_TIME_DVS946
His clock shows 45 seconds.
IN_TIME_DVS947
He caresses her cheek, then leans in and kisses her.
IN_TIME_DVS948
Pulling away, he lifts his thoughtful gaze to the cruiser atop the hill.
IN_TIME_DVS949
They take off toward the cruiser. The distance between SOMEONE and SOMEONE grows and SOMEONE checks his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS950
20 seconds. He glances over his shoulder.
IN_TIME_DVS951
He frantically sprints ahead, his eyes focused on the top of the hill.
IN_TIME_DVS952
Behind him, SOMEONE checks her clock.
IN_TIME_DVS953
SOMEONE reaches the cruiser and jumps inside. He sets his arm in the scanner.
IN_TIME_DVS954
He reads the balance, then races back down the hill. Lifting her arm, SOMEONE finds six seconds left on her clock.
IN_TIME_DVS955
SOMEONE reaches out as they draw closer. SOMEONE launches into his arms.
IN_TIME_DVS956
As she clings to him, SOMEONE drops to one knee, his arms wrapped around her limp body.
IN_TIME_DVS957
With a relieved look, he presses a hand to the back of her head,
IN_TIME_DVS958
then pulls away and grins.
IN_TIME_DVS959
He checks his clock.
IN_TIME_DVS960
With his arms still around her, he helps her to her feet.
IN_TIME_DVS961
Cupping her face, he kisses her.
IN_TIME_DVS962
Now, in SOMEONE's office, SOMEONE watches the time zone map, which lights up in a frenzy.
IN_TIME_DVS963
SOMEONE gazes into his empty vault.
IN_TIME_DVS964
A news report plays.
IN_TIME_DVS966
SOMEONE and three others watch the circulation map at their headquarters.
IN_TIME_DVS967
A female timekeeper turns to him.
IN_TIME_DVS968
He gives a resolute nod.
IN_TIME_DVS969
Setting his gun on a table, he heads away past a poster kiosk which displays photos of SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
IN_TIME_DVS970
Now, a news report shows the same images.
IN_TIME_DVS971
A captions under the photos reads 100 Years Reward. A wider view shows the news report on a television in a car's console. SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in front. They share a look and SOMEONE inserts a magazine clip into a gun.
IN_TIME_DVS974
They get out of the car.
IN_TIME_DVS976
SOMEONE gazes up the wide steps leading to a stately building.
IN_TIME_DVS977
He shakes his head.
IN_TIME_DVS978
SOMEONE gives a sly smile.
IN_TIME_DVS979
She and SOMEONE ready their guns, then jog up the steps.
IN_TIME_DVS980
Our view widens to reveal a broad row of pillared stone archways opening into the towering bank's courtyard.