Vanishing from view, as the van continues onward.
KARATE_KID_DVS28
SOMEONE frowns and leans his head against the seat.
KARATE_KID_DVS29
They drive past urban apartment buildings and parks.
KARATE_KID_DVS31
Now, the taxi drives past tall warehouses and over a set of train tracks. Downtown, the windshield wipers clear a rainy view of towering high-rises.
KARATE_KID_DVS34
Now at an airport, a jumbo jet reads, Air China.
KARATE_KID_DVS35
Inside, travelers bustle around the cabin.
KARATE_KID_DVS36
Almost all but SOMEONE and his mother are Asian.
KARATE_KID_DVS37
SOMEONE stands on a seat and shoves a satchel into an overhead bin. His mother watches as he struggles to close it.
KARATE_KID_DVS40
He doffs his jacket and takes a seat.
KARATE_KID_DVS41
His mom uses a laptop.
KARATE_KID_DVS47
He shows a magazine.
KARATE_KID_DVS49
She looks across the aisle.
KARATE_KID_DVS52
SOMEONE leans toward a stocky Asian man with a pierced ear.
KARATE_KID_DVS57
The man shrugs his brow noncommittally. A title, The Karate Kid
KARATE_KID_DVS58
Later, the plane takes off.
KARATE_KID_DVS59
On-board, passengers sip tea and uniformed flight attendants work the aisles.
KARATE_KID_DVS60
Nighttime. In the dim cabin, SOMEONE plays a handheld video game. Later, he sleeps on his mother's shoulder. As time passes, SOMEONE's sleeping form fades in and out of multiple contortions in his seat.
KARATE_KID_DVS67
Now, sunlight bathes SOMEONE's face as he blinks awake.
KARATE_KID_DVS68
His mother wakes and smiles at him.
KARATE_KID_DVS70
Now, the plane touches down. In an airport, a statue shows four serpentine dragons holding up a globe.
KARATE_KID_DVS71
SOMEONE and his mother roll two heaped luggage carts.
KARATE_KID_DVS72
A nearby sign shows a Chinese character.
KARATE_KID_DVS73
A woman holds a sign in English.
KARATE_KID_DVS74
From a van on a highway, SOMEONE looks out at China's central TV headquarters, a looming skyscraper resembling a pair of rectangular legs, bent at the knees, and spread apart.
KARATE_KID_DVS76
A man in a passing bus peeks out his window at SOMEONE. In the van, their driver hands SOMEONE's mom some papers. They pass a courtyard featuring a Mao statue.
KARATE_KID_DVS77
The stadium resembles a sleek-steel bird's nest.
KARATE_KID_DVS78
The boy eyes his mother.
KARATE_KID_DVS79
Now in a park, men and women relax in and around a small pavilion. The van drives past.
KARATE_KID_DVS80
Story by Robert SOMEONE Kamen. Screenplay by SOMEONE Murphey. Directed by Harald Zwart.
KARATE_KID_DVS81
It parks in front of an apartment building and the Parkers get out.
KARATE_KID_DVS82
A golden sign reads, "Beverly Hills Luxury Apartment."
KARATE_KID_DVS84
SOMEONE gives the sign a skeptical look.
KARATE_KID_DVS85
A tall, blond, Caucasian boy jogs up to them.
KARATE_KID_DVS87
SOMEONE grabs some luggage.
KARATE_KID_DVS89
They head inside.
KARATE_KID_DVS90
A man gardens in the hallway.
KARATE_KID_DVS92
SOMEONE peeks out a window at a park across the street.
KARATE_KID_DVS94
SOMEONE stares after SOMEONE, then eyeballs the doorway to his new apartment, and frowns.
KARATE_KID_DVS95
He surveys the run-down hallway, lined with houseplants,
KARATE_KID_DVS96
and heads inside.
KARATE_KID_DVS99
SOMEONE drops his jacket on the floor and turns on the TV.
KARATE_KID_DVS100
He smiles.
KARATE_KID_DVS101
His smile wilts.
KARATE_KID_DVS102
His mother spots his jacket on the floor.
KARATE_KID_DVS103
SOMEONE stifles an amused grin and picks up the jacket herself.
KARATE_KID_DVS104
She hangs it on a coat rack.
KARATE_KID_DVS106
She draws him into a hug.
KARATE_KID_DVS107
Later, SOMEONE moves a suitcase into the apartment, then ambles over to the windows lining the hallway.
KARATE_KID_DVS108
Children play in the tree-filled park across the street.
KARATE_KID_DVS109
Now in the lobby, SOMEONE faces a guard.
KARATE_KID_DVS112
The puzzled guard squints.
KARATE_KID_DVS113
The guard points. In the busy street outside, SOMEONE hikes around the corner of the building, passing a shabby office. He enters a long shadowy hallway and looks around.
KARATE_KID_DVS114
Passing a row of empty chairs, he finds a small break room, where a group of grubby maintenance men lounge around a table.
KARATE_KID_DVS115
The men stare at him.
KARATE_KID_DVS118
His friendly expression fades as they keep staring.
KARATE_KID_DVS119
His eyes search their faces.
KARATE_KID_DVS120
He mimes using a showerhead to spray himself down, hugs himself, and pretends to shiver.
KARATE_KID_DVS121
The maintenance men continue to stare.
KARATE_KID_DVS126
Outside at the office,
KARATE_KID_DVS127
SOMEONE peeks through the screen door and finds a man hunched in front of a fan, with his back to the entrance.
KARATE_KID_DVS128
The lone man shifts his head.
KARATE_KID_DVS129
Mr. SOMEONE slurps up a wad of noodles.
KARATE_KID_DVS130
SOMEONE steps inside. The mustached, middle-aged man glares at him over his shoulder.
KARATE_KID_DVS133
SOMEONE watches a fly darting around his head. Raising his chopsticks, he follows its movements.
KARATE_KID_DVS134
SOMEONE watches the man from outside.
KARATE_KID_DVS135
The fly lands on a yellowed schematic of a sedan, posted on the wall.
KARATE_KID_DVS136
SOMEONE raises his chopsticks. He smacks the bug with the flyswatter.
KARATE_KID_DVS138
He turns the swatter in the light.
KARATE_KID_DVS139
He pinches the dead fly off with his chopsticks. He discards the bug, wipes the utensils off on his thigh, and resumes eating his noodles with them.
KARATE_KID_DVS141
A woman bursts in with a broken light fixture.
KARATE_KID_DVS142
SOMEONE looks past her, eyeing SOMEONE as he trudges off.
KARATE_KID_DVS143
SOMEONE's gaze follows SOMEONE outside the windows as the boy halts in the middle of the street.
KARATE_KID_DVS144
Several young teens with a basketball rush past into the park.
KARATE_KID_DVS145
SOMEONE glances up and down the street, then follows.
KARATE_KID_DVS147
In the park, two women use a pair of public-access exercisers that simulate cross-country skiing.
KARATE_KID_DVS148
Two older men play ping-pong.
KARATE_KID_DVS150
SOMEONE notices a pre-teen Chinese girl sitting on a bench, practicing finger positions on a violin.
KARATE_KID_DVS152
A layered-bob haircut, parted in two pigtails, frames her pixie-like face.
KARATE_KID_DVS153
SOMEONE smiles to himself.
KARATE_KID_DVS154
SOMEONE tosses a basketball.
KARATE_KID_DVS155
SOMEONE speaks Chinese.
KARATE_KID_DVS161
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE play basketball with a group of Chinese boys. SOMEONE passes to SOMEONE and the pixie-faced girl looks up. A boy misses a basket.
KARATE_KID_DVS165
SOMEONE's teammate passes to him and he launches the ball into the air. It sails over the backboard. All the boys gape.
KARATE_KID_DVS166
SOMEONE heads off the court and the pixie-faced girl grins. A Ping-Pong ball bounces toward SOMEONE and he picks it up.
KARATE_KID_DVS167
He shows it to the aging players at the table, who nod.
KARATE_KID_DVS168
SOMEONE notices the pixie-faced girl watching him.
KARATE_KID_DVS169
A man offers his paddle.
KARATE_KID_DVS170
SOMEONE accepts the paddle and faces a paunchy man in an old tank top.
KARATE_KID_DVS171
SOMEONE gently hits the ball to the man, who gently swats it back. They trade easy shots over a row of rocks taking the place of a net. SOMEONE whacks the ball and scores on his paunchy opponent. The boy offers a cocky shrug.
KARATE_KID_DVS172
His opponent smiles sympathetically and the pixie-faced girl giggles.
KARATE_KID_DVS173
Eyeing SOMEONE, the paunchy man tosses the ball into the air, and slams it across the table, acing him.
KARATE_KID_DVS174
SOMEONE dodges and cowers as the man fires the ball at him repeatedly.
KARATE_KID_DVS176
The man's next shot hits SOMEONE. As he hides his face behind his paddle, the ball bounces off of it. The pixie-faced girl laughs. Later.
KARATE_KID_DVS179
Sitting on a basketball, SOMEONE sneaks a look at the girl.
KARATE_KID_DVS181
SOMEONE shifts his conflicted gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS182
SOMEONE gets to his feet.
KARATE_KID_DVS183
He ventures over to the bench, where the girl studies sheet music.
KARATE_KID_DVS184
She peeks nervously at him as he nears.
KARATE_KID_DVS185
She looks up at the American and shuffles her feet.
KARATE_KID_DVS186
She nods.
KARATE_KID_DVS187
She removes her ear buds.
KARATE_KID_DVS188
He hands her a combination cell phone and MP3 player.
KARATE_KID_DVS189
She smiles appreciatively.
KARATE_KID_DVS190
SOMEONE performs pop-and-lock dance moves for her. She watches with a charmed grin. Across the yard, a boy with close-cropped hair beckons a friend with hard features.
KARATE_KID_DVS191
He and four buddies watch, as does a smiling SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS192
One local boy in a ball cap tries to copy him.
KARATE_KID_DVS193
SOMEONE stops dancing and stares.
KARATE_KID_DVS194
She gives a meek nod.
KARATE_KID_DVS195
The American leans close and she fondles his chocolate-brown braids.
KARATE_KID_DVS196
The hard-featured Chinese boy steps in close. He backs SOMEONE off with a glare, then faces the girl.
KARATE_KID_DVS199
He throws her music down.
KARATE_KID_DVS201
SOMEONE picks up the sheet music. The boy’s friends gather around. SOMEONE starts to return the music to the girl. The boy knocks it out of his hands.
KARATE_KID_DVS202
As the girl starts to put her violin away, SOMEONE picks up the music again.
KARATE_KID_DVS203
SOMEONE offers the music to the girl.
KARATE_KID_DVS204
The boy swipes at it, but SOMEONE yanks it out of reach.
KARATE_KID_DVS205
The boy shoves SOMEONE to the ground. Looking on, SOMEONE gets to his feet.
KARATE_KID_DVS206
SOMEONE stands and raises his fists.
KARATE_KID_DVS207
The boy in the cap points out the defiant gesture to his hard-featured friend.
KARATE_KID_DVS208
The bully advances and beckons SOMEONE, who runs at him. With a crouching-leg sweep, the boy sends him sprawling. The girl bends down toward him, but the shorthaired boy holds her back.
KARATE_KID_DVS209
The boy in the cap hauls SOMEONE to his feet.
KARATE_KID_DVS211
SOMEONE runs at the bully, who flips him over his shoulder. He lands hard on his back.
KARATE_KID_DVS212
SOMEONE approaches the bully. SOMEONE lies clutching his chest.
KARATE_KID_DVS213
He gestures imploringly at his injured friend and shakes his head.
KARATE_KID_DVS214
The bully orders SOMEONE away. At their feet, SOMEONE wipes his eyes and pushes himself up.
KARATE_KID_DVS215
SOMEONE backs off.
KARATE_KID_DVS216
The bully glares at SOMEONE, who wipes his sleeve across his eyes and raises his fists again.
KARATE_KID_DVS217
He swings, but the skilled fighter catches his arm. The bully punches him in the solar plexus, then boots him backward with a kick to the chest.
KARATE_KID_DVS218
Now, the girl wrenches herself free of the other boys, runs to the bully, and yells at him.
KARATE_KID_DVS219
The boy looks down at SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS220
SOMEONE springs up, delivering a fierce backhand. It knocks the bully down, but he does an instant kick-up to his feet. As he circles the American, his friends restrain the struggling girl. He assaults SOMEONE with a rapid series of vicious kicks and punches, then flings the limp American to the ground.
KARATE_KID_DVS221
Crouching over his fallen opponent, he delivers a brutal punch to SOMEONE's left eye.
KARATE_KID_DVS222
The boy winces painfully and covers the injury with both hands. The girl wrenches free again. She angrily shoves the bully, who stalks off. SOMEONE leans in.
KARATE_KID_DVS223
The girl reluctantly backs off.
KARATE_KID_DVS225
SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE to himself and the other gawkers disperse.
KARATE_KID_DVS226
Later, shadows streak the concrete, as SOMEONE remains sprawled across a free-throw line, a chalk circle framing his form.
KARATE_KID_DVS227
Our view slowly spins above him, and the circle becomes a peephole in their apartment door, marked 305.
KARATE_KID_DVS228
SOMEONE arrives and peeks in.
KARATE_KID_DVS229
In the small living room, SOMEONE naps on the sunlit couch.
KARATE_KID_DVS230
SOMEONE creeps through the shadowy foyer, a hand to his battered chest.
KARATE_KID_DVS231
Entering his room, he shuts the door behind him.
KARATE_KID_DVS232
Now, a classical Chinese tower, with stacked roofs, stands silhouetted against a golden sky and low sun. It juts above treetops overlooking tranquil shimmering water.
KARATE_KID_DVS233
Now, traffic packs the modern streets of Beijing in the early morning light.
KARATE_KID_DVS234
In a bathroom, SOMEONE applies makeup to his bruised eye.
KARATE_KID_DVS236
SOMEONE blends the makeup on his skin.
KARATE_KID_DVS238
The bathroom door opens, revealing SOMEONE with a cap tipped over his eyes.
KARATE_KID_DVS239
Now, the Parkers arrive at a building marked with a red, five-pointed star.
KARATE_KID_DVS241
A smartly dressed administrator waits for them.
KARATE_KID_DVS242
SOMEONE spies the bully and his friends.
KARATE_KID_DVS243
SOMEONE wears an orange polo.
KARATE_KID_DVS244
SOMEONE removes his cap.
KARATE_KID_DVS249
SOMEONE scowls at her son and he looks away.
KARATE_KID_DVS250
SOMEONE follows Mrs. Po toward the entrance.
KARATE_KID_DVS251
With an embarrassed pout, SOMEONE turns away.
KARATE_KID_DVS252
Now, students race along first-and-second-story walkways. In a cafeteria, SOMEONE holds a combination tray and bowl in one hand.
KARATE_KID_DVS253
With the other, he struggles to serve himself food with chopsticks.
KARATE_KID_DVS254
A hand strokes one of his braids. It's the pretty violinist.
KARATE_KID_DVS255
He beams at her.
KARATE_KID_DVS256
She gets a tray and bowl for herself, then circles around behind him, with a scrutinizing gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS258
Using her chopsticks, she fills his bowl with noodles.
KARATE_KID_DVS259
SOMEONE allows a humble smile.
KARATE_KID_DVS260
With a shy grin, SOMEONE leads him to a counter protected by a glass barrier. She hands her tray to a cafeteria worker.
KARATE_KID_DVS262
SOMEONE grins and giggles.
KARATE_KID_DVS263
The girl grins sweetly and leaves. SOMEONE watches her go, with a peaceful smile, and wanders in her general direction.
KARATE_KID_DVS264
SOMEONE knocks the tray out of his hands.
KARATE_KID_DVS265
As SOMEONE obeys, SOMEONE bumps his shoulder.
KARATE_KID_DVS266
Mrs. Po sends SOMEONE in the opposite direction.
KARATE_KID_DVS267
Outside, SOMEONE gazes after SOMEONE sympathetically.
KARATE_KID_DVS268
Now, as students file out from the school, SOMEONE lumbers down the front steps and shuffles glumly to the gate.
KARATE_KID_DVS269
Turning, he passes a man in a gray uniform, standing guard beneath a red flag.
KARATE_KID_DVS271
SOMEONE mopes down the sidewalk, passing between two cramped rows of parked bicycles.
KARATE_KID_DVS273
Now, twin skyscrapers under construction stand silhouetted against a rising sun that glows through the smog.
KARATE_KID_DVS274
Cars pack a four-lane artery.
KARATE_KID_DVS276
In the park, two women twirl long colorful ribbons.
KARATE_KID_DVS277
Nearby, dozens of other locals perform graceful steps and gestures in unison.
KARATE_KID_DVS278
Now, Mr. SOMEONE carries a toolbox to the apartment building's entrance.
KARATE_KID_DVS280
gIn the living room of 305, SOMEONE practices martial-arts drills, uided by an instructor on TV.
KARATE_KID_DVS281
Mr. SOMEONE peeks in through the open door.
KARATE_KID_DVS284
SOMEONE points lazily. Mr. SOMEONE enters the apartment, watching as the boy flings his fists and feet in sloppy punches and low kicks.
KARATE_KID_DVS285
SOMEONE notices the man watching him, but continues the drills.
KARATE_KID_DVS286
With a barely perceptible shake of the head, Mr. SOMEONE enters the cerulean-tiled bathroom.
KARATE_KID_DVS287
SOMEONE sneaks a peek at the man, who sets his toolbox down.
KARATE_KID_DVS288
Mr. SOMEONE examines the shower, while the American boy practices elbow jabs.
KARATE_KID_DVS289
Looking around, the maintenance man spies a toothpaste cap on the sink.
KARATE_KID_DVS290
He picks it up, takes careful aim, and flicks it. It hits SOMEONE in the neck.
KARATE_KID_DVS291
The boy turns and Mr. SOMEONE beckons him with a finger.
KARATE_KID_DVS292
Frowning, SOMEONE picks up the toothpaste cap on his way to the bathroom.
KARATE_KID_DVS297
Mr. SOMEONE reaches to his toolbox.
KARATE_KID_DVS299
SOMEONE approaches his mother.
KARATE_KID_DVS300
As SOMEONE returns to the TV, SOMEONE notices his jacket lying crumpled at the base of the coat rack.
KARATE_KID_DVS304
SOMEONE picks up his jacket.
KARATE_KID_DVS305
SOMEONE goes to the kitchen.
KARATE_KID_DVS306
Gazing after her, SOMEONE flings the jacket up on its hook, with a broad sarcastic smile.
KARATE_KID_DVS307
He turns to find Mr. SOMEONE staring at him, his screwdriver motionless at the door.
KARATE_KID_DVS308
The boy sheepishly meets Mr. SOMEONE's sharp gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS309
SOMEONE returns to the living room.
KARATE_KID_DVS310
At school, dozens of students pour into the central courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS311
SOMEONE enters the cafeteria, his backpack slung over one shoulder. He starts to get a tray, then pauses.
KARATE_KID_DVS312
At another entrance, SOMEONE enters with his shorthaired friend.
KARATE_KID_DVS313
SOMEONE slips back out the nearest door and strides briskly alongside the building.
KARATE_KID_DVS314
A few more boys join SOMEONE and his friend. And they leave through the same door.
KARATE_KID_DVS315
SOMEONE detours down a short corridor, glances toward one offshoot, then ducks around another corner, and presses his back to the wall.
KARATE_KID_DVS316
The boys stroll in his direction, then turn down the off-shooting hallway.
KARATE_KID_DVS317
SOMEONE gazes after them and his shoulders sag.
KARATE_KID_DVS318
Turning, he cocks his head.
KARATE_KID_DVS319
He glances after the bullies, then ventures from his hiding spot.
KARATE_KID_DVS320
Before him, two, red, wooden doors stand open, revealing a pair of inner doors upholstered in dark-green leather.
KARATE_KID_DVS321
The inner doors open on an auditorium.
KARATE_KID_DVS322
SOMEONE crosses to a window separating the lobby from the house, pulls a curtain aside, and peers through.
KARATE_KID_DVS324
On a stage decorated with a colorful interpretation of the sea at night, SOMEONE plays the violin.
KARATE_KID_DVS325
A lanky man with graying hair accompanies her on the piano.
KARATE_KID_DVS326
Transfixed by the pretty young musician, SOMEONE steps out from behind the partition and cocks his head dreamily.
KARATE_KID_DVS328
SOMEONE bows her head and tightly grips her violin.
KARATE_KID_DVS329
The instructor steps through a doorway near the stage.
KARATE_KID_DVS330
SOMEONE peers into the house and smiles.
KARATE_KID_DVS331
SOMEONE approaches the stage.
KARATE_KID_DVS332
SOMEONE gazes out into the house and spreads his arms.
KARATE_KID_DVS334
SOMEONE drops his backpack.
KARATE_KID_DVS335
SOMEONE's smile fades and she shifts her puzzled gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS336
The instructor heads back in.
KARATE_KID_DVS337
As SOMEONE scrambles away, SOMEONE resumes practicing.
KARATE_KID_DVS338
The instructor sits at the piano and nods.
KARATE_KID_DVS339
The violinist spies SOMEONE's shadowy form creeping toward the exit.
KARATE_KID_DVS340
She allows a brief chuckle.
KARATE_KID_DVS341
Now, SOMEONE steps outside and ambles along with a smile.
KARATE_KID_DVS342
He encounters SOMEONE and his friends.
KARATE_KID_DVS343
He touches one of SOMEONE's cornrows.
KARATE_KID_DVS344
The American starts to go, but the bullies surround him. He drops his bag.
KARATE_KID_DVS346
The shorthaired boy circles around behind him.
KARATE_KID_DVS347
He and another boy kick the backpack around.
KARATE_KID_DVS348
The shorthaired boy picks it up.
KARATE_KID_DVS350
He and his friend dump out its contents, then give the bag another kick. SOMEONE steps closer to SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS351
He glances toward the auditorium.
KARATE_KID_DVS352
With a kick, he sends SOMEONE's bag flying high. One of the other boys kicks it as it lands, and the third tosses a book at SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS353
As they leave, the American stands motionless, staring after them.
KARATE_KID_DVS354
His shoulders droop.
KARATE_KID_DVS355
Now, the living room TV shows SpongeBob Square Pants.
KARATE_KID_DVS356
SOMEONE lies on the couch, watching the cartoon.
KARATE_KID_DVS357
As his mother comes in, SOMEONE curls up and shuts his eyes.
KARATE_KID_DVS358
She sets a tote bag and purse on a dining table.
KARATE_KID_DVS359
Coming into the living room, she adjusts the strap of her summery pink dress.
KARATE_KID_DVS360
SOMEONE maintains his slumbering charade as she crouches beside him.
KARATE_KID_DVS361
SOMEONE heaves a sigh as she regards her son, then smiles affectionately.
KARATE_KID_DVS362
She picks up a remote and turns the TV off.
KARATE_KID_DVS364
As she steps away, SOMEONE opens his eyes.
KARATE_KID_DVS366
Now, people crowd a sunny market.
KARATE_KID_DVS367
One booth holds huge stacks of watermelons.
KARATE_KID_DVS368
The vendor tapes half a melon to the back of a customer's bike. SOMEONE and his mom walk the market.
KARATE_KID_DVS370
She eats ice cream.
KARATE_KID_DVS371
She dabs ice cream on his forehead.
KARATE_KID_DVS372
SOMEONE looks past her and stares.
KARATE_KID_DVS373
He rushes across a busy street without her. Catching up, SOMEONE follows him through a gate flanked by gilded sculptures of Kung Fu warriors in action.
KARATE_KID_DVS375
SOMEONE halts, staring, and so does she.
KARATE_KID_DVS376
SOMEONE smiles. On a large rain-soaked courtyard stretching before them, 100s of students in identical crimson uniforms stand in tidy ranks.
KARATE_KID_DVS377
At the instructor's command, they perform athletic moves with razor-sharp precision.
KARATE_KID_DVS378
Their faces betray no sign of emotion as they pivot on their feet, kick, and crouch.
KARATE_KID_DVS379
Beaming, SOMEONE rushes forward. His mother lags behind, her face awestruck.
KARATE_KID_DVS380
SOMEONE strolls along the outdoor class' perimeter, watching the students.
KARATE_KID_DVS381
Turning, he licks his lips, hurries to a door with a glass window, and peers through. On an elevated platform set with padded mats, older students in black uniforms follow the commands of their square-jawed instructor.
KARATE_KID_DVS382
SOMEONE opens the door and leans in.
KARATE_KID_DVS388
The students execute crisp bows. Among them, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE and sneers. The bully glares at him as he practices his drills with unsettling precision.
KARATE_KID_DVS389
SOMEONE leaves. He finds his mother adoring a dozen young boys and girls clad in red gis.
KARATE_KID_DVS390
She follows SOMEONE out.
KARATE_KID_DVS391
Brushing past her, SOMEONE sulks off.
KARATE_KID_DVS392
SOMEONE huffily marches in front of his mother, who hurries across the street after him.
KARATE_KID_DVS393
They reach the outer gate of their apartment complex.
KARATE_KID_DVS394
SOMEONE shifts his weight as he stares uneasily at his mother.
KARATE_KID_DVS397
He gives his mother an anguished look, his brow creased.
KARATE_KID_DVS398
Her face softens.
KARATE_KID_DVS399
He rocks back and forth on his feet. His lips wrinkle into a pout. SOMEONE lowers her thoughtful eyes, then meets her son's pained gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS400
SOMEONE wears a wounded smirk.
KARATE_KID_DVS401
His mom steps closer.
KARATE_KID_DVS402
SOMEONE shakes his head, his chin trembling.
KARATE_KID_DVS403
With his bottom lip jutting angrily, SOMEONE trudges past his mother and into the complex.
KARATE_KID_DVS404
SOMEONE lowers her gaze, and sucks in a breath, then waves a hand helplessly.
KARATE_KID_DVS406
As she follows SOMEONE, Mr. SOMEONE plods to his screen door and peers after them.
KARATE_KID_DVS407
Now, outside a sprawling ancient complex, a teacher speaks into a megaphone and leads a group of students.
KARATE_KID_DVS408
Two huge, gleaming, red doors open, each studded from top to bottom with domed gold caps. Students flood through to a vast palatial courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS409
Their teacher clutches a red flag in a raised hand.
KARATE_KID_DVS410
As SOMEONE trudges through the gates, the only student not wearing his uniform, his eyes lock on the golden caps studding the doors.
KARATE_KID_DVS412
At the back of the advancing group, SOMEONE pauses and turns around. She spots SOMEONE staring at the door and heads over.
KARATE_KID_DVS413
With a smile, she stands beside him and joins him in craning her head back to take in the doors' full height.
KARATE_KID_DVS414
SOMEONE glances at her. She places one of his hands on a golden cap.
KARATE_KID_DVS415
SOMEONE meets her gaze, then paws at the cap with both hands.
KARATE_KID_DVS416
SOMEONE grins and SOMEONE rubs more of the caps.
KARATE_KID_DVS417
He faces her and they share a smile.
KARATE_KID_DVS418
Shifting his eyes, he sees SOMEONE and his friends staring at them.
KARATE_KID_DVS419
SOMEONE follows his gaze to the boy, who gives a menacing look.
KARATE_KID_DVS421
SOMEONE averts his eyes.
KARATE_KID_DVS422
He walks away. As SOMEONE stares after him, he glances back and smiles faintly.
KARATE_KID_DVS423
Now, the teacher leads the group along a stone-railed walkway overlooking the courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS425
As SOMEONE walks some distance behind the others, Mrs. Po stops beside him.
KARATE_KID_DVS429
Mrs. Po kindly rests a hand on SOMEONE's back and ushers him toward the group.
KARATE_KID_DVS430
Later, a student-filled bus passes the gate bordering Tiananmen Square and the Forbidden City. A framed image of Mao Zedong hangs above an arched entrance.
KARATE_KID_DVS431
On the bus, SOMEONE sullenly stares ahead.
KARATE_KID_DVS433
Two seats back, SOMEONE glares at him, then switches with a friend to the seat directly behind SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS435
As SOMEONE leans forward menacingly, Mrs. Po glances back from the front of the bus.
KARATE_KID_DVS436
SOMEONE returns to his friends' chat.
KARATE_KID_DVS438
A few seats ahead of SOMEONE, SOMEONE glances back worriedly.
KARATE_KID_DVS440
Now, SOMEONE and his friends exit the bus and join a group of older students. As the uniformed boys head down the sidewalk outside the school gate, SOMEONE watches with fearful eyes.
KARATE_KID_DVS441
The group files off in the same direction that SOMEONE takes when leaving school.
KARATE_KID_DVS442
SOMEONE nervously lags behind on purpose.
KARATE_KID_DVS443
Later, SOMEONE and the other boys walk through an arched gateway onto a narrow street.
KARATE_KID_DVS444
SOMEONE follows at a safe distance.
KARATE_KID_DVS445
The boys stop at a collection of parked bicycles and goof around. SOMEONE hides around the corner and watches.
KARATE_KID_DVS446
He turns as a motorcycle cab trundles closer on a parallel course.
KARATE_KID_DVS447
Using the cab as a moving shield to hide from the boys, SOMEONE walks at a crouch alongside it.
KARATE_KID_DVS448
He nervously peers through a window as he passes the rowdy group undetected.
KARATE_KID_DVS449
He scurries from the cab to a parked car and crouches behind it.
KARATE_KID_DVS450
Across the street, a vendor shoos the unruly boys away and they move on.
KARATE_KID_DVS451
Now, SOMEONE creeps beside the car, his eyes moving from window to window, watching SOMEONE and the boys pass.
KARATE_KID_DVS452
He hurries behind another parked car and sees them halt on a stoop.
KARATE_KID_DVS453
A few sit.
KARATE_KID_DVS455
With a defeated look, SOMEONE squats behind the car and waits.
KARATE_KID_DVS456
His eyes shift to a grimy steam vent on the side of a building.
KARATE_KID_DVS457
Filthy water drips from it into a bucket.
KARATE_KID_DVS458
SOMEONE glances over the car at the boys, then ducks as SOMEONE turns in his direction. On the stoop, SOMEONE demonstrates kung fu moves to his friends.
KARATE_KID_DVS461
Dirty water splashes them. Gaping, SOMEONE glances around and spots SOMEONE racing down the street. He and his friends give chase.
KARATE_KID_DVS464
SOMEONE sprints down the street, passing vendors with their carts. SOMEONE and his friends follow him across a road and into an alleyway. SOMEONE topples a stack of boxes, knocking them in front of his pursuers. Around a corner, men load items into the back of a truck. SOMEONE scales a pile of boxes beside them and climbs onto a roof.
KARATE_KID_DVS465
Behind him, SOMEONE swiftly follows.
KARATE_KID_DVS470
Half the boys acrobatically navigate the roof. The other half track SOMEONE from the alley. As SOMEONE touches back down to the street, SOMEONE's crew course after him through an alley filled with old tires. SOMEONE defensively tips over a stack of bottle-filled crates, but SOMEONE and his friends quickly surmount them. SOMEONE races through a set of double doors in a six-foot-high wall, then pulls them shut.
KARATE_KID_DVS471
He finds a piece of wire hanging from a nearby hook and laces it through two eyelets on the doors, binding them together. As SOMEONE's crew struggle to open the doors, SOMEONE steps back and waits. SOMEONE leaps over the wall.
KARATE_KID_DVS472
SOMEONE bolts and SOMEONE springs after him. Another boy leaps over the wall, then opens the doors for his friends. Following SOMEONE, the group races behind residential buildings, where drying clothes hang on lines. SOMEONE reaches the outer gate of his apartment complex, and races through its wide green doors, into a courtyard by the maintenance shed.
KARATE_KID_DVS473
He halts as he notices the closed inner gate.
KARATE_KID_DVS474
He glances around frantically, then hurries to the maintenance shed's doors and rattles them.
KARATE_KID_DVS475
Turning from the locked shed, he sees SOMEONE and his cronies enter the courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS476
SOMEONE tries to climb over the inner wall, but SOMEONE grabs him and throws him to the ground. SOMEONE hastily stands and backs away, as SOMEONE and two others close in on him. An older boy bolts the outer gate. SOMEONE races toward it, but two boys grab him by the arms. SOMEONE strolls toward him.
KARATE_KID_DVS477
SOMEONE glares tauntingly.
KARATE_KID_DVS478
He sinks a fist into SOMEONE's gut. As SOMEONE doubles over, the two boys holding him straighten him back up. SOMEONE punches him again.
KARATE_KID_DVS479
In slow motion, SOMEONE winces as SOMEONE smiles. The boys straighten SOMEONE again.
KARATE_KID_DVS480
SOMEONE drives his fist into SOMEONE's stomach.
KARATE_KID_DVS481
SOMEONE grits his teeth and squeezes his eyes shut.
KARATE_KID_DVS482
SOMEONE lifts his arms, then releases a powerful frontward kick.
KARATE_KID_DVS483
He knocks SOMEONE to the ground.
KARATE_KID_DVS484
The beaten boy lies on his side, his arm clutching his stomach.
KARATE_KID_DVS485
SOMEONE steps closer and stares down at him. Through SOMEONE's point of view, we see SOMEONE's blurry outline, his chest heaving.
KARATE_KID_DVS486
One of SOMEONE's friends holds him back. He's had enough.
KARATE_KID_DVS487
SOMEONE glares.
KARATE_KID_DVS488
His friends grab him. SOMEONE, stop.
KARATE_KID_DVS489
Glaring, SOMEONE shakes them off.
KARATE_KID_DVS490
SOMEONE faces the fallen American boy who looks up, his face grimacing helplessly.
KARATE_KID_DVS491
SOMEONE lunges with a punch, but a hand grabs his wrist.
KARATE_KID_DVS492
Mr. SOMEONE bends SOMEONE's hand down and in toward the wrist.
KARATE_KID_DVS493
He stares at the boy.
KARATE_KID_DVS495
He shoves SOMEONE back into his group of friends.
KARATE_KID_DVS496
SOMEONE gapes.
KARATE_KID_DVS497
Mr. SOMEONE crouches to SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS498
Two of SOMEONE's older cohorts step forward. He stops them, then advances on Mr. SOMEONE himself.
KARATE_KID_DVS500
He delivers a kick, but Mr. SOMEONE intercepts his ankle.
KARATE_KID_DVS501
The man lifts SOMEONE's leg, then shoves him back.
KARATE_KID_DVS502
As SOMEONE falls, one of the other boys attacks. Mr. SOMEONE deftly blocks every strike. Two boys' fists fly toward Mr. SOMEONE's face, and he bends backwards evading them.
KARATE_KID_DVS503
Mr. SOMEONE waits in a fighting stance, his wrists crossed in an X shape.
KARATE_KID_DVS504
He blocks a strike and holds a tall boy against his body. As a younger boy kicks, Mr. SOMEONE blocks the attack with the tall boy.
KARATE_KID_DVS505
He pulls the young kicker in, uses him as a shield against the tall boy, then flips the younger into a trash barrel. SOMEONE and the others rush SOMEONE, who deflects their blows. He sends two slamming into each other, chest to chest, then bonks another flat with his own chest. He lifts one boy by his britches, and swings him in a circle, letting his sneakered feet whack another boy flat.
KARATE_KID_DVS506
In a move like ballroom dancing, SOMEONE spins the controlled boy out, and the kid's loose-swinging arm slaps another boy in the face. Now, SOMEONE grips the boy's wrists in one hand, and draws back his fist to punch. The boy cringes.
KARATE_KID_DVS507
As SOMEONE lowers his fist, an older boy attacks. Mr. SOMEONE absorbs, then redirects the strike into a boy's face. Now, as SOMEONE fends off several boys simultaneously, SOMEONE lifts his head and watches the fight.
KARATE_KID_DVS508
Mr. SOMEONE grabs the arms of a boy in a warm-up jacket. He tangles a sleeve around the arm of another boy, and wraps the other sleeve around the jacket-wearer's neck.
KARATE_KID_DVS509
He catches a third boy's leg in the sleeve, then guides his foot into SOMEONE's chest. He pushes the tangled boys to the ground. As he turns back to SOMEONE, a small boy steps toward him.
KARATE_KID_DVS510
Mr. SOMEONE gives him a look and the boy backs away. His chest heaves as he turns from the group.
KARATE_KID_DVS511
He crouches and gently grabs SOMEONE's arm.
KARATE_KID_DVS512
Later, Mr. SOMEONE holds a cotton ball between chopsticks, and lights it on fire.
KARATE_KID_DVS513
Shirtless, SOMEONE lies on a wicker couch and watches as Mr. SOMEONE holds a glass cup over the flaming cotton ball.
KARATE_KID_DVS515
Mr. SOMEONE sets the heated cup on SOMEONE's side.
KARATE_KID_DVS516
Grabbing another, he briefly holds the flame inside it, then places it on SOMEONE's skin, next to the first bulb-shaped cup.
KARATE_KID_DVS517
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE drops the flaming cotton ball into a bowl, and dips a hand in, gathering a dancing blue flame in his palm.
KARATE_KID_DVS518
He rubs his hands together, then moves them over SOMEONE's chest.
KARATE_KID_DVS519
Flames flicker between his palms and SOMEONE's skin.
KARATE_KID_DVS520
Mr. SOMEONE repeats the process, and SOMEONE winces as the man presses against him.
KARATE_KID_DVS521
The flames die out.
KARATE_KID_DVS522
Mr. SOMEONE extinguishes his bowl of flames and pulls the heated cups from SOMEONE's side.
KARATE_KID_DVS523
He turns away.
KARATE_KID_DVS524
SOMEONE touches his injured side.
KARATE_KID_DVS528
He packs up his fire cupping equipment.
KARATE_KID_DVS531
Mr. SOMEONE glances at him.
KARATE_KID_DVS532
Sitting on the couch, SOMEONE leans forward.
KARATE_KID_DVS533
He puts on his shirt.
KARATE_KID_DVS535
Mr. SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a look.
KARATE_KID_DVS536
SOMEONE lifts his chin.
KARATE_KID_DVS538
Mr. SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a glass of water. The boy downs it, then hands back the empty glass.
KARATE_KID_DVS542
Mr. SOMEONE looks at him. SOMEONE shifts his eyes.
KARATE_KID_DVS544
SOMEONE watches as Mr. SOMEONE continues to clean his dingy workroom.
KARATE_KID_DVS545
He steps toward him.
KARATE_KID_DVS546
He ushers SOMEONE to the door.
KARATE_KID_DVS547
Mr. SOMEONE folds a blanket on the wicker couch. SOMEONE stares disappointedly as the man ignores him.
KARATE_KID_DVS548
He nods and reaches for the door.
KARATE_KID_DVS549
Mr. SOMEONE looks up as SOMEONE heads out. The seasoned martial artist thoughtfully watches him go.
KARATE_KID_DVS550
Shifting his sad eyes, Mr. SOMEONE presses his lips together, then returns his gaze to the door.
KARATE_KID_DVS551
Now, Mr. SOMEONE and SOMEONE pass through the gates to the kung fu school, where the throngs of red-clad students hang out.
KARATE_KID_DVS552
Inside the studio, two students spar while the others kneel around the edges of the platform. Their instructor sits on a bench and watches. Mr. SOMEONE scans his surroundings as he and SOMEONE enter.
KARATE_KID_DVS553
One of the sparring boys throws his opponent to the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS554
Grabbing him by his shirt, the aggressor lifts the boy, then drops on his back, and flings him over his head.
KARATE_KID_DVS555
The boy stands and they face off.
KARATE_KID_DVS556
As one boy attacks, the other blocks him, then grabs his arm, and flips him to the floor.
KARATE_KID_DVS557
He crouches over his fallen opponent, draws back his fist, and hesitates.
KARATE_KID_DVS560
The boy brutally punches his opponent in the face.
KARATE_KID_DVS562
Looking on, Mr. SOMEONE swallows uneasily.
KARATE_KID_DVS564
The winning student approaches his instructor, his eyes averted.
KARATE_KID_DVS565
The square-jawed man rises from his bench and faces the boy, who shifts his eyes nervously.
KARATE_KID_DVS566
The instructor ceremoniously raises his open hand and smacks the boy's cheek.
KARATE_KID_DVS567
The boy stumbles.
KARATE_KID_DVS569
The students stand at attention, their arms behind their backs, and their eyes straight ahead.
KARATE_KID_DVS570
We do not stop when our enemy is down. No mercy.
KARATE_KID_DVS571
The instructor strolls in front of his students.
KARATE_KID_DVS572
No mercy in the studio. No mercy in competition.
KARATE_KID_DVS573
No mercy in life.
KARATE_KID_DVS574
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE and Mr. SOMEONE watching the class.
KARATE_KID_DVS575
He stares at them as his instructor continues.
KARATE_KID_DVS576
Our enemies deserve pain.
KARATE_KID_DVS577
The instructor faces SOMEONE, who returns his attention to his teacher.
KARATE_KID_DVS579
SOMEONE points at Mr. SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS581
With a hard expression, the instructor turns to the visitors.
KARATE_KID_DVS582
As they approach, SOMEONE's cohorts turn to look at them.
KARATE_KID_DVS583
Mr. SOMEONE addresses the instructor.
KARATE_KID_DVS584
The instructor stares down at them.
KARATE_KID_DVS586
Mr. SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS591
In unison, his students sit at the platform's perimeter.
KARATE_KID_DVS592
SOMEONE strides to the center.
KARATE_KID_DVS594
Eyeing them, SOMEONE limbers up his strained wrist.
KARATE_KID_DVS596
Mr. SOMEONE and SOMEONE head for the door.
KARATE_KID_DVS597
The instructor leaps off the platform and catches up to them.
KARATE_KID_DVS600
He holds his arm across Mr. SOMEONE's chest.
KARATE_KID_DVS603
As the instructor grabs him by the wrist, Mr. SOMEONE tensely grips SOMEONE's arm.
KARATE_KID_DVS604
Master SOMEONE stares firmly.
KARATE_KID_DVS606
Mr. SOMEONE shifts his eyes.
KARATE_KID_DVS607
The boy SOMEONE fight there.
KARATE_KID_DVS609
wMaster SOMEONE follows his gaze to a poster here a Chinese character sits in the center of a gold circle.
KARATE_KID_DVS612
Master SOMEONE grins.
KARATE_KID_DVS614
He releases Mr. SOMEONE's wrist, and Mr. SOMEONE releases SOMEONE's.
KARATE_KID_DVS616
Mr. SOMEONE holds Master SOMEONE's gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS618
Master SOMEONE cocks his head.
KARATE_KID_DVS620
He turns to his students.
KARATE_KID_DVS623
The students look at their instructor.
KARATE_KID_DVS624
Mr. SOMEONE starts for the door.
KARATE_KID_DVS625
He stops.
KARATE_KID_DVS626
Master SOMEONE glares at his back.
KARATE_KID_DVS629
SOMEONE stares after Mr. SOMEONE, then hurries to catch up.
KARATE_KID_DVS630
Outside, a formation of red-clad students practices in the grassy courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS631
SOMEONE follows Mr. SOMEONE outside.
KARATE_KID_DVS634
SOMEONE gives an uneasy look.
KARATE_KID_DVS637
SOMEONE stops walking and stares.
KARATE_KID_DVS638
His jaw drops.
KARATE_KID_DVS639
He catches up to Mr. SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS643
They stop just outside the courtyard's gate.
KARATE_KID_DVS645
He briefly locks eyes with SOMEONE, then heads off.
KARATE_KID_DVS646
SOMEONE smiles.
KARATE_KID_DVS647
Morning. SOMEONE carries a skateboard under one arm, and races down the stairs in his apartment building. He passes his mother as she collects their mail in the lobby.
KARATE_KID_DVS654
SOMEONE smiles as she watches her son leave.
KARATE_KID_DVS655
Now, a man rides a bicycle down the street, the back of his bike piled high with plastic containers. On his skateboard, SOMEONE holds on to the container bouquet and catches a ride.
KARATE_KID_DVS656
Down the road, he grabs the back of a bicycle-driven cart.
KARATE_KID_DVS657
He lets go as he reaches a gate into a neighborhood.
KARATE_KID_DVS658
Checking a slip of paper, he heads through the gate's double doors and walks down a winding alley cluttered with boxes and junk. An aerial view shows Mr. SOMEONE standing at a utility pole in a courtyard behind his house.
KARATE_KID_DVS659
SOMEONE strides through SOMEONE's home, toting his skateboard.
KARATE_KID_DVS660
Dirty dishes clutter the cramped kitchen.
KARATE_KID_DVS661
SOMEONE passes into a living room where soft light filters through ornate geometric screens covering the windows.
KARATE_KID_DVS662
Scanning the space, the boy finds an antique curio cabinet and several Chinese paintings hanging on a wall.
KARATE_KID_DVS663
A run-down car, missing its front SOMEONE, crowds the center of the room.
KARATE_KID_DVS664
SOMEONE sidles past.
KARATE_KID_DVS666
Sneering, he hurries into the rear courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS667
SOMEONE takes off his jacket and drops it in the doorway.
KARATE_KID_DVS668
He hops around.
KARATE_KID_DVS669
He cartwheels.
KARATE_KID_DVS671
SOMEONE stares, his brow furrowed.
KARATE_KID_DVS672
SOMEONE plants SOMEONE's hand on his shoulder, then seizes it, and twists.
KARATE_KID_DVS673
SOMEONE dances from side to side, knocking over a ceramic vase. It shatters on the garden's tiled ground.
KARATE_KID_DVS675
SOMEONE shoves a peg into the freshly drilled hole in the utility pole.
KARATE_KID_DVS676
SOMEONE hangs his jacket on the peg.
KARATE_KID_DVS678
SOMEONE snatches his jacket back off the bar and faces SOMEONE skeptically.
KARATE_KID_DVS680
The irritated boy swings the jacket behind his back and works his arms into the sleeves.
KARATE_KID_DVS683
Scowling, SOMEONE obediently pulls the jacket off his shoulders and arms.
KARATE_KID_DVS685
Arching his brow indulgently, he hangs the jacket on the makeshift coat rack.
KARATE_KID_DVS688
SOMEONE drops it on to the tile.
KARATE_KID_DVS689
The boy lazily bends forward and grabs the jacket.
KARATE_KID_DVS690
He hangs it on the peg.
KARATE_KID_DVS691
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE, then obeys.
KARATE_KID_DVS693
He swings it over his shoulders.
KARATE_KID_DVS695
He irritably obeys.
KARATE_KID_DVS697
He flings it down.
KARATE_KID_DVS698
He retrieves it.
KARATE_KID_DVS699
SOMEONE drapes the jacket over the peg.
KARATE_KID_DVS700
He takes it back off.
KARATE_KID_DVS701
He swings it around his body.
KARATE_KID_DVS702
Our view floats above them.
KARATE_KID_DVS703
SOMEONE obeys each repeated command.
KARATE_KID_DVS704
Later, SOMEONE sits on his patio, fanning himself.
KARATE_KID_DVS705
He watches coolly as SOMEONE hangs his jacket on the peg, then takes it back off.
KARATE_KID_DVS708
SOMEONE waves him on.
KARATE_KID_DVS709
Wincing, SOMEONE wearily whirls the jacket around his shoulders, pauses,
KARATE_KID_DVS710
then hangs it off the utility pole.
KARATE_KID_DVS711
Later, he returns home.
KARATE_KID_DVS712
He sets down his skateboard.
KARATE_KID_DVS714
He hangs up his jacket.
KARATE_KID_DVS715
As he mopes into his room, SOMEONE stares at the hanging jacket and shifts her wide-eyed gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS716
Now, in the courtyard, SOMEONE holds an umbrella over SOMEONE as the boy takes off his jacket,
KARATE_KID_DVS717
drops it on the ground, picks it up, and hangs it.
KARATE_KID_DVS718
He glances at his mentor's blank face, then repeats the cycle.
KARATE_KID_DVS719
Now, on the school's athletic field, dozens of uniformed students stand in neat ranks. An instructor leads them in simple calisthenics.
KARATE_KID_DVS720
SOMEONE works his way up beside SOMEONE and adjusts his red kerchief.
KARATE_KID_DVS721
The students head off the field.
KARATE_KID_DVS723
They stroll together.
KARATE_KID_DVS725
SOMEONE greets a couple of passing friends, then beams at SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS726
SOMEONE grins and heads off.
KARATE_KID_DVS727
Now wearing casual clothes, the boy makes his way down the winding alley, and steps into SOMEONE's house.
KARATE_KID_DVS728
Halting, he turns back and sets down his skateboard.
KARATE_KID_DVS729
He quickly takes off his jacket and hides it beneath a giant gourd in a pile of items just outside the door.
KARATE_KID_DVS730
In the living room, SOMEONE rubs a sander over the side of his car.
KARATE_KID_DVS732
His teacher's gaze remains locked on the vehicle as SOMEONE strides by.
KARATE_KID_DVS734
SOMEONE whirls around sheepishly.
KARATE_KID_DVS737
SOMEONE stares at the kung fu master, then trudges back through the house.
KARATE_KID_DVS739
Rain drizzles down on SOMEONE's courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS740
A metal stand holds an umbrella above SOMEONE's head as the boy mechanically takes off his jacket,
KARATE_KID_DVS741
drops it on the ground, and hangs it up.
KARATE_KID_DVS742
In his brightly lit living room, SOMEONE works on his car. He glances at the boy through the open doors, then studies his robotic movements over his shoulder.
KARATE_KID_DVS743
SOMEONE glumly hangs up his jacket.
KARATE_KID_DVS745
SOMEONE sets down his things and heads outside.
KARATE_KID_DVS747
SOMEONE swings his jacket around his shoulders, pauses, takes it off, and drapes it on the peg.
KARATE_KID_DVS749
SOMEONE re-hangs it with a sarcastic smile.
KARATE_KID_DVS750
The boy takes the jacket off the peg.
KARATE_KID_DVS751
SOMEONE mugs for him.
KARATE_KID_DVS754
SOMEONE jerks his head at the utility pole
KARATE_KID_DVS755
SOMEONE hangs his jacket with a sarcastic sneer.
KARATE_KID_DVS756
He drops it.
KARATE_KID_DVS757
SOMEONE glances at the car.
KARATE_KID_DVS760
She notices his jacket lying on the tiled courtyard and frowns.
KARATE_KID_DVS762
SOMEONE musters a smile for SOMEONE and saunters away.
KARATE_KID_DVS763
The kung fu master glances at SOMEONE, wide-eyed. Now at the Shi Shi Festival, delicate lanterns shaped like birds and flowers hang from trees above the throngs of guests.
KARATE_KID_DVS764
They weave through the crowd and arrive at a pond.
KARATE_KID_DVS765
Stylized cloud-like graphics adorn a moon bridge. Colorful figures stand atop its arch.
KARATE_KID_DVS769
SOMEONE runs off.
KARATE_KID_DVS774
SOMEONE gazes after SOMEONE suspiciously.
KARATE_KID_DVS775
The boy trots past twinkling lights and hurries up to a terrace.
KARATE_KID_DVS776
He halts and eyes its neon sign, then heads inside.
KARATE_KID_DVS777
A crowd of adults and children exit the terrace courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS778
Benches line the space, facing a performance screen.
KARATE_KID_DVS779
SOMEONE walks along the side of the courtyard, scanning the crowd.
KARATE_KID_DVS780
A broad grin spreads on his lips as he spots SOMEONE across the room.
KARATE_KID_DVS781
She beams back at him and jerks her head toward the screen.
KARATE_KID_DVS782
They each head past it and arrive backstage, where performers ready delicate paper puppets.
KARATE_KID_DVS783
The children lock gazes from the wings, then meet behind the screen.
KARATE_KID_DVS784
A spotlight shines on the screen from a lantern in a projection room.
KARATE_KID_DVS785
SOMEONE holds a CD.
KARATE_KID_DVS786
He hands her some sheet music and the CD. The cover shows a photo of SOMEONE on a hand-drawn background that reads, "Play along. Hope you enjoy."
KARATE_KID_DVS787
SOMEONE hugs the items.
KARATE_KID_DVS788
She waves for him to follow her and steps into the storage room.
KARATE_KID_DVS789
As she takes a seat on a bench beside the lantern, she points SOMEONE to a bench opposite.
KARATE_KID_DVS790
The beam shines between them.
KARATE_KID_DVS791
SOMEONE smiles.
KARATE_KID_DVS798
Now in the terrace courtyard, they sit on a bench. A stunned SOMEONE arches her brow. Curtains rise, revealing the performance screen and several puppets glowing from behind.
KARATE_KID_DVS804
An intricately decorated puppet gestures angrily.
KARATE_KID_DVS815
Two puppets mount a bridge formed by bird puppets.
KARATE_KID_DVS819
As SOMEONE stares at his friend tenderly, SOMEONE gives a shy smile and fidgets.
KARATE_KID_DVS820
She glances at the screen, then locks eyes with him.
KARATE_KID_DVS824
She quizzically knits her brow.
KARATE_KID_DVS826
He hooks his pinky around hers.
KARATE_KID_DVS827
Grinning, SOMEONE glances down at their linked hands and bashfully tugs her pinky away.
KARATE_KID_DVS828
The performance screen shows puppets of the Goddess and her lover holding hands.
KARATE_KID_DVS830
As the two children watch, the puppets intertwine, seeming to cradle each other's heads.
KARATE_KID_DVS831
Their faces press together as if sharing a kiss.
KARATE_KID_DVS832
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, who smiles.
KARATE_KID_DVS834
The two young sweethearts lean toward each other into the beam of light from the lantern.
KARATE_KID_DVS836
The spotlight silhouettes them as they move closer and touch foreheads, then press their lips together in a gentle steady kiss.
KARATE_KID_DVS837
In the audience-packed house, SOMEONE's smile vanishes. She stares at the screen, slack-jawed, then disbelievingly cocks her head.
KARATE_KID_DVS838
The spotlight projects the children's shadows onto the screen as they kiss.
KARATE_KID_DVS839
A puppeteer lights a sparkler behind the kissing puppets, brightening their image within the shadow of the kissing youngsters.
KARATE_KID_DVS840
SOMEONE frowns and SOMEONE shifts uncomfortably.
KARATE_KID_DVS842
Now, a second sparkler dramatizing the puppets' kiss blurs to become sparks thrown by a welding torch in SOMEONE's grip.
KARATE_KID_DVS843
As he works on the car in his living room, SOMEONE strides in.
KARATE_KID_DVS846
SOMEONE retreats to the door and stands facing the kung fu master. His jacket hangs tied around his waist.
KARATE_KID_DVS847
SOMEONE ambles back into the room.
KARATE_KID_DVS850
He unties his jacket.
KARATE_KID_DVS851
Later, in the courtyard outside, dozens of bells dangle from leafy tree branches on strings.
KARATE_KID_DVS852
SOMEONE stands facing the utility pole, hanging his jacket on the peg.
KARATE_KID_DVS853
He pulls the garment down, flings it to the ground, then picks it up and whirls it around his shoulders.
KARATE_KID_DVS854
Whipping it off, he flings it back onto the peg with a grouchy sarcastic smile.
KARATE_KID_DVS856
As he continues the routine, SOMEONE strolls outside with a mug.
KARATE_KID_DVS857
He holds it under a spigot and pumps a handle.
KARATE_KID_DVS858
His mug filled, SOMEONE stands watching SOMEONE as he spins his jacket around his shoulders once again.
KARATE_KID_DVS859
The boy drops the jacket, then flings it onto the peg.
KARATE_KID_DVS860
SOMEONE shuffles off and takes a seat on a shaded stoop.
KARATE_KID_DVS861
SOMEONE grabs his jacket and storms off.
KARATE_KID_DVS862
He irritably faces his instructor.
KARATE_KID_DVS864
SOMEONE stands and strides into the center of the courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS866
He points insistently.
KARATE_KID_DVS867
SOMEONE swaggers toward him, his jacket draped over his shoulder. The boy glares up at SOMEONE as the older man nods.
KARATE_KID_DVS870
SOMEONE sneers and yanks his jacket off his shoulder, then whirls it toward his back.
KARATE_KID_DVS871
SOMEONE seizes it and snatches it out of his hands.
KARATE_KID_DVS872
The boy frowns as SOMEONE tosses it aside.
KARATE_KID_DVS874
SOMEONE offers a befuddled blink, then mimes putting the jacket on.
KARATE_KID_DVS875
SOMEONE grabs his arm at the wrist and elbow.
KARATE_KID_DVS876
He smacks SOMEONE's fist.
KARATE_KID_DVS877
He grabs SOMEONE's other arm.
KARATE_KID_DVS878
He pushes on SOMEONE's forearm.
KARATE_KID_DVS879
SOMEONE jerks his other arm forward. SOMEONE seizes it.
KARATE_KID_DVS882
SOMEONE lifts his other arm up. SOMEONE pushes on his crooked arm as SOMEONE holds the block.
KARATE_KID_DVS883
SOMEONE holds both SOMEONE's arms up. SOMEONE obeys.
KARATE_KID_DVS884
SOMEONE bends, ducking a kick from SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS887
SOMEONE dodges SOMEONE's kick again.
KARATE_KID_DVS888
SOMEONE hurls SOMEONE's jacket down in front of him.
KARATE_KID_DVS890
SOMEONE bends to grab it, but SOMEONE kicks his hands away. He grabs SOMEONE's arms and smacks his palms.
KARATE_KID_DVS891
He jerks SOMEONE's arms up.
KARATE_KID_DVS892
SOMEONE jerks his arms upward, hitting SOMEONE's palms.
KARATE_KID_DVS893
SOMEONE poses with his arms out.
KARATE_KID_DVS894
He smacks palms with SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS895
SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS897
He repeatedly jerks his arms up and shoves his teacher back.
KARATE_KID_DVS898
SOMEONE snarls his teeth.
KARATE_KID_DVS899
SOMEONE pushes him away.
KARATE_KID_DVS900
SOMEONE jabs and kicks at SOMEONE, but the boy instinctively blocks and evades with the ingrained jacket moves. SOMEONE swallows and gapes at his hands. SOMEONE lunges forward in a second melee. SOMEONE blocks, deflects, and swats his teacher's attacks. SOMEONE seizes the stunned boy by the shoulders.
KARATE_KID_DVS909
Sunlight flares around SOMEONE's intense gaze. He releases the boy and shuffles off.
KARATE_KID_DVS910
SOMEONE watches, slack-jawed, as the kung fu master hobbles into his living room.
KARATE_KID_DVS911
The student retrieves his jacket and whirls it around his shoulders.
KARATE_KID_DVS912
He pauses, then spins it off and whips it around his body again.
KARATE_KID_DVS913
He continues sweeping the jacket around his body, practicing as he heads out of the courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS914
Now, we soar over an emerald-hued mountain range with conical peaks, drifting over a ridge, we spy a train winding its way alongside a tranquil muddy river. On a crowded passenger car, SOMEONE gazes out a window at the exotic landscape.
KARATE_KID_DVS915
Mr. SOMEONE dozes beside him.
KARATE_KID_DVS917
SOMEONE shifts his puzzled gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS918
Mr. SOMEONE faces him wearily.
KARATE_KID_DVS922
Leaning across SOMEONE, SOMEONE draws a character on the dusty window.
KARATE_KID_DVS926
As he settles back into his seat, his student gazes solemnly at the character for chi.
KARATE_KID_DVS927
Mr. SOMEONE gives him a wry look.
KARATE_KID_DVS928
Now on the station platform, Mr. SOMEONE leads SOMEONE off the train and hails a motorcycle taxi. Later, as it travels along a winding road overlooking the mountains, SOMEONE and his student ride on the rear-facing back seat.
KARATE_KID_DVS929
The teacher smiles at the boy, who happily takes in the stunning terrain. The taxi crosses a lofty stone bridge spanning the tranquil river.
KARATE_KID_DVS930
Later, they arrive at a stairway leading down to a footbridge. Beyond it, a path winds up into the mountains.
KARATE_KID_DVS933
They descend the stone steps.
KARATE_KID_DVS938
SOMEONE eyes a tall distant peak haloed by the sun.
KARATE_KID_DVS939
Now, monks in snowy robes and canary-yellow scarves sit in lotus position, along the rim of a stone dam.
KARATE_KID_DVS940
Water streams past them, down the glossy rocks.
KARATE_KID_DVS941
Now, a jagged peak looms high above mountains patched with snow.
KARATE_KID_DVS942
Our view tilts down to a dizzyingly long stairway beneath us.
KARATE_KID_DVS943
Mr. SOMEONE marches up the narrow steps, followed by his student.
KARATE_KID_DVS944
One section of the stairs rests on a fin of rock
KARATE_KID_DVS945
barely wider than the stairway itself.
KARATE_KID_DVS946
They ascend the steep run.
KARATE_KID_DVS948
Later, at another section, SOMEONE stops, leaning against a stone banister.
KARATE_KID_DVS951
Mr. SOMEONE continues up without breaking his stride. Now, we drift over an elaborate mountaintop monastery.
KARATE_KID_DVS952
Rust-red walls support ancient rib-tiled roofs.
KARATE_KID_DVS953
Mr. SOMEONE leads his pupil up onto a small balcony, then along a shadowy corridor.
KARATE_KID_DVS955
It leads them into a stone courtyard where dozens of male and female monks, in snowy tunics, perform tai chi.
KARATE_KID_DVS956
With fluid grace, they execute the meditative movements in perfect unison.
KARATE_KID_DVS957
On a balcony, a man in a navy tunic rapidly twirls a fighting staff around his lithe frame. As Mr. SOMEONE leads SOMEONE past, the monk crouches on one foot,
KARATE_KID_DVS958
balancing on his staff, as he extends his other leg, parallel to the ground.
KARATE_KID_DVS960
Where two railings make a corner, a monk does a split from one to the other, and snaps open a large fan.
KARATE_KID_DVS961
SOMEONE swallows, staring at the magnificent feat.
KARATE_KID_DVS962
Venturing onward, the boy spies a third monk sitting in the lotus pose.
KARATE_KID_DVS964
From a pair of twin platforms, he pushes himself up by his knuckles, and balances.
KARATE_KID_DVS965
Now, an enclosed walkway stands built into a high cliff face. Mr. SOMEONE leads SOMEONE inside, glancing out the windows as he marches along.
KARATE_KID_DVS966
Following his gaze, the boy halts in his tracks.
KARATE_KID_DVS967
Outside, a woman in a white tunic faces the drop-off.
KARATE_KID_DVS968
She crouches, revealing a cobra poised before her, its hood fanned out.
KARATE_KID_DVS969
Slack-jawed, the boy runs to another window. The female ascetic stands on an ornamental-stone jut over the 1,000-foot drop. As she straightens, the reptile rises to match her.
KARATE_KID_DVS970
Balancing on one foot, the woman sweeps an arm in an arc behind her head, and holds the other gently crooked before her.
KARATE_KID_DVS971
The disciple tucks her extended leg in briefly, and folds her arms across her torso, then lifts her knee up to her chest, and extends her arms in a slanted T, pointing down at the serpent.
KARATE_KID_DVS972
Her eyes wide, the woman slowly tilts her head, side to side,
KARATE_KID_DVS973
her sharp-featured gaze fixed on the snake.
KARATE_KID_DVS974
The cobra mirrors her, weaving left and right.
KARATE_KID_DVS975
As SOMEONE stares at the spectacle, his head tips side to side as well.
KARATE_KID_DVS976
Further down the corridor, Mr. SOMEONE stops.
KARATE_KID_DVS978
Doubling back, he steps into the light as he finds his pupil entranced by the woman's practice.
KARATE_KID_DVS979
He allows a faint smile and shifts his gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS981
The boy turns, wide-eyed. Mr. SOMEONE beckons with a wave of his hand.
KARATE_KID_DVS982
SOMEONE gives one last look to the exquisite spectacle, then follows his teacher to a doorway.
KARATE_KID_DVS983
SOMEONE removes his hat.
KARATE_KID_DVS984
A basin stands paved with the Yin-Yang of black and white marble.
KARATE_KID_DVS985
The basin stands upon a compass-like framework of white stone that's submerged in a shallow pool.
KARATE_KID_DVS991
Mr. SOMEONE gazes reverently upon the well, then faces SOMEONE, and nods toward the water.
KARATE_KID_DVS992
The boy solemnly steps up on one of the white-stone beams and approaches the basin.
KARATE_KID_DVS993
The boy lays his hands on the rim. He plunges his face into the water. Mr. SOMEONE smiles as his pupil drinks eagerly.
KARATE_KID_DVS994
SOMEONE lifts his dripping face.
KARATE_KID_DVS996
He watches his teacher roaming the chamber wistfully.
KARATE_KID_DVS997
He imitates the woman.
KARATE_KID_DVS1001
Mr. SOMEONE steps up on the latticework and joins his pupil at the basin.
KARATE_KID_DVS1002
He regards SOMEONE with a thoughtful nod, then points at the water.
KARATE_KID_DVS1004
SOMEONE ripples the water with his finger.
KARATE_KID_DVS1009
He points to SOMEONE's head and heart.
KARATE_KID_DVS1013
Now on a lakeside dock, SOMEONE attaches bamboo poles to SOMEONE's wrists by loops at their ends.
KARATE_KID_DVS1015
Mr. SOMEONE steps back, gripping a bamboo pole in each hand.
KARATE_KID_DVS1016
He moves SOMEONE's hand to his head.
KARATE_KID_DVS1019
He puppets the boy.
KARATE_KID_DVS1023
SOMEONE tips him over the dock's edge and holds him inches from the water.
KARATE_KID_DVS1026
Now, a train's headlights cut through the night air. In a passenger car, SOMEONE sleeps with his cheek on Mr. SOMEONE's shoulder.
KARATE_KID_DVS1027
As he stirs, his head flops down to his teacher's lap.
KARATE_KID_DVS1028
The man stares at the boy, then slowly rests a hand on his back.
KARATE_KID_DVS1030
He gives SOMEONE a gentle pat, then looks away, and takes a deep breath.
KARATE_KID_DVS1033
Now, Mr. SOMEONE puts SOMEONE to bed, as SOMEONE looks on.
KARATE_KID_DVS1034
The mother smiles at the man, then goes to her sleeping son.She kisses SOMEONE's forehead and caresses his cheek.
KARATE_KID_DVS1035
SOMEONE returns to the bedroom doorway, where Mr. SOMEONE looks on with a fond smile. The quickly closing door thins the shaft of light cast on the boy until it's gone.
KARATE_KID_DVS1037
Now, a child's drawing shows a coiled cobra with a fanned hood. A dotted line connects his eyes to the eyes of the slender woman striking a kung fu pose.
KARATE_KID_DVS1040
Sitting at a sunlit desk, SOMEONE hunches over a sketchbook and shades in the woman's hair. Now, he stares intensely at his mother, as they lunch in a marketplace.
KARATE_KID_DVS1043
SOMEONE frowns at her glowering son, then glances over her shoulder.
KARATE_KID_DVS1046
Later, he and SOMEONE bow, each signing a fist-to-palm gesture.
KARATE_KID_DVS1047
Now, SOMEONE limbers SOMEONE up, bending him over his knee, then pushing him into a full split. Next, SOMEONE works the water pump with precise arm movements. SOMEONE has a go, but struggles. Now, trying elevated push-ups, SOMEONE collapses. SOMEONE hangs a bell high above SOMEONE's head. The boy kicks at it unsuccessfully. On a roof, a hanging bed sheet separates them.
KARATE_KID_DVS1048
A boxing glove smacks him. The glove's attached to a pole.
KARATE_KID_DVS1050
SOMEONE peeks under the sheet.
KARATE_KID_DVS1051
The glove smacks him again.
KARATE_KID_DVS1052
He jabs SOMEONE's stomach.
KARATE_KID_DVS1053
In his courtyard, SOMEONE lobs tennis balls at SOMEONE. On the roof, he jabs again.
KARATE_KID_DVS1054
He gives another smack.
KARATE_KID_DVS1055
He jabs SOMEONE again, then steps around the sheet and faces him.
KARATE_KID_DVS1059
Now, SOMEONE holds a bamboo staff across his shoulders as he executes moves under SOMEONE's command.
KARATE_KID_DVS1060
In the rain, the teacher demonstrates a squatting leg sweep. In clear weather, he holds SOMEONE's ankles as the boy does handstand push-ups. The boy kicks at the bell with improved grace, but still misses. In his room, he poses at a mirror, and falls over.
KARATE_KID_DVS1062
Nighttime. In his living room, Mr. SOMEONE waxes the refinished car.
KARATE_KID_DVS1064
Pausing, Mr. SOMEONE faces the boy.
KARATE_KID_DVS1068
As SOMEONE leaves, Mr. SOMEONE slows his gaze pensive.
KARATE_KID_DVS1069
Now at school, the American boy turns down the brief corridor. At the other end, he spots SOMEONE standing outside the auditorium,
KARATE_KID_DVS1070
staring at a posting on the door. He joins her.
KARATE_KID_DVS1072
She leaves.
KARATE_KID_DVS1074
SOMEONE looks past her shoulder and freezes.
KARATE_KID_DVS1075
SOMEONE takes her by the wrist.
KARATE_KID_DVS1076
They run from the school, hand in hand. SOMEONE freezes, spotting a guard at the gate.
KARATE_KID_DVS1077
He leads SOMEONE around a pillar. He peeks around, signals for SOMEONE to be quiet, then leads her at a sprint down the sidewalk.
KARATE_KID_DVS1078
Now, they arrive at a vendor selling fried insects on sticks. A metal bowl writhes with live bugs and scorpions. SOMEONE selects a stick of fried scorpions, and thrusts it playfully in SOMEONE's face. She smirks as he recoils.
KARATE_KID_DVS1081
She chases him with it. From overhead, we watch numerous umbrellas part to make way for them. Now, they run among jetting-fountain plumes outside the Olympic Stadium. SOMEONE clutches SOMEONE's violin case as she chases him. Later, they gaze at the still water.
KARATE_KID_DVS1082
He disrupts it with his hand.
KARATE_KID_DVS1083
SOMEONE faces the water and blinks.
KARATE_KID_DVS1084
Now, the two hurry down a crowded escalator. In an arcade, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE to a digital dance game, faces its touch screen, and makes a selection from a list.
KARATE_KID_DVS1085
She leaves SOMEONE on the dancer's platform, claps her hands, and nods encouragingly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1086
Facing her, he performs a series of dexterous steps.
KARATE_KID_DVS1087
As he quivers his body side to side, he twirls his arms in front of his chest, then waggles his legs, making them look like rubber.
KARATE_KID_DVS1088
SOMEONE reluctantly steps up onto the platform.
KARATE_KID_DVS1089
She nervously faces the screen, putting her back to SOMEONE. She stands tensely, her shoulders hunched and her fists clenched at her sides. The girl looks over her shoulder, giving SOMEONE an anxious pleading look.
KARATE_KID_DVS1090
He lifts his brow, smiles, and nods. Words on the screen read, Get ready. SOMEONE nods to herself. She flings her hands out to the side, turns, and flips her hair. She struts toward SOMEONE, gives a shimmy, then pops her bent arms. Under his stunned gaze, she hops her feet out and in, and extends her arms to match. She gracefully shimmies her hips, steps away, then turns and points to SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1091
He glances away briefly, his eyes wide. SOMEONE swirls an arm around her head, as she swivels her hips, then tosses her head side to side. Gliding across the platform, she sweeps a hand beneath her face. SOMEONE stares.
KARATE_KID_DVS1094
With a modest sigh, she steps down off the platform.
KARATE_KID_DVS1095
Later, they gaze out from a balcony.
KARATE_KID_DVS1096
SOMEONE digs out her cell phone. Answering it, she turns away.
KARATE_KID_DVS1097
She hurriedly ends the call.
KARATE_KID_DVS1101
Grabbing her violin case, she rushes off. Now, she runs along a sidewalk, with SOMEONE trailing close behind. Reaching a brick pillar, he stops at the sight of a stern man waiting by a black luxury sedan.
KARATE_KID_DVS1102
As SOMEONE dashes to the car, he gets behind the wheel. A lovely woman rides up front, wearing a worried gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS1103
SOMEONE ducks behind the pillar as he watches the car leave.
KARATE_KID_DVS1104
Shifting his worried gaze, SOMEONE breaks into a run, and sprints down a tree-lined path.
KARATE_KID_DVS1105
In the school auditorium, a pre-teen boy plays the piano, his fingers moving nimbly over the keys. At the front of the house, a panel of judges watches him intently.
KARATE_KID_DVS1106
In the back, SOMEONE's instructor shifts anxiously on his feet. On a city street, SOMEONE sprints around pedestrians.
KARATE_KID_DVS1109
Back in the auditorium, the house lights blink on, and the judges make notes. On stage, members of a small orchestra tune up.
KARATE_KID_DVS1110
The judges turn as SOMEONE and her mother run in.
KARATE_KID_DVS1111
Her instructor urges the girl forward, then takes a seat near the back of the house.
KARATE_KID_DVS1112
SOMEONE arrives on the stage, kneels, and removes her violin from its case.
KARATE_KID_DVS1113
As her parents take seats near the front of the house, she steps center stage, bows first to the judges, then to the orchestra.
KARATE_KID_DVS1114
She raises her violin and bow.
KARATE_KID_DVS1119
One judge knits his brow, while another lowers his folded arms. Mrs. Po looks on with a softened gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS1120
SOMEONE's instructor listens, stone-faced.
KARATE_KID_DVS1121
On stage, the girl plays with closed eyes and a furrowed brow.
KARATE_KID_DVS1123
Meanwhile, SOMEONE races doggedly down a sidewalk, dodging other pedestrians. He turns into the school gates and dashes through the entrance. Nearing the auditorium, he shoves past waiting young musicians.
KARATE_KID_DVS1125
Inside, as the instructor watches his pupil, SOMEONE's face pops up in the window behind him.
KARATE_KID_DVS1126
He sees SOMEONE playing on stage, and steps around the partition.
KARATE_KID_DVS1127
SOMEONE slips into a seat behind the instructor's shoulder.
KARATE_KID_DVS1128
SOMEONE stares tenderly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1129
As SOMEONE opens her eyes, the boy claps his hands earnestly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1131
The instructor's eyes widen and he turns.
KARATE_KID_DVS1132
As others shoot SOMEONE offended looks, he sheepishly trails off.
KARATE_KID_DVS1133
SOMEONE leaves the stage as the judges chat and nod.
KARATE_KID_DVS1134
SOMEONE leans toward her instructor.
KARATE_KID_DVS1135
The instructor gets to his feet, walks past SOMEONE, and leaves the auditorium.
KARATE_KID_DVS1136
Craning his neck, the boy watches SOMEONE's parents proudly greet her.
KARATE_KID_DVS1137
She looks back at SOMEONE and holds up her pinky.
KARATE_KID_DVS1138
Beaming, he returns the gesture.
KARATE_KID_DVS1139
As they follow their daughter's gaze, the parents' smiles fade.
KARATE_KID_DVS1140
The father clasps his hands behind his back and addresses SOMEONE sternly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1141
Her joyful grin vanishes.
KARATE_KID_DVS1142
SOMEONE blinks quizzically at them.
KARATE_KID_DVS1143
SOMEONE's parents walk her up the aisle, stopping to face the young American boy.
KARATE_KID_DVS1147
SOMEONE stares at her, crestfallen.
KARATE_KID_DVS1148
SOMEONE unhappily bites her lip.
KARATE_KID_DVS1149
Her father pats her shoulder and they continue up the aisle as SOMEONE helplessly watches them go.
KARATE_KID_DVS1151
SOMEONE approaches, flanked by his friends.
KARATE_KID_DVS1153
SOMEONE shifts on his feet as they saunter past.
KARATE_KID_DVS1155
At dusk, SOMEONE shuffles through a teaming marketplace illuminated softly by lanterns in each kiosk.
KARATE_KID_DVS1156
He pauses and digs his cell phone from his pocket.
KARATE_KID_DVS1157
The message from his mom reads, Where are you? You need to get home.
KARATE_KID_DVS1159
SOMEONE pushes a button and the display reads, Message deleted.
KARATE_KID_DVS1160
Now, SOMEONE enters SOMEONE's house.
KARATE_KID_DVS1161
He slows, and looks around anxiously, then treads through the kitchen.
KARATE_KID_DVS1163
SOMEONE steps into the living room and finds SOMEONE bludgeoning the car with a sledgehammer.
KARATE_KID_DVS1164
The boy stares, slack-jawed, then notices a half-empty bottle of liquor sitting nearby.
KARATE_KID_DVS1168
SOMEONE blearily notices his student.
KARATE_KID_DVS1169
SOMEONE slings his backpack off and faces him.
KARATE_KID_DVS1171
Shoulders slouched wearily SOMEONE heaves a sigh and staggers around the front of the car.
KARATE_KID_DVS1172
He stares off, vacantly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1173
SOMEONE paces toward him and glances at the wreck.
KARATE_KID_DVS1175
The boy's confused gaze drifts.
KARATE_KID_DVS1176
SOMEONE paces to the driver-side door and plops down behind the wheel.
KARATE_KID_DVS1177
SOMEONE walks alongside the car, scanning the destroyed vehicle.
KARATE_KID_DVS1179
In a deep dent on the hood, he notices a newspaper clipping lying under pebbles of shattered glass.
KARATE_KID_DVS1180
SOMEONE leans closer, then picks the scrap up,
KARATE_KID_DVS1181
dumping off the glass bits.
KARATE_KID_DVS1182
The clipping shows photos of a smiling young woman and a pudgy-cheeked young boy.
KARATE_KID_DVS1184
a third photo shows a wrecked Scirocco,
KARATE_KID_DVS1185
its front end smashed and bumper hanging
KARATE_KID_DVS1187
SOMEONE regards the front end of SOMEONE's car and finds it similarly damaged.
KARATE_KID_DVS1188
The bumper lies on the floor beneath a cock-eyed headlight, and the sledgehammer stands leaning against the hood.
KARATE_KID_DVS1189
SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE, who frowns through the windshield,
KARATE_KID_DVS1190
his face nearly obscured by a milky haze of cracks.
KARATE_KID_DVS1191
SOMEONE edges back to the passenger-side door and hesitantly climb aboard.
KARATE_KID_DVS1194
The teacher and student sit motionless, side by side.
KARATE_KID_DVS1195
SOMEONE glances nervously at the kung fu master, then drops his gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS1197
Lifting his eyes, he studies the middle-aged man's care-worn face.
KARATE_KID_DVS1199
SOMEONE blinks, then summons a breath.
KARATE_KID_DVS1200
He looks to the dashboard, leans over, and grabs something.
KARATE_KID_DVS1201
SOMEONE watches soberly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1202
SOMEONE holds up a snapshot of the slender young woman posing with her hands on the shoulders of the chubby-cheeked boy.
KARATE_KID_DVS1204
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the photo and winces.
KARATE_KID_DVS1207
He grips the wheel and smiles woefully.
KARATE_KID_DVS1212
SOMEONE stares at the photo, then pulls a stack of rumpled snapshots out of the glove box.
KARATE_KID_DVS1214
SOMEONE clenches his jaw, staring off, as the boy rifles through the photos.
KARATE_KID_DVS1215
One shows Gong Gong peeking through a beaded curtain, and another shows Zhang smiling as Gong Gong harvests a piece of fruit from a tree.
KARATE_KID_DVS1216
Tears shine on SOMEONE's cheeks as he hunches toward the wheel.
KARATE_KID_DVS1217
SOMEONE eyes the grieving father shyly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1227
SOMEONE slumps forward, his hands loosely gripping the wheel.
KARATE_KID_DVS1228
SOMEONE watches his teacher solemnly, then looks away.
KARATE_KID_DVS1229
A glistening tear rolls down his cheek
KARATE_KID_DVS1230
and he glances at another photograph.
KARATE_KID_DVS1231
It shows SOMEONE posing with his wife and son, surrounded by greenery.
KARATE_KID_DVS1233
SOMEONE sets the pictures down and eyes SOMEONE, who keeps his head bowed.
KARATE_KID_DVS1235
SOMEONE shoves the door open and climbs out.
KARATE_KID_DVS1237
He circles around the front of the car, watching SOMEONE through the cracked windshield.
KARATE_KID_DVS1238
SOMEONE loops the rope handle of a bamboo training pole around SOMEONE's hand.
KARATE_KID_DVS1240
The kung fu master lifts his head and finds another rope handle lassoing his other hand.
KARATE_KID_DVS1241
He glances at SOMEONE, who pulls on the poles.
KARATE_KID_DVS1242
Following their guidance, the teacher climbs out of the car.
KARATE_KID_DVS1245
SOMEONE locks eyes with him and draws him forward, tears shining on his cheeks.
KARATE_KID_DVS1247
The car's single working headlight flares brightly into the courtyard,
KARATE_KID_DVS1250
silhouetting the pair, as SOMEONE tugs SOMEONE outside. They descend from SOMEONE's patio and move into the center of the courtyard.
KARATE_KID_DVS1252
The headlight projects their shadows onto the wall behind them, as the boy maneuvers them into position.
KARATE_KID_DVS1254
SOMEONE stares at him wearily.
KARATE_KID_DVS1256
Using both hands, SOMEONE angles a pole upward, raising SOMEONE's hand to his face.
KARATE_KID_DVS1257
He smears the tears from his cheeks.
KARATE_KID_DVS1258
Gripping one pole in each hand, SOMEONE crouches.
KARATE_KID_DVS1260
SOMEONE remains slouched and the boy shakes the poles insistently.
KARATE_KID_DVS1262
The teacher unloops one hand from a handle and wipes at his face again, then grips the poles and crouches low.
KARATE_KID_DVS1264
Jerking the poles, he puppets SOMEONE into an attack stance with his arms outstretched.
KARATE_KID_DVS1265
He slowly guides the boy through a squat, then yanks the poles again.
KARATE_KID_DVS1267
SOMEONE thrusts his fists and strikes a pose, Later, he shoves his hands out, palms forward.
KARATE_KID_DVS1268
SOMEONE whips the poles around and moves the boy into another stance.
KARATE_KID_DVS1269
Now, SOMEONE stands between the poles with his back to SOMEONE. The poles dangle from his wrists, as he punches his fists forward.
KARATE_KID_DVS1270
Behind him, SOMEONE controls his movements.
KARATE_KID_DVS1271
Later, he pulls SOMEONE forward, the boy’s hands crooked into snake-like hooks.
KARATE_KID_DVS1272
Now, the student grips the poles, allowing his teacher to pull his arms upward.
KARATE_KID_DVS1273
His shadow shows him raise one knee and balance on one leg.
KARATE_KID_DVS1275
Behind them, SOMEONE enters SOMEONE's living room.
KARATE_KID_DVS1276
She peeks through the ornate screens covering the windows, and studies SOMEONE and SOMEONE outside.
KARATE_KID_DVS1277
Her jaw hangs slack.
KARATE_KID_DVS1278
Their shadows show SOMEONE puppet SOMEONE through a series of fluid movements. SOMEONE beams proudly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1279
SOMEONE waves the poles up and down, and SOMEONE expertly mimics his movements.
KARATE_KID_DVS1280
Kicking his leg up, he balances it along one pole.
KARATE_KID_DVS1281
SOMEONE steps closer, raising the pole, and lifting the boy's leg into a near-vertical position.
KARATE_KID_DVS1282
SOMEONE's shadow shows the high-kick pose, as he balances easily on his other leg.
KARATE_KID_DVS1283
Fade to black.
KARATE_KID_DVS1284
Now, an aerial view soars over the Great Wall winding along a lush mountain ridge.
KARATE_KID_DVS1285
Watchtowers dot the fortification, standing on the mountain's highest peaks. On the roof of one watchtower, SOMEONE and SOMEONE practice.
KARATE_KID_DVS1286
SOMEONE executes kung fu sequences against the powder-blue sky as SOMEONE looks on.
KARATE_KID_DVS1287
The boy whirls with precision and grace from one stance to the next.
KARATE_KID_DVS1288
Golden sunlight bathes the pair as we orbit them.
KARATE_KID_DVS1289
Later, SOMEONE practices on the pathway between the battlements, kicking his way forward along the wall.
KARATE_KID_DVS1290
SOMEONE follows behind him, watching closely.
KARATE_KID_DVS1291
Now in the courtyard, SOMEONE rapidly swats tennis balls at SOMEONE. The boy smacks the barrage aside, ducks another, catches two, and kicks a third.
KARATE_KID_DVS1292
Nighttime. SOMEONE peeks into SOMEONE's room and finds him doing push-ups, with his feet
KARATE_KID_DVS1293
elevated on a stack of books upon a chair. Daytime. In the courtyard, SOMEONE whirls a staff.
KARATE_KID_DVS1294
Now at a bank of lockers at school, the boy spots SOMEONE and offers a faint smile.
KARATE_KID_DVS1295
The pixie-faced girl frowns and hurries away.
KARATE_KID_DVS1296
SOMEONE glumly averts his gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS1297
Now in SOMEONE's courtyard, SOMEONE kicks the utility pole which stands thickly wrapped in padding.
KARATE_KID_DVS1298
SOMEONE thrusts a pillow at him, and SOMEONE swats it aside, then refocuses his attacks on the padded pole.
KARATE_KID_DVS1299
Later, he kicks at the bell dangling overhead, but misses.
KARATE_KID_DVS1300
Flinging his foot upward again, the kick still comes up short.
KARATE_KID_DVS1301
Now on the rooftop, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand on either side of the bed sheet.
KARATE_KID_DVS1302
SOMEONE repeatedly jabs the boxing glove at SOMEONE, who easily deflects it.
KARATE_KID_DVS1303
SOMEONE halts and walks away.
KARATE_KID_DVS1304
SOMEONE frowns curiously and peeks under the sheet, finding SOMEONE halfway across the roof.
KARATE_KID_DVS1305
Now in the rain, SOMEONE runs in place in the thick mud of SOMEONE's courtyard garden.
KARATE_KID_DVS1306
He holds his fists curled up toward his chest.
KARATE_KID_DVS1307
SOMEONE coaches him to keep his fists up.
KARATE_KID_DVS1308
Later at school, SOMEONE passes SOMEONE by.
KARATE_KID_DVS1309
He watches sadly as she gets into her father's luxury sedan.
KARATE_KID_DVS1310
Now in the courtyard, SOMEONE performs push-ups with his feet on a chair.
KARATE_KID_DVS1311
SOMEONE sweeps his closed fan in front of SOMEONE's face, and SOMEONE follows its movements with his body.
KARATE_KID_DVS1312
Nighttime. SOMEONE hooks the back of his knees over the utility pole pegs, and does suspended sit-ups, as SOMEONE holds his feet.
KARATE_KID_DVS1313
He punches at the top of each rep.
KARATE_KID_DVS1314
Now on the rooftop, SOMEONE does chin-ups on a bamboo laundry line. In the courtyard, he spars with SOMEONE, blocking the man's strikes. On another rooftop, he does pull-ups on a corner railing. His body dangles inside the corner as he grips rails above his head. Now, SOMEONE runs laps on the Great Wall. Back in the courtyard, the pupil and teacher continue to spar. SOMEONE plants his hands on SOMEONE's chest and shoves. SOMEONE slides backward.
KARATE_KID_DVS1316
SOMEONE snarls, and circles his arms around each other, then takes a ready stance. SOMEONE nods.
KARATE_KID_DVS1317
Now on the rooftop, SOMEONE's feet rest on either side of the corner railing.
KARATE_KID_DVS1318
Gripping an upper rail, he lowers himself toward a lateral split across the gap.
KARATE_KID_DVS1319
Now, he practices atop the watchtower. On the rooftop, SOMEONE completes the lateral split.
KARATE_KID_DVS1320
He balances on the corner railing with only his legs.
KARATE_KID_DVS1321
The boy holds up one hand, and slowly sweeps it through the air in front of him.
KARATE_KID_DVS1322
Nighttime. In a shadowy arena, workers unroll kung fu mats decorated with Yin-Yang symbols. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stock across the floor.
KARATE_KID_DVS1323
Dozens of trophies stand on a nearby table.
KARATE_KID_DVS1324
A transparent silhouette of a warrior in a kung fu pose tops each, the tallest trophy depicting a nearly-vertical high kick.
KARATE_KID_DVS1327
SOMEONE paces across a mat, loosely rehearsing a sequence.
KARATE_KID_DVS1328
SOMEONE takes a package out of his jacket.
KARATE_KID_DVS1330
SOMEONE unties the fabric wrapping and finds a white uniform.
KARATE_KID_DVS1331
He holds it up to himself.
KARATE_KID_DVS1332
They solemnly lock eyes.
KARATE_KID_DVS1336
SOMEONE's expression softens fondly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1337
SOMEONE wraps his arms around his teacher's waist, seizing him in a hug.
KARATE_KID_DVS1338
SOMEONE hugs him back and gives him a pat, as they stand in the center of the vacant arena.
KARATE_KID_DVS1339
The middle-aged man smiles
KARATE_KID_DVS1340
and rests his cheek on the top of SOMEONE's head.
KARATE_KID_DVS1341
Pursing his lips, he shifts his gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS1342
SOMEONE breaks the embrace and hobbles away.
KARATE_KID_DVS1343
SOMEONE bounds after him.
KARATE_KID_DVS1344
Now, two monstrous bronze faces form door handles. SOMEONE opens the door.
KARATE_KID_DVS1345
The door swings open further, revealing her father standing behind it.
KARATE_KID_DVS1346
SOMEONE bows his head and reads,
KARATE_KID_DVS1347
Sir, my name is SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1348
SOMEONE hides nearby.
KARATE_KID_DVS1355
SOMEONE looks up from his notes
KARATE_KID_DVS1356
and shrugs uneasily.
KARATE_KID_DVS1357
The stern man studies the boy.
KARATE_KID_DVS1358
SOMEONE peers up at her father.
KARATE_KID_DVS1360
He jerks his head in SOMEONE's direction.
KARATE_KID_DVS1361
SOMEONE beams.
KARATE_KID_DVS1363
SOMEONE gives a relieved smile. Her father grins.
KARATE_KID_DVS1364
SOMEONE gives a slight bow and plants his fist against his palm.
KARATE_KID_DVS1365
SOMEONE beams as her father closes the door.
KARATE_KID_DVS1366
SOMEONE lifts his brow and looks to SOMEONE, who stands hiding in the bushes.
KARATE_KID_DVS1369
Daytime. In the courtyard, SOMEONE glares up at the bell dangling overhead. As SOMEONE watches, the boy crouches, then launches his foot upward.
KARATE_KID_DVS1370
His leg swings into a near-vertical kick and he hits the bell. The image freezes and he becomes the high-kick silhouette on the tallest trophy. At the tournament, SOMEONE wears the white jacket from SOMEONE. In the stands, SOMEONE waves SOMEONE over, and SOMEONE's mother takes a seat between the girl and SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1372
Images of boys in kung fu stances flash on a giant video scoreboard. In the packed stands, audience members wave large flags. On the arena floor, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE's first match anxiously. SOMEONE spins and delivers a roundhouse kick, flipping his opponent onto the ground. An official snaps a score flag.
KARATE_KID_DVS1373
As SOMEONE swaggers off the mat, he glares at SOMEONE on the sidelines.
KARATE_KID_DVS1374
SOMEONE high-fives his teammates and murmurs to Master SOMEONE. An official steps up to SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1376
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step forward. SOMEONE flips through a soft-cover book.
KARATE_KID_DVS1385
On the mat, SOMEONE faces a boy in a green-and-black uniform. Master SOMEONE watches.
KARATE_KID_DVS1386
The boys plant their fists against their opposite palms and bow to each other. An official waves two flags.
KARATE_KID_DVS1387
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder at SOMEONE, who shakes his fist encouragingly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1389
The official drops the flags and the boys circle each other. SOMEONE's opponent kicks at him, but SOMEONE backs away, running off the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1397
On the mat, SOMEONE's opponent kicks SOMEONE in the shoulder, then charges him. SOMEONE flees off the mat and the official snaps his flag.
KARATE_KID_DVS1398
SOMEONE heaves a sigh.
KARATE_KID_DVS1399
SOMEONE stares up at the video scoreboard, which shows an instant replay of him running from his opponent.
KARATE_KID_DVS1400
The score reads, "SOMEONE 1, SOMEONE 0."
KARATE_KID_DVS1401
SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE, who points at his eyes, then SOMEONE. SOMEONE attacks again, but SOMEONE dodges. He shoves SOMEONE off the mat. The scoreboard replays SOMEONE's counter-offensive and awards him a point.
KARATE_KID_DVS1405
SOMEONE nervously faces off with SOMEONE. The official studies the boys, then snaps his flags.
KARATE_KID_DVS1407
SOMEONE locks eyes with SOMEONE, then barrels forward. As he leaps toward the American fighter, SOMEONE kicks him in the side, and knocks him to the floor. The official snaps a score flag. In the stands, SOMEONE cheers wildly. SOMEONE claps and glances at SOMEONE, who beams. Now, the scoreboard reads, The Fighting SOMEONEs, The Reigning Champions.
KARATE_KID_DVS1408
On a mat, SOMEONE's teammate with close-cropped hair jumps, and boots his opponent in the chest, knocking him flat, and scoring a point. SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch soberly. As the match continues, the Fighting SOMEONE wraps his legs around his opponent's neck, and swings him to the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1409
His legs hold tight as his opponent writhes.
KARATE_KID_DVS1410
The official pulls the Fighting SOMEONE off the defeated boy.
KARATE_KID_DVS1411
Now, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE, who struts onto a mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1412
He and a boy in a gray uniform bow to each other. The flag drops, and SOMEONE attacks before his opponent even breaks his bow.
KARATE_KID_DVS1413
With a single powerful kick, he knocks the boy off his feet, and sends him crashing to the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1414
Master SOMEONE happily shakes a fist.
KARATE_KID_DVS1415
Later, SOMEONE fights a boy in gray, the American struggling to fend off his opponent's attacks. The boy in gray kicks at him, and SOMEONE seizes his leg, flips him over his shoulder, and slams him onto the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1416
The official gives SOMEONE a point.
KARATE_KID_DVS1418
SOMEONE asks SOMEONE if that was okay and his teacher nods.
KARATE_KID_DVS1419
Now, a cocky boy in blue smooths his hands up his tall Mohawk. He downs his opponent with two powerful kicks, and the official raises his arm triumphantly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1423
Now, SOMEONE jogs onto a mat. He whirls toward a boy in gray, kicking his opponent in the head. The boy falls flat and SOMEONE sneers. SOMEONE urges SOMEONE toward another mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1424
SOMEONE's new opponent takes a ready stance. An official drops the flags and the boy leaps at SOMEONE. SOMEONE dodges easily, then attacks. Jumping up, he kicks his opponent to the mat. The official waves the score flag and SOMEONE's name appears on the leader board.
KARATE_KID_DVS1425
Now, SOMEONE bludgeons an opponent while he's down. The official blocks SOMEONE's next blow with his flags. A worried SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1426
SOMEONE saunters off, idly checking his knuckles. His opponent's teammates carry their peer off the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1427
Later, the boy with the Mohawk faces off with a Fighting SOMEONE. He sweeps a kick at the boy's feet, but the SOMEONE jumps it. As he lands, the boy with the Mohawk spins and kicks him in the head. The Fighting SOMEONE falls. SOMEONE and SOMEONE glower. Now, SOMEONE and a SOMEONE bow to each other.
KARATE_KID_DVS1428
The SOMEONE snarls.
KARATE_KID_DVS1429
A motionless SOMEONE watches, slack-jawed, as the boy bounces around excitedly. The Fighting SOMEONE finally crouches into a ready stance, then flails wildly at SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1430
SOMEONE backs off, dodging, and his opponent lands a hard hit to SOMEONE's side. In the stands, SOMEONE cheers her son on. On the mat, SOMEONE and the SOMEONE trade blows. SOMEONE knocks the boy to his knees, then kicks him in the head. The official waves a score flag. SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE leap to their feet.
KARATE_KID_DVS1432
In the locker room.
KARATE_KID_DVS1436
Now, workers unroll a single kung fu mat, on a raised platform in the center of the arena.
KARATE_KID_DVS1437
And now, the first semifinal of the evening.
KARATE_KID_DVS1438
The big screen shows the names and photos of the four semifinalists.
KARATE_KID_DVS1439
Next, it shows SOMEONE versus the Mohawk boy, named SOMEONE Ping.
KARATE_KID_DVS1440
The boy in blue steps onto the platform, followed by his crimson-clad opponent.
KARATE_KID_DVS1441
From the sidelines, Master SOMEONE tensely looks on.
KARATE_KID_DVS1442
SOMEONE's brow glistens with sweat as he stands at Mr. SOMEONE's side. On the platform, SOMEONE saunters to his starting position. With an icy glare, he gives SOMEONE Ping a perfunctory bow. His opponent smooths his Mohawk and straightens his gi.
KARATE_KID_DVS1443
A referee lowers two flags between them.
KARATE_KID_DVS1444
SOMEONE Ping charges at SOMEONE, who sidesteps his attack. The two opponents swiftly parry each other's strikes. SOMEONE Ping executes a series of roundhouse kicks, but SOMEONE back-handsprings out of harm's way. As they face off again, SOMEONE kicks him across the mat. Snarling, he races toward his fallen opponent.
KARATE_KID_DVS1445
The referee pulls SOMEONE Ping aside, and SOMEONE's pounding fist hits the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1446
He rushes at SOMEONE Ping again, but the referee forces him back, gestures firmly for him to stay, and signals him with a flag.
KARATE_KID_DVS1447
SOMEONE Ping stands, clutching his stomach, and eyes SOMEONE resentfully.
KARATE_KID_DVS1448
In the crowd, a woman beckons SOMEONE and SOMEONE, who follow her.
KARATE_KID_DVS1449
SOMEONE blocks SOMEONE Ping's deft kicks and blows. Grabbing his opponent's arm, he flips himself around SOMEONE Ping's body, and pins him to his knees.
KARATE_KID_DVS1450
SOMEONE holds the Mohawk boy in a chokehold, as he wrenches his arm upward. SOMEONE Ping's flushed face grimaces and he frantically taps the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1451
Moving through the crowd with SOMEONE, SOMEONE stares worriedly. On the platform, the referee wrenches SOMEONE off of his opponent.
KARATE_KID_DVS1452
In the crowd, Mr. SOMEONE sets SOMEONE in a seat near the platform. On the mat, SOMEONE Ping charges his opponent again. The two trade rapid-fire kicks and punches. SOMEONE kicks SOMEONE Ping's leg out from under him. As his opponent falls on his back, the bully drops on top of him, slamming his elbow into his sternum.
KARATE_KID_DVS1453
From the sidelines, his classmates cheer wildly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1454
The referee lifts SOMEONE's hand overhead. From their seats, Mr. SOMEONE and SOMEONE turn. The big screen reads, SOMEONE wins. SOMEONE advances to final.
KARATE_KID_DVS1455
SOMEONE swallows and licks his dry lips.
KARATE_KID_DVS1458
SOMEONE's shorthaired friend stands.
KARATE_KID_DVS1459
And the surprise finalist, SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1460
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand, the people around them applaud.
KARATE_KID_DVS1461
Master SOMEONE stops SOMEONE on his way to the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1462
Putting an arm around him, he leans close.
KARATE_KID_DVS1467
Meanwhile, Mr. SOMEONE leans close to SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1469
The boy swallows nervously, then shuffles to the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1470
Members of the press snap his photo as he passes.
KARATE_KID_DVS1471
Eyeing the platform, he finds SOMEONE gazing down on him with a stony expression.
KARATE_KID_DVS1472
A referee stands at the mat's edge, pointing with a flag.
KARATE_KID_DVS1473
Reaching the platform, SOMEONE takes his place.
KARATE_KID_DVS1474
In unison, the two opponents press their fists to their open palms and bow deeply from the waist.
KARATE_KID_DVS1475
SOMEONE looks to his instructor, who watches impassively.
KARATE_KID_DVS1476
The referee raises his flag and the Fighting SOMEONE lifts his fists.
KARATE_KID_DVS1477
SOMEONE draws one fist back and extends a straightened hand forward.
KARATE_KID_DVS1478
The crowd solemnly looks on as the two opponents circle one another.
KARATE_KID_DVS1479
SOMEONE repositions his hands in fluidly graceful movements.
KARATE_KID_DVS1480
SOMEONE charges with rapid-fire kicks. As SOMEONE blocks and dodges them, Mr. SOMEONE and Master SOMEONE look on intently. SOMEONE attempts a roundhouse kick, but SOMEONE catches his ankle and elbow jabs the side of his knee. Kicking his other leg out from under him, the Fighting SOMEONE continues to pound on the knee. The referee wrests him away. Mr. SOMEONE rushes to his student's side. The referee gestures to SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1482
Master SOMEONE sits with a grim smirk.
KARATE_KID_DVS1483
SOMEONE gazes down at SOMEONE remorsefully.
KARATE_KID_DVS1484
On the big screen, a word appears over SOMEONE's face, in Chinese and English - Disqualified.
KARATE_KID_DVS1485
Mr. SOMEONE glares at Master SOMEONE, who meets his gaze with a cavalier expression.
KARATE_KID_DVS1486
SOMEONE turns away remorsefully and shuffles across the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1487
Now in the stadium's infirmary, a doctor gently tries to rotate SOMEONE's bruised swollen knee.
KARATE_KID_DVS1488
SOMEONE looks on.
KARATE_KID_DVS1491
He faces SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1493
SOMEONE looks up at his teacher.
KARATE_KID_DVS1495
The boy heaves a dissatisfied sigh.
KARATE_KID_DVS1496
As the doctor leaves, SOMEONE and SOMEONE rush in.
KARATE_KID_DVS1497
The boy drapes an arm over his eyes as they arrive at his side.
KARATE_KID_DVS1498
In the arena, the announcer holds a trophy.
KARATE_KID_DVS1499
SOMEONE has two minutes to return to the match. If he's unable to return, the Fighting SOMEONE win by default.
KARATE_KID_DVS1500
Master SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand beside him.
KARATE_KID_DVS1502
Back in the infirmary, she shares a look with Mr. SOMEONE, then beckons SOMEONE to join her. The two females leave together.
KARATE_KID_DVS1503
Uncovering his face, SOMEONE looks up at his teacher.
KARATE_KID_DVS1507
Mr. SOMEONE averts his gaze and blinks thoughtfully.
KARATE_KID_DVS1509
SOMEONE gestures toward his knee.
KARATE_KID_DVS1510
SOMEONE glances briefly at it.
KARATE_KID_DVS1517
Mr. SOMEONE regards the boy with a furrowed brow.
KARATE_KID_DVS1518
His pupil gazes into his eyes, then gravely looks away.
KARATE_KID_DVS1522
Gazing up, SOMEONE takes a deep breath.
KARATE_KID_DVS1523
He licks his lips and faces his teacher.
KARATE_KID_DVS1524
Mr. SOMEONE stares tenderly at him.
KARATE_KID_DVS1525
Mr. SOMEONE gives an understanding nod.
KARATE_KID_DVS1526
Now, he lifts a match to a cotton ball held in a long pair of tweezers.
KARATE_KID_DVS1527
It blazes with a greenish-yellow flame.
KARATE_KID_DVS1528
In the arena.
KARATE_KID_DVS1529
Since SOMEONE has not returned to the ring
KARATE_KID_DVS1530
SOMEONE runs out and faces the judges.
KARATE_KID_DVS1531
The center judge uses a microphone.
KARATE_KID_DVS1532
Holding the champion trophy, the announcer leaves SOMEONE and SOMEONE on the mat, and goes to the judges.
KARATE_KID_DVS1533
The announcer nods.
KARATE_KID_DVS1534
Returning to the center of the mat, he raises the microphone.
KARATE_KID_DVS1535
SOMEONE fight.
KARATE_KID_DVS1536
Spectators spring to their feet.
KARATE_KID_DVS1537
SOMEONE stares, wide-eyed, and SOMEONE glares resentfully, as SOMEONE reenters the arena.
KARATE_KID_DVS1538
The crowd parts for the American, as he marches forward with a limping gait.
KARATE_KID_DVS1539
In the stands, SOMEONE cranes her neck for a view of her son, as the spectators cheer him on.
KARATE_KID_DVS1540
Master SOMEONE eyes the boy, then faces Mr. SOMEONE with a smirk.
KARATE_KID_DVS1541
He hobbles toward the rival teacher with a mocking limp.
KARATE_KID_DVS1543
Mr. SOMEONE observes him with a stony expression.
KARATE_KID_DVS1544
SOMEONE grins in his face and claps. As he steps away,
KARATE_KID_DVS1545
SOMEONE shifts his troubled gaze.
KARATE_KID_DVS1546
SOMEONE waits at the edge of the platform as SOMEONE steps near. The American looks the bully dead in the eye, then approaches Mr. SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1547
They share a solemn look.
KARATE_KID_DVS1548
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a supportive nod and pat on the back. And the boy climbs the platform steps.
KARATE_KID_DVS1549
SOMEONE applauds hopefully as her son takes his place on the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1550
The rival teachers move to vantage points nearby.
KARATE_KID_DVS1551
SOMEONE bounces on his feet as the official steps between him and SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1552
The two boys take their starting poses.
KARATE_KID_DVS1553
SOMEONE creeps toward his opponent with a taunting smirk.
KARATE_KID_DVS1554
His face glistening, SOMEONE edges back.
KARATE_KID_DVS1555
His opponent gives a small jump forward.
KARATE_KID_DVS1556
He delivers a sidekick which the American blocks. The two trade deft punches and kicks, each expertly blocking the other.
KARATE_KID_DVS1557
SOMEONE attacks with a hitch kick, but his opponent sidesteps out of the way.
KARATE_KID_DVS1558
As the bully swings his fists, SOMEONE leaps back onto his hands, and springs onto his feet. The two boys swing fiercely at one another, each blocking the other with precision. SOMEONE catches SOMEONE's arm and forces him back with a powerful blow. He faces the bully with a fearless scowl. SOMEONE charges. SOMEONE drops to his knees and slides under the boy's aerial kick. As he stands, SOMEONE charges again and kicks him off of the platform. SOMEONE angrily looks away and SOMEONE rushes to SOMEONE's side.
KARATE_KID_DVS1561
The boy bravely sits up. Master SOMEONE shifts on his feet as he watches grimly. The big screen shows a point awarded to SOMEONE. The bully faces his opponent with a remorseless scowl.
KARATE_KID_DVS1562
Holding his gaze, SOMEONE exhales through pursed lips, then springs back onto the platform.
KARATE_KID_DVS1563
SOMEONE limps to his starting position as SOMEONE regards him wearily. The bully's expression hardens and he raises his fists.
KARATE_KID_DVS1565
SOMEONE swings, but SOMEONE blocks his arm. As the boys spar, Mr. SOMEONE's eyes widen. SOMEONE drops to his knees and spins, sweeping SOMEONE's legs out from under him. He slides across the mat to his opponent, subduing him with two fierce blows. SOMEONE staggers to his feet and the official lowers a red flag. SOMEONE cheers wildly and SOMEONE grins.
KARATE_KID_DVS1566
The big screen shows a point awarded to SOMEONE, tying the score at 1 to 1. Master SOMEONE's expression hardens. SOMEONE stands, his face shining with sweat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1567
SOMEONE bounces fearlessly on his feet.
KARATE_KID_DVS1568
Both boys catch their breath.
KARATE_KID_DVS1570
The two boys circle each other. Mr. SOMEONE watches with a knitted brow. SOMEONE pulls his fist back, extending his flattened hand forward. SOMEONE charges. SOMEONE blocks his fevered attacks, then kicks him back. SOMEONE handsprings onto his feet. SOMEONE leaps at him hooks his legs around the bully's neck, and arcs backward, flipping SOMEONE over his frame. The bully lands on his back and SOMEONE delivers a blow to his nose. The official takes the American's wrist and helps him up.
KARATE_KID_DVS1571
Master SOMEONE watches gravely. SOMEONE and SOMEONE share excited grins. Guided by the official, SOMEONE compliantly backs off, and SOMEONE gets to his feet. Master SOMEONE eyes Mr. SOMEONE, who grimly meets his gaze. Standing, SOMEONE exhales heavily and faces his opponent. The official examines his nose. He makes an X with his flags, then gestures toward Master SOMEONE, who beckons SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1572
As the teacher meets with his Fighting SOMEONE, SOMEONE calls to SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1574
Master SOMEONE holds SOMEONE's face, peering closely at his nose.
KARATE_KID_DVS1577
SOMEONE stares, wide-eyed, as his master releases his grip.
KARATE_KID_DVS1579
The student shifts on his feet and looks up at his opponent.
KARATE_KID_DVS1580
He leaps back onto the platform and marches to a starting position, with a hardened scowl.
KARATE_KID_DVS1581
Shifting his calculating gaze, Master SOMEONE returns to the sidelines. SOMEONE rolls his shoulder as he and SOMEONE face off.
KARATE_KID_DVS1582
Raising his fists, he wipes his nose.
KARATE_KID_DVS1583
Mr. SOMEONE eyes his rival teacher worriedly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1584
Raising his hands, SOMEONE tensely licks his lips and blinks the sweat out of his eyes. SOMEONE glances at his leg, with a faint smirk. The two boys circle each other slowly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1586
SOMEONE takes a deep breath, edges toward SOMEONE, and attacks. The American expertly blocks his swinging fists and feet.
KARATE_KID_DVS1587
SOMEONE looks to his teacher, who gestures with a cold tilt of his head.
KARATE_KID_DVS1588
The boy delivers a swift kick to the leg, then leaps and spins, plunging his foot into the side of the injured knee. SOMEONE falls, baring his gritted teeth.
KARATE_KID_DVS1589
He presses his painfully grimacing face to the mat, clutching his thigh. The official extends a red flag. As Master SOMEONE looks to the big screen, it shows a slow-motion replay of the brutal kick.
KARATE_KID_DVS1590
The score display shows a point being awarded to SOMEONE,
KARATE_KID_DVS1591
tying the match at 2 to 2.
KARATE_KID_DVS1592
The score is tied. The next point wins.
KARATE_KID_DVS1593
SOMEONE towers over his writhing opponent, then faces his teacher.
KARATE_KID_DVS1594
Master SOMEONE looks to Mr. SOMEONE with a satisfied smirk. The official speaks to SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1596
A hand to her brow, SOMEONE briefly averts her anguished gaze. The injured boy pushes himself up on his elbows, then rolls himself onto his uninjured side.
KARATE_KID_DVS1598
His head bows, and he doubles over.
KARATE_KID_DVS1599
Master SOMEONE watches with a heartsick gape.
KARATE_KID_DVS1600
SOMEONE looks up at SOMEONE, who looks away, his gaze betraying a hint of contrition.
KARATE_KID_DVS1601
On the sidelines, his corrupt teacher maintains a cool smirk.
KARATE_KID_DVS1602
SOMEONE pushes himself up on his uninjured knee, then buckles. Near tears, SOMEONE shifts anxiously on her feet.
KARATE_KID_DVS1603
His brow furrowed, Mr. SOMEONE mouths, Come on, SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1606
The injured boy scoots forward on the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1607
He pushes himself up, then stands on his good leg.
KARATE_KID_DVS1608
SOMEONE cheers wildly and SOMEONE gives an astonished smile.
KARATE_KID_DVS1609
Spectators joyfully wave their flags in support.
KARATE_KID_DVS1610
Master SOMEONE's lips part as he stares. His brow furrowed, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE with glistening eyes.
KARATE_KID_DVS1611
The American boy's gaze hardens and his nostrils flare.
KARATE_KID_DVS1612
As Mr. SOMEONE watches with a knitted brow, he steels himself by exhaling through his pursed lips.
KARATE_KID_DVS1613
Raising his injured knee to his chest, he lifts both hands before him, palms upturned.
KARATE_KID_DVS1614
He lowers his palms and sweeps his arms into the shape of a crooked T,
KARATE_KID_DVS1615
adopting the female monk's cobra-charming pose.
KARATE_KID_DVS1616
Mr. SOMEONE lifts his brow.
KARATE_KID_DVS1617
The boy gracefully maintains the advanced position, gazing steadily at his opponent.
KARATE_KID_DVS1618
SOMEONE's shoulders heave as he edges toward SOMEONE,
KARATE_KID_DVS1619
while Master SOMEONE blinks at the unconventional stance.
KARATE_KID_DVS1620
Lowering his chin, SOMEONE stares piercingly at his opponent, who shifts uncertainly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1621
As the American tilts his head, SOMEONE drops his fists and matches him.
KARATE_KID_DVS1622
SOMEONE cocks his head the other way and so does his opponent.
KARATE_KID_DVS1623
The official lowers the flags between them. Master SOMEONE shouts, Finish him!
KARATE_KID_DVS1624
Rushing forward, SOMEONE kicks at him. SOMEONE turns away, then back-flips off his one good leg. His descending foot kicks SOMEONE, knocking him to the mat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1625
As the crowd cheers, SOMEONE lands balanced in the one-legged cobra pose.
KARATE_KID_DVS1626
Writhing before him, SOMEONE presses a hand over his left eye.
KARATE_KID_DVS1627
As SOMEONE maintains the graceful pose, Master SOMEONE stares.
KARATE_KID_DVS1628
The official lifts a blue flag high.
KARATE_KID_DVS1629
Snapping out of his meditative focus, the boy shifts his confused gaze, then looks to Mr. SOMEONE.
KARATE_KID_DVS1630
His beaming teacher mouths, You won.
KARATE_KID_DVS1631
The official lifts SOMEONE's hand aloft.
KARATE_KID_DVS1632
Mr. SOMEONE gives a proud nod, his eyes glistening.
KARATE_KID_DVS1633
SOMEONE and SOMEONE jump up and down.
KARATE_KID_DVS1634
As SOMEONE turns away with his head bowed, SOMEONE looks to the big screen. It replays his masterful kick in slow motion.
KARATE_KID_DVS1635
SOMEONE's face and name appear alone on the display, surrounded by Chinese text.
KARATE_KID_DVS1636
As the announcer approaches with the trophy, SOMEONE intercepts him.
KARATE_KID_DVS1637
With a nod, the man hands it over to the defeated boy.
KARATE_KID_DVS1638
SOMEONE carries it to his opponent,
KARATE_KID_DVS1639
gives a crooked smile, and offers it to him. As SOMEONE accepts it, they share a respectful smile.
KARATE_KID_DVS1640
SOMEONE leaves the platform, briefly facing Mr. SOMEONE, who smiles and nods to him. Master SOMEONE leads his students away and SOMEONE faces the crowd.
KARATE_KID_DVS1641
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive at the platform.
KARATE_KID_DVS1642
Grinning, the boy sets the trophy before his mother, then turns and locates his beaming teacher.
KARATE_KID_DVS1643
Standing, he hops along the mat, then limps down the steps.
KARATE_KID_DVS1644
SOMEONE arrives at Mr. SOMEONE's side and nods,
KARATE_KID_DVS1645
his face shining with sweat.
KARATE_KID_DVS1646
SOMEONE comes up behind them.
KARATE_KID_DVS1647
Mr. SOMEONE faces him.
KARATE_KID_DVS1648
The boy earnestly presses his fist to his open palm.
KARATE_KID_DVS1649
Lined up behind him, his fellow students sidestep into view, copy the gesture, and bow solemnly.
KARATE_KID_DVS1651
Standing apart, Master SOMEONE stares, slack-jawed.
KARATE_KID_DVS1652
Mr. SOMEONE respectfully returns the bow.
KARATE_KID_DVS1654
As the crowd cheers, SOMEONE heads off with his teacher.
KARATE_KID_DVS1655
They bump their fists, flaring their fingers as they part.
KARATE_KID_DVS1656
Mr. SOMEONE beams and puts an arm around SOMEONE.