More costumes.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS28
Katy Perry: Part of Me.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS29
SOMEONE and others rehearse or perform live on stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS30
From the stage she squirts glitter at an empty arena.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS32
Daytime outdoors. Young women cheer and wave. Several fans hold up a sign, SOMEONE our Teenage Dream is to meet you.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS33
A middle-aged woman wearing glasses smiles.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS34
A woman DJ addresses the cheering fans.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS35
SOMEONE does sit-ups in a black hoodie zipped up over her face.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS38
In fast motion fans fill the arena. Performers dress backstage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS40
Lights flash among the crowd of cheering men and women. In a hallway backstage, two costumed women practice dance moves.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS41
Another smiling performer wears a pink wig and a headband topped with a cupcake. In full makeup and wearing a pinwheel dress, SOMEONE applies deodorant to her own underarms. More performers clap and dance in the hallway.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS43
As SOMEONE extends one gloved hand, other performers stack their hands atop hers.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS44
SOMEONE's husband SOMEONE walks into the circle of performers.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS47
The platform ascends, raising her to the stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS48
Audience members cheer, scream, and wave.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS49
Camera bulbs flash. One woman holds up a sign with a downward arrow, SOMEONE Cats here.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS52
Written on one fan's palms, Love You.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS53
On stage SOMEONE points one finger skyward. Later four young teen girls
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS54
SOMEONE, still in costume, walks down a hallway backstage then sachets into a room where several fans wait to meet her.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS55
She waves.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS58
She poses for photographs and signs autographs.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS59
Bradford Cobb, manager.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS62
Fans mill around outside. SOMEONE walks backstage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS63
She pops a snow pea in her mouth.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS64
She approaches and hugs a tall balding man.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS65
SOMEONE Wujek, stylist.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS68
On stage SOMEONE wears a flouncy powder blue dress with short puffed sleeves.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS69
A male dancer lifts dark fabric up around SOMEONE, then lowers it revealing her in a red and white dress.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS72
Fans surround dark-haired SOMEONE.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS73
Lying in bed, SOMEONE swats SOMEONE with a pillow. SOMEONE swats her back with some clothing.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS81
As the glitter clears, her dress has changed from striped to one covered in flames.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS83
In the audience a young blond girl wears a headband with a flashing pink heart bauble.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS84
In fast motion night turns to day revealing the cityscape of Las Vegas, Nevada.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS85
In an arena, stagehands move and work on stage equipment.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS86
Elsewhere, the now light-haired SOMEONE steps into a suburban home and hugs her short white haired grandmother.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS87
The front door.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS88
SOMEONE wears a sleeveless dress.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS89
SOMEONE helps her grandmother into the pink jacket.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS90
Family photographs.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS91
SOMEONE and her grandmother exchange smiles.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS92
On television, 1987 Keith Hudson, SOMEONE's father.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS94
SOMEONE Hudson, SOMEONE's brother. In a video, young SOMEONE reads.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS96
In another video, young SOMEONE sings.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS97
She smiles and waves while she sings.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS99
Another video.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS102
A taped family interview.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS104
SOMEONE stares wide-eyed at the camera.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS106
Aka The Cobra Snake.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS107
Shannon Woodward, best friend, actress.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS108
SOMEONE Moretti, friend, international DJ.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS109
Day 43: City buildings line a body of water. Zurich, Switzerland. SOMEONE and others gather in a hotel room.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS110
SOMEONE gazes toward SOMEONE. Subtitles: It's fine, right. Smiling SOMEONE shrugs.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS111
Smiling wide, SOMEONE shakes her shoulders then falls sideways and sticks one leg in the air. Later SOMEONE steps into a car and kisses SOMEONE, who sits in the driver seat.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS112
Backstage SOMEONE and her performers join hands then raise their arms in unison.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS113
SOMEONE rides up on a platform to face her cheering audience.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS114
Tour cities include Milan, Berlin, London.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS115
A man interviews SOMEONE.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS116
In a montage, thousands of fans cheer. SOMEONE steps off an airplane, Performers raise their arms in their pre-show circle.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS117
SOMEONE rides upward on her stage platform. Standing on stage she points one gloved hand toward the audience. Elsewhere SOMEONE steps through a crowded room and hugs a shaggy haired man.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS118
Record producer Alanis Morissette. SOMEONE.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS120
A music video.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS124
In a studio, SOMEONE throws things.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS126
She knocks over a stool.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS127
Wearing a tight black shirt and pants, SOMEONE performs on stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS128
SOMEONE addresses a brunette woman.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS129
Male dancers attach rope lights to SOMEONE's arms and waist.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS130
On stage, SOMEONE and several men dance while holding ropes that join them together.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS131
2006, Hotel Cafe, Hollywood. SOMEONE plays guitar and sings.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS132
Cheering fans fill a large arena. Elsewhere, SOMEONE Flom, former CEO: Capital Records.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS134
She holds out a cat charm on her necklace.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS135
On stage, SOMEONE wears a sequined gown.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS136
Later on video.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS137
Myspace friends: 15,121.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS138
Facebook likes grows from 402 to 25,297.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS139
SOMEONE runs to her tour bus. Twitter followers: 2 million.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS142
Back on stage, SOMEONE wearing the sequined gown and a long feather boa slides on the floor between the legs of her guitarist.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS143
Smiling, SOMEONE's mother pats her own chest.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS144
Elsewhere, a dressing room door marked KP private. Inside.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS145
SOMEONE's mother smiles and shakes her head.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS146
Day 105. Nighttime. A tweet from SOMEONE is superimposed over her tour bus.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS147
Falling asleep, dreaming of cotton candy clouds.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS148
Hello, I am cotton candy SOMEONE.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS149
Daytime. Santa Barbara, California.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS150
SOMEONE points to large cloud props hanging over an outdoor stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS151
A nighttime concert.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS152
Male dancers surround SOMEONE as she performs.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS153
Lights flash on stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS155
At the Grammy Awards, SOMEONE and SOMEONE kiss.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS156
Wearing a wig cap over her hair, SOMEONE runs backstage then sits and talks with Bradford.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS157
Longhaired SOMEONE approaches.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS158
They hug and kiss.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS159
SOMEONE leaves.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS160
In the hallway, they hug again before SOMEONE walks on.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS161
Wearing her black wig now, SOMEONE approaches two young boys.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS162
SOMEONE steps into a reception room, then greets several visitors as they enter the room.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS163
She crouches in front of one boy.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS164
The boy wears a white tracheotomy tube neckband. He and SOMEONE high five.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS166
SOMEONE signs an autograph.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS168
SOMEONE poses for a photograph with the boy, then hugs him.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS170
Elsewhere, SOMEONE addresses five children.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS171
A teen boy's jaw drops.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS172
Elsewhere, another teen boy hugs SOMEONE.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS173
SOMEONE's dancers perform on stage. A man in a pale purple cat costume dances. Wearing a costume resembling a one-piece bathing suit with blue, red and yellow balls attached to it, SOMEONE dances across the stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS175
SOMEONE hugs the tall furry cat and waves to the audience and dances. Elsewhere teens in costumes stand outside.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS177
SOMEONE approaches waiting fans.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS179
A blond girl with large dark rimmed glasses runs off.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS184
Dozens of people, including the Banana Boy and the man in a leotard climb on to the stage and dance.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS186
Dots of flashing lights sparkle throughout the arena's huge audience.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS187
In her dressing room, SOMEONE bites into a slice of pizza.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS188
A statue of a man on horseback stands amidst several city buildings.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS189
Day 141. A hallway leads to a large arena. A spotlight shines. A person jogs around a nearly empty arena.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS190
On the arena floor, a blond woman wearing a hooded jacket watches a man in a burgundy tank top dance then imitates his moves.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS191
Backstage, SOMEONE's personal trainer stretches SOMEONE's left leg skyward as she lies on her back.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS192
The trainer pushes on SOMEONE's left leg then presses down on her spread knees.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS193
SOMEONE bends over in laughter. On a laptop screen fart soundboard.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS194
SOMEONE laughs again.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS195
Wearing a ball cap, SOMEONE works out on an elliptical trainer. White haired SOMEONE Jensen approaches her.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS196
The man walks away. Facing each other, SOMEONE and her trainer squat as they hold arms straight out in front.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS197
Holding dumb bells, SOMEONE performs squats.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS198
Later, she and her trainer rest on their forearms as they hold plank positions.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS199
SOMEONE jumps rope.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS200
She drops the jump rope then walks out of the room. Elsewhere SOMEONE strolls down a hallway.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS202
SOMEONE dances. A television reporter.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS204
The American Music Awards.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS205
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a triangular award. Elsewhere, Lady Gaga wearing a huge hat obscuring her face high fives SOMEONE.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS208
SOMEONE dances with SOMEONE.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS210
Wearing large eyeglasses and orthodontic headgear SOMEONE pumps her fist.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS212
Tour cities include Vienna, Dublin, Sidney.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS214
SOMEONE wearing a tiara holds his palms together and bows.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS215
Tampa, Boston.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS216
Newark, Pittsburgh, Philadelphia, Toronto, Cleveland.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS218
SOMEONE rides various waterslides.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS219
Ropes lift SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and Shannon on a huge harness into the air. The women dangle horizontally.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS220
The ropes zip back and forth. People on the ground hold their arms above their heads as they gaze skyward.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS222
The three young women soar back toward the ground.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS223
Later they step away from the ride. SOMEONE walks slowly.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS224
SOMEONE gazes downward. SOMEONE's eyes widen.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS225
In Raleigh, North Carolina, people file toward an arena. Two young women sing.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS227
Later SOMEONE wearing glasses and headgear makes two peace signs with her hands.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS228
SOMEONE runs down a hallway.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS229
SOMEONE rises on a platform. A huge video image of her looms on the screen above the stage. She descends a set of steps, then joins the colorfully dressed dancers.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS232
SOMEONE sits atop a dancer's shoulders.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS233
Tokyo, Japan, nighttime.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS234
Walking on a crowded street, SOMEONE waves to fans.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS238
Later, she and SOMEONE sit in a restaurant.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS240
Later, a woman gives SOMEONE a manicure.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS241
Another tweet, Just hanging at the Cat Cafe in Tokyo with my besties.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS242
SOMEONE holds out her hand.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS243
SOMEONE smiles.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS245
One cat bats a toy mouse, another cat leaps over SOMEONE's lap.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS246
A black and white cat lies in a glass enclosure.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS247
Elsewhere a young woman sings,
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS248
as another young woman bobs her head.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS249
SOMEONE holds up an I Love Japan t-shirt. Fans laugh as they enter the arena.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS250
A person holds up a drawing of SOMEONE, California Girls. Four men dressed like SOMEONE. Later SOMEONE sings on stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS252
SOMEONE hugs a young girl who wipes away tears.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS253
Dancers twirl in midair high above the stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS254
Colored lights flash on stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS255
Day 214. On a private plane, SOMEONE wearing sunglasses glances out a window.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS256
Later she sleeps with her head against a thick pillow.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS259
Bradford closes a laptop.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS260
SOMEONE Jensen dons eyeglasses.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS261
Bradford looks up.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS264
Holding a microphone SOMEONE leans against the wall.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS265
Later she steps into an SUV. Palm trees stream past.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS266
A plane flies. A traffic light changes from red to green.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS267
Lying in a large bed, SOMEONE covers herself.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS268
On TV SOMEONE DeGeneres interviews SOMEONE.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS269
she checks her makeup.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS270
Day 287. A tall brick building stands beneath hazy skies.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS271
Indoors a woman styles SOMEONE's pink hair.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS272
9:00 am. Incoming text from SOMEONE.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS273
Someone hands SOMEONE a cellphone.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS274
She peers at the screen.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS275
SOMEONE hands the phone back.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS276
As the stylist works, SOMEONE gazes into a mirror.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS277
SOMEONE picks up her cellphone.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS278
SOMEONE shrugs.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS279
Peering at the phone, SOMEONE holds her hand to her head.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS280
Elsewhere, a mass of people moves through a parking lot.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS281
Hartford, Connecticut.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS282
Backstage, SOMEONE lies curled on her side on a massage table.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS283
SOMEONE sits up.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS284
She stands then walks out of the room.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS285
Wearing a hat resembling a red cherry , SOMEONE hugs a young female fan.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS286
Performing on stage, SOMEONE wears a long striped dress as she sits on a dangling swing.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS287
Shimmering bubbles float around her.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS288
The swing rises high above the stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS289
As the swing lowers, a sinking bubble pops against the stage floor.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS290
Daytime. Teenage fans trot into an outdoor arena. Sao Paulo, Brazil.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS291
Cheering people standing behind a security barricade wave their arms.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS292
Lying in a makeup chair backstage SOMEONE sobs.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS293
Nearby SOMEONE whispers to Bradford, She never cries.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS294
Wearing sunglasses, SOMEONE tugs on her own fingers.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS295
SOMEONE pulls off one of SOMEONE's boots.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS296
SOMEONE holds out her hands. Subtitle: Let me see that. Lying back in her chair, SOMEONE sobs again.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS297
SOMEONE takes a necklace out of a clear plastic bag and holds it up.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS298
SOMEONE puts on the necklace then lies motionless.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS299
Bradford kneels beside her.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS301
You have a lot on your mind right now.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS302
Outside fans pack the concert grounds.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS303
A young man in the crowd smiles as he pumps one fist in the air.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS304
A sound technician wearing headphones gazes at the audience.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS305
Backstage a blond dancer walks through the dressing room.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS307
SOMEONE lies in her makeup chair as Bradford and SOMEONE stare at her.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS308
Bradford stands and moves aside as SOMEONE begins applying SOMEONE's makeup.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS309
A woman pulls a sheer wig cap over SOMEONE's scalp.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS310
SOMEONE stands in front of SOMEONE and smiles at her, as she gets ready.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS311
SOMEONE and her entourage head toward the stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS312
As fans cheer the performers stack their hands in a pile.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS313
SOMEONE hangs her head and sobs.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS314
Bradford leads SOMEONE away by the hand.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS315
A male performer dressed in a sequined costume stands with his hands over his mouth.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS317
SOMEONE clutches a microphone as she takes her position on the platform under the stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS318
Her chest heaves as she swallows big gulps of air.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS319
She glances down at the pair of pinwheels spinning on the front of her costume.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS320
Smiling, she holds the microphone up like a torch as the platform raises her on to the stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS321
In the crowd, fans hold up signs or wave their arms.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS322
Fans in the audience, some with tears shining in their eyes, applaud wildly.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS323
The crowd chants, SOMEONE, a ti amo.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS324
SOMEONE, we love you.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS325
Smiling at her audience, SOMEONE raises one fist in the air, choking back tears. She blows a kiss to the crowd.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS326
Wearing a headset microphone SOMEONE strums an acoustic guitar.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS327
A TV news reporter.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS328
Tweets and text messages from supportive fans hover over a city skyline at night.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS329
@Katy Perry, I love you, you are the best. You are a firework, please don't be sad.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS330
@Katy Perry, Your SOMEONE Cats are there for you. We love you, SOMEONE.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS333
SOMEONE smiles.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS334
Furrowing her brow she places one hand over her face then brushes back her hair and blinks away tears.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS335
She wipes her eyes with a tissue.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS336
In rehearsa,l SOMEONE stands at a microphone.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS337
Day 356. Music Cares Charity Concert rehearsal.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS338
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk into a bridal shop.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS339
SOMEONE hugs her sister. SOMEONE's wedding dress fitting.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS340
SOMEONE looks through dresses on hangers.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS341
Wearing her wedding gown, SOMEONE gazes at herself in a mirror.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS342
SOMEONE stands aside and gazes at her sister then blinks and stares downward.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS343
SOMEONE smiles as a man pins a white veil to the back of her hair.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS344
Sitting in the shop, SOMEONE dabs away a tear.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS353
In concert colored lights pulsate on SOMEONE's costume as she stands on stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS354
One performer does backflips on stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS355
Sitting nearby, SOMEONE's grandmother smiles wide.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS357
SOMEONE's smiling mother claps along with the music. Fireworks blaze on stage.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS358
Rockets shoot upward.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS359
Dancers pose around SOMEONE as she stands center stage with one arm raised straight up.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS360
Fountains of sparking fireworks shoot up behind them.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS361
With her eyes closed, SOMEONE mouths the words, Thank you, God.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS362
Thank you, God.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS363
The stage curtain falls.
KATY_PERRY_PART_OF_ME_DVS364
Spotlights shine over a sea of cheering fans.