At the guys house
KNOCKED_UP_DVS6
SOMEONE stares blankly.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS7
Executive's office.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS8
He cups his flexed hands toward his chest.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS9
SOMEONE points to his head.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS10
Later they walk past a nightclub.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS11
Smile at each other.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS13
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE wearily.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS14
Daytime. The pool sparkles outside the guesthouse.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS15
Now a pale chubby butt lies naked under tangled sheets.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS16
SOMEONE, standing and dressed, wrinkles her brow at SOMEONE's butt. She bounces the mattress with her foot.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS17
She bounces it harder.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS18
She extends her foot and touches SOMEONE's side. He jerks up and glances around.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS19
Stares at his bare behind.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS21
SOMEONE cocks her head.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS22
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE step out of the guesthouse.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS23
SOMEONE in a well-cut suit. In front of the house they walk across the lawn as SOMEONE carries the baby toward them.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS24
They shake hands.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS25
SOMEONE faces the baby.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS26
Now in a dinner, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE in a booth.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS27
SOMEONE shakes his head gazing off.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS28
SOMEONE frowns.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS29
SOMEONE sits back down.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS30
Eight weeks later.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS31
SOMEONE and an editor watch James on a computer monitor.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS32
She swallows hard.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS33
SOMEONE touches her throat and heaves forward. She claps a hand over her mouth.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS34
Raising his hands overhead.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS35
SOMEONE slowly sits back up.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS36
She wipes her mouth.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS37
She takes another swipe at her mouth, then freezes
KNOCKED_UP_DVS38
She leans back.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS39
They sit by the pool.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS40
SOMEONE gazes off.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS41
A web page reads, Coming Soon.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS42
The screen shows the guys email address.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS43
An email pops up.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS44
SOMEONE wrinkles her nose. Now in their backyard the guys smoke.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS45
Now SOMEONE paces as she dials the phone. Back with the guys.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS46
SOMEONE raises both arms.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS47
SOMEONE forces a smile.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS48
He leans back in his chair.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS49
Now in an exam room, a smiling doctor enters.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS50
SOMEONE's eyes shift.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS51
Puts her feet in the stir-ups and the doctor
KNOCKED_UP_DVS52
covers her legs with a blanket. SOMEONE glances around uncomfortably.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS53
The blanket.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS54
SOMEONE gazes at the ceiling. The doctor squeezes gel onto the end of a wand.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS55
Smiles indulgently as the doctor forces a smile and inserts the wand. SOMEONE shifts. An image appears on a monitor.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS56
She is sobbing face.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS57
Pats SOMEONE's back.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS58
Now at SOMEONE's place.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS59
SOMEONE leans forward.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS60
SOMEONE gets up.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS61
Now at home and wearing pajamas SOMEONE makes a phone call.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS62
Her eyes glisten tearfully.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS63
Now SOMEONE pulls into the driveway of the rental house.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS64
SOMEONE gestures to his chubby friend.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS65
His amiable smile fades as he eyes her body.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS66
They gaze at her through blurry eyes.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS67
As SOMEONE leaves the room SOMEONE sits. SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE, all stare at the TV.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS68
SOMEONE follows their gaze to a clip from Wild Things. Neve Campbell kisses a topless Denise Richards in a swimming pool. SOMEONE shrugs.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS69
On screen, SOMEONE removes SOMEONE's shirt.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS70
Little hat and holds a tiny outfit.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS71
SOMEONE walk outside they tentatively hold hands. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand in their bathroom facing opposite directions. Brushing his teeth he turns to face her.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS72
She dabs under her eyes with her fingertips.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS73
Shifts his stunned gaze.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS74
Now in the guesthouse SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a tender passionate kiss. He gazes into her eyes.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS75
SOMEONE pulls away.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS76
SOMEONE sits on the bed and pulls SOMEONE down beside her.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS77
SOMEONE gives a slow thoughtful nod.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS78
Face each other sharing a warm smile. They lean close and enjoy a tender kiss. Pulling away slightly.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS79
Takes a long sip of coffee. The toddler beams at SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS80
He lifts his brow and smiles.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS81
Now in the backyard, SOMEONE plays with the girls.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS83
Her sister forces a smile.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS85
Now outside the rental house, SOMEONE and SOMEONE play Ping-Pong while the others watch.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS87
Now under an ultrasound video words appear. Sixteen weeks.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS88
A wardrobe lady fits SOMEONE with a belt.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS89
A female executive passes by.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS90
SOMEONE gives a defensive shrug
KNOCKED_UP_DVS91
A Baby Bjorn Baby Sling box shows a couple beaming at each other. SOMEONE winces at the picture then shows it to SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS92
They join SOMEONE at a crib. He eyes the price tag.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS93
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE exit the store.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS94
Now at Record Surplus record store.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS95
He grins broadly.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS96
Now a website shows a grinning cartoon logo.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS97
He remains behind and sits facing SOMEONE who thoughtfully tokes on a joint.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS98
Now in the guesthouse.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS99
SOMEONE's eyes glisten.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS100
SOMEONE's bed.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS101
In SOMEONE's car.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS102
Now under an ultrasound video.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS103
SOMEONE drains his glass and pounds the table.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS104
Now in his bedroom SOMEONE lies on top of SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS105
Now she lies sideways with her back.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS106
Later SOMEONE sits in the living room.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS107
A woman covers her bare breast.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS108
SOMEONE shakes his hand exposing...
KNOCKED_UP_DVS109
SOMEONE shrugs at the passing cruiser.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS110
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit by the open cabinet among piles of stuff. She touches an overturned marijuana plant and a large branch breaks off in her hand. Dropping it, she finds a bank statement with SOMEONE's name on it.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS111
It reads $117.13.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS113
SOMEONE notices a shopping bag protruding from the cabinet.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS115
She finds Three baby books. SOMEONE eyes the covers one by one.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS117
With her mouth agape she drops the books
KNOCKED_UP_DVS118
into the bag, then stares off with a pensive expression.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS119
Beneath an ultrasound showing a fetus.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS120
SOMEONE answers the phone.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS121
As SOMEONE leaves, SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS122
To a large suburban house.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS123
Gently shuts the door.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS125
Comes downstairs.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS126
SOMEONE creeps toward the back of the house.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS127
With a furrowed brow, SOMEONE turns and walks out.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS128
She wipes a tear and heads off.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS129
SOMEONE and SOMEONE wait by the car.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS130
SOMEONE squints at her then unbuckles his seat belt.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS132
SOMEONE's teeth clench.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS133
Leaves with his middle finger raised.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS134
SOMEONE strains to regain her composure.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS135
Now at Del's Saloon.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS136
SOMEONE shakes his head.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS137
The guesthouse, SOMEONE reclines and watches a program.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS138
Opens the front door and stares through red-rimmed eyes.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS139
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS140
SOMEONE shuts the door on him. Nighttime.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS141
SOMEONE watches nervously.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS143
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on the curb.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS144
Now a hotel TV.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS145
SOMEONE sits on a bed.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS146
Moves to a shorter chair.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS147
He curls up in a cushioned chair.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS148
SOMEONE jams his fist in his mouth.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS150
Sadie answers in a princess outfit.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS151
She nods to herself then cracks up.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS152
SOMEONE a gift.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS153
Now standing away from the party SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS154
She glances over her shoulder.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS155
SOMEONE holds a large castle cake with ice cream cone turrets.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS156
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE stares after him with a wounded gaze. Then walks out to the backyard.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS157
SOMEONE clenches his jaw.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS158
Sadie runs downstairs.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS159
Denise Richards grabs Neve Campbell's arm. On the couch SOMEONE shakes her head at the screen.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS160
She pauses thoughtfully and puts a hand on her belly.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS161
SOMEONE reads What to Expect When You're Expecting.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS162
He picks up.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS163
In her bedroom SOMEONE struggles to pack a suitcase without bending over.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS165
He enters the main house.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS166
He heads upstairs and strides down the hall.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS167
SOMEONE's bed stands empty. He steps toward the bathroom. SOMEONE lounges in the tub covered in bubbles.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS168
She lets her hands drift downward.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS169
He paces in the hall.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS170
SOMEONE pokes his head into the bathroom.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS171
Hangs up and gazes off. Now he returns to the bathroom and sits on the edge of the tub.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS172
SOMEONE smiles.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS173
SOMEONE stares.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS174
The tense doctor enters.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS175
In the waiting room SOMEONE fidgets.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS176
Meanwhile, SOMEONE rubs SOMEONE's back.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS177
Samuel strides in.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS178
Between her legs and another on her belly.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS179
In the hall, SOMEONE clutches his hand while talking.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS181
SOMEONE lifts her head off the pillow as Dr. SOMEONE and SOMEONE return to her beside.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS182
As Dr. SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS183
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in.. wheelchair.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS184
He lowers his head to one side and taps his fingers on the armrest.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS185
A passing doctor shakes his head at them.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS186
In the hall SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS187
As SOMEONE walks away, SOMEONE stares after him. Her mouth agape.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS188
Now she mopes over to the waiting room and plops down beside SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS189
Watching his wife, SOMEONE smirks.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS190
In the delivery room.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS191
He returns to the others.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS192
Shakes his head and sits down.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS193
SOMEONE winks.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS194
SOMEONE's eye Shift between his wife and SOMEONE.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS195
In a wheelchair.
KNOCKED_UP_DVS196
On car seat, mother watches her baby. SOMEONE drives.