SOMEONE storms off.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS10
Three years later, at a presentation
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS11
He cups his ear.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS12
SOMEONE stands before a class of 12
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS13
She sets a rock on his lab table.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS14
She holds a crystal on her necklace.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS15
She walks off and SOMEONE fixes his gaze on the fossil.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS16
He puts down a stack of papers, and picks up the prehistoric rock, which shows a familiar indentation.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS17
The scientist takes a flip-top lighter from his pocket and eyes the inscription: Big Cat.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS18
He flips open the top and places it in the indentation, a perfect fit.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS19
SOMEONE breathes in deeply.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS20
Now outside the La Brea tar pits.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS21
Inside, SOMEONE lies on the floor. SOMEONE enters his office.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS24
finds a makeshift electronic device on his desk.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS25
He grabs a French fry.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS26
near a fun house with a devil's open mouth.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS27
by the store.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS28
SOMEONE eyed the scruffy clerk.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS29
He removes the tarp, revealing a model of a golden building with two pointed towers.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS30
A man with a rifle enters.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS31
The slack-jawed man points at the clerk.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS32
At the cave entrance, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on a raft with the store clerk.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS33
SOMEONE glares.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS34
store clerk tosses trash out of the way.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS35
the beat-up raft down a narrow canal. As they enter the dim cave, he turns on a string of Christmas lights overhead.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS36
SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS37
The clerk furrows his brow and glances around.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS38
He studies a hand-held meter.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS39
He turns on the amplifier.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS41
Rocks fall from the ceiling.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS42
Into a swirl of white water, they topple out of the raft and disappear into a bright blue light. Back in the cave, the Christmas lights sway over the peaceful canal. A fake alien arm floats on the glassy water at the mouth of the cave. Fade to black.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS43
Bright light fills our view, then fades to pale desert sand. SOMEONE lies with his headphones askew and his lips parted. An orange life jacket from the raft still sits on his shoulders. He opens his eyes and blinks.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS44
SOMEONE lifts his head.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS45
SOMEONE peers through a small window in a homey red door. Slowly opening it, she looks around and gapes. Splintered wood of a destroyed freestanding wall surrounds the door. Two large wooden oars rest at an angle on the sand.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS46
SOMEONE looks at three daytime moons in the sky.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS47
SOMEONE stands by a massive Viking ship with a crashed plane in its hull.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS48
SOMEONE throws down his life jacket.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS49
As SOMEONE sprints away, the video camera blips off. At a dune, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE plop on their stomachs and peer down at three creatures.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS50
SOMEONE fidgets.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS51
looks to SOMEONE at the top of the dune. SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive beside her.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS52
SOMEONE holds out a lighter.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS54
A furry face peeks out from behind a stone block. SOMEONE tilts her head curiously. The time travelers draw closer to the block etched with arrow-shaped hieroglyphics. As it spots them, the primate hides itself behind the block.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS55
SOMEONE huddles against the stone as SOMEONE bends down.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS56
SOMEONE stares suspiciously.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS57
SOMEONE holds out her hand. The primate creeps closer.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS58
She touches her chest.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS59
The primate imitates her by resting a hand on SOMEONE's breast.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS60
She moves the primate's hand and touches his knee.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS61
SOMEONE cups SOMEONE's breast.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS62
SOMEONE's hand away. SOMEONE pats her shoulder.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS63
SOMEONE reaches for SOMEONE.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS64
SOMEONE clings to SOMEONE's leg, his hand on her breast
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS65
then pounds her chest.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS66
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE, then rushes over.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS67
SOMEONE humps SOMEONE's leg.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS68
SOMEONE's waist. The four dangle, side by side, high above the ground.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS69
They glance worriedly over their shoulders.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS70
SOMEONE gapes at the bones below. A shiny space suit lies amid the rubble.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS71
They swing back and forth, picking up momentum.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS72
SOMEONE's fingers almost touch the
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS73
lips tremble. It angrily withdraws its head from the hole.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS74
T-rex stomps off, its tail swishing behind it. SOMEONE and SOMEONE peer after it.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS75
SOMEONE comes up behind them.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS76
He lifts his trembling chin.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS77
SOMEONE turns into the cave, and takes in its ridged high-rising walls.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS78
He drops to one knee.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS79
The group cautiously follows the music, moving deeper into the cave.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS80
Three crescent moons hover in the dark sky above a warm glow from the setting sun. Inside the cave,
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS81
continues to turn on the phonograph. SOMEONE rips her pant legs into shorts. SOMEONE touches SOMEONE's bare legs.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS82
SOMEONE slaps his hand away. He touches her
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS83
SOMEONE takes a piece of SOMEONE's pants over to a blanket, where he sits and flails around.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS84
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS85
She squats in front of him.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS87
SOMEONE smiles and walks away.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS88
SOMEONE glares as SOMEONE squats down.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS89
spots SOMEONE carrying a crate.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS91
Now, SOMEONE creeps to the mouth of the cave, clutching a set of bicycle handlebars. Beside him, SOMEONE wears a helmet and carries a shield, while SOMEONE wields a gardening hoe. SOMEONE's gaze falls on a large round object wrapped in leaves.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS92
With wide eyes, he crouches down in front of the mysterious package. He grits his teeth as he peels back a waxy leaf.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS93
SOMEONE lifts an object the size of a large beach ball.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS94
From across the lush valley,
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS95
SOMEONE turns off the camera as SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS96
SOMEONE breaks open a melon-like fruit.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS97
The spiders crawl out of the fruit and up SOMEONE.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS98
He eats it, then smiles.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS99
SOMEONE and SOMEONE race outside and she hands him binoculars. Through the lenses, he sees a flash of light receding into the jungle.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS101
They chase SOMEONE.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS102
In the jungle, SOMEONE jogs to a stop.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS103
He faces a crystal pylon.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS104
He ducks a thrown rock, which smashes into a statue.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS105
SOMEONE points fearfully at a statue. The others enter the plaza ruins.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS106
Clawed reptilian feet step out from a row of niches along a rock wall.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS107
They see hundreds of eagle-sized bats.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS108
They face the pylon.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS109
He places both palms on the transparent structure.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS110
He puts his hands on it.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS111
Nearby graffiti reads, "Beware of Sleestak."
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS112
SOMEONE grips SOMEONE's chin and turns his head to look at dozens of lizard-like creatures emerging from niches in the plaza wall.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS113
Survivors back away from them.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS114
SOMEONE manipulates her hand until the buckle reflects a beam of sunlight. He aims the ray at the eye of a statue and it bounces among the reflect
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS115
They linger outside.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS116
They're standing in a vast limbo.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS117
from SOMEONE's vision, lies prone.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS118
He stands at a table of crystals.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS120
He uses a laser pointer.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS121
He fills a mini hot air balloon made out of a blowfish.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS122
SOMEONE folds his arms with a smirk. SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS123
He raises the jug.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS124
SOMEONE winces queasily and SOMEONE clutches a hand to her mouth.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS125
He holds out the jug. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS126
He wipes his eyes and blinks.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS127
He rubs his eyes.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS128
SOMEONE sits on a rock, pointing.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS129
Now, SOMEONE leads the humans out of the jungle and into a vast desert.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS130
SOMEONE points. Our view pulls back through the broken window of a British phone booth. Beyond it, the Golden Gate bridge juts from
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS131
A Union 76 Ball revolve
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS132
vendor peers through the window.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS133
rush past SOMEONE and the scientist heading
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS134
Two Allosaurus sniff the air, then face the humans.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS135
The Allosaurus moves on. Grumpy plunges his head in. From a distance, SOMEONE video-records the T-Rex emerging from
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS136
SOMEONE races through a row of tollbooths.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS137
They Bounce on the limo's roof.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS138
He scampers off, kicking a can.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS139
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hide near a medieval catapult.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS140
He falls over, frozen stiff.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS141
SOMEONE grins hopefully.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS142
Pterodactyl swoops down and grabs it, taking the amplifier with it. SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE stare helplessly as the predator flies away with the device.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS143
Hanging his head, the scientist sulks off. SOMEONE gazes after him worriedly. Later, she, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE trek through the dumping ground. They find SOMEONE reclining listlessly in the back of an old half-buried Cadillac convertible.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS144
He robotically sticks his hand halfway down his pants.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS145
away, SOMEONE storms off through the dumping ground. SOMEONE steps closer to SOMEONE and shrugs his brow.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS146
The scientist scratches his head.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS147
They leave SOMEONE alone. Nighttime. In the jungle, SOMEONE writes in her journal by a campfire. Bugs the size of
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS148
hummingbirds flutter around her and she waves them away. SOMEONE crosses to SOMEONE, who sits forlornly on his own.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS149
SOMEONE and SOMEONE turn and SOMEONE looks up from her journal. In tree-dappled moonlight, SOMEONE strolls into view, strumming a
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS151
scientist plants his feet, facing his companions with a sober expression.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS154
the bug and splattering blood everywhere. He looks up, his face ashen and his chest heaving.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS155
SOMEONE blinks groggily, then leans his head back.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS156
Daytime. Sunbeams filter through the trees. SOMEONE sleeps curled up by SOMEONE, his hand on her breast. SOMEONE sleeps nearby. A few feet away, SOMEONE stands up
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS157
He twists from the waist, exposing a basketball-sized welt on his shoulder blade.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS158
He puts his shirt on.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS159
As they climb, SOMEONE lags far behind. Now they near the top. The pterodactyl swoops overhead.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS160
SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE, who grins and gives an encouraging nod. He points up and they climb to the top.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS161
He turns to find his primitive friend feigning
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS162
He drops his backpack.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS163
SOMEONE touches his shoulder and he pauses.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS164
They share a tender look.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS165
He removes his khaki shirt, leaving his T-shirt on.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS166
The eggs tremble atop their perches. SOMEONE fearfully turns and one of the eggshells cracks. Several more begin to hatch as he watches helplessly.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS167
On the other side, SOMEONE edges back and SOMEONE swallows hard.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS168
beak hooks through one of the eggshells as a baby pterodactyl
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS169
Several more follow suit.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS170
He smiles modestly. SOMEONE turns, finding all the hatchlings asleep behind him.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS171
Now, SOMEONE flies through the air, waving his arms. SOMEONE follows, belly down. SOMEONE
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS172
and hands one to SOMEONE and another to SOMEONE.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS173
Both men drink the fruit's nectar.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS174
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a look of concern.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS175
Later in the pool, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE with bloodshot eyes.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS176
As SOMEONE's stoned gaze remain
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS177
SOMEONE, he shifts his jaw. SOMEONE pops up again.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS178
By the table, SOMEONE stands with the Tachyon Amplifier strapped over her chest. She turns it on.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS179
She takes a few steps away from the pool.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS180
across the desert, she grins.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS181
over the pristine white sand, SOMEONE carries the device about 100 yards from the pool.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS182
She stops, frowning. Before her, a triangle rises from the ground. From a distance, the crystalline pylon almost disappears against the cloudy sky.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS183
SOMEONE approaches it, her hand still on the Tachyon Amplifier. Now, clumps of vines hang from the rough-hewn walls of the cavern. Entering,
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS184
two massive crystals jutting out at opposite angles, and each emitting a bluish glow. Meanwhile, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE lie on their backs on a dune.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS185
On the distant horizon, a huge creature crawls toward them. SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE all turn their heads in unison. It's a giant crab, snapping two huge claws.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS186
The guys lift their heads, fixated on the creature. The crab draws closer.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS187
Now as the sun sets, the three feast on the giant crab.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS188
SOMEONE squeezes a humongous lemon wedge over SOMEONE's piece, then adds some juice to his own.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS189
SOMEONE high fives SOMEONE.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS190
From a distance, we see SOMEONE and SOMEONE
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS191
Meanwhile, SOMEONE steps across the spongy cavern floor. A dozen more crystals jut from the walls. She notices a group of softball-sized eggs on a brown steaming mound.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS192
She pulls one of the eggs from the mound and clear goo drips from its bottom.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS193
As she examines the egg, the SOMEONE's hologram pops up behind her.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS194
The SOMEONE collapses.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS197
SOMEONE approaches his slain body.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS198
Now, the tree of the narcotic fruit lies bare. Poolside, the three pals sleep, wearing matching towels around their waists.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS199
SOMEONE awakes.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS200
Inside the cavern, SOMEONE pops up, shifting his eyes side to side. He attempts to move stealthily amid the crystals.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS201
Looking back, he flashes a complex set of hand signals. At the mouth of the cave, SOMEONE shrugs.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS202
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE past the crystals.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS203
they hide behind a wall. Beyond an opening into another chamber, two SOMEONE walks.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS204
As two SOMEONE hold each other, their frog-like throats expand.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS205
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look on.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS206
Their voyeuristic expressions sour and two Sleestak skins land at their feet.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS207
SOMEONE covers his mouth. SOMEONE grimaces and they share a look.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS209
She wraps her arms around his neck and gives him a passionate kiss.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS210
SOMEONE stops kissing her.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS212
they fall in line.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS213
SOMEONE notices the dot of his laser pointer on his chest. It works its way up to his forehead.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS214
He steps out to face Grumpy.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS215
He picks up a rock and throws it at her.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS216
With a hurt gaze, SOMEONE walks down the steps, past Grumpy.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS217
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a bag.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS218
He gives him a man hug.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS219
SOMEONE leaves past Grumpy.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS220
He hurries across the platform and
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS221
tosses aside the bag of fireworks. SOMEONE
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS223
behind a rock, SOMEONE watches the battle.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS224
digs in the bag.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS225
a Roman candle, he takes out his lighter.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS226
SOMEONE looks on.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS227
SOMEONE rocket him. He ducks.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS228
out of the plaza.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS229
SOMEONE leans wearily against a rock and faces SOMEONE.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS231
He guards the humans.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS233
SOMEONE sniffs at SOMEONE's stained clothes.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS234
The Tyrannosaur faces SOMEONE.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS235
SOMEONE holds out his fist. Grumpy steps forward and taps it with
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS242
SOMEONE stares at the tiny fragments of the broken crystal. He runs to SOMEONE and rips off her necklace.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS243
As they race toward the vortex,
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS244
SOMEONE purses his lips.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS245
Holding hands, they jog toward the image of Earth in the vortex.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS246
SOMEONE smiles and waves. SOMEONE and SOMEONE jump through the vortex, which vanish
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS247
beside the trailer. Light flashes from the fun house.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS248
The two scientists face each other, their jaws hanging slack.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS249
They share a tight embrace. SOMEONE pulls away, cupping SOMEONE's head in her hand.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS250
Her hazel eyes shine as she beams up at him.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS251
SOMEONE knits his brow and shakes his head. SOMEONE's smile grows forced and she drops her gaze. Wincing, the scientist leans his head back, then puts a finger beneath her chin, and guides her face upward. He leans in for a kiss.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS252
They notice SOMEONE outside.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS253
Back in the Land of the Lost.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS254
SOMEONE hops on SOMEONE for a piggyback.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS255
SOMEONE carries the primate to the top of a dune. A vast Pakuni village sprawls in the lush valley below.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS256
nearly nude Pakuni women race up the dune.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS257
The women fawn over SOMEONE.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS258
He notices a woman standing behind
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS259
Today Show logo rotates.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS260
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a thick book. The host eyes it irritably.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS261
black. A title appears, word by word: Land of the Lost.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS263
As the overhead lights dim, an assistant picks up the egg.
LAND_OF_THE_LOST_DVS264
The TV crew shuts off the lights and heads out of the studio.