He unfastens his brace.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS11
In apparel with a trainee.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS12
It shows all team of executives.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS13
He points to a crown on his mug.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS14
SOMEONE glances from his white-mustached boss to a trio of younger executives.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS15
The senior executive meets his gaze.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS16
Man shows a ring.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS17
Unfazed executive grins.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS18
SOMEONE stares.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS19
The beefy executive callously picks pizza out of his teeth.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS20
Larry’s eyes glisten in a helpless stare.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS21
The brown-faced executive spreads his hands. SOMEONE takes a breath
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS22
to speak then swallows and looks away. Now traffic lines up behind SOMEONE as he drives his SUV with a stunned gaze.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS23
A view with the left break light shows the SUV gliding into the driveway of a modest home with a well-manicured front lawn. Nighttime. A doorway on the opposite end of the cluttered room frames SOMEONE as he sits on the edge of his bed. Later he lies awake on his stomach, with one-half of his face against a pillow. Now on his back, he presses his hands to his face.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS24
An open doorway shows a glimpse of SOMEONE shoveling through the house. In an adjacent room a globe lamp glows softly. Standing in a closet of mostly empty hangers, SOMEONE hangs up his red U-Mart polo shirt. He stares at it for a moment, then slides the closet door shut.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS25
Daytime. A series of phone calls.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS26
SOMEONE flips his cellphone shut and rests this chin in his hand. Now at a bathroom sink he turns on the cold-water tap and bends over to splash his face. Later, he gazes worriedly into the mirror, as he blots his skin with a towel. Now he holds a pair of slacks on an ironing board.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS27
Now he sits across from a banker with blond, feathered hair.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS28
SOMEONE's chest heaves.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS29
Now at home, SOMEONE hauls lawn chairs and a bag of golf clubs out to his front lawn.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS30
SOMEONE puffs a pipe.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS31
SOMEONE follows his neighbor into a garage filled with secondhand goods.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS32
He hands SOMEONE a booklet.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS33
Back in the present.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS34
Entrance reads East Valley Community.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS35
He looks at map and checks it, then.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS37
Now at a registration desk he looks over a course book.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS38
A silver haired man with a bowtie and a toothy smile approaches him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS39
He points at the course book.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS40
He gives a suggestive wink.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS41
Camera bulb flashes and a student ID appears, featuring a photo of a puzzled-looking SOMEONE. Now at a gas station SOMEONE inspects the ID.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS42
Gas tank pocketing his wallet, he eyes the pump’s display. As his gas cost ticks up past $60
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS43
He fills his small tank.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS44
SOMEONE’s total passes $70.00.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS45
The scooter’s total is less than four.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS46
The scooter’s meek.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS47
He wrenches the gas nozzle from his tank.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS48
SOMEONE approaches a scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS49
SOMEONE smiles.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS50
Now SOMEONE carries over a flat screen TV. Later he straddles the scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS51
He falters, half astride the scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS52
Mill around outside East Valley Community College.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS53
She pulls into a space in the parking lot.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS54
Driver side door opens and a woman’s hand sets a pair of high heels on the ground.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS55
Shapely foot slides into each high heels.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS56
Owner an alluring woman with wavy auburn hair emerges. Wearing
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS57
she trudges down a hall.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS58
She enters her in her cluttered office reading the document.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS59
She sits at her desk,
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS60
she brushes her hair out of her face.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS61
Then opens a drawer and takes out a pill.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS63
She takes a weary breath. A full-figured raven-haired woman holding a to-go cup appears in her doorway.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS64
Her colleague enters an office across the hall.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS65
Still sitting, she sips her drink.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS66
The young woman grins.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS67
Removing her helmet, she shakes out her curly hair.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS68
SOMEONE eyes his belted khakis.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS69
Now the auburn haired professor peeks in through a window in a classroom door.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS70
She enters and looks around.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS71
She counts the meager number of students.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS72
She checks again.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS73
The students stare at her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS74
SOMEONE bursts in through another door.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS75
The students follow his gaze to their professor, whose shoulders sag disappointedly.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS76
Strides to the front of the class.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS77
He watches from a front desk off to one side, as Professor SOMEONE sets down her back. The instructor gazes out at their expectant faces, then gives an indifferent shrug. She writes on a chalkboard in front of them.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS78
Breaks, she waves dismissively.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS79
She gives a bright firm nod.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS80
She eyes the students who shoot each other uneasy glances, then return their attention to their professor.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS81
A young man with dark curly hair raises his hand.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS82
With a wry look she cocks her head.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS83
Her eyes narrow.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS84
SOMEONE blinks apprehensively.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS85
He smiles and nods. The other students shift their uneasy gazes to Miss SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS86
SOMEONE half-smiles in SOMEONE’s direction but breaks off an urge to comment to him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS87
He answers his cell.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS88
Miss SOMEONE's jaw drops.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS89
With a resolute nod she strides up to SOMEONE's desk and raps on it.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS90
He hangs up. As the professor leaves SOMEONE's desk, SOMEONE watches her alertly. Later, he hurries.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS91
Seated at the end of one. He stops.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS92
He sits beside her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS93
SOMEONE gives a puzzled frown, SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE. Tilting her head she considers him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS94
SOMEONE's brow crinkles.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS95
She snags his cell.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS96
She tosses its casing to.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS98
He adjusts a mic.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS99
He smiles. The students stare. His smile widens,
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS100
he grins more broadly.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS101
He lifts his brow at the unresponsive students.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS102
Another classroom Miss SOMEONE writes care on a blackboard then faces two males and two females.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS103
She gives a disappointed nod.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS104
With her eyes averted, she grabs her bag off the table and strides to the back of the classroom. The students watch as the professor exits. Now in a computer
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS105
saw an image of a woman in her underwear.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS109
She grabs two bottles from a liquor cabinet. Her high heels off, she dumps ice into a blender.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS110
Scans his office.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS111
He grabs a book and enters the kitchen.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS112
His wife indifferently sips her drink.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS113
She lowers the cocktail.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS114
She sits in an armchair.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS115
Guilty frown.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS116
He rolls his eyes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS117
As he sits across from SOMEONE, she looks up from her magazine.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS118
She takes two long swigs.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS119
Closing her eyes, she leans forward.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS120
She holds her brow. She winces.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS122
SOMEONE meets his gaze. She opens her mouth to speak, then strides off.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS123
Escaping to a balcony, SOMEONE closes the sliding door and sits. Her husband wraps on the glass, his gaze intolerant.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS124
He cups his hands around his mouth.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS125
Now in speech class a blond student hyperactively swivels a Lacrosse stick in her two-handed grip.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS126
SOMEONE shyly raises a hand.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS127
SOMEONE squares a stack of notecards on his desk then rises from his seat. As he moves behind the lectern the dean smiles excitedly.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS128
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS129
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS130
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE checks his phone
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS131
and picks lint of his shirt. He blinks nervously.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS132
He checks his notes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS133
As the dean gapes, SOMEONE narrows her eyes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS134
As SOMEONE sits back down the dean grins.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS135
SOMEONE heads to the podium.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS136
SOMEONE stares disbelievingly.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS137
Into the mic.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS138
Grinning he glances around at his classmates.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS139
Lying on the floor with his toe and the other two back away.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS140
He snaps as he steps from side to side repeatedly putting his feet apart then together.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS141
Legs bent, he swivels his knees in and out.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS143
Hovers on the movie screen, asking, Scoot?
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS144
takes the phone out again. Another
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS145
and look to your left. Furrowing his brow
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS146
He turns over his shoulder and sees SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS147
riding a scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS148
Professor SOMEONE glares.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS149
He stands in front of SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS150
SOMEONE closes his cell and places it in the professor's hand.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS151
As he walks off, SOMEONE
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS152
to SOMEONE, who winces. Later.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS153
SOMEONE reverts his gaze as she
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS154
his polo.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS155
SOMEONE locks his menacing.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS156
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS157
Hurries over.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS158
SOMEONE heads home. A scruffy friend studies a
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS159
while he searches a rack of clothes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS160
Her pair of shorts.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS161
In SOMEONE's house, the middle-aged student highlights almost every line on a textbook's pages. Seated at his kitchen island he looks to the front door and doffs his glasses.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS162
SOMEONE enters with a blonde friend.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS163
SOMEONE gets up.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS164
Later Sal cuts SOMEONE's hair in the bathroom.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS165
His friends redecorate.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS166
SOMEONE shrugs. Later SOMEONE drapes a silk scarf over a lamp. In the now smartly arranged living room,
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS167
SOMEONE and a friend read.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS168
Sal introduces SOMEONE. He sports a hip close-cropped haircut.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS169
SOMEONE eyes the made over room.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS170
SOMEONE complies.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS171
SOMEONE gives him a kiss.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS172
She follows the others out.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS173
He peeks through his window blinds, then turns. SOMEONE faces him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS174
SOMEONE nods.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS175
SOMEONE makes eye contact.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS176
Nodding, SOMEONE swallows.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS177
They stack their left hands on top.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS178
SOMEONE's look goes from smiley to severe in a split second. He leaves. SOMEONE smoothes his new do, rubbing the sides forward and padding down the back. He views his handsome living room.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS179
Lamar bites down on his pipe.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS180
SOMEONE sees SOMEONE watching.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS181
She raises her window. Later in class.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS182
SOMEONE doffs his glasses and beams. He sees the female Lacrosse player watching his googly eyed response.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS183
SOMEONE eyes his professor.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS184
He winks at her. SOMEONE eyes him flatly, then looks to her right.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS185
Talk about dance steps sleeps.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS186
An eraser hits him and he jolts awake.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS187
She regards SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS188
His smile wilts and he nervously glances aside. SOMEONE looks to the center.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS189
SOMEONE points.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS190
SOMEONE frowns studiously.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS191
At Talia's photo, teacher's pet.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS192
I read the course pad.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS193
The professor's hand reaches out. SOMEONE flips his cellphone shut and hands it over. Standing over him, SOMEONE angrily shakes the phone. Now at a storage facility.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS194
SOMEONE bends over, his cotton-clad rear inadvertently mooning SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS195
Takes off his shades and glares at SOMEONE. She shrugs then drapes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS196
SOMEONE waggles his bottoms into the pants.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS197
Puts his shades back on.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS198
Now SOMEONE's scooter sits parked outside of SOMEONE's Restaurant. Inside, he pours coffee for group of older men.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS199
men playing cards. He sets down the pot and sits by SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS200
SOMEONE eyes him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS201
He doffs his glasses.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS202
Carlos resumes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS203
Raul nods grimly.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS204
Now SOMEONE cracks an egg.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS205
SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand. Now in class.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS206
The students look over their shoulders. SOMEONE wears vampire fangs.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS207
SOMEONE hangs his head, SOMEONE wipes her brow.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS208
His chest. Now our view follow SOMEONE as he weaves through traffic o0n his blue scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS209
SOMEONE smiles.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS210
SOMEONE hands over his cell. Later he talks with to the professor outside.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS211
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS212
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch her go. SOMEONE low
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS213
parked outside donut prince.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS214
SOMEONE sits in the car with a pen and a slip of paper. Rain trickles down.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS215
The square of paper aside and grabs another.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS216
An SUV parks in front of her car.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS217
SOMEONE drinks from her travel cup.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS218
Peering ahead, she notices something and sets the cup back down. She gawks as SOMEONE and SOMEONE leave the SUV for the donut shop.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS219
Windshield wipers swish before her view of the duo closing their umbrellas and entering.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS220
She feeds SOMEONE a bite.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS221
They return to SOMEONE's SUV.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS222
Later, SOMEONE enters the classroom wearing a tasseled scarf.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS223
SOMEONE enters.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS224
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS225
As SOMEONE enters, SOMEONE adjusts the podium.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS226
She puts down a box then crosses to her desk at the back of the room. SOMEONE draws a paper slip from the box.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS227
SOMEONE heads for the podium. SOMEONE seated at the desk and checks her watch.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS228
SOMEONE looks up at a clock, which reads two minutes to eight. He scans his fellow students.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS229
He fidgets with the paper slip.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS230
SOMEONE glares.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS232
She gives him a trendy dark rimmed pair.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS233
She wraps her arms around his neck and kisses him on the cheek.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS234
SOMEONE takes a seat opposite them. SOMEONE regards him uneasily.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS235
SOMEONE glares.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS236
Later, SOMEONE rides glumly as her husband drives. A dessert box sits on the dashboard.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS237
SOMEONE rolls her eyes at him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS238
SOMEONE stares ahead, her jaw hanging open.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS239
She picks up a fistful of pebbles from a tree planter, hurls them after the departing car, then staggers off. Now she sits cross-legged on a bus stop bench in front of a row of dark
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS240
with the flow of traffic the street
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS241
SOMEONE sneers at her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS243
She puts on her high heeled pumps.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS244
She stands. SOMEONE frowns.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS245
She looks at him with a withering gaze.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS246
He Drags his lips in an affable
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS247
Now riding behind him.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS249
To the landing outside her apartment. Turning she finds SOMEONE behind her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS250
She looks around.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS251
SOMEONE searches a potted plant.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS252
She examines her door locks.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS253
In between SOMEONE and the door SOMEONE unlocks it.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS254
SOMEONE returns the key tin to its pot, then keeps his back to SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS255
SOMEONE's brow furrows as he listens.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS256
He rolls his eyes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS257
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS258
Facing her, SOMEONE takes in her drunken grin.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS259
She shows her ring.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS260
She smiles through half closed eyes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS261
SOMEONE frowns.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS262
SOMEONE gives him a playful grin and SOMEONE stares at her with concerned eyes. She sways slightly, her hands joint beneath her chin and her gaze softens. As she grabs him, SOMEONE wraps his arms around her waist. They kiss.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS263
Her off her feet and she slaps.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS266
He digs in the plants pot, finds the key.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS267
Pressing her hands to the door the teacher peers through a peep hole and sees SOMEONE as he joyfully move around.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS268
passenger door arrives at SOMEONE's apartment building.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS269
SOMEONE's husband climbs out.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS270
He raps against the trunk, the cab pulls away.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS271
Cheesecake drips from the takeout box in his hand.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS272
He lumbers on to the sidewalk and approaches the apartment building.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS273
On the landing, he finds the contents of his home office. Multiple copies of the same book sit in stacks around his computer, which displays a porn site.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS274
Box and it splatters against the door.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS275
In class SOMEONE wears sunglasses.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS276
Grabbing a skateboard, SOMEONE smirks at SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS277
The middle-aged student gathers his things and makes his way towards SOMEONE's table at the back of the room. She sits stiffly, her large dark sunglasses masking most of her expression.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS278
SOMEONE offers a tender smile.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS279
SOMEONE's hopeful smile fades.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS280
SOMEONE's brow knits in a wounded look.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS281
She gazes off.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS282
She gives a brisk headshake then returns her attention to SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS283
With his lips pressed in a solemn line SOMEONE gives a respectful nod. SOMEONE's chin twitches as she firmly returns the gesture.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS284
As he turns away, SOMEONE's shoulders sag.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS285
Chain swings from SOMEONE's pocket as he pulls his bag over his shoulder. Sitting motionless, the teacher gazes after him, then bows her head as he exits. Now at home, SOMEONE packs papers into a large accordion file. He places a checkmark on the last line of a list. Picking up a key, he eyes a handwritten tag tied to it with string, then throws it in the file.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS286
He rides his scooter down a street.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS287
He gives her the accordion files.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS288
With a triumphant smirk he turns on his heel and strides out of the bank. Now at the yard sale, he smokes a pipe with Lamar.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS289
SOMEONE gives him a thoughtful look.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS290
A mother and daughter arrive with a measuring tape.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS291
While lying in bed, SOMEONE wipes a tear from the corner of her eye.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS292
Still in her pajamas, she opens a windows blinds. As she peers outside, falling
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS293
rain reflects against the glass. Lingering by the window
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS294
from a mug. Now in class she walks among her students with a box of folded slips of paper. Each student draws one.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS295
SOMEONE draws a topic and reads it.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS296
SOMEONE draws his.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS297
SOMEONE the Lacrosse player reads her topic.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS298
SOMEONE strolls up to the podium and sets the cardboard box on top. Her students gather there.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS299
Picking up a notebook, she heads to the back of the classroom.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS300
SOMEONE removes his reading glasses, then gazes after her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS301
He follows the other students out. Now SOMEONE walks down the hall to her office.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS302
SOMEONE gapes.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS303
SOMEONE looks over.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS304
With her gaze fixed on SOMEONE's SOMEONE twitches a faint, crooked smile.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS305
SOMEONE enters her office.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS306
Now in Economics.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS307
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS308
SOMEONE stands his class.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS309
He regards his sober students with wide eyes. SOMEONE taps his pen.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS310
SOMEONE's smile fades.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS311
She shows her lower back.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS312
SOMEONE touches it. Watching them, SOMEONE knocks on the window.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS313
He throws up his hand and turns away.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS314
He gets on his scooter.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS315
Now in the kitchen at SOMEONE's, SOMEONE transfers a grilled sandwich on to a plate, garnishes the meal and sets the order on a pickup or a paperback.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS316
He highlights a passage near the end. Now a view through
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS317
booth consulting notes and typing on a laptop.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS318
Scooter through his neighborhood.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS319
He passes the neighbor walking a dog, then
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS320
His scooter's headlights briefly illuminates red-striped diagonally across the sign.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS322
The aging man removes his helmet.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS323
It's warmly lit window show a family milling about inside. SOMEONE stands and
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS324
He sweeps his gaze over the surrounding neighborhood.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS325
The idyllic tranquil moment, then turns away and grimly heads inside.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS327
He looks at the now empty house, then exits, shutting the door beside him. Outside Lamar sits on SOMEONE's sofa, which rests on the front lawn among his other belongings. SOMEONE brings SOMEONE his box.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS328
SOMEONE works on a car.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS329
An approaching BMW sports a pizza joint sign on its.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS330
The beefy U Mart exec.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS331
SOMEONE stares.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS332
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a twenty.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS333
SOMEONE averts his gaze.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS334
He reaches into his pocket.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS335
Lamar gives him three lottery tickets.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS336
Two kids ride past them.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS337
SOMEONE disappear as SOMEONE follow.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS341
Delivery boy hands her a pizza box.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS342
SOMEONE smirks.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS343
In a pizza box.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS344
Driver side door opens SOMEONE places her heels on the ground
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS345
She slides her feet into them. Now SOMEONE strolls the campus.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS347
He scoops the litter up. He drops the can in a recycle bin and throws out the paper.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS348
Joins SOMEONE on the walkway.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS349
Outside the classroom.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS350
He reaches for the door.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS351
It opens. She mouths.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS352
SOMEONE grips off his palm.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS353
SOMEONE regards SOMEONE intently.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS354
SOMEONE beams.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS355
He meets SOMEONE's gaze, she grins broadly in reply.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS356
Later in economics, Professor SOMEONE watches his students from his desk. He caps a thermos then sets it near a collection of cellphones and sips from the thermos cup. Sitting at the long tables, the econ students diligently work on their exams. SOMEONE stands. He collects his bag and papers and makes his way to the professor's desk.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS357
He returns SOMEONE's smart phone.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS358
As SOMEONE heads out of the lecture hall the professor lifts his thermos.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS360
Taking a sip, she stares to SOMEONE.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS361
SOMEONE comma SOMEONE, a cursor blinks beside an A.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS362
SOMEONE considers, then adds a plus.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS363
She briefly touches her flushed cheeks.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS364
SOMEONE enters following her raven haired
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS365
SOMEONE notices her. SOMEONE glances at him with a smile.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS366
Who shares a booth with SOMEONE spots SOMEONE too.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS367
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE's booth.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS368
SOMEONE smiles at her.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS369
She smiles sincerely.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS370
As SOMEONE heads away, SOMEONE turns back to her friend.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS371
SOMEONE glances out the window.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS372
He sits among the greatly diminished headcount.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS373
Bored elsewhere, SOMEONE finishes writing the word care next to her course title. English 40, Shakespeare the Politician. She faces a handful of students.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS374
Door in the back opens.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS375
She smiles as SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the Lacrosse player hurry in.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS376
SOMEONE subdues a delighted smile.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS377
SOMEONE slaps his forehead. SOMEONE glances at his friends then slumps in his seat, as SOMEONE distributes a handout.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS378
Later the auburn haired professor walks down the narrow corridor toward her office.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS382
Horton number seven. A doodled black crown marks the bottom as his signature. Closing her eyes, SOMEONE gives a wide
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS383
She slips the note off the bin.
LARRY_CROWNE_DVS384
Displays an arrow moving along the map as she drives.