Our distant view sharpens to reveal a cheetah patting across a lush habitat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS43
Two black aardvarks wade through water up to their heads, flapping their long snouts as they move along.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS49
An array of colorful exotic birds perch around a pond.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS51
Elsewhere, a proboscis monkey rubs its dangling, bulbous nose.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS52
Coming out of a cave-like shelter, a rhinoceros turns around.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS53
Going back in, it halts half way. Its rear-end sticking out in the sunny yard.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS55
Now a nimble primate swings among the branches of a tree.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS57
It reaches a high branch and gazes out over its surroundings.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS58
A small, red-ish bird stands on a floating pad near the concrete rim of a pool.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS59
The still waters reflect a Bengal tiger stalking past.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS61
A lizard darts through the rainy yard.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS62
In a modern kitchen, a middle aged man stands at a stove.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS63
He eyes a pleasant-faced young man.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS64
The younger man smiles.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS66
SOMEONE, she carries a boy.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS67
He tosses the little boy into the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS68
In the present.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS69
In a flashback, a sign labels a complex surrounding a pristine public pool.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS71
Stylish guests relax on the elegant deck.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS72
Boasting a broad chest, narrow waist and dark mustache, SOMEONE gazes out with a love-lorn smile.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS73
As he scans one of the complex's balconies, a swimmer paddles across our view.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS74
From under water, we watch SOMEONE dive in.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS75
A flashback at a school.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS76
A boy peers down into a courtyard.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS79
The teacher holds a beaker full of yellow fluid.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS80
Noticing what's in his hands, he puts it down.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS81
Mortified, SOMEONE glances around the classroom.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS82
Leaving his seat, the skinny, sad-eyed SOMEONE marches up to the front of the class.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS83
He writes on a chalkboard.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS84
The teacher and student stare.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS85
SOMEONE puts the chalk down and resumes his seat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS86
SOMEONE leaves another chalkboard and resumes his seat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS87
On a walkway.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS88
A librarian rushes with a book among a throng of students to a classroom.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS89
Inside, SOMEONE fills the chalkboard with numbers.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS90
Several more boards stand filled to his left and students call out each number he writes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS92
The librarian consults his book.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS93
Back in the present.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS94
The writer averts his eyes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS95
The writer shrugs good naturedly.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS96
He helps his host bring food to a table and they sit down to lunch.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS97
He graciously serves his guest.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS98
In a flashback, two stylish blondes ride bicycles down a street.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS99
They follow the charming, colorful street toward the sea.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS100
Elsewhere, a beautiful woman teaches gardening.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS101
Taking a disc of naan, he notices his host's eyes closed in prayer.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS102
The writer sets down the bread.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS106
She tells her sons the story.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS111
The lovely woman snuggles on a bed with her two boys.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS112
So Krishna opened his mouth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS115
She saw in Krishna's mouth the whole entire universe.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS116
Young SOMEONE screws his mouth up thoughtfully.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS117
Later in the dark, SOMEONE sits hunched beneath the sheet and uses a flashlight.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS118
His brother sleeping beside him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS119
SOMEONE turns the pages of a comic book depicting the Krishna story.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS120
A large panel illustrates a smiling Krishna holding his mouth open.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS121
Beyond his lips swirl colorful galaxies, planets, and stars.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS122
As we peer closely at the universe between Krishna's lips, it moves.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS124
With the boy's father.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS125
A barge carrying a depiction of Vishnu floats passed SOMEONE's mother.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS126
Our view lifts up and away from the floating candles to the stars twinkling in the night's sky.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS127
Our view spins, then descends to a sunny day in a lush valley.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS128
Facing his sad-eyed, skinny brother, an adolescent SOMEONE points out a church at the rim of the misty valley.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS129
It overlooks a tranquil river winding through verdant lands.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS130
Now, as we peer out the church's open door.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS131
SOMEONE leans into view with wide eyes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS132
He slips inside, then creeps to an alcove.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS133
Scooping up water from a basin with his hand, he takes a few sips then turns and takes in the space with a curious reverent gaze.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS134
Now SOMEONE stares across the pews at the alter where golden candlesticks surround a crucified Jesus statue.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS135
His gaze drifts along a high row of paintings and fixates on one.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS137
The priest approaches the boy and offers a glass of water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS138
Staring at the glass, SOMEONE cautiously accepts the drink and takes a tiny sip.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS139
He glances at the priest then holds out a hand and regards the painting of Jesus being crucified.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS140
Now young SOMEONE sits beside a glimmering river.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS141
He stands and stumbles into the water. Now in the church.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS142
SOMEONE removes his hand from a Vishnu figure and presses his palms together in Christian prayer.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS143
He turns off a lamp and goes to bed.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS144
Now young SOMEONE walks down a dirt road lined with grimy homes. Looking right, he sees dozens of kneeling men bowing, performing Salah in the mosque's courtyard.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS145
SOMEONE watches from outside the gate, then slowly moves towards to courtyard congregation.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS146
Speakers sit atop the mosque's tower.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS147
Now at home, the young Indian performs Salah alone.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS148
Later at the dinner table with his family.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS149
SOMEONE crosses himself and prays as his family begins dining.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS150
His father watches him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS151
Gita nods and swallows her food.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS152
She touches her chest.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS153
He glances between his sons.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS154
SOMEONE nods gently at his father.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS155
His beautiful mother eyes her family.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS156
Slowly lifting his sheepish gaze, SOMEONE looks around the table.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS157
His father stops eating and faces his wife who returns an amused smile.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS158
In present day, SOMEONE and the writer leave his house.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS159
At the zoo, young SOMEONE leads SOMEONE into a shadowy back room.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS160
SOMEONE continues into a caged area.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS161
He grabs handfuls of raw meat from a table.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS162
He turns a wheel near a gate.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS163
At the zoo.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS164
SOMEONE crouches before the gate with SOMEONE kneeling behind.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS165
A Bengal tiger steps beneath the lifted gate and enters the narrow corridor before them.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS166
SOMEONE turns and runs but SOMEONE remains still.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS167
Stopping near the end.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS168
The beautiful animal stares at the boy.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS169
SOMEONE extends a handful of meat between the bars.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS170
SOMEONE glances at a gated off entrance to his side, then slowly stalks down the feeding corridor toward SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS171
The young boy remains still as the tiger nears. Its long striped tail swaying behind.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS172
Keeping his eyes fixed on SOMEONE Parker's, SOMEONE's hand trembles with the slab of meat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS173
The magnificent tiger stops a foot away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS174
His ears point backward as he extends his nose to the meat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS175
SOMEONE's father hurries inside.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS176
The tiger bolts away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS177
Glaring, his father shakes his head and faces SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS178
SOMEONE runs off.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS179
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch a zoo keeper enter the room carrying a live goat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS180
He sets it before the feeding corridor.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS181
Securing its rope leash to the bars, Selvam faces SOMEONE's father.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS185
SOMEONE's mother enters.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS186
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS187
SOMEONE crosses his arms and stares ahead as Selvam spins the metal wheel.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS188
At the end of the corridor the tiger's gate slides open.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS189
The family stands together facing the gate.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS190
The alarmed goat shakes its head and ears, then spins in a circle.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS191
SOMEONE slowly turns the corner and eyes the goat with his mouth hanging open.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS192
Lowering his head, the intimidating beast stalks forward.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS193
SOMEONE watches as he suddenly springs toward his prey.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS194
SOMEONE winces and SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE against her as SOMEONE remains completely still.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS195
With the goat now on the other side of the bars, SOMEONE pulls it back toward his cage.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS196
With his head pressed to his mother's bosom.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS197
SOMEONE watches the carnivore drag his kill.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS199
Now in bed, teenage SOMEONE reads a Dostoyevsky novel as SOMEONE awakes to an alarm.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS200
Later outside their school, young students rush passed SOMEONE through the rain.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS201
Now SOMEONE sits on a beam below an ocean SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS202
He reads L'Etranger by Albert Camus.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS203
Now a round-faced teenage beauty dances with other girls wearing a vibrant red saari.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS204
SOMEONE plays the dholak drum and watches her closely.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS205
An older teacher sits crossed-legged and chants as teenage girls perform a lively dance. The round-faced girl spins rapidly, catching SOMEONE's gaze on several twirls.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS206
SOMEONE glances at the teacher as the dance slows.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS207
Keeping her hands on her hips, the round-faced beauty steps forward. SOMEONE stares at her with mesmerized eyes. His mouth hanging open slightly.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS208
The teacher breaks his trance.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS209
SOMEONE closes his lips and glances at SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS210
She keeps her eyes cast down as her classmates smile.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS211
Later in a bustling marketplace, SOMEONE spies on SOMEONE as she shops with friends.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS212
A girl spots him and he quickly ducks behind colorful hanging items. As SOMEONE and her friends move on, SOMEONE attempts to follow them with the drum satchel draped over his shoulder.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS213
He exits the market and stops, searching in both directions. Now SOMEONE scurries through a section of tall root-like banyan trees where SOMEONE awaits with her friends.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS214
SOMEONE stares at the ground then forms a bowl with his hands.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS215
She furrows her brow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS216
SOMEONE smiles and looks down.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS217
He forms the bowl.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS218
Surrounded by banyan trees, SOMEONE glances down then shows SOMEONE a warm smile.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS219
Later at the zoo, SOMEONE and SOMEONE view the tiger lounge.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS220
He faces them with his ears pointed back.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS221
SOMEONE tilts her head and looks up.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS222
A big smile spreads on SOMEONE's face and he glances between her and the tiger.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS223
Later at the dinner table, SOMEONE stares off in a trance, smiling to himself as his father speaks.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS224
SOMEONE shakes his head with a furrowed brow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS225
His mother looks down.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS226
SOMEONE stares longingly at his mother who catches SOMEONE's humorless gaze. Later beneath the ocean SOMEONE, SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE as she ties pink string around his wrist.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS227
The young beauty takes his hand.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS228
Now on a freighter ship, SOMEONE leans on the rail of the main deck.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS229
He gazes back at the brilliant sun setting beyond his homeland on the horizon.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS230
He faces forward then looks back at the sun as his mother approaches.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS231
SOMEONE stops beside her boy, following his gaze to the setting sun.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS232
SOMEONE shifts his weight.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS233
SOMEONE eyes her son then walks away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS234
Blinking rapidly, SOMEONE keeps his gaze fixed on the horizon.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS235
Now in the eating quarters, SOMEONE faces a husky, larged-nosed cook.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS239
The cook reaches behind the counter and puts a morsel of parsley on the plate.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS240
She asked if you have something vegetarian.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS241
The cook glances at the plate.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS242
The cow that produced this liver was vegetarian, the pigs that went into these sausages were vegetarian.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS243
Very funny but my wife doesn't eat liver.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS244
The cook shrugs and grabs another plate.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS245
Then she can eat the sausage, the rice and the gravy or you can cook your own food.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS246
How dare you talk to my wife like that.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS248
I cook for sailors not curry eaters.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS249
SOMEONE grabs the cook.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS254
The sailors pull SOMEONE away from the crazy-eyed cook.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS255
Now the family sits with their eyes cast down as a teenage Asian boy joins them.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS256
SOMEONE eyes the amiable boy and shakes his head with a smile.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS257
Now below the deck, two orangutans sit in a four by four cage. The larger one takes the smaller one's hand and comforts it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS258
SOMEONE sits outside the cage, watching them closely and eating a banana.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS259
His father dumps food in an ostrich pen as a camel and giraffe watch attentively.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS260
Stacks of animal crates line the cargo hold.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS261
SOMEONE stares at his son as he shoves pills into a banana.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS262
SOMEONE shifts his gaze to the ship's floor.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS263
Present day on a park bench.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS264
The writer watches him with a furrowed brow as adult SOMEONE stares into the river before them.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS265
The writer nods and grins.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS267
Facing the river, he leans forward.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS268
A map of the South Pacific fills the screen.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS269
We zoom to the Mariana trench.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS270
As we push through thick, churning storm clouds, deck lights illuminate a freighter in the night. Heavy rains pound on the swelling ocean.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS271
Ramping off a wave, the ship's bow lands hard on the seething surface. Water bursts upwards as it skips to another wave.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS272
Below deck, SOMEONE slowly awakes in his cabin bunk.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS273
His eyes dart about. His parents sleep in a bed across the room.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS274
He leans down to the bottom bunk and shakes his sleeping brother.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS275
SOMEONE quickly pulls himself into his bunk as his mother rolls over.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS276
The hands on a travel clock point to 1:17.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS277
SOMEONE climbs a flight of stairs and enters a corridor.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS278
The door swings shut behind him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS279
He staggers and steadies himself on a railing as he moves along.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS280
Turning, he faces a door with a port hole.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS281
SOMEONE peers through at the lightning flashing in the darkness.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS282
He turns a latch and the door swings open. The wind and rain lash in at him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS283
Venturing out, SOMEONE leans over a railing and scans his tempestuous surroundings. As he steps along a walkway, his feet slide on the wet flooring.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS284
He stumbles as the ship violently rocks and he catches himself on a banister.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS285
SOMEONE climbs stairs to the neck deck and slides on his bare feet again.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS286
He catches himself on a railing and clings to it as he beams down at the churning, roiling ocean.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS287
Stepping back, he looks skyward and waves his arms giddily.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS288
He struggles to perform a worshipful dance.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS292
Getting to his feet, he notices a red light flashing from a high post. Falling again, SOMEONE slides into a barrier at the edge of the upper deck.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS294
He braces himself and climbs to his feet. The ship plunges into a wave sending water crashing over him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS295
It leaves the upper deck flooded as he recovers.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS298
SOMEONE watches two sailors moving frantically below with flashlights.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS300
SOMEONE reaches for them futilely as they wash overboard.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS301
Sobered, he races back inside.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS303
He staggers through a corridor.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS304
Finding his level flooded, he dives into the water and swims. He passes a panicking zebra.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS306
SOMEONE surfaces.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS307
Gasping then submerges himself and swims onward.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS308
The teen passes through a dark section lit only by the pulsing red emergency lights.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS309
Reaching a door at the end of the corridor, he struggles to open it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS310
It springs open releasing a powerful current of water and air bubbles.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS311
SOMEONE hangs onto the door frame and tries futilely to pull himself into his family's quarters.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS312
Releasing it, he drifts back down the corridor and returns to the deck.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS313
An animal leaps passed him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS315
A bird seeks refuge in the nearby tower. Other animals struggle for footing on the rocking ship.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS318
A sailor gives him a life jacket.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS319
The Buddhist struggles to free a lifeboat carrying the cook.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS321
The Buddhist leaps to SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS322
The Buddhist, captain and the sailor shove him onto the boat. SOMEONE tumbles across the canvas cover and hangs off the edge. The cook signals to the men on the ship.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS324
SOMEONE climbs back up and scrambles around as the others shout at him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS327
As SOMEONE clings to one set of lines, the cook unfastens another.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS328
The Buddhist points as the zebra at the railing of an upper deck.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS331
The boat tips and the cook falls off.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS333
SOMEONE loses his grip on the lines and the lifeboat plummets to the sea.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS334
SOMEONE lands on his belly and struggles to hold on as the boat bucks on the churning waters. SOMEONE slides backward, landing at a wave that buoys him back on the boat again.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS335
It carries him past the shouting men at the edge of the ship's deck. A giant wave washes them from view.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS336
The lifeboat carries SOMEONE through the wreckage. A boom sweeps low over his head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS337
Escaping the wreckage, the lifeboat briefly capsizes. As it rights itself, we find SOMEONE holding on tightly and the zebra lying inside. SOMEONE peers across the giant waves and locates the sinking ship. He notices a whistle on his life jacket and blows it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS338
He frantically waves his arm at the ship.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS340
Peering into the seemingly endless expanse of rolling waves, SOMEONE spots a figure in the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS342
Finding a life preserver, he climbs up on the canvas secured tautly over the front half of the boat. He casts the flotation device out into the water with all his might.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS343
The lights of the capsizing ship twinkle and pulse in the distance as SOMEONE uses a line to reel in the drowning figure.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS345
He slides a long handles oar out from beneath the canvas cover and extends it over the water toward the life preserver.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS347
Two paws and a large furry head emerge from the center of the ring.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS350
SOMEONE jabs futilely at the tiger with the oar. A wave carries the beast to the lifeboat's rim.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS351
SOMEONE grabs on and climbs partially aboard. Scrambling to the prow, SOMEONE dives into the water. Getting his bearings, he looks back at the lifeboat, then gazes out over the roiling water. A giant wave looms stories high above him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS352
SOMEONE takes a deep breath and submerges. The wave briefly rolls him as it passes by.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS353
Staying under, SOMEONE swims past a shark as he makes his way beyond the lifeboat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS354
Turning, he finds himself facing the completely submerged ship.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS355
The teen halts and hovers in the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS356
His limbs splayed as he stares at the enormous craft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS357
The deck lights glow as the ocean's depths claim the vessel.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS358
SOMEONE looks on helplessly as the ship descends into the deep.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS360
Turning away, he swims.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS362
Two other sharks fight over a fresh kill beneath him. The tempestuous waters swirl over SOMEONE as he makes his way back to the surface.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS363
The teen thrusts his head above water and gasps.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS364
With long strokes, he swims back to the lifeboat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS365
SOMEONE grabs for a mast jutting five feet from the prow, but a passing wave compromises his reach.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS366
Another carries him to the boat's rim.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS367
SOMEONE climbs on to the deck with the zebra who lies curled up on its side on one end.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS368
Knee-deep water sloshes around the deck.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS369
SOMEONE climbs back on the canvas cover, then scrambles to the prow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS370
He leans far out, clinging to the mast.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS371
A wave sends a blast of spray into his face.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS372
Shaking his head, he catches his breath and peers down into the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS373
Another blast of sea-spray drenches the teen.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS374
He watches helplessly as the ship sinks further beneath the churning waves.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS375
The ocean's rippling surface distorts SOMEONE's view of the lost vessel.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS376
We drift up and away from the boy as the lifeboat carries him over the ship's watery grave.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS377
A section at a time, the deck lights flicker then blink out.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS378
Lightning flashes then diminishes leaving the boy alone in the darkness.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS380
The next day a seemingly endless expanse of choppy waves roll beneath a low ceiling of storm clouds. The lifeboat bobs amidst the whitecaps.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS381
With the life preserver looped over the prow beam, a huddled, shivering SOMEONE sits in the rain while clinging to the mast with his hands.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS382
His feet brace against the front of the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS383
A shark passes beneath him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS384
Glancing down at it, SOMEONE struggles his way to the canvas covered bow and rolls over on top of the beam.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS385
Lifting the edge of the canvas, he peers inside.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS386
Water sloshes over the floor of the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS387
The water splashes the zebra who still lies curled up on the wooden bench-like seats rimming the far end.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS388
One of its hind legs lies unnaturally straight as it drags its haunch along the bench.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS389
Later, SOMEONE uses a bucket to bail water from the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS390
With weary, dogged motions, he scoops out one bucketful after another.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS391
SOMEONE drops the bucket and collapses on the bench near the canvas cover's edge.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS392
He leans back, his arms draped on the boat's rim and cover.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS393
SOMEONE lifts his head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS394
A hyena emerges from the canvas shelter.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS395
The hyena darts back under the canvas. As SOMEONE takes up a long handles oar and jumps to the canvas cover.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS396
SOMEONE the hyena darts out. It leaps at SOMEONE clumsily and snaps at the oar. Its jaws clamp on the oars paddle.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS397
SOMEONE drops the oar and retreats to the prow beam.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS398
Clinging by his arms, he swings himself around so his legs dangle over the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS399
Curling his abdominal muscles, he lifts his legs and fits them through the life preserver.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS400
From his makeshift seat, he watches SOMEONE mid-boat as the hyena tries to climb up onto the canvas. The beast makes it only half way up, its hind legs staggering with the rocking of the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS401
The spotted hyena keeps its four paws on the canvas, staring at SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS402
It turns its head. SOMEONE follows its gaze, peering across the surf.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS403
From a cresting wave, an orangutan rises into view, perched on a floating bundle.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS404
SOMEONE ducks into the canvas and the zebra stretches its neck toward the approaching ape.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS405
As she draws near, we recognize her flotation device has bananas wrapped in netting.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS406
SOMEONE extends an oar to her and she climbs aboard.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS407
The teen gives her a weary smile then leans over the side of the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS408
In the water, the banana bundles float free of the netting.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS409
SOMEONE gathers up the net.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS410
Pulls out a stray banana and tosses it to Orange Juice.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS411
The orangutan lets it bounce off her shoulder and land on the flooded floor of the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS412
Facing SOMEONE, she grimly works her lips and folds her long arms.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS413
Frowning, the teen peers out over the sea.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS414
As SOMEONE faces her with a concerned expression, the orangutan lowers her gaze and sighs. Turning her head over her shoulder, she gazes off over the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS415
SOMEONE blinks understandingly.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS416
SOMEONE settles wearily onto the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS417
He gives a resigned sigh.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS418
Now flies swarm around the injured zebra, a thin white foam covering its lips.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS419
Standing on the canvas cover, SOMEONE turns.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS420
He drops to all fours and picks up the bucket.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS421
Lying on his belly, he slams it against the boat's hull.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS422
The hyena emerges from beneath the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS423
Rediscovering SOMEONE, it leaps at him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS424
The teen scrambles back and fends off SOMEONE with the oar.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS425
The animal gnaws on its paddle.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS426
Orange Juice scoots back on the bench and shrieks as SOMEONE bounds passed her and runs in circles. The hyena briefly leans over the edge the resumes its wild laps as SOMEONE stands ready with the oar.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS427
SOMEONE stops at the center, his body convulsing. He vomits on the floor.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS428
Licking his chops, he makes another try for SOMEONE but slumps weakly against the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS430
The netting dangles from the base of the prow beam.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS431
SOMEONE sits at the bow sharing a vigilant gaze with the hyena who remains back at the edge of the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS432
The teen wavers wearily, his eyelids heavy.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS433
Glancing over his shoulder.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS434
SOMEONE bounds to the zebra and snaps at its injured hind leg.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS435
The wounded animal kicks at the predator.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS436
SOMEONE and Orange Juice watch helplessly as SOMEONE kills the zebra.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS438
On a gently rolling current, SOMEONE sits in the makeshift seat at the boats prow, hugging the life preserver.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS439
Dark circles shade his bleary eyes above his red, chapped cheeks.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS440
SOMEONE's eyelids droop and he blinks himself awake.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS441
The teen nods off again.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS442
He falls back into the water, hanging by his knees from the life preserver.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS443
Waking, he jolts up and gasps.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS444
The sputtering teen manages to sit up and catch his breath.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS445
A line of saliva streams from his mouth as he looks around and recovers.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS446
In the boat, the zebra lies dead.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS447
Orange Juice slumps against the edge of the canvas cover taking slow, deep breaths.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS448
He lifts away a hatch beneath the canvas cover and finds a duffle inside. Opening it, he finds a red booklet titled, "Survival at Sea" lying atop an array of supplies.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS449
SOMEONE takes it out and flips through pages illustrated with diagrams.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS450
Lifting another hatch, the teen finds it packed with life jackets. He takes one out and tosses it to Orange Juice.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS451
The orangutan picks it up, turning it in her hands and feet as she examines it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS452
Beyond her, SOMEONE digs out several more life jackets.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS453
Orange Juice gives hers a shake, the throws it down.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS454
Later, using ropes and netting, he bundles the life jackets together into a small, makeshift raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS455
The life preserver crowns it and three long handled oars criss-cross out from it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS456
Forming six branch-like spokes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS457
As SOMEONE struggles to maneuver it into the water,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS458
SOMEONE emerges from the canvas shelter.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS459
Perching atop the zebra's carcass, he starts to take a bite. Orange Juice angrily thumps the rim of the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS460
SOMEONE turns and stalks the orangutan who backs against the canvas' edge.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS461
As SOMEONE lunges, she strikes him down.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS462
As SOMEONE looks on, his jubilant smile fades.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS463
Orange Juice peers down at the hyena, then sits on steadily and faces her human companion.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS464
SOMEONE attacks her.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS465
He drags her down to the floor and tears into her.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS466
SOMEONE climbs over his raft and unsheathes a knife.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS467
The hyena retreats to the boat's stern and cowers.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS468
Our view sweeps down to Orange Juice's body as it grows still.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS469
Blood stains the wood near her throat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS470
As he stares down at her, SOMEONE's mournful expression hardens wrathfully.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS471
Facing SOMEONE, he swings the knife.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS472
The tiger springs out from the shelter beneath him. Landing on the zebra, SOMEONE kills the hyena with a wrench of his jaws. Behind him, SOMEONE scrambles for his makeshift raft. As he pushes it overboard, the tiger faces him with a snarl.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS473
Standing, SOMEONE picks up the oar.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS474
SOMEONE swats it from his grasp.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS475
As the tiger climbs onto the canvas, SOMEONE curls up in a fetal position with his back to him and squeezes his eyes shut.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS476
SOMEONE backs off, returning his attention to his kill.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS477
SOMEONE leaps from the boat, following a rope, tethering the raft to the lifeboat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS478
He tries to climb on top of the raft but it rolls under his weight.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS479
Later, the boy persists as the bundle of life jackets loosens and rolls beneath his grasp.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS480
He strikes it angrily.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS481
Later still, he ties the life jacket to the end of an oar spoke, balancing the raft's buoyancy.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS482
A shark swims passed as he works, spotting it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS483
The boy climbs on top of the raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS484
Now SOMEONE lies still beneath the canvas shelter.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS485
At the boat's prow, SOMEONE peaks in at the tiger, he lifts out the duffle of supplies, revealing a sizable stock of canned goods and boxed food beneath.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS486
SOMEONE eagerly climbs in to retrieve them.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS487
Now, perched at the prow of the lifeboat, SOMEONE drinks down the contents of a can.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS488
He fits a plastic lid on top, then drops it into a sack nestled at the center of his makeshift raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS489
SOMEONE takes a handful of cans from the supply hatch and drops those in as well.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS490
Taking out small boxes, he chucks one in and opens the other.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS491
Unwrapping a nutritional biscuit, he takes a big bite.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS492
Looking down, he finds a sizable rat scurrying over the cans.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS493
SOMEONE watches it as he eats.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS494
SOMEONE lunges at him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS495
The tiger halts, his claws sticking in the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS496
He staggers back, snapping irritably at the fabric as a recoiling SOMEONE watches with wide eyes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS497
SOMEONE turns his gaze out over the slate-grey water surrounding them.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS498
He walks along the benches lining the boat's perimeter, pausing to paw at the zebra carcass.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS499
With the animal distracted, SOMEONE starts to climb from the prow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS500
SOMEONE charges forward, his head jetting up from the canvas' open flap at the bow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS501
His enormous mass knocks SOMEONE onto his back on the canvas and the rat scurries along the cover.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS502
SOMEONE emerges from the opening at the boat's center and climbs partway up on the canvas. The rat climbs up SOMEONE's arm and over his head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS503
The teen grabs the rodent.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS504
SOMEONE pauses, staring hungrily.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS505
SOMEONE throws the rat at the tiger who catches it in his mouth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS506
As SOMEONE slurps it down, SOMEONE jumps off the boat, he tries to push away on the raft but finds a line tethering him closely to the boat's prow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS507
As he tries to release the line, SOMEONE lunges over the prow swiping his massive claws at his head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS508
SOMEONE ducks and the tiger nearly falls off the boat. Scraping his rear claws against the painted metal hull, the tiger climbs back aboard.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS509
SOMEONE pushes off from the boat on his raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS510
SOMEONE returns to the center of the boat as the frightened teen paddles away. Still securely connected by the tether.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS511
Stopping a few yards from the boat, SOMEONE vomits into the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS512
At night, a full moon shines through a gap in the clouds. On the boat,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS513
SOMEONE drags the zebra carcass out of view.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS514
From his raft, SOMEONE watches tearfully.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS515
His sits cross-legged, his shoulders hunched.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS516
SOMEONE peers out at him from the edge of the boat, his parted lips showing his long, sharp fangs.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS517
The tiger calmly flops his tail as he observes the boy.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS518
His lips quivering.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS519
SOMEONE regards the tiger woefully.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS520
Thick clouds drift before the enormous full moon.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS521
As the boat and raft float of gently rolling waves, the clouds gradually blot out the moonlight leaving the boy and tiger in darkness.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS522
Now a rising golden sun cuts through the dark.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS523
As it illuminates the sky, we find the boat and raft adrift on perfectly still, glassy waters that reflect the cloudy sky.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS524
As we peer down on them from above,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS525
we find a perfect mirror-like image of the sun-lit clouds, undisturbed on the water's surface.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS526
SOMEONE maintains his cross-legged pose as he watches the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS527
Later he writes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS528
He uses blank pages in the survival book.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS529
He write with a pencil.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS530
He presses the tip to the paper making a period.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS531
Later, he puts the folded torn out in an empty water can and caps it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS532
As we watch from a distance.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS533
SOMEONE stands from the center of his raft and throws the can with all his might.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS534
It lands close to us and bobs peacefully in the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS535
A birds-eye view shows the can about ten yards from SOMEONE's raft sending out gentle ripples over the current-less sea.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS536
The boy turns, looking over his shoulder.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS537
Tethered a few yards off, the lifeboat appears empty and peaceful.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS538
SOMEONE emerges from the canvas shelter at the center of the boat, steps up on a seat below its rim,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS539
He gazes out over the vast expanse of motion-less sunlit sea.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS543
Watching him calmly, SOMEONE crouches down and takes up the rope tether.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS544
Tugging hand over hand, he reels the boat closer.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS545
At the prow, SOMEONE lifts the end of the canvas cover and peers beneath.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS546
Nestled inside, SOMEONE snarls up at him but makes no move to rise.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS547
The carcasses of the zebra and the hyena flank the predator.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS549
SOMEONE gives a small nod and gazes into the animal's fierce amber eyes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS550
The teen lowers the flap, then pushes the boat off.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS551
Standing along in the vast, isolated expanse, he turns his gaze toward the sunlit clouds above.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS552
Now a map from the survival book illustrates the world's ocean currents with inter-swirling circles.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS553
Reading it on his bobbing raft, SOMEONE looks over his shoulder.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS554
Now SOMEONE reads through the book and follows its advice.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS555
SOMEONE notices a rash along his side.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS556
Later, he lies back, his hands over his face.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS557
He catches rain in the bucket, his open mouth, and cans in each hand.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS558
SOMEONE collects water puddled on the canvas cover.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS559
Now ten hash marks mar the hull off the prow. SOMEONE carves an eleventh with his knife.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS560
Juxtaposed with the scenes, SOMEONE reads the book.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS561
On an overcast day, he studies the book on his raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS562
Pausing, he faces the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS563
SOMEONE uses the canvas cone.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS564
He drags the boat sideways over the waves.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS565
He pulls the boat close.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS566
SOMEONE emerges from his shelter, his ears back and his eyes wide.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS567
Standing on the raft, SOMEONE rocks the boat by its prow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS568
Blinking his amber eyes, the tiger hangs his head and convulses nauseously.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS569
Gritting his teeth. SOMEONE pushes himself up on the boat's canvas cover.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS570
He plants his feet wide apart and crouches over, getting his balance as he faces the tiger.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS571
He lunges forward, his arms raised and spread. SOMEONE retreats to the boat's stern, sits on the rear seat and leans his face over the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS572
SOMEONE watches him with wide eyes then reaches for his pants.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS573
In front of his feet, urine hits the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS574
Finishing, SOMEONE fiercely points downward.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS575
SOMEONE opens his mouth wide in what appears to be a lazy yawn.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS576
He turns, putting his tail to SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS577
He sprays the teen in the face.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS578
Sputtering, SOMEONE rolls off the canvas and the tiger reclaims it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS579
Now wearing the sea anchor as a hat that shades his face, neck and shoulders,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS580
SOMEONE reels in a floating beach ball-sized device shaped like a chocolate kiss.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS581
It collects dew.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS582
Harvesting a plastic sack of fresh water, SOMEONE drinks through a straw.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS584
He pours the rest into the bucket.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS585
Later, he hefts the bucket into the lifeboat, setting it on the seat at the stern.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS586
He raises the whistle to his lips.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS587
The tiger emerges from his shelter.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS588
SOMEONE pushes off as SOMEONE approaches the bucket.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS589
The tiger bats it gently, sniffs it, and sticks his face in.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS590
He writes in the survival book.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS591
He baits a fishing hook with chewed biscuit then lowers it into the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS592
From the lifeboat, SOMEONE licks his chops as he looks on.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS593
SOMEONE faces him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS594
The boy tries casting the line again.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS595
Later, the low sun casts a shimmering beam across the sapphire blue ocean.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS596
SOMEONE paces along the seats, peering into the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS597
We glimpse a few green-tinted shapes swimming just below the surface.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS598
Prepping his fishing line, SOMEONE glances up at the tiger.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS599
A few fish splash the water surface.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS600
SOMEONE jumps in.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS601
SOMEONE looks up, his eyes wide.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS602
From underwater, we watch SOMEONE paddling expertly among the darting fish.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS603
His head held high, he snaps his jaws at one and misses.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS605
Looking on, SOMEONE allows an amused smile.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS606
Shaking water out of his pressed back ears, SOMEONE turns toward him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS607
SOMEONE's smile fades.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS608
Grabbing the tether, he tugs hand over fist to reel himself toward the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS609
SOMEONE, paddles steadily, his gaze calm.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS610
As SOMEONE nears the boat, the tiger draws close to him,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS611
the teen climbs aboard just as the predator reaches his rafts outer spokes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS612
The tiger tries to climb the raft, then the ship's hull.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS613
His claws find no hold in its painted metal.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS614
SOMEONE tries climbing aboard the raft from another spoke.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS615
From the boat, SOMEONE struggles to heft up the raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS616
Lying back, he uses one leg as extra leverage. The tiger hangs off the far spokes, adding to its weight then drops into the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS617
With the raft resting on the canvas cover,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS618
SOMEONE circles the boat, pawing at its hull.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS619
SOMEONE takes a hatchet from the supply hatch.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS620
He glances around, then beats SOMEONE at the side of the boat and raises the hatchet.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS621
The tiger hangs on by ropes draped around the hull. Staring him down, SOMEONE's gaze softens.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS622
The mostly submerged tiger stares up at him helplessly.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS623
Clinging to the ropes with his front claws.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS624
Lowering the axe, SOMEONE gets down and kicks a seat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS626
As he looks around, SOMEONE paddles along the hull and tries again without success.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS627
SOMEONE taps the boat's inner wall with his hatchet, the ducks into the canvas shelter.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS628
He emerges, the stands and peers over the side of the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS629
Standing between the two broken stumps of a broken off bench that once stretched across the boat,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS630
SOMEONE looks around again.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS631
He crouches and lifts up a hatch in front of his feet.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS632
He sets the sizable pallet of wooden slats on the seat then reaches for his raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS633
At dusk, our gaze drifts over the water, back to the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS634
A beam of light dances up through the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS635
SOMEONE emerges from the shelter with a flashlight in hand.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS636
Shining it over the side, he finds SOMEONE clinging to the whole rope.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS639
He lowers his raft, now larger, sturdier, and stocked with supplies, over the other side of the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS640
He keeps hold of it with a rope as he crosses back to SOMEONE's side and puts the whistle to his lips.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS641
He drops the slatted pallet overboard.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS642
Attached to the boat with ropes, it forms a crude ladder.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS643
As SOMEONE uses it to climb on board,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS644
SOMEONE jumps off the other side and lands on his raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS645
Standing on his hand-crafted flotation vessel,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS646
the teen slowly lets out the tether connecting him to the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS647
SOMEONE arrives back on board.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS648
His soaked fur revealing his lean frame.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS649
As he shakes himself off,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS650
SOMEONE watches him carefully.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS651
The tiger faces him, then steps down out of view.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS652
Now, under sun-lit water, we watch fish swim beneath the improved raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS653
Our view surfaces to find SOMEONE seated at one end making notes as he overlooks his stock of supplies.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS654
He marks off an illustrated list.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS655
Later, as he makes modifications to the raft,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS656
an enormous green fish with a blue crest swims toward a net dangling from the humble craft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS657
Re-attaching a life jacket to an oar beam, SOMEONE pauses and stares down at it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS658
The colorful fish swims right into the net.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS660
Reaching down, SOMEONE gingerly scoops up the other sides, closing it off, then yanks the fish out of the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS661
Straddling the new criss-crossing grid of oar beams, SOMEONE struggles to wrestle the fish into submission.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS662
Roughly 2/3 his size, the fish thrashes wildly in his grasp.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS663
SOMEONE pins it down on an oar beam, stretches one arm out and grabs the hatchet from the edge of the supply pallet. He sits up, holds the fish down with one hand and uses the other to club the fish with the blunt end of the hatchet.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS664
He pauses, his features set in a savage glare.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS665
The stunned fish feebly works its sharp-toothed jaws, blood seeps out beneath its gill.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS666
SOMEONE stares with a softened remorseful gaze.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS667
The fish grows still and its vibrant colors fade to dull, mottled shades of grey.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS668
SOMEONE joins his hands and bows.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS669
Later with his whistle between his lips, SOMEONE hefts the dead fish into the life boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS670
SOMEONE creeps out from his shelter.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS672
Standing on the raft grid, SOMEONE holds onto the boat's hull rope as he looks on.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS673
The tiger chomps down on the fish and drags it back into the shelter.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS674
The teen leans an ear close to the hull.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS675
SOMEONE plants both hands on the painted metal, then gently pushes off.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS676
On a starry night beneath a full moon, countless sea creatures swimming around the boat and raft give off a cerulean-hued phosphorescent glow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS677
From the boat's prow, the tether sets off the same luminescence where it submerges beneath the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS678
SOMEONE takes in the dazzling array of ocean life glowing beneath his raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS679
A few jelly fish gracefully open and shut their bells.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS681
Shifting to all fours on the grid, SOMEONE dips a hand into the ocean.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS682
The water gives off a sparkling glow with each motion of his hand.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS684
He turns and peers off into the distance with wide eyes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS685
The teen looks around cautiously then returns his attention to the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS686
His lips curl into a delighted child-like smile as he sets off the bright glow with strokes of his hand.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS688
As his movements gain intensity, the resulting glow gathers mass and brightness.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS689
It illuminates SOMEONE's grinning face as he plays.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS690
The boy slows to a halt, his smile fading.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS692
From the depths, a slowly glowing shape rapidly ascends between the raft and lifeboat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS693
It's a humpback whale.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS694
The creature leaps from the water as big as a small ship.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS695
SOMEONE stares as the gigantic whale corkscrews through the air, glowing water streaming from its fins.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS696
Descending, it lands on the tether and overturns the raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS697
SOMEONE plunges into the water along with the boxes of biscuits and cans of water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS699
he quickly makes his way back to the raft and climbs on board.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS700
From high above, we watch the whale create a luminescent trail as it swims an arc around the lifeboat and raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS701
It sprays brightly glowing water from its blow-hole then paddles away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS703
Now a long row of hash marks wraps around the prow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS704
Wearing his shirt as a turban,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS705
SOMEONE scratches yet another SOMEONE with his knife, then sheathes the blade.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS706
He pushes himself along the hull, standing on a new triangular version of the raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS707
Now holding the long wooden handle of a blunt-edged metal boat hook,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS708
SOMEONE tries to pry a grappling tool from the canvas cover.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS709
With no luck, he cautiously climbs from his raft onto the bow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS710
As he tugs at the grappling tool, SOMEONE emerges from his covered quarters. He faces SOMEONE with fangs bared.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS711
A fish suddenly whacks SOMEONE in the face. He falls onto the canvas and the fish flops beside him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS712
SOMEONE SOMEONE growls as several more shoot over the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS713
Glancing around with wide eyes, SOMEONE backs away from the tiger and grabs the flailing fish.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS714
The teen stands at the bow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS715
He hurls the fish at the tiger's mouth and it spreads wings. The flying fish makes a sharp turn and glides along the ocean.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS716
The both watch it fly away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS717
As they turn, hundreds of flying fish soar directly at them.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS718
SOMEONE SOMEONE frantically swipes at the small fish as SOMEONE shields his face.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS719
The fluttering silver creatures pelt his exposed torso.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS720
Glancing between his arms, SOMEONE watches his carnivorous shipmate bat fish from the air.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS721
The frothy surface seethes around the boat as countless flying fish skip along the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS722
SOMEONE flails atop the canvas, swinging his arms and body.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS723
As two fish skitter side by side, a larger fish snatches one.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS724
The companion fish dodges a breaching predator which we follow as it dips beneath the surface.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS725
A large spiny, fish rapidly cuts through the ocean and leaps out, landing in the boat. SOMEONE SOMEONE swipes at it as SOMEONE's eyes grow wide.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS726
SOMEONE wildly swings the boat hook, sticking the metal end in SOMEONE's mouth. Shaking his head, the tiger backs away and swipes at it. SOMEONE maintains his balance and keeps the boat hook between them.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS727
SOMEONE SOMEONE bares his fangs.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS728
The ferocious animal reluctantly backs away. Trembling, SOMEONE grabs his grappling tool and sticks it in the large fish. He heaves it onto the canvas and turns starting down SOMEONE SOMEONE as fish continue flying by.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS729
Beneath the angry tiger, a pile of fish writhe on the boat floor.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS730
SOMEONE SOMEONE backs away and focuses on the smaller fish.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS731
Grabbing the handle of the boat hook, SOMEONE stands tall atop the canvas. His chest heaves as he glares down at the tiger.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS732
A few fish continue passing by and they skip along the calming surface.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS733
The triangular raft floats beside the lifeboat as SOMEONE watches SOMEONE SOMEONE feast.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS734
At night, SOMEONE sits on the raft filleting the large fish he claimed.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS735
The vegetarian warily places a piece of fish in his mouth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS736
Without hesitation, he eagerly slices a large hunk of meat from the fish.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS737
SOMEONE takes in several big bites, filling his mouth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS738
Next day, he rubs ointment on a small shin wound and wraps it in gauze.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS739
Sitting on his raft, SOMEONE uses a knife to carve a wood panel from the boat into a slim, pointy spear.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS740
Now, standing on the canvas, he challenges SOMEONE SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS741
The tiger stalks along the port side bench as the teen creeps closer with his spear in hand.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS742
SOMEONE pokes the spear directly in front of SOMEONE's face and the beast pins back his ears to his head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS744
As the brave trainer inches forward, SOMEONE backs away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS745
Reaching the stern, the tiger lies down and kneads its massive paws on the port side bench.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS746
He gets a claw stuck in the wood and rips it free then shows his teeth to SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS747
The teen flinches but keeps his spear aimed at the tiger.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS748
SOMEONE SOMEONE beats his tail against the bench, then sits up and raises a front paw.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS749
He swats at the spear.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS750
Standing his ground, SOMEONE slowly turns his head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS751
Watching the tiger out of the corner of his eye, he extends the spear toward him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS752
SOMEONE SOMEONE swats it away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS754
As SOMEONE brings the spear back, the tiger angrily swipes with both paws and charges.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS756
Facing the beast, SOMEONE glares and shakes the spear.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS757
SOMEONE SOMEONE backs away and lies down at the stern.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS758
SOMEONE's gaze softens as he watches the dominated cat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS759
He reaches into a yellow pouch tied around his waist and pulls out a slab of fish.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS761
Glancing between the tiger and the bait, he cautiously slides it onto the spear.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS762
SOMEONE SOMEONE bares his teeth as SOMEONE slowly extends the reward.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS763
Closing his mouth, SOMEONE SOMEONE wiggles his nose and lip at the dangling morsel.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS764
SOMEONE keeps his eyes locked on the tiger's movement.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS765
He guides the cat's face to the bench and slides the food off the spear.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS766
SOMEONE SOMEONE happily indulges.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS767
Their eyes connect as the tiger looks up.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS768
And SOMEONE remains in the dominant position.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS769
He holds out the spear.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS771
SOMEONE taps the port side bench and tosses a piece of fish in the exact spot.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS772
Stepping forward, SOMEONE SOMEONE gobbles it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS773
As he paws back toward the stern, he glares at the teen.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS774
SOMEONE's mouth hangs open and he shows a slight grin, then glances at the other side of the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS775
He taps the starboard side and tosses a piece of fish.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS776
The tiger moves to it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS777
SOMEONE steps onto the port side bench and taps again, relocating the tiger with another piece.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS778
As he points at the canvas covered section at the bow of the boat,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS779
SOMEONE SOMEONE sits down on the starboard bench and scowls.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS780
SOMEONE's ears perk up as he shifts his gaze away from SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS781
Baring his teeth, the tiger backs away from the bow and SOMEONE lifts the spear.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS782
SOMEONE charges and the tiger scurries below.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS783
SOMEONE stares at the draped canvas with wide eyes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS784
SOMEONE SOMEONE remains underneath and the victorious teen sits back on the bench at the stern.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS785
He stays alert with the spear in hand.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS786
SOMEONE gazes with bewildered eyes. His dry, cracked lips rest slightly open.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS787
Later, he stands on the raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS788
Building a canvas canopy attached to a wooden cross.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS789
Rope tied from a crossbar to the raft holds the canopy flat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS790
SOMEONE SOMEONE watches from the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS791
SOMEONE lounges underneath in a makeshift net hammock.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS792
He takes out his survival journal and a pencil.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS793
Now, he stabs at sharks.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS794
On the raft, SOMEONE uses two pails as a dholak drum then suddenly stops.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS795
SOMEONE quickly stands and moves around the raft gazing at a massive school of dolphins.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS796
They dip in and out of the ocean about 100 feet away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS797
A flock of seagulls fly along with them.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS798
SOMEONE's smiling mouth hangs open as he follows their movement.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS799
Far behind them, a large ship appears on the horizon.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS800
SOMEONE waves his arms and stares ahead then quickly moves to the other side of the raft.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS801
He pulls a flare gun from his survival pack and checks the chamber.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS803
Facing the ship, he cocks the gun and raises it in the air.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS804
SOMEONE SOMEONE watches the flare burst in the sky and retreats below the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS805
SOMEONE reloads and aims again.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS806
He glances toward the ship then swiftly grabs another flare.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS807
Later, the ship resembles a speck on the horizon moving toward the massive setting sun.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS808
Orange signal smoke wafts from the raft as SOMEONE waves a different type of flare.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS809
Now only a small pink glow marks the horizon.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS810
On his raft, SOMEONE gazes out with defeated eyes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS811
He glances back at SOMEONE SOMEONE who sits calmly on the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS812
SOMEONE raises the flare gun beside his sullen face and fires upward.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS813
From a distance, the bright orange flare briefly illuminates the dark night sky and the screen fades to black.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS816
From directly overhead, we view sharks and large fish swimming just beneath the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS817
A massive whale shark slowly passes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS819
At night, reflections of stars glimmer on the black water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS821
The tiger remains still, keeping his gaze fixed.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS822
SOMEONE watches the mysterious cat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS823
SOMEONE's ear twitches and he slowly turns his head looking down into the dark ocean.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS824
Glancing from the regal beast's profile toward the water,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS825
SOMEONE climbs to his knees.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS826
The weakened teen gazes over the side of the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS828
Behind him, hundreds of stars sparkle across the calm, black sky.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS829
Beyond his reflection in the water, SOMEONE SOMEONE watches a slim fish swim by with a soft blue glow trailing behind it.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS830
Several more follow as we move through the tiger's image and below the surface.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS831
Now dozens of fish cut through the water and a shark swims into the school.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS832
A large squid emerges from the dark abyss.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS833
Pumping its tentacles, the squid propels itself farther from our view.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS834
As a large whale approaches, the squid latches onto its back.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS835
The whale frantically swims about with the flailing squid squeezing its long tentacles.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS836
Suddenly, the whale transforms into a jumble of zoo animals.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS837
As they burst apart, the squid becomes a school of scattering fish.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS838
A hippo, rhino, giraffe and other animals disperse.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS839
Mixed in with a sea turtle, manta ray and other sea life.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS840
A brilliant light zooms and reveals a snaggletooth angler fish with an illuminated antenna.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS841
Diving deeper into the abyss.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS842
Tiny particles erupt into vibrant pockets of glowing light.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS843
We move through a glowing orange trail and dissipating blue particles into an array of teal and purple bubbles.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS844
A glowing blue lotus flower quickly dissolves and forms into SOMEONE's beautiful mother.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS845
A pink creature swims before her smiling face as we zoom through her forehead into the blackness.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS846
Now the Tsimtsum lies on the ocean floor, a blue and teal glow surrounds the sunken ship.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS847
Our view suddenly backtracks out of the water through SOMEONE's bewildered reflection.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS848
Perched on the bench, SOMEONE SOMEONE watches his dazed shipmate.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS849
SOMEONE remains in a kneeling position, gazing over the side.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS851
the boat resembles a white speck on a vast black surface.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS853
As SOMEONE writes, the lead runs out on his only pencil.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS854
He lies over the journal and rolls the half inch stub between his fingers.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS855
Later, a thick cloud brews in the distance.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS856
Lightning flashes in the darkest section.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS857
SOMEONE glares at it, then faces SOMEONE SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS858
The tiger finishes grooming his paw and looks up.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS859
Now the raft floats on choppy water beside the bow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS860
SOMEONE unties his canvas canopy and takes down the wooden post.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS861
Kneeling on the raft, he quickly collects his tools as the agitated surface intensifies beneath him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS862
With his ears pinned back, SOMEONE SOMEONE takes cover under the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS863
SOMEONE secures his tools in the bow and grabs the journal.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS864
As a large wave sprays over, strong wind whips it away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS865
He falls forward and rolls off the canvas into the turbulent water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS866
SOMEONE watches the journal get sucked into the darkening sky.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS867
He climbs onto the boat and secures a rope around his torso.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS868
Rain pounds down as the boat rocks between surging waves. SOMEONE brushes his chin length hair from his face and sees a yellow beam of light protruding through a hole in the storm cloud.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS869
A massive lightning bolt smacks down beside the boat, spreading a web of brilliant electricity beneath the surface.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS870
A large wave knocks SOMEONE off the canvas and into the boat. He struggles to his feet.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS871
He pounds on the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS872
He stares into the sky with a huge smile then pulls himself to a crouching position on the bench. Ocean water pours over the frenzied teen as he rips the canvas free of each hook, trying to uncover his friend.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS875
A massive wave suddenly overtakes the lifeboat. It briefly suspends underwater then shoots through the surface.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS876
SOMEONE continues unhooking the canvas as the boat ramps off surging waves. He uncovers SOMEONE SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS878
The tiger flails around in the boat, desperately clawing at the side to keep his head above water. Perched on the bow, SOMEONE gazes at the panicked animal as swirling water covers them both. Lightning fills the sky.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS881
A wall of water crashes down knocking SOMEONE off the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS882
His raft floats atop the churning water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS883
With the rope around his waist, he climbs back up the side and flops onto the bench.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS884
Shaking his head, SOMEONE blinks rapidly and sees SOMEONE SOMEONE struggling across the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS885
The tiger manages to secure his front legs on the bench.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS886
SOMEONE glances behind him and pulls himself up, then crawls to his feet at the bow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS887
The teen grips the edge and steadies himself. Up ahead, the violent ocean surface pulls the raft farther from the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS888
SOMEONE gazes longingly after it, then glances back at SOMEONE SOMEONE and grabs the canvas cover.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS889
He struggles to secure it to the hooks along the bow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS890
In the distance, a brilliant lightning bolt strikes down followed by flashes of lightning throughout thin pockets in the clouds.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS891
Now SOMEONE secures the canvas to the final hook and cowers beneath.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS892
Water rushes along the boat and completely covers him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS893
As it recedes, he lies on the bench gasping for air.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS894
The boat rocks the water to the stern and washed SOMEONE SOMEONE off the bench toward SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS897
SOMEONE SOMEONE lies next to SOMEONE as the water recedes from them both.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS898
He desperately claws at the bench but the water in the rocking boat sweeps him back to the stern.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS899
SOMEONE watches the tiger climb onto the bench just as the water rushes back and submerges the teen.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS900
Now sun shines on SOMEONE's back through a hole in the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS901
Water calmly sweeps up over the bench waking him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS902
He looks across the boat at SOMEONE SOMEONE who sleeps on the bench in a small shaft of sunlight.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS903
Two feet of ocean water rocks from side to side in the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS905
Pushing more canvas back, SOMEONE squints as bright sun blankets his face.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS906
The rolling ocean settles from the storm.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS907
Sunlight shines on SOMEONE who stands atop the canvas covering the lifeboat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS908
A short length of rainbow prism light filters from the dark clouds on the horizon.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS910
Viewed from high overhead, the half covered lifeboat resembles a tiny, two-toned capsule adrift in a sea of black.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS911
The darkness rapidly lightens to a shimmering and opaque surface with reflected grey clouds.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS913
By the side of the boat, a few raindrops land in the water causing tiny, circular ripples.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS914
SOMEONE drinks from a plastic yellow pail.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS915
He lowers it to reveal dead sunken eyes and untamed black hair forming a nest around his drawn and weary face.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS916
His blurry gaze shifts into focus revealing SOMEONE SOMEONE, emaciated and lying on the bench with one arm dangling.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS917
SOMEONE gently steps toward him across the canvas cover.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS918
Holding the yellow container by his side.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS919
Using the rim of the boat for support, he steps onto the bench and approaches the resting beast.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS921
Standing back, he reaches out and tilts the container over SOMEONE's head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS922
A thin stream of water lands in the tiger's mouth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS923
The cat's lip reflectively curls barely exposing his razor sharp teeth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS924
The tiger swallows with a labored breath.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS926
With saddened eyes, SOMEONE lowers himself toward the resting creature.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS927
The gaunt voyager's hand trembles as he reaches toward the beast's massive head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS928
As he touches the fur of SOMEONE's brow, the cat briefly flinches then lies still.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS929
The teen's eyes glisten and his lips tremble.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS930
The tiger weakly looks up at him as SOMEONE strokes its forehead.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS931
He holds his hand still for a moment then pulls away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS933
Holding onto the rim of the boat, SOMEONE takes a seat beside the sickly animal.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS934
He places the yellow contain aside and slides closer to the tiger.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS935
SOMEONE lifts his companion's head without resistance,
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS936
and nestles close to the animal.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS937
He rests the tigers head on his lap and softly rubs its crown.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS938
He stares for a moment.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS939
Then looks up at the sky as despair wells in his eyes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS940
A teardrop travels down his face and neck.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS941
Drops of rain land on SOMEONE's sun-blistered face and chest.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS942
He leans close to the tiger.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS943
SOMEONE SOMEONE nuzzles his head on SOMEONE's lap.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS944
The teen rubs the tiger's head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS945
The boat drifts on the calm, grey water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS946
Fade to black.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS947
Now lying on the sun-dappled canvas, SOMEONE's eyes flutter open.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS948
A gentle breeze wafts through his bushy black hair.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS949
He gazes up with barely comprehending eyes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS950
He glances to the side.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS951
The lifeboat rests on a green and overgrown shore.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS952
Only feet from the water's edge, densely packed trees form a lush forest.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS953
SOMEONE rolls over and props himself up on his week arms.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS954
He crawls to the bow of the craft and peers down through a hole in the canvas.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS955
SOMEONE climbs off the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS956
As he steps on to terraferma, his legs give out and he falls.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS957
He picks himself up onto his knees and pulls from the boat the grappling tool attached to a rope.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS958
He anchors the tool firmly around a moss covered root.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS960
He removes a leafy bit, inspects it, then puts it in his mouth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS961
After a few curious bites he looks down.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS962
Tears up more of the leafy bits and shovels them into his mouth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS963
A wider view reveals tall, bushy trees towering over the lifeboat and all along the edge of what appears to be an island.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS964
SOMEONE tears off a chunk of root and inspects the light pink center within its dark green outer shell.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS965
He takes a large bite and chews.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS966
He closes his eyes and eats.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS967
Now SOMEONE walks through the forest of lanky green growth, similar to banyan trees.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS968
Branches intertwine over ahead creating shade as he passes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS969
A layer of densely interlocked roots covers the ground.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS970
SOMEONE climbs up a small hill using an arched root for support.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS971
He turns his head and approaches a crest.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS972
He looks out over a vast area where the ground seems to ungulate around several circular pools.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS973
Thousands of meerkats stand up straight with their tawny fur covered chests pumped out.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS974
Their whiskered snouts quiver as their darkly inset eyes peer in SOMEONE's directly.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS975
Now SOMEONE walks among the knee-high mammals, waving his hand at them.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS976
They scatter among bones on the ground.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS977
SOMEONE approaches a glistening pond surround by a three foot tall bank of roots.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS978
Meerkats run around him as he sits at the edge, reaching one foot down.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS979
He tests the water with his toes then drops in.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS980
He raises his head from the pond and looks around.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS982
Swimming forward, he opens his mouth wide and fills it with water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS983
SOMEONE tilts his head back and takes a big gulp.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS984
He smiles as he looks at the surrounding mass of water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS985
Viewed from overhead, meerkats surround the deep blue, almost-perfectly round pool with green roots fringing its perimeter.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS986
SOMEONE swims to the center, the rolls over and backstrokes beneath the sun.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS987
He swims to the edge of the pond.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS988
Now he rests against the root wall and splashes water on his face.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS989
Later he climbs out of the pond and notices the meerkats staring behind him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS990
He turns to see SOMEONE SOMEONE walking through the field of attentive little creatures.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS991
The tiger grabs a meerkat in his teeth and swings its lifeless body.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS992
SOMEONE presses his lips together with a resigned smile as SOMEONE SOMEONE lies down and eats his meal.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS994
SOMEONE treks through the forest on his own.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS995
Looking down, he stops and unties SOMEONE's string bracelet, unwrapping it from his wrist.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS996
He crouches down and ties it around a thick root.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS997
Later, a beam of light dissipates over the ocean as the sun lowers into the horizon.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS998
Soft, red light ripples over the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1000
SOMEONE ties a net between branches the width of his torso.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1001
He looks out over the field as thousands of meerkats stampede into the forest.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1003
The creatures climb into the trees. SOMEONE turns his head and sees SOMEONE SOMEONE springing toward the lifeboat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1004
The meerkats scatter up the branches around SOMEONE. A few crawl into his net.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1005
He pushes them away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1006
More surround him as he attempts to lie in the makeshift hammock.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1007
He smiles as a few of them jump on top of him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1008
At night, a meerkat yawns with his hind legs hanging over a branch.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1009
Its head slumps over and it falls toward another sleeping meerkat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1010
A group of them lie across the branch.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1011
A smaller one nuzzles noses with a tiny meerkat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1012
Then cuddles up with a larger one.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1014
SOMEONE rolls over in his hammock.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1015
A rippling blue and green light glows onto the bottom of the branch.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1016
A meerkat climbs onto SOMEONE's back and rests across his shoulder.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1017
SOMEONE's eyes open up and he peeks over the branch.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1018
He stands up and holds a branch for support.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1019
With his mouth ajar, he stares down at a pool emitting a phosphorescent blue/green light.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1020
The body of a large, dead fish surfaces and floats atop the water beside dozens of smaller dead fish.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1021
The soft light glows on SOMEONE's face as he looks down open mouthed.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1022
More fish die and float to the surface of the gurgling pool.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1023
SOMEONE's fearful gaze looks up.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1024
He trembles as a breeze brushes over the island's trees.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1025
A glowing light shimmers around the lifeboat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1026
SOMEONE SOMEONE sits up and stares inland as the boat lightly bobs on the water.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1027
Beneath him, the same eerie light surrounds the lifeboat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1028
From a distance, the island shows contours like that of the human body lying on its back.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1029
A teal light glows beneath, surrounding the entire island.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1030
Now SOMEONE rips a spherical object from a glowing branch.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1031
His eyes fixate on it as he spins it between his hands.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1032
Overlapping leaves surround the orb.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1033
As he peels back the layers, the inner part of the leaves glow along their veins.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1035
The leaves separate to reveal a black and yellow tooth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1036
His eyes fix on the weathered tooth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1037
Light reflects off his glistening face.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1038
Now at SOMEONE's house.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1039
At sunset, SOMEONE kneels on the lifeboats canvas cover and ties up bundles of roots.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1040
SOMEONE hops off the boat looking inland.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1041
He blows the whistle and stares up a hill.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1042
With his mouth open, SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE SOMEONE hurries down the hill toward him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1043
He un-anchors the hook from the root and waits for the tiger to hop on board.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1044
The boat floats into the distance.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1045
Later, SOMEONE tumbles off the side and grabs onto a rope connected to the bow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1046
Underwater, his feet graze the sand as he pulls the boat to shore.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1047
SOMEONE struggles with the boat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1048
Beyond the shore line, a jungle looms in the distance.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1049
SOMEONE collapses onto the sand as the boat sways with the waves.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1050
Later, SOMEONE lies prone on the beach, his arms out stretched from his sides.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1051
SOMEONE looks up as SOMEONE SOMEONE hops over him from the lifeboat.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1052
The tide washes over the tiger's claws.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1053
The scrawny tiger stretches and yawns.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1054
The tiger awkwardly ambles across the sand.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1055
Sand covers SOMEONE's face as he peers at the beast.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1056
Now at adult SOMEONE's house.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1057
He takes a long breath and blinks.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1058
On the beach, SOMEONE struggles to keep his head up but collapses.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1059
Later, a group of men jog toward him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1060
He stares into the jungle.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1061
Mouth agape.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1062
He stares and cries as they carry him away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1063
At his house, adult SOMEONE's eyes glisten.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1064
With his mouth open, the story teller stares at his guest.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1065
The writer lowers his gaze.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1066
He wipes his nose.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1067
A tear spills from his eye.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1068
His lips twitch and he looks down.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1069
The writer blinks at him then briefly glances away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1070
He watches SOMEONE wipe the tears from his cheeks.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1071
The writer lightly tilts his head and shifts his eyes.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1072
SOMEONE looks off then turns.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1073
He stands and approaches a cabinet.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1074
The writer takes the report.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1075
Now at the hospital.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1078
They stare at SOMEONE.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1079
The younger Japanese man stares at SOMEONE as the older one turns to him.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1081
The older man flips the tape in his recorder.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1082
They sit at the foot of SOMEONE's hospital bed.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1083
The older man nods and raises his eyebrows.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1084
SOMEONE swallows and looks off.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1085
The older SOMEONE leans back with his arms folded and gazes off.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1086
The teen survivor frowns.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1087
SOMEONE gives a conceding nod.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1088
SOMEONE allows a fawned, wistful smile.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1089
It fades and he takes on a haunted expression.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1090
SOMEONE lowers his eyes and shakes his head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1091
He bites his lower lip.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1092
The younger insurance rep solemnly faces his partner.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1093
The older man shifts his grim, compassionate gaze.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1094
SOMEONE faces the older man earnestly then looks away.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1095
As the young survivor hangs his head, the older insurance investigator faces his partner with a softened gaze.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1096
He looks back at the teen and his brow knits uneasily.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1097
The orphan's eyes fill with tears.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1098
SOMEONE's mouth twists willfully and his nostrils flare.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1099
He stares off mournfully.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1100
His expression hardens and SOMEONE turns his earnest gaze on the older man.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1101
Tears stream down his cheek.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1102
Facing the young investigator, SOMEONE sniffles and shakes his head.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1103
SOMEONE's parted lips show a chipped front tooth.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1104
He stares off with a haunted expression and takes a deep breath.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1105
At SOMEONE's house, the young writer stares off with parted lips and a furrowed brow.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1106
The middle aged SOMEONE faces his guest with a careworn gaze.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1107
The writer gives a slight frown.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1108
The writer gazes at the mild mannered older man.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1109
The young man nods.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1110
SOMEONE regards the younger man with a calm, sad expression.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1111
The writer shifts his gaze thoughtfully.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1112
His deep set eyes glistening. SOMEONE gives a faint smile.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1113
SOMEONE's smile grows.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1114
The writers eyes sparkle and the corners of his lips turn up.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1115
He lowers his eyes, tries to bite back his smile and fails.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1116
The two men share a warm smile.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1117
SOMEONE's eyes dart toward a window.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1118
SOMEONE crosses toward the door.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1119
Seated on a couch, the young writer glances after him then opens the insurance file.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1120
It contains a news clipping featuring SOMEONE at the end of his journey.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1121
Along with a document with a Japanese seal.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1122
The writer flips to the last page.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1123
The writer looks up from the file and beams.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1124
The writer shakes hands with SOMEONE's beautiful wife and children.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1125
Now the teenage SOMEONE floats on the ocean gazing toward us.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1126
As he smiles, the tiger appears to his left facing away from us. The boy fades from view and the sparkling ocean becomes the Mexican jungle.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1127
The powerful animal ventures into the lush forest.
LIFE_OF_PI_DVS1128
He vanishes within the thick, jungle growth.