A blizzard sweeps across the boy's disappointed gaze. Daytime. In Manhattan, a business man talks on his cell phone. 30 years later.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS24
SOMEONE smells the bound contract.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS25
Inside, SOMEONE faces a secretary.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS27
SOMEONE hands him the contract.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS28
SOMEONE points to a model ship.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS29
SOMEONE rocks SOMEONE's chair.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS30
He nods to SOMEONE who turns on a fan.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS31
He sprinkles SOMEONE with water from a pitcher.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS32
SOMEONE tosses scraps of newspaper.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS33
SOMEONE spins his client's chair.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS34
SOMEONE cocks an eyebrow at his assistant.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS35
He looks at SOMEONE who hands him a newspaper hat.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS36
He places the hat on his client's bald head.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS37
SOMEONE shuts his eyes, and shakes his head.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS38
SOMEONE pats him on the shoulder.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS39
As he and his assistant head out, SOMEONE swivels his chair to face them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS40
SOMEONE turns back with a smile. Now in a boardroom.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS41
He unveils a marble slab etched with Franklin, Popper, Reader and Yates.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS42
He grabs a chair.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS43
On a residential street.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS44
SOMEONE leaves his Town Car for a brownstone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS45
SOMEONE wraps his arms around him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS46
The bearded man holds him in a long, unblinking gaze.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS47
SOMEONE enters the house to find a boy dribbling a soccer ball.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS48
The boy kicks the ball into his groin and he collapses on the floor.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS49
He peeks in the refrigerator.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS50
The boy joins them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS51
A confused SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS52
A teenager comes downstairs.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS53
The teen plops on a couch with her cell phone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS54
SOMEONE and his son eye the girl.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS55
They swap a look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS56
SOMEONE ambles into the living room and stuffs his hands in his pockets.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS57
He sits beside his daughter who rolls her eyes.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS58
SOMEONE glances aside and subtly shakes his head.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS59
SOMEONE gets up.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS60
She storms out.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS61
SOMEONE stuffs his hands in his pockets.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS62
Now the Town Car parks.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS63
A doorman greets him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS64
Later, SOMEONE enters his spacious two-floor apartment.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS65
Glancing over the sleek black furnishings, he sets gift bags on a table.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS66
He takes off his sunglasses, then adjusts the dining room chair.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS67
He leans his hands on the table.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS68
SOMEONE looks around the immaculate living room.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS69
He takes out a cell phone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS70
In an office,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS71
SOMEONE sits and crosses his legs.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS72
SOMEONE stares off.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS73
Now the city's buildings stand against a muted dawn sky.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS74
An alarm clock reads, 6:30 AM.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS75
SOMEONE shuts it off and sits up on the side of his bed.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS76
Now fully dressed, SOMEONE opens his front door and finds a wooden crate waiting for him in a hallway.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS77
He removes the top and finds a frozen penguin inside.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS78
He removes the SOMEONE penguin from the crate and smirks as he sets it down on an end table.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS79
As SOMEONE turns, the penguin blinks and stretches its neck.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS80
It lifts its flippers.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS81
It shakes off ice chips from head to toe.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS82
He turns around.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS83
The penguin's gone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS84
He abruptly stands upright with his eyes wide, and his mouth slightly agape, then slowly turns to find the knee-high, black and white bird standing behind him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS85
He raises his cell phone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS86
Facing the penguin, he puts his cell phone back in his pocket.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS87
Eyeing the penguin he cautiously crouches down and pokes its white chest.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS88
The penguin glances around.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS89
SOMEONE leans in, reaching out to the flightless bird.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS90
He carefully grabs the penguin by the waist and picks it up.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS91
SOMEONE stands upright, gazing at it.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS92
White bird droppings land on his black leather shoe. He sours and carries the penguin away. Later, SOMEONE dumps ice into a bathtub.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS93
He pats the tub.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS94
In the living room.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS95
SOMEONE walks into the crate, breaking it apart and sending an envelope sliding under a dresser.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS96
He rubs his shins.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS97
He grabs his briefcase and leaves.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS98
Our view presses in on the envelope.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS99
Now in Central Park, SOMEONE jogs to the Tavern on The Green, a quaint brick restaurant. Inside, SOMEONE paces.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS100
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS101
He offers his hand for a shake, but the wealthy old woman holds hers out for a kiss. SOMEONE gives it a quick peck.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS102
In a dining room with crystal chandeliers, she leads him past four staff members.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS103
SOMEONE and SOMEONE eye him flatly.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS104
She leads him to a corner table.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS105
At the apartment, the penguin pecks at the tub, then tries to hop on a ledge and accidentally turns on a faucet.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS106
It dunks its head under the running water.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS107
At Tavern on The Green.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS108
He gazes at the corner table.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS109
Mrs. SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE stands and SOMEONE joins him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS110
Meanwhile in SOMEONE's bathroom water trickles over the edge of the tub and onto the floor.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS111
As more flows from the faucet, the penguin swims and dives in the overflowing bath.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS112
Later, SOMEONE arrives at home and makes a call.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS113
He heads upstairs.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS114
Behind the bathrooms glass paneled door, the penguin swims by.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS115
He reaches for the bathroom door.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS116
As he opens it, water gushes out, knocking SOMEONE down.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS117
Engulfing him, it washes over the staircase landing, to the floor below.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS118
SOMEONE's fingers clutch the landing's edge as he dangles over his dining area.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS119
The penguin approaches.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS120
The bird poises its rear above SOMEONE's face.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS121
As it releases a stream of white droppings, SOMEONE lets go of the landing.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS122
Later he makes a call.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS123
He drops his phone into a blender. Sparks flash as he turns it on.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS124
Now he answers his door.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS125
The penguin appears behind him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS126
Another official.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS127
The sanitation man leaves. Nighttime.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS128
SOMEONE lies on his couch with a laptop and navigates a website called, The Penguin Recipe Page.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS129
He notices his own penguin watching him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS130
As the bird tilts his head curiously, SOMEONE minimizes the recipe window.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS132
SOMEONE sleeps with the closed computer still on his lap.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS133
His limp hand slides off the couch's edge.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS134
The penguin waddles to his side.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS135
Leaning closer, it eyes the weary man.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS137
As SOMEONE sleeps soundly, his penguin watches with its beak mere inches from his face.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS138
Waking up, SOMEONE finds himself staring straight into the birds open beak. Later.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS139
He ushers it into the hall.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS140
He points.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS141
The penguin stares at him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS142
SOMEONE notices a vase of flowers sitting on a table in the hallway.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS143
He pours the vase's water down the hall.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS144
He grabs the bird.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS145
He tosses it onto the path of water.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS146
The penguin slides away on its belly.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS147
Later, SOMEONE passes the building's front desk.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS148
He holds it up.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS149
SOMEONE sets the penguin on the floor, then turns to a computer.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS150
He pulls up security footage of SOMEONE tossing the penguin down the hallway.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS151
He shows a closer image of SOMEONE cheering and freezes it.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS152
SOMEONE hands it over.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS153
SOMEONE offers a SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS154
SOMEONE looks at the bird standing behind him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS155
SOMEONE hands him more cash.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS156
He doles out even more.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS157
SOMEONE feels SOMEONE's face.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS158
SOMEONE returns to his apartment.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS159
A neighbor emerges.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS160
SOMEONE's smile fades and his eyes shift.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS161
He backs through his doorway.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS162
Later, on a nature program,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS163
as SOMEONE ties a ribbon on a gift box, his penguin steps closer to the television.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS164
It examines its flippers, then flaps them as it watches a soaring eagle on the nature show.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS165
He picks up the TV remote.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS166
He changes the channel to a news program called, The Squawk Box. The penguin waddles over and unties the gift's ribbon.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS168
Opening the door, SOMEONE finds a wooden crate.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS169
With its flippers extended behind it, the penguin hurries over.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS170
SOMEONE removes a panel on the crate.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS171
The penguin runs off and SOMEONE gives chase.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS172
Two penguins exit the crate.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS173
He places his penguin in the crate.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS174
As he turns away, two of them run out.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS175
Two more escape unseen.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS176
With a confused look, SOMEONE sets his penguin down and heads into the kitchen. He finds a penguin eating from a tipped trashcan.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS177
In the bathroom, he finds a penguin in the toilet.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS178
The bird spins with the flushing water. SOMEONE grabs it.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS179
Covering his ears he drops the penguin.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS180
His gaze shifts to the dining area. As he heads over, the bathroom penguin follows.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS181
SOMEONE jumps in surprise. In the dining area he finds three more birds. A fourth slides down the stairs.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS182
He finds a fifth atop a panel fountain.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS183
He opens a tin of sardines.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS184
The penguins charge at him. Now he answers the door.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS185
A penguin appears at his feet.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS186
The other penguins run over.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS187
He points at his original penguin.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS188
A second bird approaches.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS189
A third nips at SOMEONE's leg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS190
A fourth lifts its rear.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS191
A fifth nestles SOMEONE's leg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS192
They see the sixth bird running into a wall. It stumbles back, then does it two more times.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS193
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS194
She touches his arm.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS195
She nods skeptically.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS196
SOMEONE chases a penguin out of the room. His sister and the other birds follow.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS197
In the kitchen,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS198
two penguins nuzzle in a refrigerator drawer.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS199
SOMEONE cracks open the door.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS200
He spots one.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS201
He points at the cake, then backs into the hall.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS202
As SOMEONE heads back inside, SOMEONE makes a call.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS203
In the apartment,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS204
as SOMEONE hugs his father, the penguins gather at SOMEONE's legs. Joining them, Nimrod trips. Later, a cab pulls up outside.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS205
To SOMEONE
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS206
She hits him playfully.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS207
SOMEONE hugs him, then climbs into the cab. His mother smiles at her ex.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS208
She enters the cab and it drives off. SOMEONE grins at a passing man.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS210
SOMEONE lies awake in bed, his eyes wide.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS211
Downstairs the penguins run in circles.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS212
They see SOMEONE on the staircase landing.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS213
He glares, then starts to walk away.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS214
He gives a crazed look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS216
SOMEONE slaps off his alarm, then frowns at a sleeping penguin with its head against his arm.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS217
He finds all of the birds in his bed.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS218
As Stinky's tail feathers rise and fall on Nimrod's face, the bird tries to shake them away, but rolls off the bed.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS219
Now in the kitchen, SOMEONE makes espresso.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS220
The penguins crowd him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS221
As he stows a wine bottle, Bitey nips him. He spills his espresso. A penguin pecks at a remote.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS222
The bird hits buttons with its beak, and the TV turns on.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS223
As the penguins move closer, SOMEONE follows and sees SOMEONE SOMEONE walking like a penguin.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS224
One penguin waddles, then turns imitating SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS225
He gives a thoughtful look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS226
Now wearing his suit and jacket, the passes the living room and finds the penguins still mesmerized by SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS227
He leaves. Now at work, he and SOMEONE hurry up a staircase.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS228
SOMEONE hands him an invite.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS229
He grins.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS230
His bosses leave.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS231
She reads.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS232
He reads from the printout.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS233
At home, SOMEONE keeps his balcony doors open.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS234
He wears his coat as he feeds the penguins. His kids arrive.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS235
Now at the park, SOMEONE kicks a soccer ball while SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE on a bench. The penguins crowd him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS236
As he waves, the penguins take a step back. Beside him, SOMEONE texts on her cell and SOMEONE gives a disappointed look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS237
The penguins find a pigeon amid them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS238
It flies off, and Captain watches, its flippers flapping.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS239
SOMEONE meets the penguins gaze.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS240
Captain flaps again.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS241
Captain looks down.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS242
SOMEONE catches the ball.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS243
He tosses it back, then joins SOMEONE. The penguins follow.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS244
SOMEONE passes the ball. As SOMEONE kicks it back, the penguins play with them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS245
The ball rolls over to SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS246
He mimes texting.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS247
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS248
She stands.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS249
SOMEONE kicks the ball and it smashes SOMEONE's face.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS250
SOMEONE falls back. The penguins imitate him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS251
Later, tissue hangs from SOMEONE's nostril as he watches a family board an elevator.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS252
SOMEONE smiles.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS253
He gives SOMEONE more cash.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS255
Nimrod bumps into a wall, then waddles off alone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS256
SOMEONE counts his cash.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS257
Later, under blankets, the family watches SOMEONE get blown across a snowy cabin.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS258
SOMEONE enters with a penguin in her hands.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS266
Smiling, SOMEONE sits. She watches the SOMEONE movie, then grins at her ex-husband.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS279
SOMEONE steps around the couch and SOMEONE follows.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS280
She gives SOMEONE a kiss.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS281
She hugs SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS283
As she turns to SOMEONE, they almost kiss, but hug instead.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS284
He watches her step out.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS285
The kids notice their father's lingering gaze.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS287
SOMEONE stands awkwardly.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS292
Now the penguins sleep on SOMEONE's bed.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS293
SOMEONE eyes them, brushing his teeth.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS294
He wears a thick vest and gloves.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS295
Now on his cell.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS299
With an older woman.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS302
He leads her to the penguins who watch SOMEONE. The babysitter stares, then faces him plainly.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS303
Nighttime. SOMEONE steps outside in a tuxedo and waves to hail a cab.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS304
He drops his arm to his side, checks his watch, then marches off.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS305
Crossing a row of street vendors he notices a five foot tall stuffed penguin standing at the end.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS306
SOMEONE reaches into his jacket and takes out his cell phone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS307
The babysitter sits on a remote control and the channel changes to a show featuring a sea lion.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS308
Frightened, the penguins charge the babysitter who runs out of the apartment leaving the front door open.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS309
One penguin holds the door for the others as they leave.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS310
Nimrod bumps into the dresser on his way out.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS311
In the lobby, Kent faces SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS312
SOMEONE sees the penguins leaving the elevator.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS313
Outside the penguins cross a wet sidewalk bordered by mounds of snow.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS314
They reach the curb, then hop onto the street and march off in single file.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS315
Now taxis drive past the Guggenheim, a white cylindrical building reminiscent of a beehive. Elegant guests gather inside the multitiered rotunda where SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a bottle of Champaign.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS316
She smiles in her elegant lavender gown.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS317
Meanwhile, the penguins pass the row of street vendors.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS318
Lovey slows to a stop on spotting the giant stuffed penguin.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS319
He bows.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS320
The white-chested penguin bears a black SOMEONE over his heart.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS321
As the penguin swoons, another approaches.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS322
Lovey follows the penguin off.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS323
With their flippers up, the line of penguins walks past the Metropolitan Museum of Art.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS324
At the Guggenheim,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS325
a server brings Champaign.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS326
The server leaves. SOMEONE unwraps his bottle and pops the cork.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS327
As an old man yawns, SOMEONE casually catches the cork before it enters his mouth.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS328
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE go, then leans back on a railing next to a white-haired man.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS329
Sipping form a bottle, SOMEONE eyes the man.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS330
He holds the bottle as if pouring it into his ear, and spits Champaign. He tosses the bottle in a trash can.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS331
He heads off.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS332
Outside, Captain sniffs around, leading the group down a sidewalk en route to the Guggenheim.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS333
Inside, our view roves up the museum's spiraling tiers. SOMEONE and Mrs. SOMEONE stand before a painting of a large black dot.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS334
SOMEONE spots the penguins on a lower tier across the rotunda. They spot him too.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS335
As they head up the spiral SOMEONE watches them over her shoulder.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS336
He escorts her to an elevator.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS337
The penguins catch up.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS338
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step onboard and the elevator doors shut the penguins out.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS339
As Captain leads the group back down the spiral, he collides with a server's white barrel, spilling water onto the smooth floor. The penguins dive on their bellies, using the wet floor to slide down the long, sloping, continuous spiral.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS340
A man steps out of their way.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS341
Dancing with SOMEONE, SOMEONE looks up.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS342
SOMEONE does the same.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS343
On their way down, the penguins trip a couple and rip off a woman's dress.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS344
More patrons jump out of their way. SOMEONE looks over SOMEONE's shoulder. As a man tips over the railing, his date catches his leg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS346
SOMEONE waves his hands in her face.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS348
Captain trips another server. Spotting an elderly man with a walker, the penguin tucks in its flippers and shoots between his legs.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS349
Reaching a smooth silver sculpture, the penguins launch into the air.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS350
SOMEONE shields SOMEONE's view as they all crash into a band.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS351
The dancing patron's part, giving Mrs. SOMEONE a view of the penguins. Bitey bites a server's leg, Lovey hugs a woman, and Stinky farts.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS352
SOMEONE points out a woman in a black and white dress.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS353
Captain spots SOMEONE who tries to slip out.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS354
Mrs. SOMEONE sees the penguins chasing SOMEONE to the exit.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS355
Squinting after them, she leans back.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS356
Later, a taxi arrives at SOMEONE's apartment building.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS357
SOMEONE steps out of the cab.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS358
Single file, the penguins follow him inside.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS359
Watching from a parked SUV, SOMEONE raises a cell phone to his ear.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS360
Daytime at work
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS361
Now at the apartment
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS362
SOMEONE buries her face in her gloved hands.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS363
SOMEONE follows her to the elevator.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS367
They exit into the lobby.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS389
She gets in an SUV and shuts the door. SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS397
Later in the bathroom.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS408
Captain waddles near and nestles his beak against his leg. SOMEONE looks up.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS410
He picks the penguin up and it poops in the toilet.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS412
He picks up another penguin and holds it over the toilet.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS414
Now in the living room.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS415
As SOMEONE crosses the room, the penguins follow.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS416
Later, SOMEONE studies a YouTube video showing trained penguins.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS417
Now, kids hold onto a rope as they walk between two chaperones.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS418
SOMEONE passes with his penguins on a walking rope.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS419
At the dinner table SOMEONE closes his eyes.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS420
As SOMEONE eats his dinner with chopsticks, the penguins eat from plates of fish. A few hop on the table.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS421
Now SOMEONE leads his penguins across a footbridge.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS422
He stops and allows them to walk between his legs, then waddles on after them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS423
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter the apartment.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS424
Standing in a row, SOMEONE and the penguins dance in sync.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS425
Nimrod tips over.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS426
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE checking a text message on her cell phone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS427
Later, at a clothing store, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sleep on a couch. A dress flips over a curtain rod, and an employee brings another one.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS428
SOMEONE steps out in a silver dress, her long hair draped over one shoulder.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS429
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit up.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS430
SOMEONE beams. SOMEONE turns to a mirror.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS431
SOMEONE pats his dad on the shoulder.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS432
They enter the apartment.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS433
SOMEONE crosses to the living room where the penguins gather around a scattering of stones from a hearth.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS434
She kneels on the floor.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS435
A penguin backs up to reveal an egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS436
SOMEONE crouches down to find another egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS438
Lovey wanders off.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS439
The penguin turns back, then scurries out as SOMEONE joins them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS440
SOMEONE steps aside and makes a phone call.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS441
SOMEONE sits at a restaurant.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS442
Now, SOMEONE answers the door for her and SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS443
SOMEONE approaches a penguin.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS444
The penguin bites his hand.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS445
Bitey leaves and another penguin approaches.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS446
Loudy charges, beak wide open.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS447
SOMEONE backs to the door.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS448
SOMEONE shakes her head.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS449
SOMEONE urges a penguin back to reveal her egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS450
SOMEONE and SOMEONE leave them. SOMEONE points to a penguin sitting on the snow globe.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS452
He rubs his chest.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS453
He zips his fly.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS454
SOMEONE faces all the penguins
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS455
He answers his cell.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS456
He hangs up.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS457
Lovey exchanges a look with Captain.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS458
Now at Tavern on the Green, a hostess leads SOMEONE and SOMEONE to the corner table.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS459
At a nearby table, he pulls a chair out for SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS460
The hostess hands them menus.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS461
SOMEONE eyes the corner table.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS462
He forces a smile, then shoots the corner table another glance.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS463
SOMEONE looks at the table again, and SOMEONE follows his tense gaze.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS464
In a flashback, young SOMEONE sits at the table with his parents and opens a gift.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS465
SOMEONE shakes her head at him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS466
Later, SOMEONE holds open the restaurant's door as SOMEONE walks outside.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS467
He offers his arm and she takes it.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS468
As they head away, Mrs. SOMEONE watches from a window.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS469
Now the former couple ice skates on an outdoor rink.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS470
He faces her.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS471
SOMEONE trips. Falling back he pulls SOMEONE down with him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS472
She lands on top of him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS473
He holds her gaze.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS474
She gives him an unsure look, then smiles.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS475
Now SOMEONE wears a dreamy smile as he strolls the hall to his apartment.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS476
He finds SOMEONE standing in his open doorway.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS477
Drawing closer, he sees SOMEONE inside feeding the penguins.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS478
He grabs the sandwich.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS479
As he dangles a fish, Nimrod trips out of the cheese drawer and waddles over.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS480
The others flock to the zookeeper, including Captain who leaves SOMEONE's side.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS481
SOMEONE gives them a sulky look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS483
Daytime, at a fish market
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS484
SOMEONE scoops up fish.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS485
He lifts a fish to his nose.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS486
Later, he shovels snow from his terrace into his apartment.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS487
HIs kids arrive and gape at the snow covered living room.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS488
SOMEONE spots them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS489
SOMEONE hits him with a snowball.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS490
He throws a snowball at his son.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS491
SOMEONE steps into the doorway and sees SOMEONE slipping in the snow as he grabs his son.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS492
SOMEONE puts snow down SOMEONE's pants.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS493
Using his phone, SOMEONE films as SOMEONE fills SOMEONE's hood with snow, then pushes it over her head.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS494
SOMEONE smiles.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS495
SOMEONE looks over.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS496
Bitey nips SOMEONE's leg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS497
SOMEONE drops his phone. Carrying it in its beak, the penguin drops the cell in a tub of ice water.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS498
In the tub, Stinky glances at rising water bubbles. At dawn
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS499
Wrapped in comforters, they head into the living area.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS500
An egg begins to hatch.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS501
Sitting between his kids, SOMEONE wraps his arms around them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS502
They watch as the egg's crack grown larger.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS503
The bird's head pops out.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS504
SOMEONE holds his kids tighter as he gazes at the tiny bird.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS505
Another baby emerges from its egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS506
Stepping out of its egg, the baby trips.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS507
Grinning, SOMEONE shoots her dad a tearful glance.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS508
The family notices Captain staring at an unhatched egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS509
The bird nudges it with its beak.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS511
In the snow covered apartment, SOMEONE builds a snowman.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS512
SOMEONE ice skates from room to room, and SOMEONE chases him with a hockey stick.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS513
One penguin makes a snow angel.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS514
SOMEONE hockey stops in front of SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS515
She throws a snowball at him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS516
As SOMEONE arrives, Nimrod tumbles down a slide covering the stairs.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS517
SOMEONE gapes at the scene.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS518
She cocks her head at the unhatched egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS519
He pushes her back with his stick. Later, outside the elevator, SOMEONE play-punches SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS520
As the elevator closes with his family inside,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS521
SOMEONE smiles and waves.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS522
Back in his apartment, Captain glances at the two baby penguins.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS523
SOMEONE blows on his hands.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS524
Nighttime. SOMEONE drifts off on the phone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS525
He stares at the unhatched egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS527
SOMEONE sleeps curled up on the floor facing the unhatched egg in Captain's rocky nest.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS528
He wakes up and furrows his brow. Answering the door he finds SOMEONE and his bosses.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS529
Yates pushes his way inside.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS530
He brushes some snow off a couch and sits, crossing his legs casually.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS531
Reader approaches Captain's egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS532
SOMEONE blocks him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS533
Crouching he reaches for the unhatched egg, then turns to his bosses.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS534
SOMEONE gives a resigned look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS535
SOMEONE's eyes remain on the egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS536
As the men head out, SOMEONE blinks bewilderedly.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS537
SOMEONE pats his back. SOMEONE waves.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS538
Now SOMEONE wipes snow off his laptop and opens it.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS539
On Google's search page he types:
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS540
PENGUIN EGG EMERGENCY HATCH HOW
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS541
Later, on his terrace, he builds a small covering with wooden beams with blankets draped across them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS542
He places the egg underneath, in a rock nest snuggled within a blanket.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS544
SOMEONE sits on the terrace. His back propped against one of the covering's six foot legs and stares at the unhatched egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS546
He heats a spoon on a turbine vent, then glances at the egg as he eats from a pot.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS548
His hands hover around the egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS549
He lifts his hands from the egg and stares with devastated eyes.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS550
Sitting back, he clutches himself.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS552
SOMEONE crouches over the egg and presses a stethoscope to it.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS553
Standing nearby,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS554
SOMEONE watches as the zookeeper listens carefully.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS555
SOMEONE lifts his gaze to the rugged, unshaven man and shakes his head.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS556
SOMEONE's shoulders heave, and he gives an anguished look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS557
With a final glance at the egg, he trudges off.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS558
Later, he stands on the terrace with his back to the open doorway.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS559
Behind him, in the apartment, the penguins cluster together and watch him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS560
SOMEONE approaches.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS561
SOMEONE continues to stare off.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS562
The penguin owner shifts his sad eyes.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS563
Turning slightly he gives SOMEONE a nod, then faces the city again.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS564
SOMEONE smiles.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS565
As he crouches in front of the penguins, they move a few steps away.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS566
SOMEONE backs into the apartment and pulls the terrace door shut.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS567
Now in the boardroom at SOMEONE, Reader and Yates, a young man displays a photo of the Statue of Liberty with a similar statue right next to it.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS568
SOMEONE watches them leave.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS569
Later, outside the apartment,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS570
SOMEONE races into the apartment and finds it returned to its original state.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS571
His smile fades as he gazes around the immaculate living room.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS572
He turns to SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS573
SOMEONE blinks back tears.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS574
She turns away.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS575
As SOMEONE follows her upstairs, SOMEONE watches, then turns to her ex-husband.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS576
He sits.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS577
SOMEONE gives a wounded look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS578
She heads to the door.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS579
She glares at the back of his head.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS580
Without turning, he nods.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS581
As SOMEONE storms out of the apartment, SOMEONE stares with a frown.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS582
Later, he gazes sadly at his laptop as he clicks through photos of the penguins.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS583
Lovey stands in some snow.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS585
In another, two penguins look down at their egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS587
Riding in a limo, SOMEONE makes a call.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS588
In his apartment, SOMEONE drops his keys.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS589
He lowers himself onto his hands and knees and peers under the dresser.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS590
His keys sit in front of the envelope from inside Captain's crate.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS591
Furrowing his brow, he slides the envelope out and stares at the handwritten name on its front.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS593
with a wistful look,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS594
he stands and slips his finger under the envelope's flap.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS595
Opening it, he pulls out a letter and reads.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS596
SOMEONE swallows.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS597
As he lifts his gaze toward the second floor, his face hardens in a resolute look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS598
Now he leads SOMEONE and SOMEONE to the limo.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS599
SOMEONE climbs in after them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS600
The kids high-five.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS601
Now at the press conference, Mrs. SOMEONE stands at a podium.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS602
She notes an empty seat beside SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS603
In the limo, SOMEONE nods at SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS604
He leans closer.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS605
She offers him her phone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS606
With a smile, he takes the phone and dials, then lifts it to his ear.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS607
In a cab, SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS608
He looks at his kids.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS609
They nod. SOMEONE smiles sadly.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS610
SOMEONE grins at her brother.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS611
In the cab, SOMEONE lowers the phone with a thoughtful look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS612
She glances at SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS613
Now at the zoo's ticket booth
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS614
The SOMEONE enter the cavern-like penguin exhibit.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS615
They burst into SOMEONE's office, and find him on the phone.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS616
Mr. SOMEONE opens a holding tank.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS617
Bitey nips at SOMEONE's finger.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS618
Luring the birds with sardines, he steps into the holding tank. Mr. SOMEONE shuts him in.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS619
Later, in a veterinary lab, he finds a stack of surgical masks.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS620
In SOMEONE's office,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS621
a guard opens the tank door
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS623
Zoo-goers hustle away from the masked family.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS624
He points to a door, but SOMEONE emerges.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS625
SOMEONE swivels his pointed arm.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS626
Removing their masks, the SOMEONE walk nonchalantly into a gift shop, followed by the penguins in single file.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS627
Nimrod bumps into a fixture and stumbles,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS628
bringing up the rear.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS629
Captain gets her webbed foot twisted in a kite string dangling from a high shelf.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS630
She turns in a circle becoming entwined. A basketball tumbles from the shelf and knocks her to the floor.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS631
Two guards, armed with nets, spire from the entrance.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS632
Captain flees with a colorful kite strapped to her back which knocks toys off display shelves as she runs past. She escapes into an elevator.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS633
Outside, SOMEONE paces by the limo.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS634
Nearby, a big guard intercepts a mother and daughter trying to leave the zoo. SOMEONE checks her cell phone. A text from Mr. SOMEONE reads: Produce a perturbance! SOMEONE eyes her boss lingering in a doorway. She gives him a nod, then strides toward the guard, swoons, and falls on her back.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS635
The SOMEONE sneak out.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS636
The family nears the guard crouching over SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS637
SOMEONE turns a corner and spots the SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS638
As the group races to the limo, SOMEONE wrestles the big guard to the ground. SOMEONE swings a catch pole and misses. Mr. SOMEONE closes and latches the zoo's gates, locking him inside.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS639
They see Captain sliding down to the edge of a high rooftop. The two guards follow close behind.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS640
She peers at the ground below.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS641
Flapping her flippers, she steps to the precipice.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS642
She jumps! As she plummets head first toward the ground, the
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS643
kite on her back spreads like wings and she soars into the air.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS644
Mr. SOMEONE fearfully opens his eyes, and gapes.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS645
As she soars over SOMEONE, he readies his catch-pole. Mr. SOMEONE grabs it and pulls it through the bars of the gate.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS646
He tightens the cable loop around SOMEONE's wrists. Captain swoops to the limo and drops into its open sunroof.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS647
With the pole, he shoves SOMEONE's hands into his face.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS648
He anchors the pole, securing the SOMEONE's bound hands between the bars.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS649
He leaves.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS650
In the limo
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS651
The big guard helps free SOMEONE who races to a worker passing in a golf cart.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS652
He throws him out, then speeds off in the cart. Now at the press conference
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS653
Mr. SOMEONE bursts in, pretending to run in slow motion.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS654
SOMEONE arrives with the police.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS655
He sees SOMEONE trying to wrangle the approaching penguins.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS656
SOMEONE takes out a sardine.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS657
With a penguins between them, they each take a few steps back.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS658
Mr. SOMEONE gives a confident nod.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS659
As SOMEONE wiggles the sardine. The penguins glance at his rival, then return their gazes to the fish.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS660
As they move toward the sardine, Captain glances uneasily at Mr. SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS661
SOMEONE smiles.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS662
Captain addresses the others.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS663
The penguins rush back to the SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS664
Mrs. SOMEONE smiles, and her staff claps.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS665
He starts a round of applause.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS666
SOMEONE brings Mrs. SOMEONE a cell phone and she speed-dials a call.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS667
The cop shakes her hand.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS668
He grins.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS669
With a smitten look, she leaves with him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS670
Mr. SOMEONE glances at his bosses.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS671
She looks toward the corner table.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS672
Reader and Yates exchange a glance.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS673
Springtime. The SOMEONE pass colorful flower beds as they approach the building. Inside, the hostess takes four menus reading, "Tavern on the Green. A SOMEONE, Reader, Yates and SOMEONE subsidiary," and leads the guests into the dining area.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS674
At a small table, SOMEONE and Quint pause their conversation and gaze at Mr. SOMEONE as he passes.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS675
He gives them a pleased look.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS676
SOMEONE gins as he crosses his path with a pitcher of water.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS677
Pointing his finger like a gun, Mr. SOMEONE smiles at a table where his business partners dine with Mrs. SOMEONE.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS678
The old woman beams at him.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS679
With a wistful look, he watches the hostess set the menus on four place settings at the corner table.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS680
He gives a wide grin, then sits with his family.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS681
The kids fist-bump.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS682
Holding her gaze, Mr. SOMEONE twitches a faint smile.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS683
A gust of snowflakes obscures our view, then clears to reveal the family in goggles and winter coats with fur-lined hoods.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS684
They walk a snowy arctic ridge.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS685
The six penguins and two babies walk in single file behind them.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS686
Below the ridge, hundreds of penguins mill around a snow-packed shore.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS687
As the family heads down to them,
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS688
their penguins drop to their bellies and slide past their feet.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS689
Nimrod tumbles last.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS690
Groups of penguins greet the new arrivals.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS691
Three penguins collide then fall over.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS692
SOMEONE sees Captain waddling off to the side.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS693
The lone penguin flaps her flippers, then hangs her head.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS694
Mr. SOMEONE heads over to the reluctant penguin and crouches in front of her.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS695
He nudges her.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS696
She steps back to reveal an egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS697
Captain flaps her flippers.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS698
Leaving their kids with Captain, he wraps an arm around SOMEONE's shoulders as they look out at the other penguins.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS699
SOMEONE and SOMEONE join their parents.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS700
Mr. SOMEONE wraps his arm around his daughter, and SOMEONE pulls her son in close.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS701
Behind them a penguin runs over to Captain and nuzzles with her.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS702
They look down at her egg.
MR_POPPERS_PENGUINS_DVS703
As the four SOMEONE gaze down at the crowd of penguins, our view lifts back over the snowy ridge and widens to show an ice burg in the rippling ocean beyond.