He stares off nostalgically.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS15
Later SOMEONE sits with his boss.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS16
Now the aging announcer wears a fedora as he looks out at the empty ballpark.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS17
He somberly walks away past a giant poster featuring his head with a Fresno Grizzly's hat.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS19
As SOMEONE leaves the lights go out one by one.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS21
Later outside a ranch style home A vintage red convertible Mustang sits in the driveway. Its license plate reads DAVOICE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS22
SOMEONE site in the driver's seat watching a stuffed grizzly bear swing from the rear view mirror.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS23
Inside the house, a short blonde in her 60s exhaustively works out on a stripper pole. An instructor leads her and three other middle-aged women on their own poles.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS24
SOMEONE exits his car and approaches the front door.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS25
SOMEONE enters.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS26
He despondently passes the women.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS27
SOMEONE watches her husband slump into the kitchen.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS29
SOMEONE looks down, then hugs his wife.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS30
Now an aerial view shows the Atlanta skyline. in a large suburban home a wall mounted screen turns on.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS34
A boy in only a cape and underwear rides in on a scooter.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS35
SOMEONE rushes to his father.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS37
The wavy haired man pulls his wife across the patio and kisses her.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS39
They embrace. Now on the phone.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS40
Nighttime in the master bedroom.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS41
He holds out a phone.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS42
She hesitantly takes it and dials. Holding the phone to her ear. She listens for a moment then drops it.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS43
She squirms.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS44
They stare into each other's eyes.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS45
As they kiss, SOMEONE jumps on the bed.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS46
Now on the SOMEONE's patio, SOMEONE cooks at the grill. Inside, SOMEONE listens to the iPod.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS49
SOMEONE slides the phone into a dock.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS50
SOMEONE glances at her husband.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS51
SOMEONE shakes his head and mouths no.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS52
SOMEONE's jaw drops.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS53
He watches her walk away and sighs.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS54
Now at the airport, a TSA agent searches SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS55
He turns his head.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS57
Smiling SOMEONE takes his wife's hand.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS60
She pulls them all into a hug. The taxi pulls into the driveway.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS61
The children peer through the window blinds.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS62
SOMEONE's eyes widen as she watches SOMEONE emerge from the taxi. At the front door.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS63
She kisses each of them on the cheeks leaving huge lipstick marks.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS65
He opens his bag.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS67
Inside, the monitor shows an animated front door closing.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS68
SOMEONE spins with his hands in the air.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS69
On the mantle photos show the kids with their other grandparents.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS72
He runs and looks back.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS75
She saunters away.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS76
Now a neon sign above a restaurant entrance reads, Healthy Tiger. Inside, the owner greets the family.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS78
The family sits.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS79
SOMEONE leans toward SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS80
SOMEONE gauges her mother's response.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS81
SOMEONE shrugs affably.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS82
Later, SOMEONE scribbles on a kid's placement.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS84
He runs off.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS85
Morning, outside the house. SOMEONE clings to SOMEONE as SOMEONE struggles to pull her away.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS88
SOMEONE kisses her and faces the driver.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS89
Behind them, the car reverses then drives off again.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS91
Pulling them from a toaster oven, SOMEONE tosses them to SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS95
She quickly cuts.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS96
Later, SOMEONE wears his mother's high-heels.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS98
As she goes, SOMEONE sternly folds his arms across his chest.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS99
In a car.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS101
SOMEONE climbs in beside SOMEONE. Now at Brookcliff Academy.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS103
SOMEONE rushes off.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS104
SOMEONE encounters bullies.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS106
SOMEONE starts over.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS107
She checks her phone.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS108
Now the family SUV pulls up outside another school. As SOMEONE hops out and opens the side door, we glimpse a sign. Anchor Charter School. In the back SOMEONE sits in a complicated safety seat.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS109
Climbing in, SOMEONE pauses at the side of the complex network of buckles. A woman behind him honks impatiently.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS110
SOMEONE grins and waves, then frantically fumbles at the buckles.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS112
Now a friend stands by as SOMEONE fits her violin case in her locker. A cute boy approaches.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS113
SOMEONE's smile fades.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS115
At home SOMEONE uses a touch screen.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS116
Getting a snack, SOMEONE freezes.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS117
Now SOMEONE's purse and laptop bag rest at her feet as she sits glumly on the stoop of the academy.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS118
SOMEONE pulls up and faces her through the window.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS119
She angrily holds up five fingers.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS120
Now we gaze out over Atlanta's skyscrapers which stand interwoven with thick sections of woodlands.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS121
Now on a mall's escalator.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS122
At a speech therapy session a little girls mimes riding a horse for a group of kids sitting in a circle.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS123
The little boy nods. As he gets to his feet SOMEONE smiles proudly.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS124
SOMEONE spreads his arms wide like wings, then walks around in a circle.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS125
Wearing a puzzled frown, SOMEONE claps slowly.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS127
SOMEONE mimes being trapped in a box, changing facial expressions with the sweep of the hand and tugging a rope.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS128
Cassandra stares, unsmiling.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS129
SOMEONE arrives behind him.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS130
The boy moves off with a wounded pout.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS131
SOMEONE follows the boy. Now SOMEONE leaves the fitting room in a shapeless black dress.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS133
SOMEONE picks up her choice. A flouncy party dress with straps.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS134
A slinky dress.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS135
At home, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE with his back against a door.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS136
SOMEONE demonstrates a pinched pout.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS137
SOMEONE nods.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS138
SOMEONE offers some cash. SOMEONE snatches it.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS139
SOMEONE enters the room and finds SOMEONE lying face down on a bed.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS140
Now the living room flat screen shows a scary puppet riding a tricycle.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS141
SOMEONE clicks a remote turning it off.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS142
Later in the kitchen.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS144
Facing a large monitor SOMEONE glances at the boys. Reads the email headed Announcer Auditions, and dials a number off the screen.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS145
SOMEONE ducks into the next room leaving the boys to their ice cream.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS146
They grin at each other with twinkling eyes.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS147
In the foyer.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS148
She answers her cell.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS151
As SOMEONE chases the boys around in circles, SOMEONE comes in.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS152
SOMEONE video phones in.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS153
SOMEONE ends the call leaving SOMEONE staring.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS156
SOMEONE tries to wrench the cake tray from her, but she clutches it like a wild animal.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS158
Later on video chat.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS159
She sucks cake from her hair.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS160
She blows him a kiss. In the guest room SOMEONE sulks listening to his iPod.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS161
SOMEONE sighs as SOMEONE brushes past.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS162
As she steps into the bathroom SOMEONE heaves another heavy sigh.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS163
Now we float over Atlanta's gold domed capital building.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS164
At the Music Academy for the Arts, SOMEONE beams proudly as a window shows SOMEONE rehearsing a piece on the violin.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS165
A stick-thin woman with a copper red SOMEONE and severe features approaches her.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS166
SOMEONE glumly comes out of the rehearsal room.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS167
Her teacher emerges.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS169
SOMEONE's joyful smile fades into a panicked expression.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS170
SOMEONE rushes out. Her teacher passes SOMEONE again.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS172
She marches out.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS173
Now we drift over Piedmont Park.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS174
On a baseball field two teams warm up.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS177
The orange team fumbles their way through a warmup game of catch. They struggle through sit-ups, toe touches, and pushups.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS179
He takes a big bite.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS180
With two other boys SOMEONE draws on a sidewalk with chalk.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS181
On the field, they put all their hands in the middle.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS182
In the stands, they sit.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS183
On the mound, SOMEONE gazes intently at his bully who scowls. SOMEONE flexes his fingers against the handle.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS184
SOMEONE throws a clean shot straight into the catcher's mitt.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS185
SOMEONE narrows his eyes. SOMEONE pitches.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS186
The catcher signals between his legs.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS188
SOMEONE nods.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS189
SOMEONE buries his face in his mitt.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS190
SOMEONE bats SOMEONE in the crotch.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS191
SOMEONE leans in close.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS194
SOMEONE gags. SOMEONE pats SOMEONE's shoulder.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS195
Later, SOMEONE ices his crotch.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS197
SOMEONE ends the call with a resigned smirk.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS198
At the park, SOMEONE faces her family.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS199
She muscles SOMEONE into a car.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS200
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS201
Now our view takes in a picturesque coastal town with a lighthouse painted in red and white stripes. In an upscale suite, Our Life pamphlets lie near a desk where SOMEONE works.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS202
He gets to his feet and lumbers to the door.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS203
Opening it, he finds SOMEONE facing him with a coy smile. He beams delightedly.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS204
As she comes in, SOMEONE lifts her up in his arms and welcomes her with a big kiss.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS205
Locked in the embrace, he shuts the door.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS207
SOMEONE sleeps alone in the guest bedroom.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS208
In the darkened living room, SOMEONE watches a baseball game on the flat screen TV.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS209
His gaze wistful, he clicks the remote.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS210
In the morning SOMEONE grins as he looks down and draws with a florescent pink paint pen.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS211
He flees.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS212
SOMEONE wakes, his face a mask of glow paint.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS213
SOMEONE runs to the bathroom mirror.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS214
Now on a train headed for the city, SOMEONE scrubs at SOMEONE's face with disinfecting gel.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS215
Later at a station, SOMEONE leads her family off an escalator.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS216
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE into a filthy restroom.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS217
He tries the stalls.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS218
SOMEONE covers the seat with toilet paper.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS219
Outside the stall.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS220
Holding SOMEONE on his lap, SOMEONE notes his straining SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS221
The other men listen in.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS222
At a concert hall.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS223
The reunited family enters the auditorium as the orchestra tunes up. They breathlessly take their seats.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS224
The house lights dim.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS225
The paint on his face glows in the dark.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS226
A young solo violinist takes the stage with a distinguished conductor.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS227
As they bow, the conductor halts and frowns at the sight of SOMEONE's glowing face.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS228
SOMEONE wears an enraptured smile. SOMEONE sits up excitedly as the concert begins.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS229
Behind his back, SOMEONE runs off.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS230
He shakes his head.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS232
Going after him SOMEONE falls over the balcony railing and drops six feet.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS233
He lands by a prim elderly woman.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS235
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE. Her smile fading.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS236
SOMEONE crawls along a row sending patrons to their feet. SOMEONE drops to all fours too.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS239
SOMEONE glances at his upraised hand, then sets SOMEONE on his feet. The boy runs to SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS240
SOMEONE gives the conductor cash.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS241
At the expo, the lighthouse sweeps its beam around in circles. At a party, an award bearing SOMEONE's name sits on a table. A crowd of guests boogie on the dance floor.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS242
In their midst, SOMEONE and SOMEONE slow dance as they share a warm animated conversation.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS243
In Atlanta, SOMEONE uses the phone.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS244
At the kitchen table.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS245
The kids arrive.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS246
As SOMEONE and the kids try the meal, their smiles vanish.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS247
Everyone raises their hands.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS248
Later, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE controlling a computer game with a huge touch screen.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS249
SOMEONE grins sheepishly. Now the kids leave the house.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS250
SOMEONE drives SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS251
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS252
He nods.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS253
Now in front of the school, SOMEONE wears a determined glare. He marches toward the huddle of bullies.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS254
He gives a taunting lunge. On a soccer field.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS256
Now a banner bears a logo, The X Games. A skater rides his board across a half pipe.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS257
BMX riders do tricks. A young hip sportscaster interviews SOMEONE Hawk.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS258
SOMEONE wears baggy track pants, a t-shirt over a long-sleeved hoodie, sleek framed sunglasses and a backwards Newsboy cap.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS259
We ride a half pipe sharing the perspective of a skateboard's wheels. Dragging SOMEONE along by the hand, SOMEONE halts at the half pipes edge.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS262
SOMEONE carries him off under his arm.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS263
SOMEONE leaves with his skateboard.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS264
SOMEONE hustled SOMEONE to one end of the announcers stand.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS265
SOMEONE sits at a table. SOMEONE holds his own crotch.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS266
SOMEONE slips out a notecard scrawled with terminology.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS267
The announcer mirthfully spits his coffee. Behind them, SOMEONE sneaks off.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS269
A cameraman aims at SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS271
Hitting the puddle, SOMEONE Hawk slides out of control and flies toward SOMEONE. SOMEONE hugs his grandson and shields him with his body.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS272
Missing them, SOMEONE plunges to the bottom of the ramp and lands hard in a sprawl.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS273
Now in a park, SOMEONE drops his hip clothes into a trashcan then joins his grandson on a nearby bench.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS274
SOMEONE and SOMEONE set off together side by side.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS275
The grandfather pauses and turns back.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS276
Now as they arrive home SOMEONE storms out and meets them on the porch.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS278
Now SOMEONE finds SOMEONE dejectedly playing with Legos in his room.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS280
Hit sits facing his shy grandson.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS281
SOMEONE nods.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS282
He produces his iPod.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS283
SOMEONE sets the player in a dock.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS284
SOMEONE sits in a chair and SOMEONE takes a seat on the floor.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS285
SOMEONE plays the audio file.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS286
As SOMEONE shuts his eyes with him, we view archived footage of the game.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS287
As SOMEONE replays it, SOMEONE covers his eyes.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS288
Now on a shelf. SOMEONE's bobble head wiggles near a metronome as SOMEONE practices.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS290
SOMEONE shakes her head.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS291
The boys sit still.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS292
The boys jump up.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS293
They rush on to the yard.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS294
SOMEONE kicks the can.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS295
SOMEONE kicks it in the air. Inside, SOMEONE turns distractedly from her violin. In the yard, SOMEONE kicks the can through SOMEONE's widespread legs.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS296
Now SOMEONE runs out of the house and kicks the can away from SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS298
SOMEONE points at her eyes, then dribbles the can through the group and deftly evades them.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS299
As they play, SOMEONE kicks SOMEONE in the shin.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS301
SOMEONE kicks the can high across the yard and grimaces. As SOMEONE and SOMEONE both go for the can they slip on the grass. SOMEONE grins, her clothes soaked with mud.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS302
The family gleefully jumps around. SOMEONE wears a huge smile as SOMEONE drags him over the soaking lawn. SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a hug. SOMEONE grins.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS303
As SOMEONE kicks at the can, he slips in the mud and knocks his wife down beside him. Smiling, they stare into each other's eyes and share a tender kiss.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS304
SOMEONE belly flops on top of them, followed by SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS305
As the kids climb off, SOMEONE lifts her head.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS306
Blood gushes from her nose.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS307
Inside, SOMEONE leaves the bathroom holding a tissue to her nose. SOMEONE approaches.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS308
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE into the bathroom. Now we soar along a sunny coastline. In a swanky bar, SOMEONE and SOMEONE smile and chat over their drinks.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS309
The couple's eyes widen.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS311
At home, SOMEONE searches a digital jukebox and finds The Book of Love in a playlist labeled SOMEONE's Most Played.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS312
SOMEONE hugs his wife.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS313
Upstairs, the boys watch their grandparents sing and dance on a video feed.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS314
The boys watch from the stairs.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS315
SOMEONE walks down the stairs in her new dress.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS316
SOMEONE snaps photos as her granddaughter shows off her curled hair.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS318
SOMEONE twirls her then pulls her close for a picture.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS319
SOMEONE nods and SOMEONE looks down with a smile.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS321
SOMEONE races across the front lawn.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS322
As SOMEONE chases him, SOMEONE steps into the street before a delivery car. The Health Tiger owner slams on his brakes.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS324
SOMEONE taps SOMEONE's arm and points to a police car.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS325
An officer approaches.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS326
As the officer looks under the car a taxi pulls up.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS327
He points to SOMEONE.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS328
SOMEONE's bloody nose.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS330
The officer nods.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS331
SOMEONE's eyes shift to SOMEONE and SOMEONE and his mouth drops open.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS332
He looks at his daughter who stares back with a disappointed gaze.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS333
The officer faces The Healthy Tiger owner.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS334
The family heads inside.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS335
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a sidelong glance.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS337
Standing beside SOMEONE, SOMEONE's gaze sinks to the ground. Inside, the couple glumly sits in the guest room.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS338
Staring off, SOMEONE slowly shakes her head.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS339
In the kitchen, SOMEONE sits alone with a wine glass.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS341
She shakes her head.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS342
SOMEONE tilts her head.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS343
SOMEONE puts her head down.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS344
SOMEONE stops on the stairs.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS345
As SOMEONE heads upstairs, he gives SOMEONE a pat on the back.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS346
SOMEONE slowly approaches SOMEONE as she takes a sip of wine.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS347
He looks down.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS348
He sits across from his daughter.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS349
SOMEONE slowly nods.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS350
SOMEONE starts to go.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS351
SOMEONE lowers her gaze and shakes her head.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS352
Her eyes glisten as SOMEONE sits back down.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS353
She smiles.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS354
She reaches for her father's hand.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS355
SOMEONE stops on the staircase.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS356
Now in the backyard, SOMEONE and SOMEONE carry a shoebox decorated with shiny stickers and the name SOMEONE written in green glitter paint.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS357
They join the rest of the family by a hole dug in a flowerbed.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS358
SOMEONE takes the box and hands it to SOMEONE, who places it in the hole.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS359
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hand a carton of almond milk and two tofu dogs to their grieving son.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS361
Grabbing the milk, SOMEONE pours it all over the box then sets on tofu dog.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS362
The young boy steps back from the hole with his arms folded.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS363
SOMEONE glances up and SOMEONE nods with an approving smile. Stepping beside his grandfather, SOMEONE faces the grave.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS365
The Healthy Tiger owner sobs.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS383
SOMEONE quickly glances down as SOMEONE grabs hold of his hand.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS384
With wide eyes, he looks up at SOMEONE and SOMEONE who smile at their son's affection.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS387
Stepping around the hole, SOMEONE grabs a shovel and pats the restaurant owner on the back.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS388
They all watch as he throws dirt in the grave.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS391
His mother eyes SOMEONE who returns the glare.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS392
Leaning forward, SOMEONE scowls with a black eye. As SOMEONE leans forward, SOMEONE's sister gives a dirty look.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS395
She spots SOMEONE glaring and shifts uncomfortably.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS400
Backstage, parents sit in rows of elevated auditorium seats with their children waiting for the audition.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS401
SOMEONE sits in the first row watching her daughter practice intensely.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS402
She stares off, then glances back as SOMEONE clenches her jaw and strokes the strings with force.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS404
Glaring, SOMEONE stops and watches her mother approach. She sets the violin in its case.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS420
SOMEONE shakes her head.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS424
Backstage, parents sit in rows of elevated auditorium seats with their children waiting for the audition.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS425
SOMEONE sits in the first row watching her daughter practice intensely.
PARENTAL_GUIDANCE_DVS426
She stares off, then glances back as SOMEONE clenches her jaw and strokes the strings with force.