An enormous saucer shaped craft hovers just above the rim of the falls.
PROMETHEUS_DVS55
The plunging water sends up pale mist that swirls around the ship.
PROMETHEUS_DVS56
From a distance we watch a cloaked, hooded figure walk over a rocky bank to the waters rim.
PROMETHEUS_DVS57
From within the hood, a stone-white human like face, with masculine features peers out through deep-set eyes, with enormous dark irises.
PROMETHEUS_DVS58
He serenely looks up at the ascending saucer-shaped craft.
PROMETHEUS_DVS59
The humanoid sets out a bowl with a heavily etched lid.
PROMETHEUS_DVS60
He doffs his cloak.
PROMETHEUS_DVS61
Revealing a pale hairless body of flawless muscle tone and proportion. Wearing only a primitive undergarment around his hips.
PROMETHEUS_DVS63
The humanoid crouches and uncaps the bowl.
PROMETHEUS_DVS65
A membrane covering a small cup disintegrates.
PROMETHEUS_DVS66
Standing, the humanoid peers into the cup and its disintegrating honeycomb-like contents. The humanoid brings the cup to his lips and drinks.
PROMETHEUS_DVS67
He watches the departing craft.
PROMETHEUS_DVS68
Still holding the cup.
PROMETHEUS_DVS69
He lurches over.
PROMETHEUS_DVS70
It drops from his grasp and plummets over the falls.
PROMETHEUS_DVS71
Large dark lesions break out all over his body.
PROMETHEUS_DVS72
One makes a seam down the side of his face and he stares at his transforming arm.
PROMETHEUS_DVS73
Our view swoops close and follows one of the lesions as it creates a trench along the limb.
PROMETHEUS_DVS74
A black fluid gushes through it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS75
Within, a microscopic view shows golden strands of DNA blackening, then breaking apart.
PROMETHEUS_DVS76
On the cliff.
PROMETHEUS_DVS77
The flesh between the humanoid's shoulder blades tears wide open.
PROMETHEUS_DVS78
As he leans his head back, it emits countless black particles like ash that float through the air.
PROMETHEUS_DVS79
He leans forward on one arm.
PROMETHEUS_DVS80
It snaps in two and he tumbles over the falls.
PROMETHEUS_DVS81
The swarm of black particles swirls in the air above the bank as the plunging figure vanishes into the mists.
PROMETHEUS_DVS82
Under water, the mangled body dismembers as it sinks. His neck rips apart, beheading him as he touches down.
PROMETHEUS_DVS83
Another swarm of black particles escapes his shell and swirls through the water.
PROMETHEUS_DVS84
Following them, we watch the golden DNA strands rebuild, then blacken.
PROMETHEUS_DVS85
Clean white lines appear, gradually forming letters that spell a title.
PROMETHEUS_DVS87
Now, zygotes multiply their cells.
PROMETHEUS_DVS88
Fade to black.
PROMETHEUS_DVS89
In the darkness, light streams in as a hand works bits of rock free from the other side of a wall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS90
A flashlight shines in at us through the hole.
PROMETHEUS_DVS92
A woman pulls more rock away increasing its size.
PROMETHEUS_DVS93
As she peers in, we glimpse her brown eyes and delicate features.
PROMETHEUS_DVS94
Auburn bangs peak out from under her hat.
PROMETHEUS_DVS95
Clearing away more rubble, she peers through the hole again and smiles excitedly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS96
Now, a figure moves down a steep verdant slope in the mountains.
PROMETHEUS_DVS97
Two more figures leave a cave, high behind him, as he waves his arms.
PROMETHEUS_DVS98
From a campsite, another man steps closer and lowers a scarf from his face.
PROMETHEUS_DVS99
Holloway glances back at two colleagues, then drops a pan and dashes up the slope.
PROMETHEUS_DVS100
Words appear.
PROMETHEUS_DVS101
2089, Isle of Skye, Scotland.
PROMETHEUS_DVS102
Later in the cave.
PROMETHEUS_DVS103
Holloway pulls a plastic curtain aside and his female colleague steps through with a flashlight.
PROMETHEUS_DVS104
She nimbly trots along.
PROMETHEUS_DVS105
Then lights Holloway's path as he comes in behind her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS106
He picks his way carefully over the rocky floor and joins the woman at her side.
PROMETHEUS_DVS107
She hands over her flashlight.
PROMETHEUS_DVS108
Its beam illuminates primitive cave paintings.
PROMETHEUS_DVS109
Holloway sweeps the light over the walls.
PROMETHEUS_DVS110
His colleague moves to the edge of the cavernous space, then watches him with a girlish smile.
PROMETHEUS_DVS111
He wanders closer to her. His flashlight beam revealing renderings of galloping horses and illustrations of people gathered together.
PROMETHEUS_DVS112
Holloway faces his colleague.
PROMETHEUS_DVS113
She directs the beam upward.
PROMETHEUS_DVS114
High on the wall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS115
A large human points up at six discs.
PROMETHEUS_DVS116
Holloway pulls off his fur trimmed hat.
PROMETHEUS_DVS117
Holloway's colleague smiles with tears in her eyes.
PROMETHEUS_DVS118
Her hand reaches out and interlaces with his.
PROMETHEUS_DVS119
He shines the flashlight on her pretty elfin face.
PROMETHEUS_DVS120
She faces him amazedly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS121
Then returns her gaze to the painting.
PROMETHEUS_DVS122
The flashlight beam sweeps up the pointing arm.
PROMETHEUS_DVS123
The beam lingers on the six floating discs. Fade to black.
PROMETHEUS_DVS124
As stars twinkle from within a cloudy nebula a point of light source passed.
PROMETHEUS_DVS129
A beam shines brightly from a chunky spacecraft as it turns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS136
Onboard, automated doors open to reveal a trim blond man in a gray jumpsuit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS137
Now, a monitor showing vital signs, bears the name SOMEONE. The man presses it with his finger.
PROMETHEUS_DVS138
Wearing a helmet with a glowing amber visor over his eyes.
PROMETHEUS_DVS139
He touches a long casket like pod. It's clouded glass clears revealing Holloway's colleague.
PROMETHEUS_DVS140
Clad in bandage-like undergarments, she appears to sleep.
PROMETHEUS_DVS141
Using a touch screen built into the glass, the man accesses an amber-hued memory of a little girl watching men carry a body on a litter.
PROMETHEUS_DVS142
Her father prepares a meal.
PROMETHEUS_DVS143
A woman's image appears then vanishes.
PROMETHEUS_DVS144
He wears a cross.
PROMETHEUS_DVS145
An image shows his hand laying the cross in hers.
PROMETHEUS_DVS146
The young SOMEONE regards the local priest.
PROMETHEUS_DVS147
The trim man appears at the vision's center.
PROMETHEUS_DVS148
As the transmission ends, the man lingers with his hand on the touch screen, then steps away.
PROMETHEUS_DVS149
Now he touches a panel and doors open before him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS151
Holding a basketball in one hand, he strides through the ships chambers.
PROMETHEUS_DVS152
Lights turn on as he passes, then blink out again.
PROMETHEUS_DVS153
Pausing by a table, he crouches and picks something up off the spotless floor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS155
Moving on, he bounces the ball.
PROMETHEUS_DVS157
In a cockpit, he activates a computer with a three-dimensional holographic screen.
PROMETHEUS_DVS158
A screen at the top shows a girl playing a violin.
PROMETHEUS_DVS159
Now, on a basketball court with a row of treadmills at one end, SOMEONE rides a bicycle in circles.
PROMETHEUS_DVS160
He shoots the basketball from the bike and it goes through the basket.
PROMETHEUS_DVS161
Now SOMEONE eats a bowl of white mush with a spoon.
PROMETHEUS_DVS162
His attention fixed on a holographic video before him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS163
At another time, he bounces his basketball as he walks the ships corridors.
PROMETHEUS_DVS165
A movie plays.
PROMETHEUS_DVS166
As T.E. Lawrence, Peter O'Toole extinguishes a match with his fingertips, silhouetted against the screen, SOMEONE watches.
PROMETHEUS_DVS167
Hair dye plasters his roots. At a mirror, SOMEONE styles his dry hair.
PROMETHEUS_DVS168
SOMEONE combs his golden hair to match Peter O'Toole's style. Later, he moves through a dark corridor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS169
SOMEONE halts, wavering unsteadily.
PROMETHEUS_DVS170
Quickly regaining his balance, he observes racked silver billiard balls and a cue rolling across a blue felt table.
PROMETHEUS_DVS171
Frowning, SOMEONE moves to a panel and types.
PROMETHEUS_DVS172
Lights blink on and off throughout the corridors as he returns to the cockpit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS173
He flips switches activating lights and computers across the bridge.
PROMETHEUS_DVS174
Holographic screens blink on above the front stations, each offering individualized data.
PROMETHEUS_DVS175
SOMEONE strides to one and pushes a button.
PROMETHEUS_DVS176
From the nose, outer panels part giving view through the glass windows to a pale gray planet floating amidst a sea of stars.
PROMETHEUS_DVS177
SOMEONE steps forward.
PROMETHEUS_DVS178
His eager gaze fixed on the lonely orb.
PROMETHEUS_DVS179
His deep-set blue eyes shine wistfully.
PROMETHEUS_DVS181
near an enormous ringed planet, the stocky insect shaped SOMEONE turns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS183
SOMEONE opens a pair of doors.
PROMETHEUS_DVS184
Looking down, he cocks his head and frowns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS185
A sleeper pod lies open and empty.
PROMETHEUS_DVS186
He follows wet prints of bare feet down a corridor's black rubber floor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS187
On illuminated floor panels, a soaking wet woman clad in bandage-like undergarments does push-ups with a determined stare.
PROMETHEUS_DVS188
SOMEONE arrives outside her door.
PROMETHEUS_DVS189
SOMEONE fully parts that partially open doors and steps into the chamber.
PROMETHEUS_DVS190
The lean woman's long blond hair drips around her face as she completes her routine.
PROMETHEUS_DVS191
SOMEONE presents her with a robe.
PROMETHEUS_DVS192
She puts it on.
PROMETHEUS_DVS193
She takes clothes from a rack.
PROMETHEUS_DVS194
Now, back in the groups sleep chamber, SOMEONE moves among the opening pods.
PROMETHEUS_DVS196
fluid streams from SOMEONE's bare feet as they dangle from her pod.
PROMETHEUS_DVS197
She vomits into a bowl.
PROMETHEUS_DVS198
He lays a blanket over her back.
PROMETHEUS_DVS199
Sitting near by, Holloway drinks fluids. SOMEONE vomits again.
PROMETHEUS_DVS200
Now in a mess hall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS201
In flight suits and hoodies, SOMEONE, Holloway, and rag-tag crew members get food and beverages.
PROMETHEUS_DVS202
In a sleek, high-collared suit, the blond arrives.
PROMETHEUS_DVS203
She spies a brawny charming man setting up a small Christmas tree on the pool table.
PROMETHEUS_DVS204
He takes a small cigar from his mouth.
PROMETHEUS_DVS205
A mohawked man sips broth.
PROMETHEUS_DVS206
A bespectacled man sits.
PROMETHEUS_DVS207
He extends a hand, the mohawked man glares.
PROMETHEUS_DVS208
SOMEONE gives an intimidated nod then smiles.
PROMETHEUS_DVS210
The rest of the crew joins the pair in a briefing area set on the basketball court.
PROMETHEUS_DVS211
Sitting at the front, SOMEONE uses a tablet to activate a huge 3-D holographic video.
PROMETHEUS_DVS212
A little dog accompanies an old man.
PROMETHEUS_DVS213
A living area appears before him as he advances.
PROMETHEUS_DVS214
SOMEONE's smile fades.
PROMETHEUS_DVS215
They both comply.
PROMETHEUS_DVS216
SOMEONE and Holloway go to either side of the holographic speaker.
PROMETHEUS_DVS217
As Weyland turns and walks away, his surroundings blink out.
PROMETHEUS_DVS218
The holographic man vanishes, ending the playback.
PROMETHEUS_DVS219
He shows a silver cube.
PROMETHEUS_DVS220
Holloway presses a few squares that make up the cube and it projects a series of images.
PROMETHEUS_DVS221
He lines up the images to show overlapping patterns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS222
He sets the discs in a map.
PROMETHEUS_DVS223
He zooms the map in.
PROMETHEUS_DVS224
He shows the ringed planet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS225
The gray sphere orbits it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS226
The mohawked crewman gives a nod.
PROMETHEUS_DVS227
SOMEONE grins.
PROMETHEUS_DVS228
Holloway nods to SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS229
The mohawked crewman lays his face in his hands.
PROMETHEUS_DVS230
SOMEONE laughs then speaks up.
PROMETHEUS_DVS231
SOMEONE regards SOMEONE attentively, then lowers his contemplative gaze.
PROMETHEUS_DVS232
Now, blue flame glows within the Prometheus' jets as it nears the mysterious moon.
PROMETHEUS_DVS233
It spirals around.
PROMETHEUS_DVS234
Bringing its angle parallel with the moon's curve.
PROMETHEUS_DVS235
The sun casts a thin crest of illumination across the pale blue and gray surface.
PROMETHEUS_DVS236
In a corridor, SOMEONE walks ahead of Holloway.
PROMETHEUS_DVS237
SOMEONE smiles at them.
PROMETHEUS_DVS238
He escorts them into a luxurious living environment.
PROMETHEUS_DVS239
Windows give the illusion of a peaceful winter scene.
PROMETHEUS_DVS240
SOMEONE steps away.
PROMETHEUS_DVS241
SOMEONE rejoins the group.
PROMETHEUS_DVS242
At a bar, SOMEONE uses a cocktail shaker.
PROMETHEUS_DVS243
The windows show a field.
PROMETHEUS_DVS244
SOMEONE serves the drinks.
PROMETHEUS_DVS245
SOMEONE stares and Holloway smiles bitterly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS246
Now, multiple screens show data and imagery over SOMEONE's computer.
PROMETHEUS_DVS247
Turning his computer off, SOMEONE smiles and turns away.
PROMETHEUS_DVS248
The crew straps themselves in.
PROMETHEUS_DVS249
SOMEONE puts up his hood and hugs his jacket closed. The ship descends towards clouds.
PROMETHEUS_DVS250
The small stout SOMEONE descends through a fierce storm.
PROMETHEUS_DVS251
Lightning flashes around the ship.
PROMETHEUS_DVS252
They pass jagged mountains peeking from thick mist as the sun shines through the clouds.
PROMETHEUS_DVS253
Fog parts, revealing a barren valley dotted with low hills.
PROMETHEUS_DVS254
Another field shows swirling patterns, indicating previous lava flow.
PROMETHEUS_DVS255
A dome shaped formation juts from a range of hills.
PROMETHEUS_DVS256
We gaze down on the SOMEONE as it progresses past jagged blades of rock.
PROMETHEUS_DVS257
SOMEONE faces the Scottish woman.
PROMETHEUS_DVS258
He gives a smile.
PROMETHEUS_DVS259
Now, we soar through a barren, unforgiving mountain range.
PROMETHEUS_DVS260
The ship slows as it approaches a gap between two outcroppings.
PROMETHEUS_DVS261
Holloway eyes a display monitor. It shows a structure peeking out from behind a mountain.
PROMETHEUS_DVS262
He gets up.
PROMETHEUS_DVS263
He peers out a window.
PROMETHEUS_DVS264
Clearing the gateway, the ship turns towards a low structure built in the distant valley.
PROMETHEUS_DVS265
The ship's jets rotate downward.
PROMETHEUS_DVS266
They slow the ships descent to a controlled pace.
PROMETHEUS_DVS267
The jets bring up massive clouds of dust around the ship as it touches down.
PROMETHEUS_DVS268
Overhead, the enormous ringed planet glows softly beside the sun.
PROMETHEUS_DVS270
Domes resembling the tops of beehives surrounded by stone walls dot the valley in single file.
PROMETHEUS_DVS271
Roughly a mile apart from each other.
PROMETHEUS_DVS272
On board SOMEONE, Holloway rushes to the front windows, while SOMEONE follows warily.
PROMETHEUS_DVS273
Other members of the crew move forward, staring out.
PROMETHEUS_DVS274
Holloway kisses SOMEONE's head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS275
Now the survey team suits up.
PROMETHEUS_DVS276
Beneath their clear helmets, skullcaps bear their names. The Scottish woman bears the name SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS277
SOMEONE notices a crewmen wielding a flame-thrower.
PROMETHEUS_DVS278
In a suit, Holloway presses buttons on his sleeve.
PROMETHEUS_DVS279
A large boxy chamber descends from the ships underside.
PROMETHEUS_DVS280
In the airlock, a hatch rises. The crew steps into a hanger.
PROMETHEUS_DVS281
SOMEONE brings a duffel to the front of a transport vehicle with twin rows of seats.
PROMETHEUS_DVS282
As the mohawked man sits, SOMEONE takes the seat facing him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS283
The mohawked man moves down a few spots.
PROMETHEUS_DVS284
The hanger hatch lowers making an exit ramp.
PROMETHEUS_DVS285
The transport pulls out alongside two ATVs.
PROMETHEUS_DVS286
In the transport, Holloway moves close to SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS287
Holloway chuckles.
PROMETHEUS_DVS288
He presses her helmet to his with an ardent gaze, then turns away.
PROMETHEUS_DVS289
SOMEONE adverts her troubled gaze.
PROMETHEUS_DVS290
The transport leads the two ATVs to an opening in a wall surrounding the structure.
PROMETHEUS_DVS291
A sharp crust tops the beehive like doom.
PROMETHEUS_DVS292
Holloway and SOMEONE come forward, crowding the front of the cabin with SOMEONE as they stare out the windshield.
PROMETHEUS_DVS293
The crust rounded front gives a hint of wind-eroded carving of a face.
PROMETHEUS_DVS294
The survey vehicles pull up around the dome and park.
PROMETHEUS_DVS295
A side hatch in the transport rises and SOMEONE leads the others out.
PROMETHEUS_DVS296
Her helmet's computerized view shows long, low entrances carved into the dome's base.
PROMETHEUS_DVS297
In the dark cockpit, SOMEONE stands behind the captain's chair.
PROMETHEUS_DVS298
The other survey team members leave the ATVs staring up.
PROMETHEUS_DVS299
Holloway ventures forward and SOMEONE follows.
PROMETHEUS_DVS300
The team members approach one of the entry ways, each carrying a kit or bag of varying size.
PROMETHEUS_DVS302
We peer up at the approaching humans from a sandy slope dotted with sharp rocks.
PROMETHEUS_DVS303
Crossing the threshold, they head down the slope.
PROMETHEUS_DVS304
SOMEONE regards the space with a calm expression.
PROMETHEUS_DVS305
A view through a helmet camera shows a few of the team exploring the cavernous space.
PROMETHEUS_DVS306
Various readings border the image along with the user's name, SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS307
Now, Holloway's view closes in on a cave opening.
PROMETHEUS_DVS308
As the team ventures in, holographic monitors each show the captain a crew member's computerized helmet view.
PROMETHEUS_DVS309
Venturing through the opening.
PROMETHEUS_DVS310
SOMEONE draws himself up with an alert stare.
PROMETHEUS_DVS311
SOMEONE follows.
PROMETHEUS_DVS312
On the other side, SOMEONE and the mohawked man linger, sharing an uneasy gaze.
PROMETHEUS_DVS313
SOMEONE ducks through first.
PROMETHEUS_DVS314
The other man glances fearfully over his shoulder.
PROMETHEUS_DVS316
Further in, the team passes through a circular archway
PROMETHEUS_DVS317
and enters a tunnel perpendicular to their path.
PROMETHEUS_DVS318
They pause, shining their lights in either direction.
PROMETHEUS_DVS319
The mohawked man readies orbs.
PROMETHEUS_DVS320
SOMEONE releases two into the air. Spinning, they shine red scanner beams in all directions as they fly down the corridor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS321
He sends two more off the other way.
PROMETHEUS_DVS322
The last scanning pup vanishes around a turn.
PROMETHEUS_DVS324
Leaving his chair the captain goes to a layout table.
PROMETHEUS_DVS326
As he activates its computerized system, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE join him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS328
In the 3-D holograph flying red beacons map out a tunnel system.
PROMETHEUS_DVS329
Yellow beacons marked with surname initials SOMEONE the team member's locations. The pups split off again as the extending network of tunnels grows more complex.
PROMETHEUS_DVS331
The survey team reaches a rounded tunnel of dark gleaming stone.
PROMETHEUS_DVS332
As he leads them on, SOMEONE curiously shines her flashlight at the etched stone walls.
PROMETHEUS_DVS333
SOMEONE takes up the rear, closely observing his surroundings.
PROMETHEUS_DVS334
They venture towards a faint light in the distance.
PROMETHEUS_DVS335
Now, beams of light sweep erratically over rock.
PROMETHEUS_DVS336
Rounding a turn, the survey team steps into view and slows.
PROMETHEUS_DVS337
The stand in a chamber where water streams to around pit at its center.
PROMETHEUS_DVS338
A pup doubles back from the far wall and drops down the pit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS339
Water rains around the probe as it plunges several stories.
PROMETHEUS_DVS340
Holloway taps keys on his sleeve.
PROMETHEUS_DVS341
Holloway unlatches his helmet then bends over and pulls it off. Straightening he inhales deeply and pulls off his skullcap.
PROMETHEUS_DVS342
His breath clouds the air.
PROMETHEUS_DVS343
SOMEONE smiles.
PROMETHEUS_DVS344
Glaring scoldingly at Holloway, SOMEONE removes her helmet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS345
In the cockpit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS346
The away team moves through a dark space.
PROMETHEUS_DVS347
Hiking a tunnel, they sweep flashlights over their surroundings.
PROMETHEUS_DVS348
Trailing behind, SOMEONE spots a panel with carved dots and lines high up on the wall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS350
Climbing up, he notices greenish slime dripping from a few of the engraved points.
PROMETHEUS_DVS351
SOMEONE collects some on his gloved fingertip,
PROMETHEUS_DVS352
then presses it to his thumb.
PROMETHEUS_DVS353
As they part, the slime stretches between his fingertips.
PROMETHEUS_DVS354
Glowing blue particles swarm within.
PROMETHEUS_DVS355
SOMEONE sniffs it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS356
Unnoticing the others venture ahead without him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS357
SOMEONE runs his finger along a few of the lines and presses the engraved dots.
PROMETHEUS_DVS358
They light up beneath his touch.
PROMETHEUS_DVS359
A screen of glowing blue particles forms and races down the tunnel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS360
Pausing, the human team members turn.
PROMETHEUS_DVS361
He stares at an approaching light.
PROMETHEUS_DVS362
Glowing blue particles form several giant humanoids racing down the tunnel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS363
As SOMEONE remains in their path, they wash over him like wind.
PROMETHEUS_DVS364
Holloway sweeps SOMEONE out of their way. The incorporeal figures continue down the tunnel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS365
The team runs after the giant ghostly figures.
PROMETHEUS_DVS366
Lagging behind the others, a lone apparition stumbles and falls. It gets up and runs on as those ahead dart out of view.
PROMETHEUS_DVS367
Holloway and SOMEONE arrive in time to watch it collapse at a doorway. It's ghostly hatch lowers on top of him and he vanishes.
PROMETHEUS_DVS368
Staying SOMEONE with a hand, Holloway ventures forward. The others arrive behind him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS369
A body lies at the door.
PROMETHEUS_DVS370
The team approaches it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS372
At the door, Holloway and SOMEONE spy ancient text carved into the stone.
PROMETHEUS_DVS373
The strange characters fill several rows.
PROMETHEUS_DVS374
SOMEONE starts to leave.
PROMETHEUS_DVS375
He marches back indignantly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS376
Leaning close to SOMEONE, SOMEONE wheels around and leaves with SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS377
Now, as Holloway, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE examine the decapitated body,
PROMETHEUS_DVS378
SOMEONE climbs a ladder.
PROMETHEUS_DVS379
Holloway hands over a flashlight sized device.
PROMETHEUS_DVS380
As SOMEONE studies the carved symbols in the wall, SOMEONE inserts a probe from the carbon reader into the alien being.
PROMETHEUS_DVS381
SOMEONE taps the symbols, which light up briefly with his touch.
PROMETHEUS_DVS382
As a pup moves in to scan the revealed chamber, SOMEONE kneels just on the other side of the door.
PROMETHEUS_DVS383
Her flashlight beam reveals a head, three times the size of a human's with a short elephant like trunk.
PROMETHEUS_DVS384
Holloway moves further inside transfixed by an enormous humanoid bust.
PROMETHEUS_DVS385
SOMEONE steps further in, studying the sculpted face.
PROMETHEUS_DVS387
the sculpture towers over hundreds of sleek gray thigh high urns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS388
SOMEONE and SOMEONE follow the others into the room.
PROMETHEUS_DVS389
One of their boots lifts from the soft dirt revealing worms wriggling about.
PROMETHEUS_DVS390
SOMEONE and SOMEONE aim their flashlights at the curved ceiling.
PROMETHEUS_DVS391
Holloway moves deeper in through the evenly spaced urns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS392
SOMEONE crouches down for a better look at one and reaches out to it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS393
Condensation beads on its flat topped metallic surface.
PROMETHEUS_DVS394
As SOMEONE gazes slack-jawed at the humanoid statue.
PROMETHEUS_DVS395
Holloway continues on around to a recess behind it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS396
A relief of snake-like creatures surrounding a central humanoid figure adorns the wall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS397
As Holloway steps around a large pedestal,
PROMETHEUS_DVS398
his flashlight beam shines through a huge emerald-like stone jutting from its center.
PROMETHEUS_DVS399
SOMEONE kneels at another urn.
PROMETHEUS_DVS400
A tar-like substance oozes on top.
PROMETHEUS_DVS401
The android tilts his head curiously and touches some spilling down the side with a gloved finger.
PROMETHEUS_DVS402
SOMEONE moves her flashlight beam across the high ceiling.
PROMETHEUS_DVS403
The painting changes.
PROMETHEUS_DVS404
The woman rushed back to the severed head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS405
On the surface, storm clouds swirl menacingly in the sky.
PROMETHEUS_DVS406
On board SOMEONE, SOMEONE studies images of the storm on a monitor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS407
In the chamber, SOMEONE and SOMEONE lift the head into a plastic bag.
PROMETHEUS_DVS408
SOMEONE turns to watch SOMEONE leave the bridge.
PROMETHEUS_DVS409
Kneeling at a clean urn, SOMEONE sprays it with a gaseous substance from a small canister.
PROMETHEUS_DVS410
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hoist the head up between them.
PROMETHEUS_DVS412
Holloway leaves the carved relief in the wall. SOMEONE surreptitiously packs the urn in a canvas bag.
PROMETHEUS_DVS413
As he walks away the black ooze pools around the urn.
PROMETHEUS_DVS414
The worms wriggle in it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS415
Outside the dome the four researchers find only the ATVs.
PROMETHEUS_DVS416
SOMEONE and SOMEONE get in one.
PROMETHEUS_DVS417
Holloway drives off with SOMEONE on the second ATV.
PROMETHEUS_DVS418
A dark shadow passes over them. Above, thick black clouds engulf the dome and the enormous carved skull on its crest.
PROMETHEUS_DVS419
On the road leading towards SOMEONE, the ATVs travel in the dusty wake of a transport.
PROMETHEUS_DVS420
As the storm engulfs us, jagged shards whip around then block out our view of the fleeing vehicles.
PROMETHEUS_DVS421
From a long distance, the storm appears as a swiftly moving wall of roiling dirt. On SOMEONE, SOMEONE watches the approaching vehicles and storm.
PROMETHEUS_DVS422
The transport makes it into the hanger. As the ATVs speed in, one hits a bump and the bagged head falls off.
PROMETHEUS_DVS423
SOMEONE races after it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS424
As SOMEONE grabs it, the silica storm knocks her 50 yards into one of the ships towering landing struts. Holloway takes an ATV.
PROMETHEUS_DVS425
On the screen SOMEONE watches Holloway leave the ship.
PROMETHEUS_DVS426
The hatch closes, Holloway reaches SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS427
As Holloway climbs out of the vehicle, it blows away.
PROMETHEUS_DVS428
The ATV tumbles through the storm.
PROMETHEUS_DVS429
As they take each other's hands amid the whirling shards, an outer door opens on the ship.
PROMETHEUS_DVS430
SOMEONE clips himself to a cable attached to SOMEONE. Meanwhile the storm lifts SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS431
Holloway struggles to keep a hold on her. As SOMEONE steps out, the storm bounces him around. He makes it over to Holloway and helps him pull SOMEONE back into a recess made by the forked landing strut.
PROMETHEUS_DVS432
The android calmly clips the humans to his line and gives SOMEONE the okay hand signal.
PROMETHEUS_DVS433
He lifts a remote control and the line pulls them back towards the open door in the ship.
PROMETHEUS_DVS434
The clustered trio bobs and bounces as the line carries them through the harsh wind and flying shards. A crew member helps pull them on board.
PROMETHEUS_DVS436
Later as they move through the hanger, a crew member blasts the floor with a flame thrower.
PROMETHEUS_DVS438
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk through a dark tunnel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS439
The two trapped men move on through the dark cramped space. Meanwhile, in a lab on board SOMEONE, the head SOMEONE collected rises into a glass chamber. A white mist blasts it, filling the chamber and an image appears on a monitor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS440
As the head slides from the chamber, SOMEONE arrives.
PROMETHEUS_DVS441
SOMEONE activates an arched scanner that glides over the head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS442
As SOMEONE studies one monitor, SOMEONE steps over the image of the head on another.
PROMETHEUS_DVS443
As Holloway plops down nearby with a bottle of liquor,
PROMETHEUS_DVS444
SOMEONE easily releases the helmet, lifting the trunk like snout.
PROMETHEUS_DVS445
Carefully lifting the large helmet off completely, he reveals a human-like head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS446
It's eyes closed peacefully.
PROMETHEUS_DVS447
Scaly patches and bumps mar the gray skin on its bald head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS449
As the others stare, SOMEONE and SOMEONE look more closely.
PROMETHEUS_DVS450
SOMEONE activates a probe.
PROMETHEUS_DVS451
She inserts it behind the engineer's ear, taps a few commands on a tablet, and waits.
PROMETHEUS_DVS452
Holloway lowers his drink as the cells on the engineer's head change.
PROMETHEUS_DVS453
The engineer's eyes twitch and open slightly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS454
Dark fluid oozes from small holes on either side of his brow and he grimaces painfully.
PROMETHEUS_DVS455
As SOMEONE activates a conveyor belt, carrying the head back to the containment chamber,
PROMETHEUS_DVS456
the engineer's face grimaces and winces. The chamber door slides shut and another shot of white mist blast it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS457
As the mist clears, the top of the head explodes, splattering the chamber walls with a greenish slime.
PROMETHEUS_DVS458
SOMEONE lowers her white doctor's mask, SOMEONE stares.
PROMETHEUS_DVS459
Holloway takes a swig from a bottle and hops down his perch on a counter.
PROMETHEUS_DVS460
SOMEONE glances after him then lowers her gaze.
PROMETHEUS_DVS461
Later, the storm continues to pelt SOMEONE. Inside SOMEONE stands by a sleep pod.
PROMETHEUS_DVS462
He wears the helmet with the glowing visor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS463
He allows a slight smile and bows his head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS464
Stepping over to the head of the sleep pod,
PROMETHEUS_DVS465
SOMEONE touches his palm to its top and a light glowing within dims.
PROMETHEUS_DVS466
He removes his helmet and amber visor, revealing his stoic expression.
PROMETHEUS_DVS467
Now, as he strides down a corridor,
PROMETHEUS_DVS468
he removes gloves and tosses them into a bin.
PROMETHEUS_DVS470
Rounding a bend, He finds SOMEONE waiting for him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS471
She steps before him and he slows to a stop.
PROMETHEUS_DVS472
She steps closer, fixing him with a piercing stare.
PROMETHEUS_DVS473
As SOMEONE tries to side step around her, she blocks him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS474
They stare at each other only a few inches apart.
PROMETHEUS_DVS475
She pins him to a wall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS476
Tensing her jaw, SOMEONE takes a deep breath through her nose and moves her hand towards SOMEONE's mouth as if to smother him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS477
She storms away.
PROMETHEUS_DVS479
SOMEONE approaches a wall of glass-doored coolers filled with supplies. Opening one,
PROMETHEUS_DVS480
he removes the urn he took from the inner chamber.
PROMETHEUS_DVS482
In the lab, SOMEONE peers through a microscope.
PROMETHEUS_DVS483
In the other lab, SOMEONE gently twists the top off the urn and sets it aside.
PROMETHEUS_DVS485
Meanwhile, with SOMEONE, a green laser beam aims at a slide.
PROMETHEUS_DVS486
On screen, a map of the engineer's DNA overlaps a human sample. The scientist's jaws drop.
PROMETHEUS_DVS487
Meanwhile, SOMEONE lifts a rack of four large vials from the urn.
PROMETHEUS_DVS488
Gray ooze drips off the container as he sets it down on a work surface.
PROMETHEUS_DVS489
The android breaks off one of the translucent, foot long vials.
PROMETHEUS_DVS490
As he tips it upside down
PROMETHEUS_DVS491
black matter collected at the bottom drips downward.
PROMETHEUS_DVS492
In the lab, SOMEONE peers at the monitor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS493
Now SOMEONE breaks off the tip of the vial.
PROMETHEUS_DVS494
Putting his fingertip over the resulting hole, he tips it upside down.
PROMETHEUS_DVS495
A tiny drop of the black matter sits on the tip of his index finger.
PROMETHEUS_DVS496
He lifts it to eye level and peers closely at it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS497
He smiles.
PROMETHEUS_DVS498
Now, SOMEONE enters the mess hall with a bottle of liquor and sees Holloway drunkenly fiddling with balls on the pool table.
PROMETHEUS_DVS499
The android lifts a glass off a shelf with his thumb and middle finger, leaving his index finger extended.
PROMETHEUS_DVS500
Holloway rolls a ball toward him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS501
Holloway shoves back his hood.
PROMETHEUS_DVS502
SOMEONE stares grimly at Holloway.
PROMETHEUS_DVS503
Holloway smiles up at him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS504
Keeping his index finger extended, SOMEONE pours a glass of liquor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS505
As he hands it over to Holloway, he dips his index finger in it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS506
Holloway takes it with a grin.
PROMETHEUS_DVS507
He takes a sip, then knocks the whole thing back.
PROMETHEUS_DVS508
SOMEONE smiles.
PROMETHEUS_DVS509
Meanwhile, in the tunnels, SOMEONE and SOMEONE come upon a pile of corpses.
PROMETHEUS_DVS510
Their flashlights illuminate the mangled mass over 10 feet tall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS511
Meanwhile, on the bridge, the holographic map shows the pups still tracing out tunnels and chambers and SOMEONE's and SOMEONE's location within.
PROMETHEUS_DVS512
SOMEONE stops playing a concertina and approaches a pinging red dot on the map.
PROMETHEUS_DVS513
The pinging probe sits motionless at what appears to be a dead end.
PROMETHEUS_DVS515
In the tunnel, SOMEONE peers at the map with narrowed eyes.
PROMETHEUS_DVS516
Watching video of the holographs in her quarters, SOMEONE speaks into a recorder.
PROMETHEUS_DVS517
Holloway enters.
PROMETHEUS_DVS518
He sets the rose in a tumbler before here.
PROMETHEUS_DVS519
Sitting on his lap she kisses him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS520
On a small handheld computer
PROMETHEUS_DVS521
SOMEONE brings up brings up the matching DNA graphs then hands it over to him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS522
She leans over and hugs him from behind with a giddy smile.
PROMETHEUS_DVS523
She flops down on a bed.
PROMETHEUS_DVS524
SOMEONE blinks back tears and shakes her head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS526
SOMEONE adverts her wounded gaze.
PROMETHEUS_DVS527
He tackles her affectionately.
PROMETHEUS_DVS528
He kisses her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS529
Gazing into her eyes he gives her a tender kiss and rubs her chest.
PROMETHEUS_DVS530
SOMEONE caresses his cheek then returns the kiss.
PROMETHEUS_DVS531
He leans in and they embrace with mounting passion.
PROMETHEUS_DVS534
Reaching down, SOMEONE pulls Holloway's shirt up his torso, revealing his toned sun-kissed back.
PROMETHEUS_DVS535
He straightens and she yanks it off impatiently.
PROMETHEUS_DVS536
Holloway leans down again and kisses her hungrily.
PROMETHEUS_DVS538
Now in a slinky black turtleneck and low ponytail, SOMEONE meanders into the cockpit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS539
Above the layout table, the probe beacons add additional detail to the now enormous map of the structure.
PROMETHEUS_DVS540
Two yellow beacons SOMEONE and SOMEONE near ground level center.
PROMETHEUS_DVS541
Leaning close, she reaches toward the map.
PROMETHEUS_DVS542
She turns, in a corner SOMEONE sits with concertina.
PROMETHEUS_DVS543
SOMEONE returns her gaze to the map.
PROMETHEUS_DVS544
SOMEONE drums the flat ends of his concertina.
PROMETHEUS_DVS545
He sips a drink.
PROMETHEUS_DVS546
She pauses as he gets to his feet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS547
SOMEONE  blinks at him and cocks her head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS548
SOMEONE lifts his brow persistently.
PROMETHEUS_DVS549
SOMEONE looks away then faces him with a coy smirk.
PROMETHEUS_DVS550
As she marches out, SOMEONE gazes after here.
PROMETHEUS_DVS551
As the storm rages outside, SOMEONE's helmet view shows fluid streaming from the urns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS552
They wander the chamber.
PROMETHEUS_DVS553
SOMEONE exhales smoke in his helmet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS554
SOMEONE sucks through a plastic hose, then blows a puff of smoke.
PROMETHEUS_DVS555
SOMEONE flips the British bird.
PROMETHEUS_DVS556
Using a space blanket, SOMEONE flips it back.
PROMETHEUS_DVS557
Black fluid streams along the ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS558
A snake-like creature rises from the muck.
PROMETHEUS_DVS559
The cockpit stands empty.
PROMETHEUS_DVS560
As he edges closer, it rears up.
PROMETHEUS_DVS561
SOMEONE falls back on his rear end.
PROMETHEUS_DVS562
He reaches a hand out. The creature's head fans out, takes the shape of a porpoise tail.
PROMETHEUS_DVS563
Grinning, SOMEONE lingers close.
PROMETHEUS_DVS564
He reaches out again.
PROMETHEUS_DVS566
The creature's hood wraps around his hand and holds on tight.
PROMETHEUS_DVS567
It's serpentine body lashes around his arm.
PROMETHEUS_DVS568
It snaps his arm like a twig.
PROMETHEUS_DVS569
Using a knife, SOMEONE decapitates it. It sprays green blood, which burns through his helmet acidly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS570
The creature's head regenerates and it burrows up SOMEONE's sleeve.
PROMETHEUS_DVS571
It reaches his helmet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS572
SOMEONE falls face first into the black fluid. As he straightens, his melting helmet collapses on his face.
PROMETHEUS_DVS573
The serpentine creature plunges into SOMEONE's mouth and forces its way down his throat.
PROMETHEUS_DVS574
Now, from the dome's crust, we view a golden sun peeking over the horizon.
PROMETHEUS_DVS575
Silhouetted against the windows of SOMEONE's quarters, Holloway hunches over and rubs his face.
PROMETHEUS_DVS576
As his partner slumbers peacefully, he shuffles to a mirror. A light switches on above him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS577
Facing his reflection, he blinks his bleary eyes. He takes a few deep breaths, then removes a gold ring and sets it on the sink.
PROMETHEUS_DVS578
Bending over, he splashes water over his face and close cropped hair.
PROMETHEUS_DVS580
Facing the mirror again, he peers at his beady bloodshot eyes.
PROMETHEUS_DVS581
Broken blood vessels redden the rims of his irises.
PROMETHEUS_DVS582
Holloway knits his brow and leans closer to the mirror.
PROMETHEUS_DVS583
He lifts a hand hesitantly, then tugs down on the skin beneath his eye.
PROMETHEUS_DVS585
Clear fluid streams from his iris.
PROMETHEUS_DVS586
She touches an intercom.
PROMETHEUS_DVS587
Now an away team leaves the airlock.
PROMETHEUS_DVS588
All but SOMEONE board a transport.
PROMETHEUS_DVS589
Holloway regards him suspiciously.
PROMETHEUS_DVS590
As the transport pulls out, SOMEONE rides beside it on an ATV.
PROMETHEUS_DVS591
A lone crew member sees them off, then twirls his finger in the air.
PROMETHEUS_DVS592
Later, the vehicles approach the structures gateway.
PROMETHEUS_DVS594
Riding behind the transport, SOMEONE halts and gazes after it as it passes through.
PROMETHEUS_DVS595
Later in the structure.
PROMETHEUS_DVS596
the team progresses downhill to a large open doorway shaped like an egg.
PROMETHEUS_DVS597
Meanwhile, SOMEONE rides the ATV through the structure's tunnels.
PROMETHEUS_DVS598
Sipping from a porcelain cup,
PROMETHEUS_DVS599
SOMEONE monitors him by way of a private station.
PROMETHEUS_DVS600
She keeps her back to us. Her straight blond hair flowing smoothly past her shoulders.
PROMETHEUS_DVS601
SOMEONE halts the ATV with a frown.
PROMETHEUS_DVS602
SOMEONE removes his helmet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS603
His suit's camera shares his view as he proceeds down a corridor marked with urn-shaped etchings.
PROMETHEUS_DVS604
He pauses, frowning gravely.
PROMETHEUS_DVS605
Several yards ahead in a rounded turn, a red probe light pulsates.
PROMETHEUS_DVS606
With an intense stare, he proceeds toward it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS608
In her lifeboat, SOMEONE watches the feed projected across her windows.
PROMETHEUS_DVS609
As SOMEONE progresses, we find the probe hovering before a heart shaped door of multiple oblong panels.
PROMETHEUS_DVS610
SOMEONE eyes the probe quizzically, then turns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS612
As SOMEONE looks on, he enters a code into a panel beside the door.
PROMETHEUS_DVS613
It rises and the probe soars through.
PROMETHEUS_DVS614
As SOMEONE ventures forward, the doorway shows thousands of urns stacked in giant hourglass-shaped units.
PROMETHEUS_DVS615
The probe casts its flickering light at the far end of the chamber as the android goes in.
PROMETHEUS_DVS616
He observes three hourglass formations before him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS617
Even more urns rest in rows several feet high in recesses cut into the surrounding walls.
PROMETHEUS_DVS618
SOMEONE's screen shows the countless supply.
PROMETHEUS_DVS619
Looking on, SOMEONE narrows her blue eyes.
PROMETHEUS_DVS620
Crossing the mist enshrouded floor, SOMEONE arrives at another code panel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS622
He operates it successfully and a door rises before him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS624
The probes dart past two humanoid figures standing on either side in suits and masks.
PROMETHEUS_DVS625
SOMEONE shines his light on the apparent corpses.
PROMETHEUS_DVS626
Turning ahead, he slows, his lips parting.
PROMETHEUS_DVS627
The probe darts out past him as he enters the chamber.
PROMETHEUS_DVS628
Sarcophagus-like pods lie before him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS629
As SOMEONE watches from her lifeboat, SOMEONE cuts off the video feed.
PROMETHEUS_DVS631
Within the chamber, we drift up to find two more giant pods resting opposite their counterparts atop a hundred foot disc marked with a spiderweb-like pattern.
PROMETHEUS_DVS632
Massive pillars stripe the surrounding concave walls.
PROMETHEUS_DVS633
SOMEONE ventures in, dwarfed by the massive disk.
PROMETHEUS_DVS635
The rest of the away team arrives at the chamber with the bust.
PROMETHEUS_DVS636
SOMEONE eyes the humanoid corpse.
PROMETHEUS_DVS637
Behind SOMEONE, Holloway stumbles.
PROMETHEUS_DVS638
They enter the fatal chamber.
PROMETHEUS_DVS640
SOMEONE leans over an urn, peering closely with his flashlight.
PROMETHEUS_DVS641
The team moves through the dark, treacherous space.
PROMETHEUS_DVS642
As SOMEONE stares, SOMEONE finds a body lying face down in his suit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS643
He sits on the ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS644
His skin bears no color. The others find SOMEONE's face green and distorted.
PROMETHEUS_DVS645
The serpentine creature leaps out at them.
PROMETHEUS_DVS646
It slithers away.
PROMETHEUS_DVS647
Leading the team out, SOMEONE supports Holloway.
PROMETHEUS_DVS648
Ducking out, Holloway collapses.
PROMETHEUS_DVS649
SOMEONE passes Ravel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS650
As she goes, Ravel watches the monitors.
PROMETHEUS_DVS651
At the edge of the giant disk, SOMEONE circles around a curved, throne-like chair to a control panel with rows of buttons the size and shape of eggs.
PROMETHEUS_DVS652
As he presses a sequence of them
PROMETHEUS_DVS653
they squish beneath his touch like soft hollow rubber.
PROMETHEUS_DVS654
An untouched button on the end pulsates with light from within.
PROMETHEUS_DVS655
SOMEONE presses it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS656
The throne-like chair rotates in his direction.
PROMETHEUS_DVS657
His flashlight sweeps over a treelike design on the backrest with twin egg-like patterns at the top.
PROMETHEUS_DVS658
SOMEONE climbs on the seat and leans back into it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS659
A holographic recording plays back.
PROMETHEUS_DVS660
Showing a helmetless engineer stepping up on the disk.
PROMETHEUS_DVS661
SOMEONE grins giddily.
PROMETHEUS_DVS662
SOMEONE shines his flashlight at the first, who bends over at one of the sarcophagus-like pods.
PROMETHEUS_DVS663
He gestures to a few others, who walk in and circle the disc.
PROMETHEUS_DVS664
One continues toward SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS665
The Android springs from the chair as the engineer takes a seat in it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS666
SOMEONE cocks his head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS667
Curiously looking on as the alien rotates the chair to face the controls.
PROMETHEUS_DVS668
He picks up a reed-like flute and plays.
PROMETHEUS_DVS669
A blue and green holographic sphere rises before the pilot.
PROMETHEUS_DVS670
Connected to the horse shoe shaped panel by streams of green energy.
PROMETHEUS_DVS672
As the pilot works the controls, more emerald hued fields of energy appear above them.
PROMETHEUS_DVS673
SOMEONE lowers a gloved hand,
PROMETHEUS_DVS674
and the energy rises up to connect with it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS675
The android climbs up on the disc and crouches, studying the control panel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS676
In the recording, the leader walks over to the pilot and crouches to face him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS678
SOMEONE listens to their exchange.
PROMETHEUS_DVS679
A tremendous, three-dimensional holographic orb appears over the center of the disc. Cerulean points of light webbed together within swirl about in steady patterns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS680
A star system appears in its midst, complete with a ringed planet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS681
Staring, SOMEONE approaches the intergalactic map.
PROMETHEUS_DVS683
Higher up, smaller spheres with concentric orbital rings revolve around the disk.
PROMETHEUS_DVS684
SOMEONE steps into the mains sphere and orbital rings appear around it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS686
Spreading his arms wide, the pilot leans back as if playing an organ.
PROMETHEUS_DVS687
The main sphere diminishes and darts aside. One of the smaller orbs takes its place and grows. Smiling wondrously in its midst,
PROMETHEUS_DVS688
SOMEONE looks up and finds a glowing sphere hovering directly above him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS689
He spreads his arms wide and turns on the spot.
PROMETHEUS_DVS690
The pilot presses more buttons and another orb drifts downward in a net of green energy beams.
PROMETHEUS_DVS692
Reaching up, SOMEONE catches it lightly in his gloved hand.
PROMETHEUS_DVS693
As he peers curiously at the softly glowing orb, we recognize the continent of Africa.
PROMETHEUS_DVS694
He releases the model of earth, letting it float back up again and gazes after it ardently.
PROMETHEUS_DVS695
His arms spread, SOMEONE sways on the spot.
PROMETHEUS_DVS696
The recording abruptly cuts out.
PROMETHEUS_DVS697
As SOMEONE steadies himself his bewildered gaze lands on the holographic model of earth.
PROMETHEUS_DVS698
Rotating inches above a translucent cone-shaped face the image fades.
PROMETHEUS_DVS699
SOMEONE turns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS700
A  soft golden glow flickering on his face.
PROMETHEUS_DVS701
From within one of the pods an amber light fades.
PROMETHEUS_DVS702
Aiming his flashlight, the android approaches it wearily.
PROMETHEUS_DVS703
Its ornate translucent lid ends at the head with an egg-shaped hatch equipped with a handle.
PROMETHEUS_DVS704
SOMEONE flashlight beam shines through the barrier, revealing an engineer lying inside.
PROMETHEUS_DVS705
He rests motionlessly with his eyes closed and a breathing mask covering his nose and mouth.
PROMETHEUS_DVS706
SOMEONE plants a gloved hand and the lid and crouches close to the pod.
PROMETHEUS_DVS707
Turning his head  he leans an ear close to it.
PROMETHEUS_DVS708
SOMEONE's lips curl into a happy smile.
PROMETHEUS_DVS709
Meanwhile the rest of the team boards the transport.
PROMETHEUS_DVS710
SOMEONE cradles Holloway as he arrives.
PROMETHEUS_DVS711
Discolored bumps on his skin spread and darken.
PROMETHEUS_DVS712
The transport doors open.
PROMETHEUS_DVS713
The crew climbs out.
PROMETHEUS_DVS714
SOMEONE strides through the hanger and grabs a flamethrower.
PROMETHEUS_DVS715
As the door lowers, SOMEONE stops halfway down, wielding the menacing weapon.
PROMETHEUS_DVS716
Holloway collapses.
PROMETHEUS_DVS717
As SOMEONE goes to help, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS718
Holloway steps toward SOMEONE, his arms outstretched. SOMEONE holds SOMEONE back. SOMEONE ignites the flamethrower, setting Holloway on fire.
PROMETHEUS_DVS719
His body completely engulfed Holloway drops to his knees. SOMEONE sobs on the ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS720
As Holloway's fiery body falls face first and lies still,
PROMETHEUS_DVS721
SOMEONE watches with a horrified expression.
PROMETHEUS_DVS722
SOMEONE opens her mouth wide in a grief stricken wail.
PROMETHEUS_DVS723
Later, wearing a white tunic,
PROMETHEUS_DVS724
she sleeps on a wide lit exam table.
PROMETHEUS_DVS725
A pair of hands reach for her cross,
PROMETHEUS_DVS726
and she instinctively grabs at them.
PROMETHEUS_DVS727
SOMEONE nods gently, and she allows him to remove her necklace.
PROMETHEUS_DVS728
As he steps away, SOMEONE lets her arms relax at her sides.
PROMETHEUS_DVS729
He puts the cross in a jar.
PROMETHEUS_DVS730
He runs a scan of her abdomen.
PROMETHEUS_DVS731
SOMEONE sits up, her jaw slack.
PROMETHEUS_DVS732
She stares wide-eyed and her lips stammer.
PROMETHEUS_DVS733
She scoots off the table.
PROMETHEUS_DVS734
She taps buttons on the exam table's panel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS735
She grips his shoulders.
PROMETHEUS_DVS736
Her mouth opens wide and she doubles over.
PROMETHEUS_DVS737
SOMEONE injects her in the back of the shoulder.
PROMETHEUS_DVS738
He lifts her limp body back on to the table.
PROMETHEUS_DVS739
As SOMEONE shifts to lie on her back, SOMEONE gazes down at her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS740
A tear falls from SOMEONE's eye and she shakes her head in confusion.
PROMETHEUS_DVS741
SOMEONE's lips tremble.
PROMETHEUS_DVS742
SOMEONE snatches the jar with her necklace and strides out.
PROMETHEUS_DVS743
SOMEONE, lying nearly motionless, stares up at the ceiling.
PROMETHEUS_DVS744
Taking a few deep breaths she drifts off to sleep.
PROMETHEUS_DVS746
She lies asleep on her side.
PROMETHEUS_DVS747
A hand in an oversized yellow glove gives her cheek a few brisk taps. SOMEONE remains motionless.
PROMETHEUS_DVS748
As a crewman in a containment suit approaches, SOMEONE whacks him with a metal object, then heads forward.
PROMETHEUS_DVS749
As the crewman forces her down, SOMEONE presses up on the plastic covering his face. She kicks him off of her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS750
As she gets down from the table, she falls briefly, clutching her abdomen.
PROMETHEUS_DVS751
SOMEONE races from the room but almost immediately collapses against the wall in pain.
PROMETHEUS_DVS752
Gritting her teeth she hurries on.
PROMETHEUS_DVS753
SOMEONE arrives in the room housing Vickers' med pod. She uses its touchscreen panel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS754
She selects manual procedure.
PROMETHEUS_DVS755
As the med pod rotates and tilts into an upright position,
PROMETHEUS_DVS756
the clear domed lid opens in three sections.
PROMETHEUS_DVS757
SOMEONE quickly removes her white hospital gown, revealing her bandage-like underwear, and grabs two auto-injectors.
PROMETHEUS_DVS758
She holds one in her mouth as she stabs her thigh with the other.
PROMETHEUS_DVS759
She limps over to the med pod and positions herself on the upright table under a curved scanner.
PROMETHEUS_DVS760
As the two bottom sections of the lid come together like a set of doors,
PROMETHEUS_DVS761
the upper section lowers down over the patient.
PROMETHEUS_DVS762
SOMEONE's taut belly bulges.
PROMETHEUS_DVS763
As the med pod lowers back down, SOMEONE scoots herself into position. She makes a few selections from a touch screen, projected over her head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS764
The scanner glides over her body.
PROMETHEUS_DVS765
A band of green light scans her abdomen.
PROMETHEUS_DVS766
As her stomach bulges up normally an image of the alien fetus appears on the screen before her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS767
A robotic arm equipped for surgical tools sprays anesthetics across her stomach below her belly button.
PROMETHEUS_DVS768
Three more arms position themselves.
PROMETHEUS_DVS769
One of the arms performs a precision cut with a laser.
PROMETHEUS_DVS770
SOMEONE arches her head way back.
PROMETHEUS_DVS771
The muscles in her neck tense as she grits her teeth.
PROMETHEUS_DVS772
As the robotic arms on either side of her pry back her skin,
PROMETHEUS_DVS773
SOMEONE's mouth opens wide in a pained SOMEONE. A large pair of forceps rotates into position at the top of the arched scanner.
PROMETHEUS_DVS774
As they lower toward her, SOMEONE gives herself another injection.
PROMETHEUS_DVS776
Her head relaxes back, then tenses again as the forceps dip into her open abdomen.
PROMETHEUS_DVS777
The forceps slowly pull the creature out. A thick tentacle wiggles inside an egg-shaped sac the size of SOMEONE's head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS778
Relaxing a bit SOMEONE lifts her head of the table and stares slack-jawed.
PROMETHEUS_DVS779
The sac brakes open splattering her with bloody fluid and revealing the squid-like alien.
PROMETHEUS_DVS780
She quickly grabs the umbilical cord and yanks it out. As she makes a selection on the overhead screen, the alien's four tentacles spread open and it moves its head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS781
Gritting her teeth, SOMEONE watches the robotic arm staple her stomach shut.
PROMETHEUS_DVS782
Above her the alien baby wriggles more vigorously.
PROMETHEUS_DVS783
Flailing its tentacles it tries to free itself from the forceps' grip.
PROMETHEUS_DVS784
The med pot starts to tilt upright and SOMEONE slams a button beside her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS785
The lid slowly opens. SOMEONE scoots down, flattening her head to one side it passes under the flailing alien.
PROMETHEUS_DVS786
Reaching the end of the table she quickly rushes around to the outer control panel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS787
The doors close back up, trapping the baby alien inside, and a white mist fills the chamber.
PROMETHEUS_DVS788
SOMEONE sinks to her knees and catches her breath.
PROMETHEUS_DVS789
She grabs some more auto-injectors from a cart,
PROMETHEUS_DVS790
then watches the baby alien grow still.
PROMETHEUS_DVS791
She quickly opens the room's door and hurries out of Vickers' life boat.
PROMETHEUS_DVS792
Inside the med pod blood drips from the alien's long egg-shaped head as it hangs motionless.
PROMETHEUS_DVS793
Now, on the bridge.
PROMETHEUS_DVS794
A crewman stops halfway down the lowering ramp in a space suit and helmet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS796
He cocks his head, then moves closer to SOMEONE who sits crouched on the ground with his legs bent forward over his shoulders.
PROMETHEUS_DVS797
On the bridge, SOMEONE's eyes shift nervously.
PROMETHEUS_DVS798
The crewman kicks SOMEONE's foot,
PROMETHEUS_DVS799
then backs away a few steps. He turns to a crewmate.
PROMETHEUS_DVS800
SOMEONE stands upright.
PROMETHEUS_DVS801
His smashed open helmet reveals his grotesquely deformed features.
PROMETHEUS_DVS802
The mutant backhands him, breaking open his helmet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS803
Meanwhile, SOMEONE hurriedly limps down a corridor. In the hanger, the mutant SOMEONE flings Wallace to the ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS804
The mutant leaps on Wallace's stomach and the crewman spews blood. The mutant smashes both fists through his helmet, pummeling his face.
PROMETHEUS_DVS805
A crewman fires at the mutant, who turns his head angrily. Meanwhile SOMEONE turns briefly as she makes her way past a hanging space suit. A door to another corridor opens for her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS806
Meanwhile,  crewmen fire flamethrowers and guns at the mutant.
PROMETHEUS_DVS807
On fire, the mutant speedily scales a smooth wall, then leaps down, tackling a crewman. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand at the air-locked door.
PROMETHEUS_DVS808
Two guys fire on the mutant as he flings a third against a transport's window. As the men escape into a transport, the mutant lodges a metal tool into ones back and pulls him out.
PROMETHEUS_DVS809
The mutant falls back and the guys run over him with the transport.
PROMETHEUS_DVS810
As the vehicle takes off, SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive, dousing the mutant with fire and bullets.
PROMETHEUS_DVS811
SOMEONE lowers the flamethrower and watches the body burn.
PROMETHEUS_DVS812
Meanwhile, SOMEONE gives herself another shot, then drops the auto-injector.
PROMETHEUS_DVS813
Our view rises from her thigh up her blood-spattered body to her drawn face.
PROMETHEUS_DVS814
She peers down a corridor, then lowers her hand from a concave wall, and shuffles toward a set of rounded doors.
PROMETHEUS_DVS815
She presses a button and the doors part.
PROMETHEUS_DVS816
She staggers into a room and collapses to her knees.
PROMETHEUS_DVS817
A man dressed in white notices her,
PROMETHEUS_DVS818
then helps her to her feet along with a guard.
PROMETHEUS_DVS819
SOMEONE notices her as well.
PROMETHEUS_DVS820
He quickly takes off his white coat and wraps it around the half-naked woman.
PROMETHEUS_DVS821
SOMEONE stares at her, sitting in a wheelchair.
PROMETHEUS_DVS822
He watches as the guard helps her take a seat.
PROMETHEUS_DVS823
Shivering, SOMEONE notices the old man.
PROMETHEUS_DVS824
SOMEONE returns to SOMEONE and kneels on the floor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS825
He washes the old man's feet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS826
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a cane.
PROMETHEUS_DVS827
then helps him put on his slippers.
PROMETHEUS_DVS828
SOMEONE and the aid help the decrepit old man to his feet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS829
SOMEONE turns away from SOMEONE and his aide readies his wheelchair.
PROMETHEUS_DVS831
SOMEONE lowers her distraught gaze.
PROMETHEUS_DVS832
Now in her cabin, she leans over her sink.
PROMETHEUS_DVS833
She splashes water on her face, then looks over the counter.
PROMETHEUS_DVS834
She picks up Holloway's ring, studies it, then slides it the ring finger of her left hand.
PROMETHEUS_DVS835
Gazing thoughtfully, she covers her mouth.
PROMETHEUS_DVS837
As she sets her hands on the counter, we glimpse the line of staples two inches under her navel.
PROMETHEUS_DVS838
Nodding, she glances around, then looks over the counter.
PROMETHEUS_DVS840
She pops a pill in her mouth, then drinks from a glass of water.
PROMETHEUS_DVS841
Later, she puts on her spacesuit and zips it up.
PROMETHEUS_DVS842
SOMEONE enters the cabin and notices his colleague in her formfitting suit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS843
SOMEONE returns to the sink and pops another pill.
PROMETHEUS_DVS844
SOMEONE heads out.
PROMETHEUS_DVS845
He stops at the door, then returns to SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS846
Holding her gaze SOMEONE steps back and leans against the wall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS847
Now in SOMEONE's bedchamber, SOMEONE stands by as SOMEONE works on the back of the old man's space suit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS848
Doors part for SOMEONE and she steps into the room.
PROMETHEUS_DVS849
Two guards stand outside.
PROMETHEUS_DVS850
SOMEONE and the others step out, then the door slides shut, leaving SOMEONE alone with the old man.
PROMETHEUS_DVS851
SOMEONE peers at her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS852
He sits on his bed.
PROMETHEUS_DVS853
She approaches him and he averts his gaze.
PROMETHEUS_DVS854
Kneeling, she caresses his hand.
PROMETHEUS_DVS855
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE bows her head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS856
She rubs her nose over his knuckles and he makes a fist.
PROMETHEUS_DVS857
She looks up at him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS858
He meets her piercing gaze.
PROMETHEUS_DVS861
She rises to her feet, Now, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE sitting in the corner of an equipment room.
PROMETHEUS_DVS862
He picks up a helmet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS863
Meanwhile SOMEONE walks down a corridor with SOMEONE and his aide close behind.
PROMETHEUS_DVS864
SOMEONE stands.
PROMETHEUS_DVS865
She doubles over in pain.
PROMETHEUS_DVS866
SOMEONE crosses the room.
PROMETHEUS_DVS867
Now a transport vehicle sets out from the ship leaving a trail of dust in its wake.
PROMETHEUS_DVS868
Later, in the network of tunnels, a flashlight shines through the darkness, leading the team.
PROMETHEUS_DVS869
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE slack-jawed.
PROMETHEUS_DVS870
A door rises and SOMEONE leads the group onward.
PROMETHEUS_DVS871
SOMEONE lags behind. The only one still wearing her helmet. As she shines her flashlight over the urns, SOMEONE watches a video feed from the bridge.
PROMETHEUS_DVS872
SOMEONE looks over the urns. The captain leaves his chair.
PROMETHEUS_DVS873
SOMEONE sits at a work station.
PROMETHEUS_DVS874
SOMEONE stands at the layout table.
PROMETHEUS_DVS875
A hologram shows the tunnel system without the surrounding terrain.
PROMETHEUS_DVS876
An alarmed SOMEONE stands upright.
PROMETHEUS_DVS877
The hologram represents an elaborate crescent shaped vessel with blunted ends.
PROMETHEUS_DVS878
Now SOMEONE leads the group into the chamber housing the giant disc.
PROMETHEUS_DVS879
He hops down from the platform, then sits in the chair and blows into the flute, calling up a holographic orb.
PROMETHEUS_DVS881
crosses the disc.
PROMETHEUS_DVS883
He leads them to the working pod.
PROMETHEUS_DVS884
SOMEONE collapses to her knees in pain.
PROMETHEUS_DVS885
SOMEONE takes off her helmet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS886
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from the bridge.
PROMETHEUS_DVS887
SOMEONE touches amber lit symbols on the pod.
PROMETHEUS_DVS888
It opens.
PROMETHEUS_DVS889
SOMEONE steps past his aide who lowers a gun.
PROMETHEUS_DVS890
As the engineer sits up, several tubes detach from his oxygen mask.
PROMETHEUS_DVS891
He takes off his headgear and hunches over.
PROMETHEUS_DVS892
As he rises to his feet more tubing detaches. Standing upright, the pale bald titan looks over his mesmerized visitors.
PROMETHEUS_DVS893
As the engineer crouches, SOMEONE stumbles but SOMEONE and his aide catch him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS894
The engineer looks at SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS895
The aide strikes SOMEONE in the gut with his gun.
PROMETHEUS_DVS896
The engineer looks at SOMEONE who eagerly waits for a reply.
PROMETHEUS_DVS897
He gently lays his hand on the top of SOMEONE's head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS898
With both hands, he grabs SOMEONE by the throat, then lifts him off his feet and breaks his neck.
PROMETHEUS_DVS899
He rips SOMEONE's head off and strikes SOMEONE with it. The aide shoots the engineer, and he drops the head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS900
The engineer turns SOMEONE around and palms her chest, knocking her off the platform.
PROMETHEUS_DVS901
He strikes the aide, flings him into a wall across the chamber, then spots SOMEONE running away, but lets her go.
PROMETHEUS_DVS902
SOMEONE slows to a stop and braces herself on a wall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS903
Now SOMEONE lies wounded on the floor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS904
SOMEONE's head lies about a foot away.
PROMETHEUS_DVS905
Eyes open, the android twitches.
PROMETHEUS_DVS906
On the bridge SOMEONE watches a video feed showing her father's heart rate.
PROMETHEUS_DVS907
She leaves the monitor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS908
Ravel watches the feed.
PROMETHEUS_DVS909
SOMEONE looks at his rattled shipmate, then lowers his gaze. He licks his lips, then shifts in his seat.
PROMETHEUS_DVS910
SOMEONE rubs his mouth.
PROMETHEUS_DVS911
Now the engineer crouches over the holographic orb.
PROMETHEUS_DVS912
The center of the disc drops, then rotates counter clockwise and opens for a head and pillar to emerge.
PROMETHEUS_DVS913
SOMEONE tries to look in its direction.
PROMETHEUS_DVS914
The engineer stands upright.
PROMETHEUS_DVS915
The rising pillar tilts, attached to a base with a seat,
PROMETHEUS_DVS916
like a cannon attached to a gunner chair.
PROMETHEUS_DVS917
The engineer faces the imposing device. SOMEONE watches him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS918
The gunner chair rotates.
PROMETHEUS_DVS919
Running through a tunnel, SOMEONE glances back.
PROMETHEUS_DVS920
As the engineer climbs onto the gunner chair, we glimpse SOMEONE's motionless face in profile.
PROMETHEUS_DVS921
The engineer takes a seat, then activates the star map.
PROMETHEUS_DVS922
A holographic sphere emerges around him, and widening outer rings flip into place.
PROMETHEUS_DVS923
SOMEONE stops to catch her breath.
PROMETHEUS_DVS924
As the engineer works the controls, a brief flash illuminates his crescent shaped ship. A helmet closes over him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS925
The helmet shields his face, then more armor shields his body. Smoke blasts from a circle of ports, blotting out our view of the ship's underbelly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS926
A torrent of smoke shoots through the tunnel, knocking SOMEONE off her feet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS927
The exhaust hurls her through  passage leading outside.
PROMETHEUS_DVS928
Through a window, the crew watches thin plumes of smoke rise from the ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS930
As our view retracts through the star map a holographic line sets out from the gunner chair and targets hologram of the planet earth.
PROMETHEUS_DVS931
Amid the flow of exhaust, SOMEONE grabs hold of a ledge, and pulls herself out of a hole in the ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS932
She rises to her feet, standing beside one of the erupting plumes. She runs for SOMEONE, but the ground fissures, threatening to cut her off from the ship.
PROMETHEUS_DVS933
As the gap widens she jumps the fissure and runs on.
PROMETHEUS_DVS934
We glimpse the ceiling opening up over the crescent shaped ship.
PROMETHEUS_DVS936
Running for SOMEONE, SOMEONE jumps another gap, but falls short and grabs hold of the opposite ledge.
PROMETHEUS_DVS937
She pulls herself up, then finds her path blocked for certain.
PROMETHEUS_DVS938
SOMEONE glimpses the rising ship, then flees the shifting ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS940
As she dashes across the rocky terrain, the massive ship ascends in the background.
PROMETHEUS_DVS942
SOMEONE stumbles but gets up and takes cover behind a rocky pillar.
PROMETHEUS_DVS943
SOMEONE gives his captain an affirming glance.
PROMETHEUS_DVS944
Now SOMEONE runs through a corridor, unzipping her clothes. Reaching the escape pods she opens a pod door and grabs a space suit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS945
Blue flames ignite from the engines. SOMEONE puts on his baseball cap as he takes the helm.
PROMETHEUS_DVS946
The four firing engines lift the SOMEONE off the ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS947
The crescent shaped ship rotates, its blunted ends turning toward the human's vessel as it rises into the sky.
PROMETHEUS_DVS948
The lifeboat section ejects from the ship. SOMEONE readies her space suit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS949
The lifeboat lands on the barren terrains, smashing a rocky pillar before it slides to a stop.
PROMETHEUS_DVS950
On the bridge.
PROMETHEUS_DVS951
SOMEONE gets in the escape pod
PROMETHEUS_DVS952
The pod ejects from the ship
PROMETHEUS_DVS953
SOMEONE watches as it loops around and swoops past her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS954
Touching ground, it slides to a stop.
PROMETHEUS_DVS955
In the cockpit, SOMEONE stands at the helm, his shipmate seated behind him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS956
SOMEONE rockets towards its target.
PROMETHEUS_DVS957
The three shipmates raise their arms overhead.
PROMETHEUS_DVS958
SOMEONE's nose pierces the outer wall of the larger ship, creating a fiery explosion.
PROMETHEUS_DVS959
As the engineer's ship careens a brilliant burst flashes,
PROMETHEUS_DVS960
Followed by an outpouring of smoke and SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS962
SOMEONE watches from the ground as does SOMEONE.
PROMETHEUS_DVS963
the crescent shaped ship turns sideways and descends to the ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS964
One of its blunted ends crash lands before the two survivors.
PROMETHEUS_DVS965
Huge plumes of smoke and SOMEONE billow from the point of impact. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare at the towering vessel, their jaws hanging slack.
PROMETHEUS_DVS966
The crescent shaped ship rolls their way, tipping on to the second of its blunted ends. SOMEONE and SOMEONE break into a run.
PROMETHEUS_DVS967
The second massive stub crashes into the ground behind them, and the ship keeps rolling.
PROMETHEUS_DVS968
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE desperately try to outrun the trundling vessel, fiery chunks of SOMEONE strike the ground all around them.
PROMETHEUS_DVS969
The rolling ship chases them past a number of rocky pillars, dotting the harsh terrain, its shadow at their heels.
PROMETHEUS_DVS970
SOMEONE trips and falls face down.
PROMETHEUS_DVS971
As SOMEONE keeps running, SOMEONE looks up at the looming mass, then rolls out of its way.
PROMETHEUS_DVS972
She rises to her knees and watches SOMEONE fall to the ground up ahead.
PROMETHEUS_DVS973
Flailing on her back, SOMEONE watches the ship's outer wall close in.
PROMETHEUS_DVS974
The ship' slows to a stop.
PROMETHEUS_DVS975
Now on its back, its blunted ends aloft.
PROMETHEUS_DVS976
Gawking at the towering vessel, SOMEONE rises to her feet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS977
The upright ship begins to tip her way.
PROMETHEUS_DVS978
She falls on her rear, scurries back toward some jagged rocks, then watches one end of the ship come down with no chance of escape.
PROMETHEUS_DVS979
As the impact plots out our view, we glimpse a burst of sparks.
PROMETHEUS_DVS980
SOMEONE lies in a pocket left underneath the ship, saved by the formation of jagged rocks behind her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS981
She looks at her wrist then turns on her side and glances around.
PROMETHEUS_DVS982
She crawls out from under the ship.
PROMETHEUS_DVS984
She rises to her feet, staggers a few steps, then glimpses an expanse of the vessel's outer wall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS985
The engineer's ship forms a semi-circle around her.
PROMETHEUS_DVS986
Turning, SOMEONE sees the lifeboat and staggers over the SOMEONE littered ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS987
Small fires dot the field.
PROMETHEUS_DVS988
Nearing the craft, SOMEONE pauses and doubles over.
PROMETHEUS_DVS989
Straightening she sways on her feet, then perseveres  to the compartment's open entryway and climbs up.
PROMETHEUS_DVS990
She swings her legs over, pushes herself up on all fours and gets to her feet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS991
SOMEONE stumbles to a touchscreen control panel and works it with shaking hands.
PROMETHEUS_DVS992
A pair of doors slides shut behind her, sealing her inside.
PROMETHEUS_DVS993
She packs supplies from nearby shelves.
PROMETHEUS_DVS994
SOMEONE halts and turns.
PROMETHEUS_DVS995
Her eyes wide, she looks over her shoulder at the doors.
PROMETHEUS_DVS997
Facing forward, she reaches into low tool compartment and takes out a fire ax with a curved handle.
PROMETHEUS_DVS998
Doors ahead open, revealing the devastated remains of SOMEONE quarters.
PROMETHEUS_DVS999
On the far end, the false windows show the video of the little girl playing the violin.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1000
Broken hoses, tubes and wires dangle from the ceiling panel surrounding the chandelier.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1001
SOMEONE shovels in, removes her helmet and sets it aside.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1003
Sparks rain down erratically from the ceiling as she ventures past the bar, her axe ready, and approaches a doorway.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1004
Pausing at its threshold, she raises the axe and gazes down a brief passageway ending in a sealed door with two small windows.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1005
She precedes hesitantly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1006
Breathing through flared nostrils.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1007
Wet with condensation, the doors windows show the med pod moving on its own in the flickering light.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1008
SOMEONE leans her face close to the glass peering through.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1009
As we watch her from the other side we find blood smearing the door.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1010
A giant tentacle slaps against the glass. SOMEONE backs away, her mouth hanging open in a terrified stare.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1011
The tentacle rubs persistently against the window then slides down the glass.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1012
As SOMEONE turns, the remaining engineer forces a pair of side doors open and leans through.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1013
Charging, he backs her against a wall.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1014
She pounds a touchscreen, a tentacle shoots out through the med pod station doors lashes around the engineer's throat and tackles him, taking SOMEONE down with them.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1015
As the creature wraps its tentacles around the engineer, she wriggles out from beneath them both.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1016
A spare tentacle wraps around her ankle, but she kicks it lose and scrambles away.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1017
The creature lifts the engineer off the floor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1018
Grabbing her helmet, SOMEONE rushes back to the airlock compartment.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1019
In the lifeboat, the engineer struggles pitily against the grasp of the giant squid-like creature
PROMETHEUS_DVS1020
Flaps on its underside blossom outward like petals, revealing egg-shaped buds surrounding a vertical mouth lined with dagger-like teeth.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1022
The engineer braces his legs against the door frame.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1024
SOMEONE opens the air locked doors with her back and hand, then jumps out and lands in a hard roll.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1025
In the lifeboat, the engineer snarls at the creature pulling him ever closer.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1026
Yet another tentacle reaches out and wraps around his head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1027
The buds shoot out tendrils that lash around his skull and hold him still.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1028
The mouth launches a serpentine appendage down the engineer's throat.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1029
It pulls him close, then lowers itself on top of him.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1030
The giant squid-like creature wriggles around completely covering its prey.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1031
It eventually relaxes and grows still.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1032
Outside the sun peeks through thick rolling clouds. SOMEONE weeps on her back.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1033
On the disc, SOMEONE's head sweats.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1034
Outside SOMEONE lifts her head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1035
Grimacing painfully, SOMEONE sits up.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1036
Her gaze darts to a wrecked ATV half-buried in a mound of dirt.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1037
In the ship, light wavers on SOMEONE's glistening face.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1038
He listens uncertainly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1040
the ATV kicks up dust as SOMEONE drives it over the uneven terrain toward the engineer's crashed ship.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1042
she steps into its dim cockpit.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1043
Light flashes erratically.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1044
A few feet from his head, SOMEONE's body twitches. SOMEONE steps closer and looms over them coldly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1045
SOMEONE puts down her bag and removes her protective space helmet.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1047
Crouching at the android's body she rummages around and finds her cross.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1048
Gazing tenderly at it, SOMEONE gently straightens the chain.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1049
She solemnly puts it on over her head
PROMETHEUS_DVS1050
and gives a relieved sigh.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1051
Looking on, SOMEONE smiles admiringly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1052
SOMEONE crouches over his head.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1053
The android stares at her with parted lips. He clamps his mouth shut.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1054
Now, SOMEONE uses a line and pulley to lower SOMEONE's body out of an opening in the ship's hull.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1055
His head lies on the floor by her feet, gazing up at her placidly.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1056
The body touches down gently.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1057
SOMEONE picks up his head in both hands. SOMEONE gives her a childlike appreciative smile as she lowers him into her bag.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1058
The wind musses his hairline.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1059
SOMEONE zips the bag closed over his earnest gaze.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1060
Wincing painfully she gets to her feet and hauls the bag up.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1061
From the edge of the hull, she repels 20 feet to the ground.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1063
the ATV travels away from the structure along the desert valley.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1064
It approaches the next structure.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1065
Now we ascend through clouds.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1066
An engineer ship rises into view.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1067
Flaring brilliantly it darts away.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1068
Beyond the clouds, the ringed planet glows. Fade to black.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1069
In the abandoned lifeboat the last engineer's body convulses on the floor, surrounded by the creature's motionless tentacles.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1070
In the flickering pulsating light his chest bulges.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1071
An exoskeletal point resembling a giant
PROMETHEUS_DVS1072
claw bursts out and slices through his sternum.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1073
A skinny body with long limbs in a gleaming dark gray exoskeleton wriggles out of the hole and onto the floor.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1074
A yellow amniotic sac pulsates beside it,
PROMETHEUS_DVS1075
connecting the newborn to the engineer's carcass.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1076
The new alien specimen pushes itself up on all fours. It lifts its head which bears the oversized claw like growth as a sickle shaped head crest.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1077
The alien straightens, sitting up on its heels and looks around.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1079
It works its slavering jaws.
PROMETHEUS_DVS1080
A set of inner jaws pops out from its mouth.Its pink gums dripping slime.