A dark-haired man runs beside him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS29
An old woman walks beside them.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS30
The brothers trade a wry smirk.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS31
Later, they use weight machines.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS32
The young man glances aside then faces SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS33
The young man lowers his gaze and continues exercising his arms. SOMEONE resumes his workout.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS35
In therapy, The young man lies on a couch.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS36
The gray-bearded therapist gets up.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS37
He hands SOMEONE a teddy bear.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS38
Now, a woman hurries into a building, passing an advertisement for two authors.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS39
SOMEONE and SOMEONE Tharp.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS40
On stage, SOMEONE addresses the audience.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS41
SOMEONE walks on stage with his hands in his pockets leaving a clapping blonde woman behind.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS42
SOMEONE shakes his hand, pats him on the back, and shows him to his seat.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS43
In a bathroom, SOMEONE splashes water on his face. He looks at himself in a mirror.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS45
Now, audience members shake his hand as SOMEONE makes his way up an aisle.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS46
Now, we follow SOMEONE through a hallway. As a crowd crosses the other end, he turns back and walks in the opposite direction.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS47
A man in a nice suit steps out from a doorway.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS48
Later, at a reception. Later, at a reception.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS50
SOMEONE signs books. The bubbly SOMEONE crouches beside him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS51
Now sitting with SOMEONE, SOMEONE nods.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS52
Cut to black.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS53
Later, SOMEONE enters his house.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS54
He drops a book on the floor then shuts the door behind him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS55
He turns on a light.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS56
He ambles across the foyer.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS57
He sets his keys on a side table.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS58
He heads upstairs to a second floor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS59
He rounds a corner and steps out of view.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS60
SOMEONE finds the dog on his bed with a shredded paperback beside a wet stain on the sheet.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS61
Crouching to SOMEONE, he shakes his head.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS62
Now, SOMEONE comes back downstairs wrapped in his comforter.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS63
He enters a darkened living room and tosses a pillow on a sofa.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS64
Letting himself fall over the back of the couch, he plops on the cushions.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS65
Now, the young woman looks down at SOMEONE, the afternoon sun gleaming over her shoulder.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS66
The red-haired young woman kneels beside SOMEONE who sits under a tree with a book.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS67
SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a gaze and SOMEONE nods.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS68
The young woman takes out a sketch book.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS69
SOMEONE closes his book and gets up.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS70
The young woman tears a page from his sketch book and hands it to him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS71
He studies her drawing.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS72
On the sofa, SOMEONE wakes with a start.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS73
He shoves the comforter aside.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS74
Puts on his glasses and dashes upstairs.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS75
Sitting at his desk, he types feverishly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS76
His eyes open wide and his jaw hanging slack.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS77
The typewriter hammers out the words, in front of him, backlit by the sun.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS78
SOMEONE slides the typewriter's carriage repeatedly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS79
Writing through days and nights.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS80
In the daytime, he sits with his feet up, reading over his pages.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS81
He types out another line, slides the carriage.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS82
Then notices SOMEONE sitting on the floor with a woman's sandal in his mouth.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS83
Eyeing the dog curiously.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS84
SOMEONE takes the shoe and drops it on the desk.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS85
Later, he reads his work.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS87
Now with his therapist. SOMEONE lies back on the couch.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS88
SOMEONE looks at a ceiling vent. He imagines SOMEONE on roller skates.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS89
In her year book photo, she wears a leather jacket.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS90
He imagines her riding a bicycle.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS91
She rides away down a leaf covered path.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS92
SOMEONE and SOMEONE jog the same path.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS93
Later, they enter SOMEONE's house.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS94
In the bathroom, SOMEONE towels off his hair and combs through it with his fingers.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS95
He opens the cabinet, revealing a woman's razor on the shelf.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS96
Behind it, a can of shaving cream with a feminine design reads, Satin Care.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS97
SOMEONE studies the razor with a confused frown.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS98
Then takes both items downstairs.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS99
SOMEONE sits on the couch with an infant.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS100
SOMEONE presents a bra.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS102
Random woman's items fill the drawer.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS103
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a wide-eyed sheepish stare as she shuts the drawer.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS104
Later, he rinses off a plate and lays it out to dry.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS105
On a patio, SOMEONE sits in a lounge chair, drinking a beer as he reads the manuscript.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS106
SOMEONE comes near, peeks over his shoulder, and perches on the edge of another lounge chair.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS107
A swimming pool shimmers nearby.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS108
SOMEONE interlaces his fingers and leans toward SOMEONE with an eager hopeful smile.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS109
He smiles gently.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS110
Later, SOMEONE uses a baby carrier to haul SOMEONE to a car.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS111
SOMEONE lowers his shy gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS112
SOMEONE sees the couple off then heads inside. Moving through the foyer, he switches off the table lamp.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS113
He steps around his staircase and picks up the manuscript.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS114
Turning, SOMEONE pauses.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS115
He opens the drawer, stashing the mysterious woman's items then gently runs his fingertips over them.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS116
Now at his desk.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS117
SOMEONE taps away at his typewriter.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS118
With a dreamy wistful gaze he writes, This thing is dripping everywhere.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS120
In the imagined scene, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on his pool deck, enjoying takeout burgers and soft drinks.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS121
Chewing, he pauses.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS122
She grins sweetly at him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS123
At his typewriter, SOMEONE beams fondly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS124
Watching SOMEONE, SOMEONE coyly nibbles her soda straw.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS125
At his typewriter, SOMEONE furrows his brow and pauses briefly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS126
Under her vulnerable gaze, SOMEONE's expression softens.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS127
She smiles tenderly at him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS128
SOMEONE leans in close to her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS129
SOMEONE springs up and dashes pass him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS130
In her sundress and bare feet, she leaps into the narrow swimming pool.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS131
SOMEONE jumps in after her, fully clothed.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS132
The two swim around one another in a softly illuminated water.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS133
SOMEONE finishes typing.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS134
Beaming wistfully at the page, he shuts his eyes.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS136
He runs through the house.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS137
He finds his cellphone in a pile of clothes and answers it.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS138
He presses a few buttons.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS139
On his way out, SOMEONE freezes. SOMEONE stands in his kitchen, eating a bowl of cereal.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS140
SOMEONE backs up and sinks to the floor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS141
He springs from her touch.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS142
He runs upstairs and into his office.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS143
SOMEONE looks around with his hand on his chest. His wide eyes magnified by his glasses.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS144
He ventures cautiously from his office.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS145
Reaching the upstairs landing, he peers over the railing.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS146
SOMEONE finds no sign of the woman downstairs.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS147
SOMEONE turns away, his body relaxing.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS148
He faces another railing with a smile.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS149
He crawls away fearfully.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS150
He dashes through doorway and slams it shut behind him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS152
Now in his bathroom, SOMEONE dials a call on his cellphone and paces. He removes his glasses briefly and rubs his eyes.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS153
Ending the call, he braces both hands on the counter and leans over breathlessly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS154
Now in the kitchen.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS155
SOMEONE whisks eggs in a glass mixing bowl.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS156
As she adds hot sauce, SOMEONE creeps downstairs and musters a casual demeanor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS157
She steps out of the kitchen.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS158
SOMEONE forces a hungry smile. SOMEONE steps closer.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS159
He lifts the bra.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS160
SOMEONE stares skeptically.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS161
Now SOMEONE hides under his desk as he uses his phone.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS162
In a conference room.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS163
SOMEONE ends the call.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS164
He crawls out from under his desk.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS165
Opening a drawer, he finds another number.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS166
He ends the call.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS167
Now as we face a stairway behind an entertainment system.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS168
SOMEONE creeps down into view, his arms crooked before him cartoonishly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS169
He stares fearfully toward the kitchen.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS170
He sinks down behind the system and peeks out.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS171
But finds no sign of SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS172
Stepping off the stairs, he accidentally squishes a dog toy.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS173
He freezes then precedes to the foyer where he picks up his keys and wallet.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS174
At the top of the foyer stairs, SOMEONE steps out in a dress.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS175
As she descends he backs to the door.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS176
He gives a feeble shake of his head.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS177
Now, SOMEONE slumps miserably as he drives down a street lined with quaint storefronts.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS178
He casts his fearful gaze aside.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS179
SOMEONE rides with him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS180
She eyes him uncertainly then smooths her hair.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS181
Leaning forward, she turns on the radio.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS182
Now SOMEONE feeds a meter in the artsy Los Feliz neighborhood.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS183
SOMEONE accompanies him down the sidewalk.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS184
Later, SOMEONE shares an outdoor table with Mabel.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS185
She stares meaningfully at him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS186
SOMEONE watches her shift giddily then glances away.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS187
SOMEONE approaches.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS188
SOMEONE adjust his chair, Mabel shifts closer.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS189
SOMEONE grabs a busboy.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS190
SOMEONE makes the busboy touch SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS191
SOMEONE throws a glass of water in his face.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS192
She runs off.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS193
SOMEONE chases after her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS194
She whacks him with her purse and he grabs her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS195
SOMEONE lifts her over his shoulder and carries her down the sidewalk.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS196
He sets her down.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS197
SOMEONE brushes her long bangs aside.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS198
He caresses her lips with his thumb.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS199
SOMEONE cups her face in his hands. Staring up at him tearfully, SOMEONE yields a smile.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS200
She shakes her head and sighs.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS201
She shuts her eyes ecstatically as he leans his face toward hers.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS202
Their lips meet in an ardent tender kiss.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS203
SOMEONE pulls back, his brow knitted emotionally.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS204
They gaze into each other's eyes. SOMEONE kisses her again.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS205
Now at the Hollywood Forever Cemetery, a movie screen shows Zombie Attacks.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS206
Seated on the crowded lawn, SOMEONE and SOMEONE each take a shot.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS207
Later, SOMEONE covers a laughing SOMEONE's eyes.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS208
A zombie tears a woman's head off.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS209
And another clumsily stalks a victim on the floor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS210
SOMEONE lunges, playfully biting SOMEONE's neck.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS211
Now he catches up to her in an arcade and she greets him with a kiss.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS212
Later, she peeks out of a video game booth and draws him in with her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS213
They play a game with gun-shaped controllers. SOMEONE coolly blows the end of her gun's barrel.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS214
They dance in the arcade.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS215
SOMEONE lays her back on a pinball machine.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS216
As he nuzzles her between her breasts, she blissfully sweeps her arms past her head. Later, SOMEONE runs up to him and leaps into his arms.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS218
Now they bounce up and down on a crowded dance floor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS219
SOMEONE raises her arms and shakes her head.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS220
While SOMEONE bobs exuberantly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS221
Later, he deeps dips her and they kiss.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS222
Straightening, she slaps his chest to the music.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS223
Now, she jerks her head side-to-side.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS229
From the top of her dress, SOMEONE pulls out panties and twirls them on her finger.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS230
SOMEONE stops dancing staring wide-eyed.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS231
SOMEONE puts their waistband in her teeth.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS232
And points discreetly off the dance floor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS233
Now at a restaurant, SOMEONE enjoys chips and guacamole.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS234
He chews blissfully.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS235
Facing him, SOMEONE stares slack-jawed.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS236
SOMEONE's brother averts his worried gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS237
SOMEONE's smile falters sheepishly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS238
He eats another chip with guacamole, points approvingly and sips a margarita.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS239
A man passes by.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS240
SOMEONE looks around then leans back in his chair.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS241
Later, SOMEONE lets SOMEONE into the house.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS242
SOMEONE jumps into SOMEONE's arms.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS243
SOMEONE steps away.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS244
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE onto the balcony.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS245
Through a glass door, SOMEONE waves to SOMEONE and motions one minute. Donning an apron, she waves back.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS246
The brothers hurry down a staircase.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS248
SOMEONE glances inside.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS249
SOMEONE looks up at the house and shakes his head.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS250
SOMEONE takes his phone back.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS251
SOMEONE leads the way up the staircase.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS252
From the kitchen counter, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE and SOMEONE return to the balcony.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS253
The cross to the door with an affected breezy air.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS254
Watching them head upstairs, she grins.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS255
In the office.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS256
SOMEONE readies the typewriter. SOMEONE glances over the railing.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS257
SOMEONE stares dumbly at the page.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS258
SOMEONE contemplates.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS259
SOMEONE meets SOMEONE's gaze and points.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS260
He steps around the desk and whispers in his brother's ear.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS261
SOMEONE shoots him an incredulous look.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS262
A reluctant SOMEONE starts typing and we glimpse his words as they spell out on the page.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS263
Speak in fluent French.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS264
She had no awareness.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS269
The brothers trade a look. Now in the kitchen.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS270
SOMEONE notes their perplexed grins.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS271
Left alone with her, SOMEONE backs against a wall.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS272
SOMEONE types rapidly, his eyes wide and his jaw slack.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS273
He looks up from his typewriter then hurries out.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS274
He returns to the kitchen presenting a bottle of wine.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS275
SOMEONE steps out.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS276
Holding a salad bowl, SOMEONE wears a silly grin on his way to the dining room.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS278
Now, the brothers step out front.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS279
They get in SOMEONE's silver Sedan.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS280
SOMEONE repeatedly slams his back against the seat.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS281
SOMEONE stares at him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS282
SOMEONE shifts his sympathetic gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS283
SOMEONE opens the passenger door.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS284
He holds his brother's gaze then pulls the door shut.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS285
The brothers look each other in the eye.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS286
Later in his office, SOMEONE gathers the pages of his manuscript and locks them away in a desk drawer.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS287
SOMEONE rolls his chair over to SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS288
She sits on his lap and wraps her arms around him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS289
They share a loving gaze then kiss passionately.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS290
SOMEONE spins the chair and they twirl in place, remaining lip locked as the image gradually fades to black.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS291
Now stuck in traffic, SOMEONE reaches for his cellphone as SOMEONE plays a game on it.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS292
SOMEONE begs SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS293
Night time at the house.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS294
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in bed.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS295
Her sketches adorned the headboard.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS296
SOMEONE leans in for a kiss.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS297
As SOMEONE sets a tablet aside, SOMEONE turns off a lamp.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS298
Leaving the room in total darkness, but for the alarm clock which reads 11:56.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS299
In the morning, SOMEONE packs a duffel bag with clothes.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS300
SOMEONE wakes up, spots him at the foot of the bed and sits up.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS301
SOMEONE beams and SOMEONE jumps on the bed with her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS302
Now SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE drive up the Pacific Coast Highway in a convertible BMW.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS303
SOMEONE snakes her hand through the wind outside of the car.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS304
Embracing SOMEONE, she feeds him a snack.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS305
They run across the beach together then pace to the opposite ends of a long drift wood log.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS306
SOMEONE mimes shooting SOMEONE and he falls to the sand.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS307
Later, they continue up the coast with the Pacific Ocean just feet from the road.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS308
Now with the convertible's top up, the couple arrives at a wooden gate.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS309
SOMEONE sits on SOMEONE's lap.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS310
The gate opens automatically, revealing an abundance of shrubs and trees around a driveway.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS311
SOMEONE parks the car then turns to SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS312
A woman with tussled hair taps on the window.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS315
SOMEONE's mom opens a wooden door and leads them pass more lush plant life.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS316
Inside an open yet cozy home, candles adorn a huge brick fireplace.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS317
A small room with an elevated bed.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS319
They find SOMEONE wielding a chainsaw.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS320
SOMEONE lifts his helmet's face mask.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS321
He grins. Later the scruffy man feeds SOMEONE table scraps.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS322
SOMEONE kisses her hand.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS323
SOMEONE glances at his brother.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS324
SOMEONE smiles at him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS325
Later, they play charades.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS326
SOMEONE's mom gestures to SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS327
SOMEONE pats his frustrated brother on the back. SOMEONE's mom points to her breasts then pushes away the men and grabs her behind.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS328
The jubilant women embrace.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS329
SOMEONE watches his mother give SOMEONE a hug. SOMEONE pats her rear end.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS330
After a shower, SOMEONE covers herself with a towel.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS331
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in bed.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS332
SOMEONE lies on her side, turning away from SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS333
He returns his attention to a book.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS334
The next day, SOMEONE cannonballs into a pool.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS335
SOMEONE stands on a roof near a waterfall flowing into the pool.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS336
SOMEONE reads in a tree house. He steps out to a railing.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS337
SOMEONE cannonballs off the roof, making a huge splash. SOMEONE watches them.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS338
Later, SOMEONE's mom climbs up to the tree house.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS339
She finds her son sleeping on his back, holding the book over his chest.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS340
SOMEONE sits up.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS341
She climbs back down. Later after dinner.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS342
SOMEONE lights a joint.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS343
Holding the dog, SOMEONE copies his blank droopy stare.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS344
SOMEONE makes the same face but with a crinkled brow. He holds glasses over SOMEONE's eyes.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS345
Wearing an indignant smirk, SOMEONE cocks his head and scans the group.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS346
SOMEONE offers the joint.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS347
He kisses SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS348
Leaving the table, SOMEONE falls down drunkenly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS349
SOMEONE rushes over, the other's stare.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS350
SOMEONE and SOMEONE help SOMEONE out.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS351
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE's mother on the head and goes. She faces SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS352
The mother picks up a photo album lying on the table.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS353
She finds a photo of herself wearing a polo shirt.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS354
Standing beside a preppy man, she holds a trophy.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS355
A large driftwood chair.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS356
SOMEONE scoldingly gestures toward the piece. SOMEONE looks back and forth between Mort and the women with folded arms.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS357
Now, the young couple drives with the ocean to the right.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS358
The chair tied awkwardly in the back seat with SOMEONE's carrier. Both SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare straight ahead unhappily.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS361
Now the young writer reads on his sofa while SOMEONE cooks. SOMEONE faces him through the kitchen window with a wounded stare.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS362
He resumes reading.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS363
Holding a cooking utensil in each hand, SOMEONE drops them on a plate.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS364
Later, SOMEONE finds her curled up in a chair facing a window.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS365
She gazes out at the view as he shuffles over to her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS366
She blinks sadly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS367
SOMEONE crouches down beside her with a furrowed brow.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS368
SOMEONE shifts in her seat to face him and leans forward.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS369
As he watches her anxiously, she meets his gaze with tearful eyes.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS370
SOMEONE's brow lifts and he bows his head.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS371
SOMEONE wraps her in his arms.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS372
SOMEONE gives an earnest shake of his head.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS373
SOMEONE shifts his bewildered gaze then shrugs and smiles.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS374
Now in bed, SOMEONE stares up at the ceiling.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS375
SOMEONE sleeps on the pillow beside his.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS376
SOMEONE rolls over and eyes the clock reading 4:45.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS377
Now he and SOMEONE wait outside as SOMEONE bikes up to the house.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS378
The little dog runs up to her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS379
Later in the foyer.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS380
SOMEONE takes off her bike helmet and shakes out her hair. SOMEONE stares at her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS381
She jogs upstairs.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS382
SOMEONE follows at her heels. SOMEONE remains below, staring up after them.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS383
Now, his digital clock reads 3:19 as he lies in bed with SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS384
Wide awake and pouting,
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS385
he rolls on to his side and curls a hand around the little dog's belly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS386
Now, he cooks an elaborate dish in a pan.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS387
He snaps up a phone.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS388
SOMEONE pauses.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS389
SOMEONE freezes, staring off with a scowl.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS390
He sets the phone in its cradle then faces the food cooking in the pan.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS391
At night, SOMEONE lies curled up in bed staring woefully at the unoccupied pillow beside him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS392
Moving hesitantly, he turns on a bedside lamp and shifts his tempted gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS393
Now in his home office, SOMEONE unlocks his desk drawer.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS394
He pulls out the manuscript.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS395
SOMEONE sets the stack of paper beside his typewriter and slips a page out from the bottom.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS396
With tentative movements, he feeds the sheet of paper into the typewriter carriage.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS397
And adjust its position on the roller.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS398
SOMEONE slides the carriage to its starting position.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS399
He brings his fingers down to the keys and hesitates.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS400
The metal type bars gleams softly in the lamplight.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS401
SOMEONE stares at the typewriter.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS402
His eyeglasses reflecting the well-worn keys.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS403
With a creased brow he types, SOMEONE was miserable without SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS404
The writer slides the carriage to the return position and writes another line.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS405
He halts, raises his hands, and rests them in his lap.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS406
SOMEONE leans back in his chair and bows his head.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS407
Silhouetted against the soft lamplight.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS408
His lanky figure curves softly in a melancholy slouch.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS409
He lunges for the phone.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS410
Now in bed, SOMEONE lies naked on top of SOMEONE as he holds her blissfully.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS411
He starts to sidle out from under her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS412
Remaining with her, SOMEONE strokes her cheek.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS413
He rolls his head to the side with an uncomfortable gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS414
Now the two share a bowl of cereal.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS415
As SOMEONE lets go of his spoon, SOMEONE grabs hold of his hand and rests her cheek against it.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS416
SOMEONE sets down his newspaper, using his free hand to take another bite of cereal.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS417
As he continues reading, SOMEONE stares at him intensely.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS418
She bursts into tears and leans against his shoulder.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS419
Now she snuggles him as they watch a movie on TV.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS420
SOMEONE grabs his hand, nearly yanking him off balance, he gives a bewildered nod.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS421
As he hurries from the room, SOMEONE trots along with him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS422
Now as he drives, she drapes herself against his shoulder.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS423
At a box office, she holds him tight and stares up at his face.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS424
SOMEONE gives a childish nod.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS425
Paying, he struggles to reach the money past her grasping figure.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS426
SOMEONE takes the tickets. As they leave Grauman's Egyptian
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS427
she points at a star on the Walk of Fame.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS428
Hand in hand, they arrive at a crowded street corner.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS429
Crossing the street, SOMEONE lets go of SOMEONE's hand to answer his phone.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS430
Reaching the other side, he looks around worriedly and ends the call.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS431
He scans the busy intersection, finding no sign of his clingy paramour.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS432
He paces the corner.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS433
Turning, he halts and calls across the busy street.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS434
She stands at the other side of the crosswalk watching him forlornly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS435
As the signal changes, SOMEONE hurries back to her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS437
Back at home. SOMEONE rubs her back as she lies curled up on the bed.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS438
In his home office, SOMEONE slips the bottom page out from under his manuscript and feeds it into the carriage.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS439
Glancing anxiously toward the hallway.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS440
He positions the page then types, SOMEONE was filled with the most effervescent SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS443
Later, he brings a glass of water to the bedroom and halts.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS444
With a girlish grin, SOMEONE bounces giddily on the bed.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS445
She moves into a curled shoulder stand and jiggles.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS446
Now in the pool, she plays manically with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS447
She waves up at a patio where SOMEONE brings his brother a beer. SOMEONE cooks meat on a grill.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS448
SOMEONE glances toward SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS449
He frowns shamefully.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS450
SOMEONE stares at his brother then looks down at SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS451
SOMEONE giddily kicks up a splash of water. Both men glance down at her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS452
SOMEONE raises his beer to his lips.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS453
SOMEONE returns his sober gaze to the grill.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS454
SOMEONE stares at his brother then looks down at the pool with a thoughtful smile.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS455
Now, SOMEONE drums spoons on the kitchen counter.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS456
As SOMEONE looks on, she tiptoes back and forth over the kitchen tiles.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS457
Then playfully drops the spoons into the dishwasher.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS458
She faces him with a silly vapid grin.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS459
SOMEONE joins her hands and smiles excitedly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS460
Regarding her with a sad worried gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS461
SOMEONE steps closer and cups her face in his hands.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS462
SOMEONE raises her arms over her head.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS463
Now, words type out on a page.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS466
Seated before his typewriter, SOMEONE lowers his hands to his lap.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS467
He lifts his gaze and takes a calming breath.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS469
Now during the day, SOMEONE sprawls on the couch in her pajamas.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS470
Half-eaten snacks litter the coffee table and a blanket covers her feet.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS471
SOMEONE hurries in with dry cleaning.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS472
She turns the TV back on and throws down the remote. SOMEONE starts toward the couch.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS473
SOMEONE snatches the remote back up and curls around it protectively.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS474
SOMEONE takes in her unstable state then sets down the dry cleaning.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS475
As he sits beside her on the couch, SOMEONE turns off the TV.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS476
She chucks the remote aside then sits up sucking in her lips remorsefully.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS477
SOMEONE sits with his hands on his knees, staring with a furrowed brow.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS478
SOMEONE folds his hands and looks away.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS479
SOMEONE faces her and swallows.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS480
SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE hopefully.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS481
Now in a large house with walls of exposed stone, SOMEONE dances awkwardly among his chatting guests.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS482
Three guests arrive.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS483
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE away.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS484
SOMEONE stares then swaps awkward smiles with Saskia. In a group.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS485
Clutching her drink, SOMEONE wanders the party and sighs. She spies SOMEONE with a woman.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS486
Looking pass the woman, he notices SOMEONE drinking on her own.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS487
She meets his gaze and he raises his champagne flute. With the movie producers.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS488
SOMEONE runs into a blonde young woman as she steps out of the bathroom.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS489
He stares at her then averts his gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS490
A guy passes between them.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS491
SOMEONE nods.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS492
SOMEONE averts his gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS493
Outside, SOMEONE dips her toes in a swimming pool.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS494
SOMEONE stands across the water.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS495
SOMEONE approaches her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS496
SOMEONE meets his gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS498
SOMEONE holds his gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS499
SOMEONE glances aside.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS500
SOMEONE nods.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS501
SOMEONE glances aside.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS502
Standing in the pool, SOMEONE covers his eyes.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS503
As SOMEONE takes off her dress, SOMEONE peeks.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS504
Searching for his girlfriend, SOMEONE heads down a hallway to a backdoor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS505
Slack-jawed, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS506
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE speed home in the convertible.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS507
In the house, SOMEONE turns on the light.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS508
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's arm.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS509
SOMEONE follows her into the bedroom and SOMEONE goes downstairs.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS510
SOMEONE brushes pass him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS511
She takes off her dress then puts on another outfit.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS512
SOMEONE ambles past SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS513
She watches him cross the upper floor then lowers her frustrated gaze and feels her brow with both hands.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS514
In the office, SOMEONE switches on a desk lamp.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS515
He takes off his jacket and drapes it over the back of the chair.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS516
Lifting the typewriter, he grabs the key to the desk drawer hidden underneath.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS517
SOMEONE grabs an article of clothing from a hanger and packs a bag.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS518
SOMEONE adds a page to the typewriter.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS519
He cranks a knob on the side of the typewriter's carriage.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS520
SOMEONE faces him, dressed to leave with her bag slung over her shoulder.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS521
He slides the carriage.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS522
He pulls in his chair.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS523
SOMEONE watches him type.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS524
He finishes a line and slides the carriage.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS525
On her way out, SOMEONE bumps into an invisible wall.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS526
SOMEONE flinches.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS527
SOMEONE shakes his head softly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS528
SOMEONE gathers herself and tries to walk out again.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS529
She covers her face with her hands.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS530
SOMEONE lowers his gaze, SOMEONE grabs her handbag and marches out once more.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS531
Standing, SOMEONE offers her the page. SOMEONE glances aside then crosses to the desk and takes the page from his hand.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS532
With tears in her eyes she reads.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS533
SOMEONE hands her the manuscript.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS534
SOMEONE deflates.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS535
SOMEONE lowers his gaze and shakes his head.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS536
He clutches his brow.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS537
SOMEONE covers her face with her hands and glances aside.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS538
SOMEONE adds a page to the typewriter.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS541
A startled SOMEONE glances around.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS543
She covers her mouth.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS547
SOMEONE crosses to the desk and looks at the page.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS548
SOMEONE watches her stagger back.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS553
SOMEONE writes, SOMEONE snaps. And she notices her snapping fingers.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS555
She starts to panic.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS559
SOMEONE writes, SOMEONE strips and sings.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS560
He slides the carriage.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS561
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE strip out of her cardigan.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS564
Acting like a dog, she crawls across the floor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS565
SOMEONE watches her pick up a book with her teeth and fling it.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS566
She backs up to a bookshelf bearing her teeth.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS567
Grimacing, SOMEONE types, I'll never leave you.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS568
SOMEONE rises to her feet and flails wildly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS574
She jumps up then waves her arms over head.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS575
SOMEONE watches her, his mouth hanging open.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS576
Tilting his head back and grinning, he pounds the desk with both hands.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS577
The typewriter bounces, jostling the sentence's period.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS578
Hanging his head, SOMEONE pounds the desk even harder.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS579
SOMEONE collapses and SOMEONE hunches over his desk.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS580
The writer drops his head on the typewriter.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS581
With SOMEONE still on the floor, hidden by a low wall and SOMEONE still hunched over his desk.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS582
Our view lingers on the open air office.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS583
SOMEONE lifts his head and metal type bars fall back into place.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS584
Two of them bearing the upside down  letters D and G.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS585
The wide-eyed author looks up from his typewriter.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS586
And sees SOMEONE on the floor in front of his desk.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS587
Breathing heavily, SOMEONE lies on her side with her arm covering her face.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS588
Our view moves down her body to her feet.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS589
Finding her ankles crossed over the hardwood floor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS590
His jaw hanging slack, SOMEONE steps over to her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS592
He crouches at her side.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS593
Planting his palms on the floor. SOMEONE reaches to SOMEONE but she pops up and dashes off to the bedroom.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS594
He stares in her direction. His hair mussed and his jaw slack.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS595
Taking shallow breaths, he remains frozen in place. His gaze unwavering.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS596
The young man closes his eyes momentarily.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS597
Then returns his attention to the bedroom.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS598
Now, the typewriter hammers out a string of letters on a new page.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS603
SOMEONE slides the carriage and starts a new line.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS606
The carriage slides to another new line.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS607
SOMEONE looks up from the page and peers in SOMEONE's direction.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS608
The typewriter's guide frames the beginning of the new line.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS610
SOMEONE lowers his gaze and adds a final word.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS612
Now, SOMEONE scribbles on a sticky note attached to his manuscript.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS613
SOMEONE, look at the last page.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS615
He withdraws his hand from the note, peers toward the bedroom.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS616
Then holds his manuscript close.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS617
Clutching it with both hands.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS618
Now, outside the bedroom.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS619
SOMEONE bends over and sets his manuscript before the closed door.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS620
Without standing upright, SOMEONE braces himself on the walls and creeps downstairs.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS621
Our lingering view lowers to the manuscript and its attached note.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS622
The next morning, SOMEONE lies asleep on his side.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS623
Still wearing his glasses and clothes from the night before, As SOMEONE lick his ear.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS625
The young man awakens to find himself on the couch.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS626
SOMEONE sits up, his hair disheveled.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS627
He rises to his feet.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS628
SOMEONE watches him approach the foot of the stairs, pause.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS629
Then head up to the second floor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS630
SOMEONE peeks over the top of the staircase and spots his manuscript on the floor outside the bedroom.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS631
As he approaches it, the stack of pages comes into focus.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS632
Revealing the sticky note now gone.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS633
SOMEONE crouches over the manuscript, letting the backs of his fingers rest on the top page.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS634
He picks up the stack as he stands upright.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS635
Hesitating, he enters the bedroom and steps around a corner.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS636
SOMEONE stop short and finding SOMEONE gone.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS637
Her artwork now missing from the headboard.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS638
He steps into the closet, stares at the bare shelves then collapses to his knees and bows his head to the floor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS639
SOMEONE topples on his side.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS640
Later, he lies in the dark clutching the manuscript.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS641
SOMEONE comes upstairs to find his brother lying on the floor.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS642
He switches on a light then crouches over SOMEONE, feeling his brother's head and shoulders.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS643
SOMEONE sits up a bit.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS644
SOMEONE drops to the floor again.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS645
SOMEONE remains at his brother's side, consoling him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS646
As our view lingers on the brothers, the image gradually fades to black.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS647
Now, a golf ball sits on a bed of tall grass.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS648
A golf club touches down beside it as SOMEONE prepares to hit the ball out of the rough.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS649
SOMEONE stands by.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS650
They watch the ball head for a green.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS651
Later, they walk the fairway.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS652
Now in his home office, SOMEONE lays a clear plastic cover over his typewriter.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS653
He lifts the typewriter off the desk and sets it aside.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS654
Sitting at the desk, he opens a laptop and stares at its screen.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS655
Standing at a window.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS656
SOMEONE overlooks his swimming pool.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS657
At the beach, he and SOMEONE approach a lifeguard house.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS658
At night, he writes using his laptop.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS659
SOMEONE sits in Mort's chair.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS660
He feeds SOMEONE some of his food.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS661
SOMEONE opens his new book, The Girlfriend. A dedication page reads For Her.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS662
At a bookstore reading.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS663
SOMEONE's family are among the crowd.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS664
SOMEONE looks up from his book.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS665
A large audience surrounds a single tree standing in the middle of the store.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS666
SOMEONE shifts his humble gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS667
Later, Cyrus chats with SOMEONE's family.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS668
Now Dr. Rosenthal holds a copy of the book.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS669
SOMEONE draws a breath and nods softly.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS670
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk through a park.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS671
The unleashed dog runs off.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS672
SOMEONE runs after him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS673
The dog joins a red-haired young woman on a blanket.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS674
SOMEONE stares at the young woman. She looks exactly like SOMEONE.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS675
SOMEONE takes the book from her then gives an awkward nod.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS676
He looks up from one of the pages.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS677
SOMEONE smiles and glances at the pages. The young woman gazes up at him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS678
SOMEONE shows her the book's author picture.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS679
Smiling, she holds his gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS680
SOMEONE stands up straight then gestures to her blanket.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS681
The young woman makes some room for SOMEONE and he joins her and SOMEONE on the blanket.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS682
She holds his gaze.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS683
She grabs the book back from him.
RUBY_SPARKS_DVS684
SOMEONE smiles at her.