Now standing together on one surfboard, the girls ride a gentle wave.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS21
and grins as he spots the girl.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS26
Sitting on her bed, SOMEONE gazes out a window as she plays her ukulele. A Shar-Pei rest its chin on her leg.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS27
Standing, SOMEONE eyes the waves outside then heads into the kitchen. SOMEONE fiddles with the video camera.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS28
His eyes light up.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS30
SOMEONE's father looks at his wife who nods.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS31
Now in an awards podium.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS33
a one-piece bathing suit off a rack.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS34
SOMEONE holds the top over her eyes.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS35
She eyes the price.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS37
She eyes SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS38
SOMEONE smirks.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS40
Now, the young woman from the choir checks her watch as she heads toward a gazebo.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS41
She beckons teens past a sign that reads, "Calvary Chapel." Nighttime. In the gazebo, the young woman shows an image on a TV.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS42
SOMEONE carries over a box.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS44
With a hard swallow, SOMEONE shifts her crestfallen eyes.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS45
Morning. At the Hamilton's, SOMEONE's mother lifts a longboard.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS46
She put longboard on pickup truck beside the van.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS47
As she loads boogie boards into the van's trunk. Rolling her eyes, SOMEONE strides off.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS49
a forecast on surfline.com. SOMEONE enters.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS50
They kiss in SOMEONE's room.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS51
Now they run over to a red pick up.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS52
SOMEONE climbs back on.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS53
kicking legs again, he climbs back on.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS55
Now, beyond palm trees the sun rises over the ocean.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS57
SOMEONE grabs a snack.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS58
SOMEONE gives her a thumbs up.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS61
race towards SOMEONE's left arm, a shark attacks.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS62
SOMEONE sprints through the banyan.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS63
descend on the others as they cross.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS64
and reaches the truck and yanks
SOUL_SURFER_DVS66
HE takes the cell from the vehicle, he dials a number.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS68
HE sits up.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS69
He watches the doctors step out.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS70
They drag SOMEONE across the sand.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS71
He puts a leash around SOMEONE's wound.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS73
Meanwhile, SOMEONE rolls SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS74
SOMEONE's mother freezes. She drops the cordless phone and sprints across the room.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS75
Her vision blurred, the wounded girl sees each of their faces.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS78
She notices the ambulance.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS79
Now, Dr. SOMEONE enters the operating room.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS80
He covers his eyes. In the ambulance, SOMEONE stares upward.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS81
An oxygen mask over SOMEONE's mouth.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS82
She shifts the minivan into Park.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS83
Her vision blurred, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE and an EMT as they wheel her down a hallway.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS84
Rounding a corner, SOMEONE's spots her father. SOMEONE sits up on his bed and stumbles to a railing. A nurse holds him back. The EMTs wheeled the wounded girl into the operating room. A nurse keeps SOMEONE and SOMEONE from entering. As the EMTs set SOMEONE on a bed, the nurse shuts the door. SOMEONE holds the defibrillator to the girl's chest inside.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS87
she gazes ahead, lips parted. Bright golden light gleams into the hallow wave and shines on the girl's face. She blinks. Surfing toward it.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS88
appears ahead. Surrounded by light, SOMEONE looks at right.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS89
The white light dissolves.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS90
hospital room where her family waits by her bed. SOMEONE leans at a window, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in chairs at the foot of the bed, and SOMEONE sits at her side.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS91
SOMEONE slides her right hand.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS92
Father who reads a Bible.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS93
SOMEONE drops his fork.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS94
SOMEONE's legs writhe under.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS95
the shark underwater approaching her surfboard attacking.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS96
SOMEONE enters SOMEONE's bedroom.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS97
SOMEONE sits up.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS98
He hand around her shoulder, SOMEONE gazes upward.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS99
The minivan drives over a bridge
SOUL_SURFER_DVS102
They pass by some restaurants then spots a few surfers.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS103
SOMEONE looks at her mother and they share a smile.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS104
She turns her attention to the side of the road where a series of propped up surfboards read, "Welcome home SOMEONE. We love you."
SOUL_SURFER_DVS105
Now, reporters and cameramen.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS107
SOMEONE sits behind the wheel.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS108
SOMEONE hurry around to open her door.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS110
She share a look, then SOMEONE watches the kids head inside.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS111
Inside, SOMEONE and her brothers look out a window. The photographers snap pictures.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS112
Her parents come inside.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS113
Ginger sniffs SOMEONE's
SOUL_SURFER_DVS114
She goes to the refrigerator.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS115
SOMEONE tries to cut the tomato.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS116
SOMEONE takes a package of deli meat from the refrigerator.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS118
sit down. Leaning against the sink, her father looks on soberly as she struggles with the bag's twist tie.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS120
The shark-bite survivor pensively touches the instrument then picks it up. Cradling it in
SOUL_SURFER_DVS121
her arm, she plucks the strings with her thumb.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS122
SOMEONE sets the ukulele back on the bureau.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS123
that, crossing to one of her surf.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS125
Later, the family sits at a table. SOMEONE starts to eat.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS126
Her mother regards her with wide eyes.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS129
the grocery store's produce section, SOMEONE reaches for a bag of apples on a high shelf.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS130
knocking a price marker down and upsetting some loose apples.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS131
Later, she carries a brown paper bag to her bicycle
SOUL_SURFER_DVS132
an assortment of fruit tumbles into her.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS133
a girl watches nearby.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS134
Her mother faces SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS135
At the hospital, SOMEONE sits on a exam table.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS136
SOMEONE's mother smiles and nods to Dr. SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS139
Her lips pressed to a thin
SOUL_SURFER_DVS141
mother steps close watching her. SOMEONE faces
SOUL_SURFER_DVS142
her mother nods encouragingly.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS143
The mother shakes her head then bursts into tears.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS144
Her husband draws her into a comforting embrace.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS147
SOMEONE's brow furrowed.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS148
Her brother carries SOMEONE's shark-bitten surfboard under one arm.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS149
Bystanders gather around.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS150
SOMEONE takes the surfboard from his son.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS152
He positions the surfboard's bite-gap around its jaws.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS154
Letting the surfboard drop, SOMEONE lays a hand.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS155
SOMEONE takes up the board and rubs his father's shoulder.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS156
Starring at the animal's jag.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS157
with the shark's long gleaming body. SOMEONE gazes after the father as he follows his sons away. At home, SOMEONE lies wide awake in bed.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS159
some boys watch excitedly as the bikini-clad SOMEONE poses with a pink surfboard for a professional photographer.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS160
Assistants hold towels up around.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS165
Later, she carries it out.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS166
Induced, her father pauses then
SOUL_SURFER_DVS167
As SOMEONE faces her parents with a hopeful smile they swap looks, then beam proudly at her. Now on a beach, SOMEONE points his video.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS168
Behind him, SOMEONE and his family stand with surfboards.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS169
Now, SOMEONE looks back at SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS170
SOMEONE and SOMEONE trot down to the water. SOMEONE hesitantly follows.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS173
She steps in close.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS175
Left alone with SOMEONE, SOMEONE soberly steps closer to him.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS176
Daytime. On a table on a grassy overlook, a man in a suit opens a case to reveal a realistic prosthetic arm.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS177
Filmed by a TV crew, SOMEONE glances at her parents.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS179
Her brothers watch.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS180
As her parents watch, SOMEONE lays a short board across the table and starts to lean down.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS181
SOMEONE calls after SOMEONE as she runs toward the house. SOMEONE hurries after her.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS182
girl flops down on her bed, her head at its foot. She holds up a Barbie doll. Bracing it between her legs, she brushes the doll's hair back then snaps off the left arm.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS183
SOMEONE turns her head and finds her mother watching compassionately from a few feet away.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS184
gaze fixed on the modified doll as her mother looks down at her.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS185
She lets it drop to her chest and blinks back tears.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS186
Now, SOMEONE plants a row of surfboards in the sand according to size
SOUL_SURFER_DVS187
from a round-ended longboard to a four-foot tapered short board.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS188
He slices a banana.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS189
Sitting at a nearby computer, SOMEONE turns and watches her.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS190
SOMEONE goes to a registration table.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS191
SOMEONE arrives, turns in a form and takes a gray t-shirt.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS192
SOMEONE moves off with a sneer. Later, an official approaches SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS194
She glowers at SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS199
SOMEONE stops SOMEONE who peers after his daughter. In a parking lot,
SOUL_SURFER_DVS200
SOMEONE gazes willfully at the three eager girls.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS201
She lowers the tailgate of her parents' truck, her lips set in a bitter frown.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS203
She give the third girl her last board.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS204
With a disappointed look, SOMEONE watches his daughter climb into the truck's extended cab. As she closes the door, her brothers pile into the backseat with her.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS205
She looks at his father through the open window.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS206
SOMEONE and SOMEONE grimly face forward. As SOMEONE props her cheek on her hand, SOMEONE watches her solemnly. Now in his backyard workshop, SOMEONE drills a hole in a surfboard.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS207
As she holds SOMEONE's hands, his eyes fill with tears and his lips tremble.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS208
Huge shafts of light beam through patches among the clouds.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS210
SOMEONE trudges up to his daughter. As he sits beside her, she shifts her gaze away
SOUL_SURFER_DVS211
She stares off blankly. SOMEONE glances at her.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS212
She regards him.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS213
She shifts her tearful gaze away.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS214
She shrugs. SOMEONE closes his eyes.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS215
Her lips pout helplessly.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS217
opens his mouth to speak. He lifts his brow then meets her gaze.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS218
SOMEONE shrugs.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS221
On another day, SOMEONE leads a youth group into an airport.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS223
The blonde teen stands and gives her older friend a tentative smile.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS224
SOMEONE mugs a comical frown.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS225
She grins and SOMEONE
SOUL_SURFER_DVS226
She hugs her. The pleased surfer beams at her fellow volunteer group.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS230
The supply helicopter passes overhead.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS232
Inside SOMEONE observes a young woman holding a baby goat in her arms. The dispirited woman stares back, her gaze broken.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS233
The bus halts a short distance from the aid tent and the youth group climbs off. Makeshift tents line the muddy road filled with foot traffic. A family tends to some goats. A desolate man carries a water jug like a suitcase.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS234
As SOMEONE takes in her surroundings, SOMEONE glances over her shoulder, her stricken expression mirroring the team.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS235
She addresses the group.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS236
She leads them back up the road, past a steady stream of people trudging in the opposite direction. Farther along the road at a dusty supply vehicle, a blonde woman beckons workers.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS237
approaches with her group.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS238
Rosemary gives a sack of grain to SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS239
Forming a line, the youth group members pass down the sacks one at a time.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS240
SOMEONE catches each in the crook of her arm then heaves it into SOMEONE's arms. SOMEONE smiles.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS241
She bandages it.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS242
The wounded woman addresses SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS243
Her gaze meets SOMEONE's.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS244
She turns from the woman and walks a short distance away, her chest heaving.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS245
briefly holds her own face as she breaks into sobs but tears slides down her cheek. SOMEONE approaches.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS246
SOMEONE blinks back her tears.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS247
SOMEONE nods. She wipes tears from her face as SOMEONE returns to the first aid table. Gazing at the ravaged town, she struggles to remain composed. Her eyes pool again and her chin trembles. Later, a volunteer passes by carrying a box of soccer balls. Several preteen locals wait before a table where SOMEONE and SOMEONE ladle chicken noodle soup into bowls. SOMEONE grins at some children.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS248
On a beach, children sit on the sand amid a small tent city. A boy pulls a little girl on a boogie board.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS249
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE shrink-wrapped bottled water. SOMEONE takes two bottles and hands some out to the kids.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS250
The gift surfboards rest on a beached boat.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS251
SOMEONE picks up a ponytailed little boy who pokes the stub of SOMEONE's missing arm.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS252
SOMEONE rubs his chest then sits him down. SOMEONE taps his arm.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS253
She points at the waves.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS254
He jogs away. As SOMEONE stares after him, the little boy hurries towards a dune covered with fallen palm fronds. SOMEONE approaches a boy who stands on one the donated surfboards.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS256
SOMEONE carries the board to the water's edge. She glances over her shoulder at the little boy.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS257
The girl shakes his head. She steps into the water and splashes it.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS258
She pretends to ride a surfboard.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS263
As SOMEONE carries the board.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS264
SOMEONE sets the board down.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS265
She walks over to the little boy who shoots her an uncertain look.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS266
Her eyes flickered.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS268
Bystanders clap.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS269
grinning as she glides away.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS270
Now piles of mail cover tables and countertops in the Hamilton home.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS271
Outside in his workshop SOMEONE uses a strip of plastic to shape.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS272
SOMEONE strides over.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS273
She smiles faintly.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS274
His lips spread into a smile.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS275
Straightening, SOMEONE folds his arms,
SOUL_SURFER_DVS276
reaches into the rafters on the workshop's roof.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS277
He pulls down a surfboard.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS278
He grips a rope handle across the board's midline a few feet from its nose.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS279
SOMEONE beams and he hands her
SOUL_SURFER_DVS281
under the churning water, SOMEONE surfaced Beach.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS282
Pushing out a tired breath, SOMEONE paddles on.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS283
Arms folded, SOMEONE returns his gaze to the surf.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS284
His sons grin.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS285
SOMEONE glances away.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS287
she pushups as her dad helps.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS288
pushups on her own.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS289
SOMEONE jogs over.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS290
SOMEONE regards her friend thoughtfully.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS291
They fought playful shoves. SOMEONE falls.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS295
SOMEONE answers with a thoughtful nod.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS296
The teen nods. Her father kisses and hugs her.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS297
SOMEONE throws an arm around SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS298
who wears an unsettled gaze.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS299
SOMEONE stands up to watch SOMEONE hook a wave.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS300
A judge jots the names for the semifinals.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS302
An official adds SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS303
The impact zone, the girls duck dived.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS304
the wave engulfs SOMEONE.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS306
A clad of surfers surfaces
SOUL_SURFER_DVS307
the timer shows less than two minutes.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS308
paddles over to the other finalists as they gaze.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS309
upon her board and scans the ocean. The timer counts down past a minute and 45 seconds. The ocean seems to stretch endlessly around the surfers without a hint of a wave. SOMEONE waits desperately. As we peer up at her board from underwater, her legs kick out widely at its sides. Leaving the other surfers, she paddles farther out to sea.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS310
SOMEONE's silhouette glides across the sparkling water. SOMEONE paddles after her.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS311
SOMEONE stops paddling and sits up, peering through narrowed eyes at the rolling water.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS312
She caresses the ocean's surface with her hand. From underwater, we peer up at it through dappled rays of sunlight.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS313
A few yards ahead a wave appears and quickly swells. SOMEONE smiles to herself and paddles toward it. On
SOUL_SURFER_DVS314
its side it looms over us, eclipsing the sun.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS315
A judge readies the air horn and consults a stopwatch. The timer ticks past five.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS317
On the still water, SOMEONE watches soberly. From the beach,
SOUL_SURFER_DVS318
SOMEONE looks on with a furrowed brow. His little sister sends up a spring.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS319
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand close, watching intently.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS320
From the water, the wave curls over
SOUL_SURFER_DVS321
Crouches as she rides through the swirling spiral of water.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS322
She keeps just ahead of the barrel as it closes behind her. Her parents anxiously wait for her to reappear. She surfs toward us.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS324
She gives a satisfied grin.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS325
SOMEONE beams proudly and cups her cheek in his hand.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS326
He plants a kiss on her forehead.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS327
As he steps away, SOMEONE beams after him.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS328
just carry her on their shoulders, SOMEONE joins her mother.
SOUL_SURFER_DVS329
SOMEONE smiles and shakes her head.