Now, SOMEONE exits the Thirsty Scholar Pub into the night. Titles. Columbia Pictures presents.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS5
Now, a stately brick facade inset with white pilasters.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS9
Opposite the building, SOMEONE passes under its overhang.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS10
SOMEONE trots alongside a brick wall as he carries a backpack over one shoulder. Passing other pedestrians, he continues down a campus
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS15
He walks along another walkway to a flight of stone steps.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS20
SOMEONE crosses through a second columned walkway ascending then descending its step.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS21
Hand stuffed in the pocket of his gray hooded sweatshirt, the young man hurries toward one of the warmly lit brick buildings and heads up a few step.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS22
As he goes inside.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS23
Molding, Kirkland House.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS25
Then enters a bedroom where he flipped his laptop.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS26
He shares the screen on a separate computer monitor.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS27
It's a small refrigerator and grabs a bottle of beer.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS28
8:13 PM, SOMEONE sits at his desk.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS29
Reading his blog post, he sips his beer.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS30
He posts the entry, the image darkens. 9:48 PM.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS31
He removes the keyboard from a drawer and sets it on the desk, then sips his beer. A dorm mate enters with a six-pack.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS32
We float down an aisle between seated college girls. The image briefly darkens. 10:17 PM.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS33
He cracks his knuckles.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS34
It shows the group and the young women.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS38
Door toward a few club members. Back with SOMEONE.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS40
the partiers dance.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS42
Outside Kirkland House, a dark haired young man hurries up the steps and scans his key card at the door.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS43
In his room SOMEONE tosses a green-tailed dart to SOMEONE, which lands in his friend's Screwdriver. Meanwhile, the dark-haired young man heads upstairs.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS44
SOMEONE notes his webpage.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS45
SOMEONE writes on the window.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS46
As two young women make out.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS47
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS48
Heated young men.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS50
Three girls have a look.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS51
While her friend sits at a desk. She looks over from her laptop.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS52
SOMEONE joins her friend at her desk.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS53
As they read, two guys barged.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS55
SOMEONE glances at him while SOMEONE spins in a chair. Now in a bedroom, an older couple sleeps.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS57
In SOMEONE's dorm.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS58
On screen, the data window goes dark.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS59
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS61
Bashes his own head. SOMEONE grins.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS62
SOMEONE smirks.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS63
Now at a deposition with multiple lawyers.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS64
SOMEONE's attorney steps away. The blonde attorney and SOMEONE beside her both get up. SOMEONE's attorney steps out. A brunette woman with shoulder length hair regards SOMEONE.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS65
She faces forward.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS66
Near a calm riverside, four two-men crews row their boats along the misty water.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS67
They pass under a bridge followed by a small motor boat.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS68
On one boat, a young man glanced.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS69
A fifth boat leads the pack, 50 yards ahead.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS70
They row through the low-lying mist, leaving the other boats far behind.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS71
The head of security blinks, his smile fading. Later, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE waiting outside.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS73
SOMEONE glances around, then stands.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS75
The twins block his path.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS76
Cameron leads SOMEONE and his brother onward.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS77
A dark-haired young man waits in the bike room.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS78
The sandwich to SOMEONE, who stares at photos on a wall.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS79
The programming whiz shrugs.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS80
The brother swap grins as SOMEONE studies SOMEONE soberly.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS81
The club members trade quizzical looks.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS82
SOMEONE shoulders his bag.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS83
Back in the present.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS84
SOMEONE nod.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS86
SOMEONE grins and follows SOMEONE outside into an alley. Wearing shorts, he briefly hugs himself then hops around and faces his warmly dressed friend. SOMEONE leans against him.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS87
We flash to the deposition.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS88
Back in the present.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS90
SOMEONE's lawyer smirks and SOMEONE blinks incredulously. In the flashback.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS91
In another deposition, SOMEONE and his lawyer share a table.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS92
twins, SOMEONE, and their attorney.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS93
Flashback show time passing.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS94
With SOMEONE and the twins.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS95
In SOMEONE's room.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS96
A call on his cellphone. An envelope slides under the bottom of his door. SOMEONE sits down his things, scoots away from his desk and stands. He treads toward the envelope then hesitates. The young man picks it up and stares at his name on the front, then flips it over and finds a wax seal over the flap. He touches his forehead and pumps a fist. Spinning around, he takes a seat and opens it. Now in his room, SOMEONE works. Several dry erase boards with notes and plans on them stand around him.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS97
SOMEONE bites his lips, then looks up resolutely.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS98
Drops his gaze then smiles and swings his arms.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS99
He shows the envelope.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS100
SOMEONE blinks and gives a wounded nod. SOMEONE takes a seat at his desk and focuses on his work.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS101
In a flashback. SOMEONE shows the twins an e-mail. Now, Phoenix pledges stand in the cold.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS102
A guy strips in the snow.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS103
A pledge pukes. Back in the deposition with the twin's attorney.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS104
SOMEONE takes notes on a page covered in doodles. In a flashback.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS105
Cameron checks his cell.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS106
Back in the twins deposition.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS107
In a flashback, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in a computer lab.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS108
SOMEONE stares blankly.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS109
SOMEONE's jaw drops. He hits escape on the computer and grabs his bag.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS110
Leaving SOMEONE with a puzzled look. SOMEONE jogs downstairs.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS111
Shoves the door open and darts out.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS112
He high steps through the thick snow on the ground and runs onward.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS113
Now, SOMEONE hurries down a dorm corridor, clutching the strap of his backpack. He trots upstairs.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS114
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE in. The programmer plops down before his computer and types frantically. He pauses thoughtfully then continues. SOMEONE peeks at his work.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS115
SOMEONE glances solemnly at his friend.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS116
SOMEONE backs away, scratching his brow.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS117
SOMEONE takes out his cell.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS118
On the bed behind him, SOMEONE glances at his cell. Then watches his friend.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS119
SOMEONE rocks forward.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS120
He rocks backward.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS121
Now in a dining hall.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS122
A woman sitting beside SOMEONE uses her laptop.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS123
SOMEONE looks over at it then grabs her computer.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS125
He puts on his jacket.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS126
Outside, he hurries upstairs and jogs across a shadowy bridge. Now, SOMEONE hurries into a boathouse where Cameron and Tyler practice in a stationary rowing tank.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS128
Tyler smacks his oar. Now in Porcellian Club.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS129
At the other deposition.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS130
His fist closed, SOMEONE shakes his head. Nighttime. We descend the facade of an academic building to the front steps. In an auditorium.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS132
Forward and slowly looks up, then gazes at SOMEONE with an astonished expression.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS133
Later outside.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS134
SOMEONE waves.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS135
They walk off, leaving the three admirers behind.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS136
SOMEONE rubs his forehead.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS137
Then faces SOMEONE.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS138
The gray-haired attorney glances at SOMEONE's legal team.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS139
SOMEONE gazes off.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS140
At Kirkland House.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS141
Now in a public bathroom.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS142
SOMEONE eyes her body.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS143
Accent the dark wood at the stall doors.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS144
Later, standing outside the bathroom, a happy SOMEONE glances at his friend. A guy approaches.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS145
SOMEONE nods.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS146
They share a grin and he goes off. SOMEONE's smile lingers.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS147
They swap a grin.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS150
She looks up then eyes him flatly.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS151
SOMEONE looks on his friend's face.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS152
SOMEONE glances aside.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS153
As SOMEONE walks out, SOMEONE faces the girls.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS154
Now in their dorm suite.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS155
After lunch into the deposition room, where SOMEONE sits alone.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS156
Seat at the table and crosses her legs. Then regards him sympathetically.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS157
He glances at her. SOMEONE looks at Scans.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS158
She faces her lunch. In a flashback.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS159
crosses to a shelf and finds a book.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS160
Now, a young woman dangles her blonde hair.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS161
He notes her Stanford panty shorts.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS162
Furrows his brow then sets the computer on his lap.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS163
the door then glances around.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS164
The twins wait in the reception room.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS165
The twins get up, fix their coats.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS166
Phone at his desk.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS167
SOMEONE wears a hoodie.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS168
SOMEONE sullenly looks up at the ad executive.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS170
SOMEONE faces the door.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS173
Tori serves another round of drinks.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS174
Looking away, SOMEONE shakes his head.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS175
SOMEONE and SOMEONE smile.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS177
SOMEONE shoots him a scolding pout. In the present.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS178
Lifts his chin. Gretchen eyes SOMEONE.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS179
SOMEONE pauses on his way out.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS180
As he goes, SOMEONE stares after him with an enthralled gaze.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS181
Breezes out, past the restaurant staff. SOMEONE drains a glass of brandy.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS182
Now in a taxicab, SOMEONE dozes on her boyfriend's shoulder.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS183
SOMEONE wakes and sits up.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS184
In the present.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS186
SOMEONE reaches for SOMEONE.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS187
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE, who shrugs sullenly.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS188
Across the room, SOMEONE's chicken turns its head inside its cage. Now the young CFO saunters down a hallway.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS189
at an intersection, he turns and follows the noise.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS191
SOMEONE scribbles on a notepad.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS193
In a backyard in California he ziplines.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS196
Going inside, SOMEONE tosses the camcorder down.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS197
Into a pixie light brunette, SOMEONE arrives at her side.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS198
Then SOMEONE opens the fridge. SOMEONE and his girlfriend tread in.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS199
SOMEONE throws SOMEONE a beer. SOMEONE catches it and smacks the cap off on a chair.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS200
Sharon one She flinches away.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS201
SOMEONE throws another.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS203
SOMEONE shakes his head and looks away. SOMEONE gives a wincing nod.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS204
Now in fast motion, the sun sets. As the sky darkens.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS205
SOMEONE stares off at the dance floor.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS206
Look over a verdant landscape with the river flowing through it.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS207
Henley Royal Regatta, Henley-on-Thames. White tents line the shore and varied boats cruise the river passing under an arched bridge.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS208
As the oars rise.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS209
Pulling to show Hollandia barely in the lead. The Hollandia coxman and shouts into a headpiece microphone.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS210
Harvard's boat edges toward Hollandia's.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS211
Harvard's boat follows.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS212
SOMEONE sighs.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS214
The prince and his aide stride off.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS215
The three students swap looks.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS216
SOMEONE Steps away.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS217
SOMEONE storms off into a step.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS218
SOMEONE swaggers through the door. SOMEONE looks helplessly to SOMEONE who bows his head. His twin link.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS219
SOMEONE pumps his fist.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS221
SOMEONE uses a phone.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS222
Holding the phone with his shoulder, he grabs some drinks.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS223
SOMEONE opens the door and finds SOMEONE outside in the rain.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS227
Six-foot bong. He rubs his eyes.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS228
SOMEONE hopples out sleepily and gives SOMEONE a playful smack.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS230
Sets down his bags. He shoots SOMEONE a glare then faces SOMEONE. The programmer uncomfortably lowers his half-eaten red licorice.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS232
In a hallway.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS234
SOMEONE clenches his jaw. SOMEONE calmly meets a stare.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS236
SOMEONE strides up To a window in the bank.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS238
SOMEONE gazes off angrily.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS239
Now in a downtown high-rise, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in a waiting room.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS240
Into an office.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS241
Two businessmen face SOMEONE.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS242
Haired businessman locks eyes with SOMEONE seriously. Nighttime. The lights of New York.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS243
In his apartment, SOMEONE lies asleep. A shadow passes through the light coming under it.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS244
At the side, SOMEONE sits up fearfully.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS245
The door swings open, revealing SOMEONE.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS246
She folds her arms.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS247
He roots through a bag.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS248
She checks his cell.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS249
SOMEONE lights her gift on fire.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS250
SOMEONE aims a fire extinguisher.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS251
SOMEONE squeezes his eye shut, swallows, and shakes his head.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS252
He freely snaps his phone shut.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS253
At the rented house, SOMEONE stands.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS254
In the living room. A girl spray champagne.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS255
He thoughtfully rumples his lips.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS256
Back in the deposition.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS257
SOMEONE sits with his back to SOMEONE and the rest of the table.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS258
He swivels his chair around to lock eyes with SOMEONE.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS259
SOMEONE stares back stonily. SOMEONE swivels away.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS260
In a flashback, at the Facebook office.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS261
He sips a beer and the friends share a smile.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS264
Office building. Grinning after him, SOMEONE kisses his fingers, flips off the building with both hands and returns to his SUV.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS265
SOMEONE arrives at Facebook headquarters.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS266
He swivels his chair around and glares accusingly.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS267
At the thriving headquarters, a Facebook lawyer beacons SOMEONE into a glass enclosed conference room.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS269
SOMEONE picks up a contract and reads. The lawyer averts his gaze.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS270
In the conference room, SOMEONE's expression darkens.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS271
Through the glass enclosure, we view the lawyer explaining. SOMEONE spies SOMEONE at a distance in headphones working at a station across the main floor.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS272
SOMEONE perches on a nearby desk. SOMEONE bursts from the room.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS274
Back in the deposition.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS275
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE. SOMEONE sucks her lower lip in, eyeing SOMEONE sympathetically. Gretchen emphatically shrugs a hand. Back at Facebook.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS277
SOMEONE backs away.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS278
In his fists, he turns and heads out.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS279
SOMEONE strolls over and hands him a check.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS280
SOMEONE winds up to punch SOMEONE, who recoils cravenly. The ousted CFO smiles.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS282
SOMEONE stares after his friend with a furrowed brow and swallows hard. Turning on the spot, SOMEONE faces the staff and shrugs playfully.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS283
Facing SOMEONE, SOMEONE puts a hand on his shoulder.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS286
She sets down two oblong boxes and goes.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS287
The two young men stare after the slender mini-skirted blonde.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS288
Grinning, SOMEONE stands and faces his staffer.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS290
There's a guy playing an acoustic guitar, two girls making out, and a group smoking pot. Upstairs, SOMEONE enters a room with Ashleigh, two other girls and a guy.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS292
Guest opens the door to two policemen. They step inside, shining their flashlights.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS293
Sobering, SOMEONE knits his brow and leaves the room. He crosses a room on the other side.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS295
Finds to slide on the others.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS296
The officer grabs SOMEONE's hand and shines his light on it, finding it dusted with coke.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS297
SOMEONE fumbles two items from his pocket and sets them on the table.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS298
The cops face the others.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS299
The first cop shines his light on SOMEONE, who turns away and runs a hand over his hair. At Facebook headquarters, SOMEONE slumps at his desk.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS300
Straightening, he answers his cell.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS301
At a police station.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS302
SOMEONE listens gravely.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS303
In the background, a staffer turns off the conference room lights.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS304
SOMEONE's chest heaves.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS306
On the other end, SOMEONE gives a weary shake of the head.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS307
He swallows and shuts his eyes.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS308
He flips his phone shut. Swiveling in his chair, he heaves a sigh. Then takes a freshly printed business card from one of the oblong boxes.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS309
It reads, "I'm CEO, bitch. Mark Zuckerberg." He eyes the card then clenches it between his curling fingers.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS310
He sets it aside with an unhappy sneer.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS311
He faces an open laptop and punches.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS312
He turns to face the young attorney.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS314
Turns away shyly. Shuts his laptop then face to.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS315
SOMEONE sighs and drums his laptop.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS316
SOMEONE taps his laptop.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS317
SOMEONE heads out.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS318
She turns back.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS320
SOMEONE regards him sympathetically.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS322
Reception area outside. SOMEONE lingers.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS323
He eyes his laptop screen. His jaw tensely clenched.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS324
He stares at it.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS325
He add SOMEONE as a friend.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS326
Cancel request pop up notes, SOMEONE have to confirm that you are friends.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS327
SOMEONE's cursor moves to the send request button.
THE_SOCIAL_NETWORK_DVS328
Then gazes.