In a crowded city square, a brown haired painter wearing a tie and tweed suit coat paints a portrait of a person sitting on a stool.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS36
The person sitting on the stool reaches down and pets a small white dog.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS37
The dog, Snowy, sits and watches the crowd.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS38
A nearby man slips on a pair of leather gloves, then wiggles his fingers.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS39
Tilting his head, Snowy steps forward.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS40
Strolling through the crowd, the man deftly picked several people's pockets.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS41
The thief takes a man's wallet out of the back of his pants.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS42
The man pats his empty pocket then glances around himself.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS43
The thief taps another man on the shoulder, then reaches into his breast pocket as he turns.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS44
The thief steals a mustached man's lighter, then lights the man's cigarette.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS45
A drawing of a red-haired boy with upraised bangs.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS46
The red-haired young man glances around himself.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS47
The young man wanders through the crowded square.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS48
Two man wearing bowlers peer through holes punched through the same newspaper.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS49
Snowy runs up to the young man.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS50
The young man kneels and pets the dog beside a mirror.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS51
He turns and inspects a model ship with a unicorn figurehead on display behind them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS52
A beefy man with a moustache pushes through the crowd as the young man pays for the ship.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS53
The man runs up to them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS54
The man hurries off.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS55
A bearded man with glasses steps up.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS56
Clutching the model ship to his chest the young man strides off.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS57
The bearded man narrows his eyes as he stares after SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS58
Later SOMEONE walks into an apartment.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS59
He places the ship onto a counter.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS60
Slipping off his jacket, SOMEONE walks into a home office and opens a desk drawer.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS61
Behind him a cat pushes open a window and drops inside.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS62
Framed newspapers hang on the office wall.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS63
Some headlines.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS64
Reporter TINTIN Unmasks Tribe of Gangsters, and, Reporter Uncovers Crime Ring.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS66
TINTIN Retrieves National Artifact, Stolen Scepter returned to King.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS68
Snowy holds a magnifying glass in his mouth.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS69
Snowy lunges at the cat who flees through SOMEONE's apartment. The cat bounces of the chair, swings around the chandelier, then lands on SOMEONE's face. The cat jumps onto a table, climbs up a curtain, and knocks over a vase as it runs along a shelf.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS70
Chasing the cat across the counter, Snowy knocks the model ship to the floor. SOMEONE picks up the broken ship.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS71
A thin metal tube slides out of the model ship's broken center mast.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS72
Snowy sniffs at the tube, but SOMEONE kicks it under a cabinet.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS73
Grabbing his coat, SOMEONE leaves with Snowy.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS74
Across the street a person using binoculars focuses in on the model ship visible through SOMEONE's window.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS75
Later SOMEONE reads in a dim library between tall stacks of books.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS76
He turns the page.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS77
As SOMEONE leafs through several more books,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS78
the beefy, mustached American creeps up behind a book stack.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS79
He peers at SOMEONE then withdraws.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS80
SOMEONE spins and looks at the book stack, but no one is there.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS81
SOMEONE and Snowy return home.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS82
They walk into SOMEONE's dark apartment.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS83
SOMEONE steps toward the counter, but the ship is missing.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS84
Later that night SOMEONE carries a flashlight, as he walks outside the front gate
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS85
of Marlinspike Hall.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS86
He tugs on the gates handles, but they are locked with a chain.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS87
Snowy appears on the other side of the gate.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS88
Snowy runs to a nearby gap in the brick wall.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS89
SOMEONE crawls through the narrow opening. He stands and faces down a long driveway toward a dark and dilapidated estate house.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS90
SOMEONE shines his flashlight over the house's ivory covered exterior, then onto a fish carved above the front door.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS91
As Snowy wanders off SOMEONE turns and shines his flashlight onto a snarling Rottweiler. He runs into the wooded property as the large guard dog chases him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS92
SOMEONE leaps over a puddle, the Rottweiler splashes through it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS93
SOMEONE pulls back a branch and releases it at the dog, but the Rottweiler crashes through it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS94
As the guard dog backs SOMEONE against a stone wall, Snowy leaps out and barks at the much bigger dog.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS95
The Rottweiler backs down and rolls onto its side.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS96
As the two dogs play in the yard, SOMEONE reaches through one of the home's broken window panes,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS97
and unlatches it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS98
He pushes open the window and jumps into a large dark room filled with disused furniture.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS99
Crystal chandeliers hang from the ceiling.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS100
As SOMEONE walks through a door in one corner a shadowy figure paces deeper into the gloom.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS101
SOMEONE steps into another room lined with scaffolding.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS102
He walks up to a large object draped with a sheet and uncovers it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS103
His model ship rests in a large case.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS104
SOMEONE opens the case and removes the ship.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS105
A bald man with a bulbous nose steps out of the shadows.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS106
He hits SOMEONE over the head with candlestick then takes the ship.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS107
The bearded man steps forward as SOMEONE sits up.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS108
SOMEONE pries the ship out of the other man's grip.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS109
The ship's center mast is unbroken.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS110
The bearded man swings a cane across SOMEONE's chest.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS111
SOMEONE's man servant returns SOMEONE's flashlight and leads him out.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS112
Nestor shuts the front door on SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS113
Snowy and SOMEONE walk home.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS114
As SOMEONE takes out his key, Snowy noses opens open SOMEONE's apartment door.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS115
SOMEONE shoves open the door and turns on the lights.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS116
The apartment lies in disarray.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS117
SOMEONE gazes around at ransacked furniture and broken items. Snowy sticks his nose under the cabinet.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS118
SOMEONE crouches and peers under the cabinet, then stands and moves it away from the wall.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS119
He picks up the thin metal tube lying against the floor molding.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS120
Moving to a lamp, SOMEONE unscrews the tube, opens it and pulls out a slip of paper.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS121
He reads the note with a magnifying glass.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS122
SOMEONE slips the note into his wallet as he steps into the hallway.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS123
SOMEONE hides a pistol behind his back as his neighbor leaves.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS125
SOMEONE drops to the floor as bullets rip through the front door.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS126
Snowy cowers on the stairs.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS127
Popping up on one knee, SOMEONE aims his gun at the door, which slowly swings open.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS128
The mustached American drops a newspaper as he keels forward,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS129
and lies motionless.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS131
SOMEONE rushes outside as a blue car speeds off.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS132
Snowy chases the car a little ways, then returns.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS133
Inside the moustached man points one finger at various letters on the newspaper.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS134
Pickpockets at large.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS135
SOMEONE rolls the man over, but he falls still.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS136
SOMEONE picks up the newspaper, which is covered with bloody fingerprints.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS137
Twin inspectors watch SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS138
One inspector trips over the cat and falls downstairs.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS139
The inspectors leave without the newspaper.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS140
SOMEONE takes one of the inspectors' wallets. It's attached to a string.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS141
The inspectors tip their bowlers, then walk off.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS142
A man follows the inspectors.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS143
The goateed pickpocket steals the inspector's wallet and runs off dragging him by the elastic cord.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS144
The wallet snaps back and smacks him in the face. The other inspector grabs the thief's coat, but runs into a lamp post.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS146
SOMEONE sets out into the thick fog and bumps into the thief coming the other way.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS147
The thief hurries up the foggy street.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS148
SOMEONE runs into the road as a car emerges from the mist, narrowly missing him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS149
Other cars swerve on all sides.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS150
Using their hooked canes, the inspectors pull Snowy and SOMEONE off the road.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS151
SOMEONE talks to Snowy as they walk.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS152
A burly man presses a rag over SOMEONE's face, then shoves him into a crate.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS153
Snowy bites the man's bottom.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS154
He shuts Snowy in the apartment building.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS155
Snowy bounds upstairs and runs into SOMEONE's apartment.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS156
He hops over a pair of chairs, then leaps onto a window sill.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS157
The abductor's red moving van drives away.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS158
Snowy leaps on top of a passing fire truck.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS159
At an intersection the van driver brakes suddenly. As the fire truck behind it skids to a halt its ladder extends out over the van.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS160
Snowy's legs dangle in front of the van's windshield.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS161
He drops onto the hood.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS162
Snowy slides on the hood as the van veers through traffic.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS163
Snowy tumbles onto the street as the van turns sharply.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS164
Snowy chases after the van then jumps into a small wagon, towed by a bicyclist.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS165
They pass a street sign.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS167
As the van makes another sharp turn, Snowy leaps out of the wagon and onto the fence of a livestock pen.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS168
Snowy jumps onto the back of a cow, which kicks him beneath another cow.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS169
Snowy raises his head and hits it on the cows utters.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS170
Several cows lift their heads and widened their eyes as Snowy races under them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS171
Snowy sprints out of the coral and into a shipyard.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS172
He locates the van which sits parked with its back doors flung open.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS173
The crane lifts the crate,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS174
which is stamped Karaboudjan,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS175
onto a cargo ship baring the same name.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS176
Later the ship steams out of the harbor and into the ocean.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS177
Below decks the burly man and a companion search SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS178
SOMEONE sits in a cage with his hands tied behinds his back.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS179
SOMEONE enters.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS180
SOMEONE pulls a sword out of his cane.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS181
Snowy peers into a hallway as SOMEONE strides out of the cargo hold.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS182
Snowy slips past the last thug and into the hold as he shuts the door.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS185
Snowy dashes up to SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS186
Snowy tugs at SOMEONE's bindings with his teeth.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS187
Now free, SOMEONE grabs a crowbar and jams the door, then covers its window.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS188
He runs to a wooden crate in the middle of room and pushes it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS189
He shoves the crate against the wall, climbs onto it and opens a porthole.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS190
SOMEONE looks out of the side of the massive ship, then up at another porthole above him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS191
Outside the burly thug tries to open the cargo hold, but the wheel won't turn.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS192
A second thug tries.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS193
In the cargo hold, SOMEONE rips a plank off a crate.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS195
The burly thug places a bundle of dynamite against the door.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS196
SOMEONE ties a rope against the plank and leans out of the porthole.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS197
He swings the board like a lasso and tosses it at the open porthole above him, but misses.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS198
The board falls and hits him in the head.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS199
Outside the thugs light the dynamite's fuse then run for cover.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS200
The burly thug hides behind his companion.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS201
SOMEONE throws the board again. It sails through the porthole and hits a man on the back of the head.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS202
Thugs rush the open hold.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS204
One thug sinks to the floor as champagne corks pelt him in the chest. The burly thug picks up a cork.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS205
Crates of open champagne bottles fizz as the men step into the cargo hold.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS206
A cork strikes a thug in the forehead.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS208
In the room above a man with a thick black beard rubs his head as Snowy leaps in through the port hole.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS209
SOMEONE tumbles into the room.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS210
Then man swings a telescope at SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS211
The man lowers his weapon.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS212
SOMEONE opens the cabin door then peers at the captain.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS213
In the hall, SOMEONE bumps into a crew member who attacks him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS215
SOMEONE punches the bigger man as Snowy jumps on his back.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS216
The captain opens his door and punches out the attacker.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS218
They move the man into the captain's cabin.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS219
A falcon lands on SOMEONE's gloved fist.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS220
The captain grabs SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS221
They hide under a stairwell as thugs search for them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS222
They dash upstairs as the thugs move on.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS223
SOMEONE follows Captain SOMEONE up a corridor.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS224
Smelling SOMEONE's breath, SOMEONE staggers backward.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS225
SOMEONE peers into crew's sleeping quarters.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS226
SOMEONE climbs into the midst of the sleeping crew.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS227
One of the sleeping man clutches a rat.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS228
SOMEONE crawls along an empty bunk with Snowy, then reaches out toward a set of keys dangling from Jaggerman's hand.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS229
SOMEONE balances on his knees as he extends his body.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS230
He slips but catches himself.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS231
SOMEONE ducks out into the hall. SOMEONE glances at Snowy then picks up the dog and holds him out toward the keys.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS232
Snowy sniffs a sandwich on Jaggerman's cot.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS233
As Snowy bites into the sandwich, SOMEONE falls. He lands on a bunk beneath Jaggerman, as the other stack of cots tilt over.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS234
A sleeping man rolls on top of SOMEONE, but he shoves him off. Both stacks of bunks collapse and bury SOMEONE under a pile of sleeping men.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS235
SOMEONE's fist emerges from the pile, clutching the keys.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS236
He joins SOMEONE in the hall.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS237
SOMEONE unlocks the door then turns to SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS238
He opens the door to a store room filled with liquor bottles.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS240
SOMEONE stuffs several bottles into his clothing.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS241
On the ship's deck crew members weld together a long track. A crane lowers a pontoon plane wrapped in canvas onto the track.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS242
Stepping out of a door, SOMEONE takes a bottle from SOMEONE and sneaks up behind a thug with a gun.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS243
As he raises the bottle into the air
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS244
SOMEONE takes it back and drinks.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS245
SOMEONE swings down his empty fist knocking the thug to the deck.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS246
SOMEONE shakes his injured fist, then follows the captain.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS247
Snowy stands on the thug's chest and growls, then trots after the others.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS248
Working together, SOMEONE and SOMEONE swing a lifeboat over the side of the ship.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS249
They crouch as the burly First Mate walks past on the level above them,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS250
then steps through a door.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS251
Snowy follows SOMEONE as he creeps toward the bridge.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS252
SOMEONE and the First Mate SOMEONE leave the radio room.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS253
SOMEONE slips inside.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS254
Snowy leaps up onto a map table and snarls at a rat nibbling on a sandwich.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS255
He picks up the sandwich in his jaws, but the rat tugs at the other end.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS256
SOMEONE searches through the ships messages.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS257
SOMEONE reads a brochure.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS258
He slips the brochure into a pocket then studies a map tacked to a wall.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS259
SOMEONE sits at the radio and switches it on, then puts on a pair of headphones.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS260
Meanwhile out on the deck, SOMEONE holds the lifeboat steady.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS261
A crewman with a bottle emerges from under the lifeboat's tarp.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS262
SOMEONE releases a rope and the lifeboat falls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS264
SOMEONE moves to a neighboring lifeboat and checks under its tarp as he readies it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS265
In the radio room, SOMEONE taps out a message in Morse code.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS266
SOMEONE walks in.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS267
SOMEONE aims a pistol, but Snowy deflects his arm. SOMEONE punches SOMEONE and grabs the gun.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS268
SOMEONE bursts out of the bridge with SOMEONE in pursuit.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS269
SOMEONE leaps over a railing then ducks between crates as a thug opens fire with a machine gun.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS270
SOMEONE shoves another lifeboat over the side of the boat as Snowy jumps in.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS271
SOMEONE skids to a stop beside an armed thug who spins and faces him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS272
SOMEONE dodges a punch, kicks out his legs, then sprints away.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS273
SOMEONE pushes Snowy in the lifeboat over the side of the ship.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS274
He slips and falls into the lifeboat causing a rope to snap.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS275
The life boat tips and dangles vertically.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS276
SOMEONE hangs on with one hand and grips Snowy with the other. Meanwhile avoiding the gunfire SOMEONE drops to a lower level, then kicks a thug down a staircase.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS278
SOMEONE fires his pistol behind himself as he rounds a corner. SOMEONE looks down from an upper deck.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS279
SOMEONE shoots the handle of a searchlight beside SOMEONE,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS280
turning it on and blinding his pursuers.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS281
SOMEONE leaps on to the lifeboat and shoots through the last rope.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS282
The lifeboat drops into the ocean with everyone aboard. Gunfire pelts the water. SOMEONE strides to a deck railing and glares down at SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they row away.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS283
As the helmsman spins the ship's wheel, SOMEONE runs onto the deck and shoots a flare into the night sky.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS284
They lie in the bottom of the lifeboat as searchlights sweep over the water.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS285
SOMEONE grabs a searchlight and focuses it on to a drifting lifeboat.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS286
The ship speeds toward the bobbing wooden lifeboat.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS287
Captain SOMEONE hugs Snowy to his chest as the ship's metal keel slices through the water like a knife.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS288
It strikes the lifeboat and shatters it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS289
Liquor bottles float up and SOMEONE amongst the SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS290
As the lifeboat sinks, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from inside their own lifeboat nearby.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS291
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE and shoves him against a railing.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS292
The wind blows a piece of paper across the deck. SOMEONE picks it up. A series of dots and dashes cover the paper, along with the word Beggar.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS293
A crewman pulled the tarp of the sea plane and swiveled the track over the side of the boat.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS295
SOMEONE rows the lifeboat while SOMEONE sits with his hands on his knees.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS296
SOMEONE takes out the brochure.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS297
SOMEONE's eyes widen, as he smiles broadly.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS298
SOMEONE accidentally smacks SOMEONE and Snowy with an oar.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS299
Back in the city, the pickpocket flexes his gloved hands
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS300
as he walks up a sidewalk.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS301
He slows as the identical twin inspectors SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach from the opposite direction.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS302
The gray haired goateed pickpocket quickens his pace and takes out a set of keys.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS303
The inspectors hurry forward and corner him on a doorstep.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS305
Silk rushes off.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS306
Birds fly around Mr. Silk's head as he sits on the pavement beside an elderly woman with an empty bird cage.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS307
The inspectors escort Silk into his apartment, which is filled with shelves of wallets.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS309
The inspectors hold a wallet labeled Property of SOMEONE pinched on 17-9. Out on the ocean, SOMEONE hangs over the side of the boat as SOMEONE rows.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS310
SOMEONE searches through a storage cabinet.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS311
Smiling he takes out a bottle of whiskey.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS312
SOMEONE's eyes flutter open.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS313
A fire blazes in the middle of the boat.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS314
SOMEONE splashes the fire with seawater.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS315
SOMEONE pours the whiskey on the fire, causing an explosion.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS316
Later they sit on the overturned lifeboat.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS317
SOMEONE stands and shakes SOMEONE's hand.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS318
SOMEONE stares up at puffy white clouds.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS319
The seaplane swoops out of the sky and strafes past them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS320
SOMEONE braces the pistol against his forearm as the plane returns for another pass.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS321
SOMEONE shoots the plane as it swoops overhead. Losing his balance, SOMEONE falls into the water.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS323
Billowing black smoke, the sea plane lands on the ocean surface in the distance.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS324
SOMEONE hops into the water besides SOMEONE as two men climb out of the plane and on to one of its pontoons.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS325
SOMEONE dives.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS326
SOMEONE surfaces.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS327
He aims his gun.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS328
Later crammed into the plane with SOMEONE and the pilots SOMEONE reads a flight manual.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS329
Sitting in the cockpit SOMEONE pulls a knob and starts the plane.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS330
Snowy sticks his head out of a window as the plane picks up speed.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS331
It bounces over waves, then lifts into the air.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS332
SOMEONE banks the plane over SOMEONE's ship.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS333
The plane flies unsteadily toward a massive storm front.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS334
Forks of lightning flash from the thunderhead as the small plane flies into it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS335
SOMEONE grips the controls as turbulent winds blow them about.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS336
SOMEONE holds one hand over his chest. His eyes widen as he looks down beside a seat.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS337
He reaches for a bottle.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS338
Lightning strikes the wing of the plane, which flips upside down.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS339
Struggling with the controls, SOMEONE rights the plane.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS340
SOMEONE quickly takes the bottle of medicinal spirits and uncaps it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS341
The plane drops into a step dive. One of the tied up pilots floats out of his seat.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS342
A globule of clear alcohol floats out of the bottle and hovers in front of SOMEONE's face.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS343
Floating upside down, Snowy sniffs the alcohol and ingests it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS344
The plane pulls out of a dive.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS346
Snowy drops to the floor of the plane as it rises steeply upwards, then stalls and falls again.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS347
A large globule of alcohol rises out of the bottle.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS348
Snowy paddles toward it, but SOMEONE grabs the dog's tongue and sucks down the alcohol himself.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS349
The plane pulls out of the dive just a few feet above the ocean surface and arises into the air.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS351
SOMEONE straps on a parachute. He opens the plane's side door, looks down and shuts the door again.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS352
Setting his jaw, SOMEONE opens the door and slips outside.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS353
The wind carries him away.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS354
SOMEONE clings to the side of the plane.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS355
SOMEONE crawls onto the nose of the plane directly behind the spinning propeller.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS356
SOMEONE glances down as the empty spirit bottle rolls into his foot.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS357
Straddling the engine, SOMEONE opens the gas tank,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS358
then beats a fist on his chest.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS359
He places his mouth over the gas tank spout.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS361
The engine sparks to life.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS362
SOMEONE is thrown back onto the windshield as the plane picks up speed.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS363
They head toward a large sand dune. SOMEONE jerks the control stick.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS364
They veer around the dune and glide down the opposite side.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS365
In the back, one of the captured pilots frees himself, then unties his partner. The plane rises over another dune revealing as vast desert filled with wrecked ships and planes.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS366
A bolt of lightning strikes SOMEONE who flips onto the plane's wings.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS367
His parachute opens and drags him backward, but he clings to the plane's tail.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS368
The two pilots jump out of the plane, and, opening parachutes, drift safely onto the sand below.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS369
SOMEONE loses his grip on the tail and lands face first in a powdery dune.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS370
SOMEONE hugs Snowy to his chest,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS371
and ducks down as the plane bounces over a sand dune, flips and crashes.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS372
SOMEONE smashes through the front windshield and sprawls across the hood, inches behind the spinning propeller.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS373
Snowy tugs on his unconscious master.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS374
SOMEONE slides toward the spinning blades.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS375
An updraft lifts SOMEONE's parachute and carries him of his feet.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS376
Kicking his legs he drops onto the back of the plane as it pitches forward.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS377
Sliding SOMEONE even closer to the whirring propeller.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS378
The spinning blades nip the tips of SOMEONE's hair.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS379
SOMEONE climbs down and grabs SOMEONE and throws him back onto the roof of the plane.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS380
The propeller snags Haddocks parachute, spins him around rapidly several times and spits him onto the sand nearby. The propeller slows to a stop then drops off.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS381
With their arms around each other's shoulders, SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk across a desert
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS382
of rolling sand dunes as Snowy trods ahead of them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS383
SOMEONE drops to his knees.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS384
SOMEONE points.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS385
Snowy grabs SOMEONE's suspenders.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS386
SOMEONE pulls free.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS388
SOMEONE falls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS389
SOMEONE points into the distance.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS390
SOMEONE slowly stands.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS391
Snowy drags a large bone then drops it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS392
As SOMEONE gazes over the rolling desert, a ship's mast
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS393
seemed to rise over the horizon.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS394
The skies darken and the sands turns to ocean,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS395
as the Unicorn crashes toward them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS396
On the deck of the ship Sir SOMEONE peers through a spyglass as the Unicorn sails through a rough sea.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS397
Shutters open along the side of the ship, revealing cannons.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS398
Sailors man battle stations.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS399
The helmsman turns the ship's wheel. An approaching pirate ship fires cannon balls,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS400
which zip through huge ocean swills and strike the Unicorn's bow.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS401
Flames burn inside the Unicorn as its cannons return fire.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS402
The pirate ship fires a volley.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS403
The cannon ball tears through a sail and setting it on fire. Sir SOMEONE marches through his ship as men and cannons
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS404
explode behind him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS405
The two ships, both on fire, sail toward each other, then crash together.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS406
As lightning flashes one ship tips over, then rights itself.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS407
The rigging of the burning ships entangles.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS408
As the Unicorn tips to one side, it lifts the other ship out of the water.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS409
Suspended by the Unicorn's rigging, the pirate ship swings over the Unicorn's deck.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS410
Pirates slide down on ropes and fight the Unicorn's crew with swords.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS411
One marauder lands on a cannon, cuts down two sailors, then stabs a third. Another invader swings past on a rope and kicks a man overboard.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS412
The pirate shoots a sailor, then lands.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS413
Sir SOMEONE shoots the pirate, punches another then kicks a third before slicing him with a sword.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS414
The two entangled ships crash into a huge wave.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS415
Pirates with swords climb their ship's tilted mast toward the Unicorn, which lies on its side.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS416
Fires rage on deck and along the sails.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS417
Sir SOMEONE runs along a horizontal mast, cuts a rope, then swings past
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS418
several pirates and lands near the tip of their mast.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS419
As more pirates approach, he slices a line and untangles the two ships.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS420
The Unicorn rights itself, but the pirate ship sinks beneath the roiling waves.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS421
Sir SOMEONE slides down a line toward the burning deck.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS422
Cutting another line, he swings over the melee, slashing at pirates before kicking two of them in the face.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS423
Sir SOMEONE picks up a piece of burning wood and lights a cannon, causing it to shoot backward and knock several pirates overboard.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS424
In slow motion, a pirate wearing a plumed hat strides down the length of a burning mast.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS425
Sir SOMEONE glares at the silhouetted figure as he approaches.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS426
In the desert SOMEONE gazes skyward.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS427
SOMEONE staggers forward, wipes his own face, then falls backward. SOMEONE catches him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS428
Night falls over the vast desert. A shooting star zooms across the sky.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS430
Snowy stands on a ridge and barks.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS431
A beam of light illuminates the barking dog.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS432
A man wearing a military cap
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS433
and holding a flashlight steps up to Snowy.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS434
Another man holds a lantern.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS435
The second man kneels beside SOMEONE and turns him toward the light.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS436
Daytime. Soldiers march into an outpost.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS437
SOMEONE sits on a bed and holds a glass.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS438
Snowy trods to a bottle marked Spirits and sniffs it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS439
Snowy sets the bottle beside SOMEONE's bed.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS440
As SOMEONE reaches for his water, Snowy rotates a bedside tray. SOMEONE drinks the bottle of spirits.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS441
Snowy backs away from SOMEONE who clutches his own throat.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS442
Delcourt and the medical staff hustle out of the room. SOMEONE picks up Snowy. SOMEONE jumps on his bed and swings his arms as SOMEONE shuts the door.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS443
SOMEONE bursts out, knocks down two men, then grabs a soldier's sword.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS444
On the burning ship the pirate stares down at Sir SOMEONE who raises his sword against an attacker.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS445
Swinging the sword, SOMEONE turns into Sir SOMEONE. He advances toward the masked Red SOMEONE, who throws open his cape and swings his sword.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS446
They fight on the ship's burning deck.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS447
SOMEONE flails his flaming cape at Sir SOMEONE,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS448
who dodges it then stabs through the cape.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS449
SOMEONE tears of his cape and drapes it over Sir SOMEONE, who falls onto his back.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS450
A spar falls toward Sir SOMEONE, which turns into a ceiling fan falling onto SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS451
Pirates surround Sir SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS452
Pirates tie Sir SOMEONE to a mast.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS453
Face covered by a red bandana, Red SOMEONE raises his sword.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS454
SOMEONE steps to a bookcase and touches the top of a book. Inside the ship Sir SOMEONE tilts a book in a bookcase, opening a secret compartment in the floor.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS455
Red SOMEONE descends into a low ceilinged room filled with treasure.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS456
Red SOMEONE inspects a string of pearls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS457
Standing he swings his sword, then points the weapon toward Sir SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS458
Using flaming torches the pirates prod sailors into the sea.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS459
Sharks converge around the bound sailors, bubbles float to the surface.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS460
SOMEONE pulls up a quill pen.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS461
On the ship, Sir SOMEONE tied to the mast jerks back his head.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS462
A feather attached to a knife blade flies upward from his hat.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS463
He catches the feather in his mouth then drops it to his hand.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS464
Grasping the blade firmly, Sir SOMEONE cuts through his ropes.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS466
Sir SOMEONE grabs a sword.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS467
Walking backward, Sir SOMEONE pours out a trail of gunpowder from a barrel.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS468
He climbs the steps to the deck where Red SOMEONE faces him with his sword drawn.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS469
Sir SOMEONE draws his sword.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS470
He cuts a rope, dropping a lantern and lighting the gun powder.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS471
Red SOMEONE darts around Sir SOMEONE and kicks out the burning gunpowder.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS472
As they swordfight, Sir SOMEONE kicks more gunpowder at the lantern. It reignites then burns across the deck and down the ladder.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS473
Red SOMEONE leaps below decks, then turns and thrusts his sword at Sir SOMEONE,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS474
who punches him. Red SOMEONE again kicks out the burning gun powder.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS475
Sir SOMEONE shoves him then cuts lose another lantern, which falls onto the trail of powder.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS476
Red SOMEONE elbows him then stomps out the gunpowder once again.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS478
Sir SOMEONE lunges, strikes Red SOMEONE, then slices another rope holding a lantern.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS479
It falls onto the gunpowder. They duel as the lit powder burns down another ladder and races across the deck and the space below them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS480
Sir SOMEONE runs his sword through Red SOMEONE, then backhands him in his face.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS481
The pirate drops to his knees then falls over.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS482
With his sword, Sir SOMEONE flicks away Red SOMEONE's bandana, revealing SOMEONE's face.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS484
Holding a sword, SOMEONE stands over SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS485
The trail of lit gunpowder races toward the ship's magazine.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS486
Red SOMEONE hurls his sword.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS487
SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE out of a window. Sir SOMEONE leaps from the ship. SOMEONE and SOMEONE fall onto crates.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS488
The ship explodes.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS489
Sir SOMEONE surfaces then swims to a piece of floating mast.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS490
Deep in water, Red SOMEONE stands on the burning sinking ship.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS491
Another explosion rocks the ship.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS492
Kneeling on the mast, SOMEONE gazes up as gold and jewels shower down around him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS493
He holds open his hat, which fills up with the falling treasure.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS494
SOMEONE watches as his burning ship tilts up,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS495
then sinks into the ocean.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS496
The boat's unicorn statue is the last thing to slip beneath the waves.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS497
SOMEONE spits into his palm, then shakes SOMEONE's hand.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS498
Later SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride camels across a rocky ridge.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS499
Far below stone dwellings cover a hillside.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS500
A ship sits in a harbor.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS501
SOMEONE points at SOMEONE's anchored ship.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS502
Later in the town, near an ornate stone tower,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS503
people walk through a market place.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS504
Men wearing head scarves fill buckets and pails with water from a hand pump.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS505
Wearing a pith helmet SOMEONE hurries past several vendors.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS506
One man drinks from a bucket.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS507
A man wearing a turban blinks.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS508
Another scowls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS509
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step through the crowd.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS510
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder as he rounds a corner with SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS511
SOMEONE spins around.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS512
Two robed figures stepped through an archway.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS513
SOMEONE and SOMEONE trip them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS514
SOMEONE shakes them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS515
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE his wallet.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS516
SOMEONE leaves through his wallet then extracts the scroll.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS518
Smiling, he holds it aloft.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS519
Nearby two men on ladders unfurl a huge banner, which reads
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS520
The Milanese Nightingale.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS521
The banner completely unfurls revealing a portrait of a blond haired woman.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS523
They all stare at the banner.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS524
Bianca poses for a crowd of photographers.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS525
A bearded man and a moustached man step toward her.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS526
Bianca extends her hand and walks toward them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS527
SOMEONE bows his head.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS528
Arm in arm SOMEONE and Bianca walk as Salaad and his secretary clap.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS529
As Bianca steps past him, SOMEONE spies a model ship in a glass case near the back of a stage.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS530
A label on the case reads bulletproof.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS531
Never break.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS532
Luxury cars stop at the palace gate.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS533
Nearby SOMEONE passes the scroll to SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS534
SOMEONE backs up.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS535
SOMEONE shoves it into SOMEONE's hand.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS536
SOMEONE kneels.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS537
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE to his feet. As more cars line up at the palace gate, several birds fly over the palace walls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS538
Palm trees grow within the palace compound.  A domed structure stands against the backdrop of rugged mountains.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS539
SOMEONE Salaad's Unicorn model sits in its glass case surrounded by narrow pillars.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS540
Beyond it people mingle in a large covered courtyard near a fountain.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS541
Statues line the tiled atrium.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS542
SOMEONE sits near a brown haired woman.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS543
SOMEONE descends stone steps to a stage.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS544
SOMEONE Salaad and the crowd rise.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS545
SOMEONE walks to a small platform.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS546
The Unicorn model sits in its case behind her.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS547
SOMEONE looks around himself as he claps.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS548
He peers at the model ship through opera glasses.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS549
SOMEONE Salaad, alone in the center of the courtyard, sits.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS550
SOMEONE Salaad gestures to SOMEONE, who begins to sing.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS551
SOMEONE puts his fingers in his ears.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS552
SOMEONE Salaad watches SOMEONE through thick eyeglasses.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS553
SOMEONE bangs his head on the seat in front of him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS554
People turn and look at him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS555
Snowy writhes then covers his ears with his paws.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS556
SOMEONE stumbles out of the audience, runs to a banquet table then yanks off the table cloth.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS557
He drapes it over his head then hurries outside to a sunny courtyard by a pool.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS558
SOMEONE pulls a bottle from an inner pocket.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS559
The scroll floats out.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS560
SOMEONE snatches the scroll from the air. He gazes from the bottle to the scroll, then slams the bottle onto a nearby table.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS561
SOMEONE appears.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS562
SOMEONE smashes the bottle against SOMEONE's head. He falls. Inside, SOMEONE gazes up at a figure standing at at balcony railing.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS563
From the balcony SOMEONE gazes through round eyeglasses at SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS564
A large falcon lands on SOMEONE's arm.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS565
SOMEONE peers through his opera glasses at SOMEONE and the falcon,
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS566
then turns his head sharply and looks at the glass case holding the Unicorn model.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS567
SOMEONE focuses on the label reading bulletproof.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS568
He stands.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS569
A woman sips from a champagne glass, which shatters.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS570
The lenses of SOMEONE Salaad's eyeglasses crack.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS571
Glass goblets on a tray shatter and break.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS572
Lines run through the words bulletproof and never break.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS573
Chandeliers crash to the floor.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS574
The glass case holding the Unicorn shatters in sprays of glass shards.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS575
SOMEONE releases the falcon, which swoops over the crowd.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS576
SOMEONE ducks.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS577
SOMEONE runs in waving his arms.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS578
Guards grab SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS579
The falcon breaks of its center mast,Snowy raises after the falcon, which grabs the boat model in its talons then drops it on the floor.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS580
grabs a metal tube in its beak then flies off.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS581
It soars to the balcony and lands on SOMEONE's arm.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS582
SOMEONE plucks the tube from the bird's beak.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS583
Meanwhile, SOMEONE punches several guards.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS584
Holding the falcon, SOMEONE strides off.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS585
As SOMEONE hurries off, SOMEONE gazes downward.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS586
Elsewhere, SOMEONE drives SOMEONE and SOMEONE in a red jeep.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS587
SOMEONE examines the scrolls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS588
SOMEONE punches a guard.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS589
SOMEONE picks up a rocket launcher, hitting the guard as he stands.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS590
SOMEONE hops into a motorcycle sidecar.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS591
SOMEONE starts the motorcycle and they race down a narrow road after the jeep.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS592
The jeep drives through a palace gate then past a tall concrete dam.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS593
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look behind themselves, as SOMEONE appears in their rearview mirror.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS594
SOMEONE fires a machine gun hitting the sidecar.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS595
SOMEONE raises the rocket launcher to his shoulder and aims.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS596
He fires, but the rocket shoots out of the back of the launcher.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS597
SOMEONE turns around, smoke pours from the dam's sluice gate. He drops the launcher.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS598
Below the road a torrent of water roars in a drainage canal.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS599
SOMEONE speeds around a curve. Water pours down a steep hill toward town. As SOMEONE aims his machine gun, Snowy leaps at him. SOMEONE grabs the scrolls from Sakharines hand.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS600
Snowy leaps into the side car.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS601
SOMEONE swats the swooping falcon, then turns onto a narrow village street.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS602
They bounce down steps, spin to a stop, then roar off again as a tank wedged inside a building rumbles after them.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS603
The tank's barrel catches SOMEONE's jacket, lifting him out of the sidecar.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS604
They grab at the fluttering scrolls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS605
The motorcycle hits a pothole.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS606
The sidecar detaches from the motorcycle. The hotel skids to a stop.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS607
SOMEONE dangles from the tank barrel over a high wall and falls and bounces off of several clotheslines.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS608
He lands wearing a dress.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS609
Above him, the falcon circles a floating scroll.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS610
As SOMEONE reaches for the paper, the falcon snatches it and flies off.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS611
SOMEONE falls onto the front of SOMEONE's motorcycle.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS612
The falcon glides just above a canal.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS613
Snowy, with a scroll in his mouth, catches up to the falcon and pins it to the sidecar.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS614
SOMEONE leaps from the motorcycle but lands on the sidecar, upending it.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS615
The falcon, with Snowy clinging to its tail, flies through a window and into a grain mill.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS617
SOMEONE grabs a rope and swings through the air. He grabs Snowy by the tail, yanking him from the falcon. The falcon snags a fluttering scroll then flies outside toward the jeep.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS618
SOMEONE shoots from a from a side chute and grabs the falcon.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS619
SOMEONE grabs one scroll from the falcon's claws.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS620
The bird flies off with the last scroll in its beak.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS621
SOMEONE races after it as SOMEONE follows.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS622
SOMEONE swings from a window and lands on the jeep, then punches out SOMEONE and Allen.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS623
SOMEONE races down a stone stairway after the falcon, then up a ramp and through a door. Inside two men weave rugs.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS624
The falcon flies through their loom.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS625
As SOMEONE repeatedly slams into walls, the entire building collapses.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS626
SOMEONE drives out of the falling building up a narrow street, then smashes through a low wall. The motorcycle breaks apart as he sails over a market. The front wheel lands on a telephone cable. Still holding on to the handlebars, SOMEONE zips down the cable over the town.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS627
The handlebars break on a crossbeam and SOMEONE swings on to a paper lantern.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS628
He reaches for the falcon but misses, then falls into a building.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS629
SOMEONE bursts through a door, leaps and grabs the falcon's talons.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS630
Holding the bird, SOMEONE lands on a floating dock near the Karaboudjan.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS631
He peers at the scrolls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS632
SOMEONE runs to the edge of the SOMEONE and glares at SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS633
SOMEONE holds SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS634
SOMEONE struggles to hang on to the scrolls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS635
Snowy hangs from a rope tied to SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS636
The thugs push SOMEONE and Snowy into the canal.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS637
SOMEONE releases the falcon and dives in.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS638
A single bubble floats to the surface, reflecting the image of the falcon landing on SOMEONE's arm.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS639
SOMEONE takes the scroll, then turns and walks off. Another bubble surfaces.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS640
The tank wedged inside a building rolls to the bottom of the town at the water's edge.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS641
The building stops but the tank falls into the water.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS642
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lean on the building's balcony.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS643
The robed manager steps out of the hotel and gazes ahead at the canal.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS644
He adds a star to the hotel's rating sign.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS645
SOMEONE pushes SOMEONE into a chair.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS646
SOMEONE stands.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS647
SOMEONE points at a moored sea plane.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS648
At night the Karaboudjan steams through a harbor then pulls up to a SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS649
SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE step down a gang plank.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS650
SOMEONE climbs into the back of a car which rises into the air.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS651
SOMEONE looks down.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS652
Nestor shrugs as a crane lifts the car. SOMEONE and SOMEONE run out.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS653
The car swings past the crane cab where SOMEONE operates the controls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS654
The crane lowers the car toward a rooftop.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS655
SOMEONE and the inspectors surround the car as it stops.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS656
He points a gun.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS657
In the crane cab SOMEONE jerks a lever as SOMEONE bursts in. He shoots at SOMEONE but misses. SOMEONE grabs his arm. As they fight the crane lifts the car, smashes it into a brick wall, then drags it up the wall. SOMEONE punches SOMEONE then sits at the controls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS658
SOMEONE pulls two levers. The crane swings the car over the water.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS660
SOMEONE pulls himself onto a railing.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS661
SOMEONE rushes into the control cab, grabs SOMEONE and drags him across the floor and tosses him over the railing. SOMEONE falls onto a passing truck. SOMEONE sits at the controls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS663
SOMEONE leaps from the car, and now with his top down into the control cab of another crane.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS664
Sneering, he sits at the controls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS665
As SOMEONE swivels his crane, SOMEONE swings the arm of his crane into him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS666
SOMEONE quickly pivots his crane and smashes him back. SOMEONE's car tumbles across a ship's deck.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS667
SOMEONE and the policemen duck as the cranes smash and twist above their heads.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS668
SOMEONE uses his crane to sweep dusty SOMEONE into SOMEONE's cab.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS669
The tip of SOMEONE's crane smashes into SOMEONE's cab, knocking him to the floor.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS670
SOMEONE backs his crane into a police car, then swings the arm straight through SOMEONE's cab.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS671
SOMEONE ducks at the last moment.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS672
SOMEONE swings at load of crates into SOMEONE's crane.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS673
The crates break apart and rain down around SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS674
Several tires fall over SOMEONE, pinning his arms to his sides.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS675
As more of SOMEONE's thugs run up, Snowy pushes over a crate of cans and spills them across the dock.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS676
The thugs slip on the cans and fall in a pile. Overhead SOMEONE and SOMEONE continue their crane duel.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS677
Both men swing the arms of their cranes together.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS678
SOMEONE's crane breaks as his cab slams against SOMEONE's cab.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS679
Separated by only a few feet, the two man sneer at each other.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS680
SOMEONE backs up his crane then swings the arm in a full circle.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS681
It smashes into SOMEONE's cab.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS682
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder as SOMEONE's crane tilts and falls. SOMEONE spills out of the cab and onto a stack of crates.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS683
Silhouetted by bright lights, Sakharin strides down a section of broken crane toward him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS684
SOMEONE picks up a metal bar.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS685
SOMEONE pulls his sword out of his cane. SOMEONE runs up to him and swings the metal bar.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS686
SOMEONE parries the blow and whacks him across his rump.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS687
SOMEONE attacks again, but SOMEONE deftly parries each blow.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS688
He stomps SOMEONE's foot and elbows him in the face.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS689
SOMEONE swings back, but SOMEONE stops the blow and kicks SOMEONE to the ground.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS690
SOMEONE gets to his feet and charges, but SOMEONE throws a fishing net over him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS691
He yanks SOMEONE into a crate of whiskey bottles.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS692
SOMEONE turns his back on SOMEONE and whips his blade through the air.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS693
SOMEONE caresses one of the nearby bottles, then stares at SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS694
A bottle strikes SOMEONE in the back. SOMEONE throws more bottles, one of which knocks the sword out of SOMEONE's hand.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS695
He drives SOMEONE backward over a small ledge.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS696
SOMEONE stands and holds a lighter's flame onto the three scrolls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS697
SOMEONE freezes with a bottle in his hand.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS698
SOMEONE swings past and grabs the scrolls.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS699
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS700
SOMEONE flies over the side of the ship and into the harbor. SOMEONE kicks the last whiskey bottle into the water after him.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS701
The bottle bounces of SOMEONE's head.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS702
SOMEONE paces, then smiles at SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS703
He smiles back.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS704
Snowy wags his tail.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS705
Inspectors SOMEONE and SOMEONE drag SOMEONE out of the water.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS706
SOMEONE raises his hands.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS707
As the sun rises, SOMEONE stands on the deck of the Karaboudjan with SOMEONE.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS708
He places the three pieces of parchment together and holds them up to the light.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS709
The combined notes reveal a set of coordinates.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS710
SOMEONE smiles and grabs SOMEONE in a bear hug.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS711
Later, gulls cross a blue sky as wind ruffles Snowy's fur and blows SOMEONE's hair.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS712
Captain SOMEONE peers through a sextant.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS713
SOMEONE drives them in a convertible.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS714
SOMEONE drives of the road and through a row of hedges.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS715
He speeds through a wooded property and emerges in front of the SOMEONE estate house.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS716
SOMEONE parks outside the front door.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS717
The butler Nestor shows them inside.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS718
Nestor leads them to a large underground chamber.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS719
SOMEONE paces across the stone floor.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS720
Nestor restrains the Rottweiler who growls at a stack of furniture.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS721
SOMEONE and SOMEONE move aside furniture, revealing a small hole in a back wall.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS723
Snowy appears in the hole on the other side.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS724
They smash through the wall with a beam of wood.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS725
SOMEONE walks toward the back of the secret chamber to a statue of a man holding a small cross.
THE_ADVENTURES_OF_TINTIN_DVS726
SOMEONE walks up to the statue and examines a stone globe.