The manager presses a button on the tall man's glasses.
THE_WATCH_DVS19
The tall man slaps the manager's rear. At night, the store's lights shut off and the metal security door rolls down.
THE_WATCH_DVS20
As the manager closes up, a chubby security guard arrives.
THE_WATCH_DVS21
He holds up a certificate.
THE_WATCH_DVS22
His arm bears and eagle over a flag.
THE_WATCH_DVS23
The manager leaves and the security guard heads into the store.
THE_WATCH_DVS24
Later, Antonio cranks up the volume on a stereo system.
THE_WATCH_DVS25
Crossing the store, he slides to a stop.
THE_WATCH_DVS26
Strutting down an aisle, he wiggles his fingers and bobs his head.
THE_WATCH_DVS27
He grabs a six-pack of Coke then spots a bottle of vodka.
THE_WATCH_DVS28
He snatches the bottle then chugs from it and spits vodka overhead.
THE_WATCH_DVS29
He dances along with a workout video.
THE_WATCH_DVS30
In the pharmacy, he picks out a medicine bottle and eats a few pills.
THE_WATCH_DVS31
Now, he rounds a corner on a tricycle, drinking and driving.
THE_WATCH_DVS33
Using a forklift, he sets a recliner chair down in front of a wall of flat screen televisions.
THE_WATCH_DVS34
Watching a movie, he lights a hand-rolled cigarette.
THE_WATCH_DVS35
In the movie, a young woman in a blue swimsuit runs her hand through her long hair.
THE_WATCH_DVS36
The televisions sputter, then cut out abruptly.
THE_WATCH_DVS37
Antonio looks around.
THE_WATCH_DVS38
He crosses to a circuit breaker panel and opens its door.
THE_WATCH_DVS39
The power goes out throughout the store.
THE_WATCH_DVS40
Antonio turns on his flashlight, then flips a few switches.
THE_WATCH_DVS41
He shines his flashlight across the store.
THE_WATCH_DVS42
An item falls from a shelf.
THE_WATCH_DVS43
Antonio leaves the circuit breaker panel.
THE_WATCH_DVS44
He walks the aisles, the beam of his flashlight leading the way.
THE_WATCH_DVS45
Advancing cautiously, he scans the surrounding shelves.
THE_WATCH_DVS46
He shines his light on a torn open box, then continues at a weary pace.
THE_WATCH_DVS47
Antonio turns to a rocking display of batteries.
THE_WATCH_DVS48
A single D battery rolls to a puddle of green slime under his foot.
THE_WATCH_DVS49
The sweaty security guard takes out a revolver and holds it up.
THE_WATCH_DVS50
Over his shoulder, he spots something coming and his eyes widen.
THE_WATCH_DVS51
Firing wild, he backs away.
THE_WATCH_DVS52
He runs out of ammo and ditches his gun, then knocks over a display of plastic bottles.
THE_WATCH_DVS54
Antonio dashes through the darkened store.
THE_WATCH_DVS55
He reaches the exit door and tries a key.
THE_WATCH_DVS56
His pursuer charges him.
THE_WATCH_DVS57
Antonio slams into the glass door.
THE_WATCH_DVS59
He falls to the floor, his blood accenting the window's emblazoned words, Join the Club.
THE_WATCH_DVS60
An empty parking lot surrounds the Costco.
THE_WATCH_DVS62
At home, the manager packs a hidden travel wallet.
THE_WATCH_DVS63
She checks a test stick.
THE_WATCH_DVS64
SOMEONE helps with her luggage.
THE_WATCH_DVS66
She leaves in a cab.
THE_WATCH_DVS67
Now, a mid-sized crossover pulls into the Costco parking lot.
THE_WATCH_DVS68
Behind the wheel, SOMEONE notices various emergency vehicles parked outside of the taped off entrance.
THE_WATCH_DVS69
The emergency responders gather around a few police cars and an ambulance.
THE_WATCH_DVS70
SOMEONE steps out of his vehicle and shuts the door.
THE_WATCH_DVS71
Noticing him, a mustached officer sets down a cup of coffee.
THE_WATCH_DVS72
The officers peers at SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS73
The officer opens the blood-spattered door.
THE_WATCH_DVS74
SOMEONE stops on the threshold, his eyes wide.
THE_WATCH_DVS75
Now, wearing a suit, SOMEONE drives alone.
THE_WATCH_DVS76
Shifting his emotional gaze, SOMEONE tugs at his collar.
THE_WATCH_DVS77
He expels a deep breath.
THE_WATCH_DVS78
Back at home, SOMEONE watches a news report.
THE_WATCH_DVS79
Sergeant SOMEONE points.
THE_WATCH_DVS80
Now, at a high school football game, the tall man who bought the 3D TV at Costco sits in the crowded bleachers.
THE_WATCH_DVS81
Players and cheerleaders leave the field,
THE_WATCH_DVS82
passing a Spartan soldier mascot.
THE_WATCH_DVS83
The announcer finds a 20.
THE_WATCH_DVS84
Wearing a blue shirt with the white printed words No More Murders, SOMEONE hurries onto the field and gets handed a microphone.
THE_WATCH_DVS85
He addresses the crowd, the back of his shirt emblazoned with a cross out sign over the word Murders.
THE_WATCH_DVS86
He raises his own hand.
THE_WATCH_DVS87
The mascot mocks him, rubbing his eyes.
THE_WATCH_DVS88
A young man glares at the heckling teens.
THE_WATCH_DVS89
The young man grabs a teen's throat.
THE_WATCH_DVS90
He releases him.
THE_WATCH_DVS91
The mascot gestures to cut it out.
THE_WATCH_DVS92
The young man nods.
THE_WATCH_DVS93
The tall man nods.
THE_WATCH_DVS94
Clapping, SOMEONE jogs off the field.
THE_WATCH_DVS95
Now, in SOMEONE otherwise vacant living room, the tall man stands at a snack table,
THE_WATCH_DVS96
while the young man sits on a couch playing with a butterfly knife.
THE_WATCH_DVS97
Standing by a presentation easel, SOMEONE checks his wrist watch.
THE_WATCH_DVS98
The tall man eats a snack.
THE_WATCH_DVS99
The young man flips his knife around, then makes a stabbing gesture.
THE_WATCH_DVS100
SOMEONE nods.
THE_WATCH_DVS101
The tall man holds up a chip.
THE_WATCH_DVS102
SOMEONE opens the door for a bushy-haired black man with glasses.
THE_WATCH_DVS103
He opens a nesting doll.
THE_WATCH_DVS104
He lifts the top off another one and grins.
THE_WATCH_DVS105
The three guys squeeze together on the couch.
THE_WATCH_DVS106
The young man with the knife stands.
THE_WATCH_DVS107
SOMEONE shoots a finger gun into the air.
THE_WATCH_DVS108
He plops back on the couch. SOMEONE and SOMEONE eye him.
THE_WATCH_DVS109
He unveils a poster board with a logo.
THE_WATCH_DVS110
It's a winged eye topped by a halo.
THE_WATCH_DVS112
Now, at a large home with a brick facade, SOMEONE opens a door.
THE_WATCH_DVS114
His basement boasts a pool table and wet bar.
THE_WATCH_DVS115
SOMEONE brings in the easel and handbooks.
THE_WATCH_DVS116
SOMEONE sits in a massage chair.
THE_WATCH_DVS117
A teenager enters.
THE_WATCH_DVS118
She leaves.
THE_WATCH_DVS119
Later, SOMEONE tapes a flyer to a pole. It reads, If you see something, say something. Call SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS120
Coming home, he sees someone crouched by his front window.
THE_WATCH_DVS122
SOMEONE smiles.
THE_WATCH_DVS123
SOMEONE holds the rolled up magazine to his eye and looks SOMEONE over.
THE_WATCH_DVS124
With a smirk, the slick-haired SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the magazine.
THE_WATCH_DVS125
SOMEONE watches his new neighbor cross the street.
THE_WATCH_DVS127
SOMEONE and his wife, a trim brunette, return home.
THE_WATCH_DVS128
She sees stacks of flyers.
THE_WATCH_DVS129
She hands it to him.
THE_WATCH_DVS130
She kisses him.
THE_WATCH_DVS131
Now, in SOMEONE's driveway.
THE_WATCH_DVS132
On the back of each blue sateen jacket, the words Neighborhood Watch surround a flaming winged tiger's face.
THE_WATCH_DVS133
He points to his shoulder patch.
THE_WATCH_DVS134
Nighttime. They sit in SOMEONE's car outside Costco.
THE_WATCH_DVS135
An empty can.
THE_WATCH_DVS136
SOMEONE opens the can.
THE_WATCH_DVS138
A squad car pulls next to them.
THE_WATCH_DVS139
From the passenger seat, SOMEONE motions to SOMEONE to roll down the window.
THE_WATCH_DVS140
A fat cop drives.
THE_WATCH_DVS141
The fat cop puts his hands up. SOMEONE leans over.
THE_WATCH_DVS142
A flyer.
THE_WATCH_DVS143
SOMEONE writes something and hands it to SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS144
SOMEONE snatches it and hands it back to SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS145
SOMEONE holds out another ticket.
THE_WATCH_DVS146
SOMEONE takes it.
THE_WATCH_DVS147
The cop car backs up.
THE_WATCH_DVS148
SOMEONE pounds the roof.
THE_WATCH_DVS150
The mid-sized crossover kicks up dust as it tears out of the parking lot.
THE_WATCH_DVS151
Now, the guys walk the empty football field with flashlights.
THE_WATCH_DVS152
Bright lights shine in their eyes.
THE_WATCH_DVS153
Raw eggs pelt their faces.
THE_WATCH_DVS154
Four boys throw eggs from the stands.
THE_WATCH_DVS155
The kids flee.
THE_WATCH_DVS156
SOMEONE chases a boy with a backpack.
THE_WATCH_DVS157
Pumping his arms, SOMEONE sprints down the field after the boy with the backpack.
THE_WATCH_DVS158
He closes in on him, lunges, and tackles him near the end zone.
THE_WATCH_DVS159
SOMEONE pins him down as the rest of the guys run over.
THE_WATCH_DVS160
They all high five.
THE_WATCH_DVS161
As the boy breaks free, they all rush to pin him down.
THE_WATCH_DVS162
Now, in slow motion, the four men saunter toward the police station, the back of their jackets emblazoned with their flaming tiger logo.
THE_WATCH_DVS163
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold the boy by his collar.
THE_WATCH_DVS164
As SOMEONE approaches, they shove the boy to his knees at the front desk.
THE_WATCH_DVS166
SOMEONE leans close on one side.
THE_WATCH_DVS167
SOMEONE leans in on the other side.
THE_WATCH_DVS168
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the kid's skateboard.
THE_WATCH_DVS169
As they strut out, SOMEONE kicks a chair.
THE_WATCH_DVS170
SOMEONE returns the kid's backpack, then straightens the chair.
THE_WATCH_DVS171
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS173
Now, the kid skates out of the station and rolls down an empty street passed closed storefronts.
THE_WATCH_DVS174
As he comes to a deserted intersection, he notices a large, green electricity transformer fizzing and sparking on the corner.
THE_WATCH_DVS175
He slows down and stops to look at it.
THE_WATCH_DVS176
Something moves alongside of it.
THE_WATCH_DVS177
An overhead street light explodes, showering sparks.
THE_WATCH_DVS178
Behind him, a trash can falls over.
THE_WATCH_DVS179
He holds up an egg.
THE_WATCH_DVS180
Something jolts a parked car.
THE_WATCH_DVS181
He drops the egg and shoves off on his board.
THE_WATCH_DVS182
As he speeds down an empty road, a huge shadow lunges over the street behind him.
THE_WATCH_DVS183
He sees something racing along the rooftops.
THE_WATCH_DVS184
He pushes faster and cranes his neck trying for a look at the creature.
THE_WATCH_DVS185
It side tackles him.
THE_WATCH_DVS186
The skateboard hits a parked car.
THE_WATCH_DVS187
Now, a triumphant SOMEONE drives while the guys drink beer.
THE_WATCH_DVS188
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sing to each other.
THE_WATCH_DVS189
They screech to a stop on an empty road.
THE_WATCH_DVS190
On the isolated country road, the four friends get out and peer closely at the car's grille.
THE_WATCH_DVS191
Green slime stains it.
THE_WATCH_DVS192
SOMEONE pulls out a long, slim tentacle with a turtle-shaped end.
THE_WATCH_DVS193
It dangles limp from his fingers.
THE_WATCH_DVS194
SOMEONE smells it.
THE_WATCH_DVS195
SOMEONE touches the slime with his fingers.
THE_WATCH_DVS196
SOMEONE scoops a sample of the slime from SOMEONE's hand.
THE_WATCH_DVS197
SOMEONE touches it.
THE_WATCH_DVS198
SOMEONE squeezes it near his ear.
THE_WATCH_DVS199
They step off the road.
THE_WATCH_DVS200
SOMEONE crouches and touches it.
THE_WATCH_DVS201
Rows of finger-sized holes dot its lower half.
THE_WATCH_DVS202
SOMEONE inserts his finger. It lights up and its sections move.
THE_WATCH_DVS203
He keeps a shotgun on them.
THE_WATCH_DVS204
SOMEONE hides it behind his back.
THE_WATCH_DVS205
On a deserted farm, the men activate the ball.
THE_WATCH_DVS206
SOMEONE lowers his uneasy gaze.
THE_WATCH_DVS207
SOMEONE sticks his finger in the ball and it shoots a beam of energy at a cow.
THE_WATCH_DVS208
Light envelops the cow until it explodes.
THE_WATCH_DVS209
Now, a radiant beam of energy hits an old tractor.
THE_WATCH_DVS210
Light ripples over its surface and it erupts in a huge fireball.
THE_WATCH_DVS211
Chunks of metal collapse in the fire.
THE_WATCH_DVS214
The explosion blows out a truck's rear window.
THE_WATCH_DVS215
Later, they face a row of round hay bales and blow one after another into smithereens.
THE_WATCH_DVS216
Dust and smoke blast several stories high.
THE_WATCH_DVS217
Now, in SOMEONE's basement, the four friends clink bottles of beer over the mysterious orb.
THE_WATCH_DVS218
Now, SOMEONE's crossover arrives back at home.
THE_WATCH_DVS219
He cuts his headlights, gets out, and lumbers wearily to the front.
THE_WATCH_DVS220
Pausing, he bends over to examine his broken grille.
THE_WATCH_DVS221
SOMEONE pulls out a small, slimy tentacle.
THE_WATCH_DVS222
Pinching one end in his fingertips, he opens a trash bin and chucks it in.
THE_WATCH_DVS223
Turning away, he pauses.
THE_WATCH_DVS224
Across the street, SOMEONE stands on his lamp lit porch, watching him with a cocktail.
THE_WATCH_DVS225
He gives a slow, creepy wave.
THE_WATCH_DVS226
SOMEONE politely returns the gesture, then heads inside.
THE_WATCH_DVS227
SOMEONE swirls the ice in his glass, smirking as he watches his neighbor.
THE_WATCH_DVS229
In his basement, SOMEONE snoops on his daughter's Facebook page.
THE_WATCH_DVS231
A video still shows her kissing a boy.
THE_WATCH_DVS233
He plays the file.
THE_WATCH_DVS234
It shows Chelsea and a tall, dark-haired boy making out in a closet.
THE_WATCH_DVS235
As they part, she faces her friend shyly while the boy makes a cocky face.
THE_WATCH_DVS237
She shuts the door in his face.
THE_WATCH_DVS238
SOMEONE lingers.
THE_WATCH_DVS239
In his house, SOMEONE stands facing a homemade evidence board covered with maps, photos, notes, and newspaper clippings.
THE_WATCH_DVS240
He studies the board with an intense stare.
THE_WATCH_DVS241
By a photo of the crazy old shotgun guy, a note labels him as Manfred Salisbury.
THE_WATCH_DVS242
SOMEONE tacks a photo of octopus sushi onto the board.
THE_WATCH_DVS243
A text from SOMEONE. Need to talk.
THE_WATCH_DVS244
Meet me at the bench on Sycamore Road. I'm desperate.
THE_WATCH_DVS246
He offers a beer.
THE_WATCH_DVS247
SOMEONE gently shakes his head.
THE_WATCH_DVS248
SOMEONE turns his stare on SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS249
Avoiding SOMEONE's gaze, SOMEONE sips his beer, smacks his lips, and shrugs.
THE_WATCH_DVS250
SOMEONE creases his brow and looks away.
THE_WATCH_DVS251
The two men sip their beers.
THE_WATCH_DVS252
SOMEONE answers his cellphone.
THE_WATCH_DVS253
They leave the bench. At night, SOMEONE's pickup pulls off the country road.
THE_WATCH_DVS254
Its headlights shine on SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they peer through the windows of a charming brick house.
THE_WATCH_DVS255
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE get in the truck, SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach a wooden fence.
THE_WATCH_DVS256
Now, its gate swings open a few inches.
THE_WATCH_DVS257
SOMEONE slips through, followed by SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS258
They move through a shadowy garden wafting with mist.
THE_WATCH_DVS259
SOMEONE finds an abandoned cellphone on the ground and picks it up.
THE_WATCH_DVS260
SOMEONE turns.
THE_WATCH_DVS261
A few yards ahead, the branches of a thick cluster of bushes move.
THE_WATCH_DVS262
They glimpse a dark shape within.
THE_WATCH_DVS263
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE look on, a head rises into view and peeks above the leafy branches.
THE_WATCH_DVS264
The hairless reptilian skin gleams softly in the moonlight.
THE_WATCH_DVS265
Staring at the creature, SOMEONE slowly stands.
THE_WATCH_DVS266
The creature peers out at him with beady yellow eyes.
THE_WATCH_DVS268
He pops it in his own mouth and chews it.
THE_WATCH_DVS269
He offers another piece.
THE_WATCH_DVS270
A large claw-like hand emerges from the bushes.
THE_WATCH_DVS271
SOMEONE sets the gum in its palm.
THE_WATCH_DVS272
The fingers curl around it and the hand withdraws.
THE_WATCH_DVS273
The creature throws out Manfred's corpse.
THE_WATCH_DVS274
They gawk at the dead man's hollowed out abdomen.
THE_WATCH_DVS275
The creature stands, towering over SOMEONE. It backhands him, sending him flying against a shed.
THE_WATCH_DVS276
SOMEONE watches him fall, then snaps back to the beast who now turns his attention on him.
THE_WATCH_DVS277
It stalks toward him.
THE_WATCH_DVS278
Thorny spikes unfold from its forearm.
THE_WATCH_DVS279
Looking around, SOMEONE spots a garden gnome.
THE_WATCH_DVS280
As the creature leans close to SOMEONE, SOMEONE smashes the gnome on its head.
THE_WATCH_DVS281
It falls and snaps its neck.
THE_WATCH_DVS282
Later, in SOMEONE's basement.
THE_WATCH_DVS283
SOMEONE unveils the dark beast prone in a chair.
THE_WATCH_DVS284
SOMEONE touches it.
THE_WATCH_DVS285
The others pose around the alien.
THE_WATCH_DVS286
Now, a series of photos shows The Watch posing with the alien in increasingly wacky scenarios.
THE_WATCH_DVS287
SOMEONE kneels before the others as they cradle the alien in their arms.
THE_WATCH_DVS288
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold it up and hit it with boxing gloves.
THE_WATCH_DVS289
Later, it wears sunglasses and a sombrero, a cigar in its mouth.
THE_WATCH_DVS290
As the others dance, SOMEONE poses with a guitar.
THE_WATCH_DVS291
Now, SOMEONE pretends to have doggy style sex with the alien.
THE_WATCH_DVS292
He grabs the prone being by the point at the back of its head.
THE_WATCH_DVS293
Later, SOMEONE poses so the alien looks like it's giving him a blow job.
THE_WATCH_DVS294
They dress it in a wig and lingerie.
THE_WATCH_DVS295
Now, a photo of SOMEONE slow dancing with the alien comes to life.
THE_WATCH_DVS296
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pair up nearby. SOMEONE snaps a picture.
THE_WATCH_DVS297
SOMEONE gropes the alien's butt, then pretends to make out with it.
THE_WATCH_DVS298
As SOMEONE records him, SOMEONE leans the alien down in a dip. Its hand rises into view and curls around SOMEONE's shoulder.
THE_WATCH_DVS299
The alien's eyes snap open. It throws SOMEONE into a jukebox and sends SOMEONE flying.
THE_WATCH_DVS300
SOMEONE and SOMEONE tumble over a sofa to get away, then split up.
THE_WATCH_DVS301
The alien knocks the sofa across the room.
THE_WATCH_DVS302
SOMEONE reaches the pool table. As SOMEONE peeks out from behind the bar, the alien leaps across the room and peers over the bar.
THE_WATCH_DVS303
SOMEONE picks up billiard balls and the alien faces him.
THE_WATCH_DVS305
SOMEONE opens a door.
THE_WATCH_DVS306
Springing from the bar, SOMEONE jumps on its back.
THE_WATCH_DVS307
The alien leaps onto a wall, then onto another, carrying SOMEONE along.
THE_WATCH_DVS308
It tackles SOMEONE. SOMEONE gets up as it leans a mouthful of sharp teeth close to the youth.
THE_WATCH_DVS312
Then helps SOMEONE wrestle it.
THE_WATCH_DVS313
SOMEONE grabs the alien's arm and SOMEONE wraps his arms around them all.
THE_WATCH_DVS314
SOMEONE puts it in a choke hold.
THE_WATCH_DVS315
It throws the men off him, sending them crashing across the room.
THE_WATCH_DVS316
Grabbing the silver orb SOMEONE, the alien escapes through a window.
THE_WATCH_DVS317
The guys writhe in pain among the SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS318
SOMEONE rolls off the broken glass on the pool table.
THE_WATCH_DVS319
Now, SOMEONE runs alone down a neighborhood street. Mrs. SOMEONE sprays him in the face.
THE_WATCH_DVS320
He slowly reaches for her startled face. She squirts him away.
THE_WATCH_DVS321
She glares at him, aiming the hose.
THE_WATCH_DVS322
Now, he runs in place at an intersection, checking his pulse.
THE_WATCH_DVS323
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pull up in a squad car.
THE_WATCH_DVS324
SOMEONE slowly removes his sunglasses and gives SOMEONE a bizarre wide-eyed stare while slowly shaking his head.
THE_WATCH_DVS325
SOMEONE scowls and jogs on.
THE_WATCH_DVS326
Elsewhere, peeking out of his blinds, SOMEONE watches the mailman across the street.
THE_WATCH_DVS327
The postal worker leisurely raises his head from a stack of mail and looks directly at him.
THE_WATCH_DVS328
In the high school parking lot, SOMEONE watches his daughter approach SOMEONE, who smiles back at SOMEONE while hugging her.
THE_WATCH_DVS330
In a park, SOMEONE emerges from behind a tree and flicks open his butterfly knife as he sizes up a group of elderly people performing Tai chi.
THE_WATCH_DVS331
Now, at Costco, the four guys sit around a fake fire in a camping display.
THE_WATCH_DVS332
SOMEONE glances around as SOMEONE eyes a woman examining a grapefruit.
THE_WATCH_DVS333
A young boy sloppily eats ice cream.
THE_WATCH_DVS334
The boy stares at his ice cream cone. SOMEONE notices SOMEONE by a display of Magnum condoms.
THE_WATCH_DVS335
SOMEONE grabs several boxes and drops one.
THE_WATCH_DVS336
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS337
SOMEONE notices piles of batteries in SOMEONE's cart, then stares into his neighbor's brown eyes.
THE_WATCH_DVS339
SOMEONE flashes a smile and wheels his cart away.
THE_WATCH_DVS340
Extending a hand after SOMEONE, SOMEONE faces the guys and sits on a cooler.
THE_WATCH_DVS341
At night, the guys follow SOMEONE to his front door.
THE_WATCH_DVS342
Inside, he finds SOMEONE in lingerie.
THE_WATCH_DVS343
The guys enter.
THE_WATCH_DVS348
He tosses up his hands, leaving her in the candle-filled room.
THE_WATCH_DVS349
He rejoins the watch.
THE_WATCH_DVS350
The guys scurry across the street to SOMEONE's house.
THE_WATCH_DVS351
They crouch behind the bushes a dozen feet below the illuminated front porch.
THE_WATCH_DVS352
As they stare up at the front door, SOMEONE pulls out a pop top can.
THE_WATCH_DVS353
He casually sips from the can as the other three glare at him. He notices them, smiles, and raises a can in a toast.
THE_WATCH_DVS354
A nicely dressed couple approach the front door.
THE_WATCH_DVS355
SOMEONE emerges in a white dress shirt and slicked back hair.
THE_WATCH_DVS356
The couple enters the house past SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS357
SOMEONE faces the group.
THE_WATCH_DVS358
SOMEONE slides to the ground and crawls back.
THE_WATCH_DVS359
He runs toward his truck and yells.
THE_WATCH_DVS360
SOMEONE stands on the rear bumper.
THE_WATCH_DVS361
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sidle along the bushes to a curtained basement window.
THE_WATCH_DVS362
They see shadowy movement in glowing red light.
THE_WATCH_DVS363
SOMEONE startles them from behind and they fall into the bushes.
THE_WATCH_DVS364
SOMEONE turns toward the front door and SOMEONE nudges SOMEONE forward.
THE_WATCH_DVS365
Elsewhere, at a party, teenage girls relax in a hot tub, while others hold plastic drink cups around an in ground pool.
THE_WATCH_DVS366
Partiers dance on the balcony of the massive white house overlooking the pool area.
THE_WATCH_DVS367
Two couples make out in front of some bushes where SOMEONE and SOMEONE hide.
THE_WATCH_DVS368
Busty, gorgeous teens dance in bikinis.
THE_WATCH_DVS369
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE as SOMEONE approaches Chelsea.
THE_WATCH_DVS370
SOMEONE wraps his arms around here and grinds her from behind.
THE_WATCH_DVS372
SOMEONE follows them into the basement stairwell, locking the door behind him.
THE_WATCH_DVS373
SOMEONE nervously glances back, then takes a step down.
THE_WATCH_DVS374
A curtain separates, revealing an orgy.
THE_WATCH_DVS375
He sees a variety of sex toys.
THE_WATCH_DVS376
Behind the bar, three guys in a circle reach for each other's crotches.
THE_WATCH_DVS377
SOMEONE eyes the young, sexy Asian.
THE_WATCH_DVS378
She drops out of sight.
THE_WATCH_DVS379
At the high school party, a blond girl opens the door for SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS380
In a bedroom, SOMEONE rubs Chelsea's lower stomach as they kiss. She pushes his hand away.
THE_WATCH_DVS381
He grabs her breast.
THE_WATCH_DVS382
She grabs her jacket.
THE_WATCH_DVS383
He shoulder bumps SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS385
SOMEONE falls over.
THE_WATCH_DVS386
As SOMEONE slowly rises, SOMEONE grabs him.
THE_WATCH_DVS387
SOMEONE hurls him through the glass front door.
THE_WATCH_DVS388
Chelsea runs to her dad as the whole party watches.
THE_WATCH_DVS389
SOMEONE flips open his butterfly knife and approaches SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS390
Smiling, SOMEONE turns and leaves.
THE_WATCH_DVS391
SOMEONE waves his knife at the partiers.
THE_WATCH_DVS392
Now, SOMEONE sits on SOMEONE's front steps as his pickup pulls into the driveway.
THE_WATCH_DVS393
SOMEONE stands as the tall man helps his daughter out of the truck.
THE_WATCH_DVS394
She reaches for SOMEONE with a bloody hanky.
THE_WATCH_DVS395
He points a finger at SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS396
SOMEONE opens the front door for SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS397
SOMEONE slowly moves to SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS398
SOMEONE touches his hand and forehead to SOMEONE's chest.
THE_WATCH_DVS399
SOMEONE opens the door and SOMEONE steps inside as SOMEONE shifts his weight in the driveway.
THE_WATCH_DVS400
SOMEONE stops in the doorway.
THE_WATCH_DVS401
SOMEONE purses his lips.
THE_WATCH_DVS402
He blinks and looks off to one side.
THE_WATCH_DVS403
Now, the dark-haired man sprints down the street, his arms rapidly pumping.
THE_WATCH_DVS404
The street lights glimmer off the flaming tiger with wings on the back of his jacket.
THE_WATCH_DVS405
In his living room, SOMEONE sips wine with a friend.
THE_WATCH_DVS406
SOMEONE charges into the living room.
THE_WATCH_DVS407
The women stare at him.
THE_WATCH_DVS408
SOMEONE's friend heads for the door.
THE_WATCH_DVS409
He looks into her eyes and shakes his head.
THE_WATCH_DVS410
She points to both of them.
THE_WATCH_DVS411
She embraces him.
THE_WATCH_DVS412
He faces his wife as they separate.
THE_WATCH_DVS413
She takes a deep breath.
THE_WATCH_DVS415
In SOMEONE's basement, SOMEONE turns to see SOMEONE and SOMEONE following SOMEONE inside.
THE_WATCH_DVS416
SOMEONE slices a knife across the palm of his hand.
THE_WATCH_DVS417
Green goo oozes from the wound.
THE_WATCH_DVS418
SOMEONE reaches out and touches SOMEONE' extended palm.
THE_WATCH_DVS419
SOMEONE gives a guilty shrug.
THE_WATCH_DVS420
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look to SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS421
SOMEONE nods.
THE_WATCH_DVS422
SOMEONE waves a dismissive hand.
THE_WATCH_DVS423
SOMEONE opens the basement door.
THE_WATCH_DVS424
They watch him go.
THE_WATCH_DVS426
SOMEONE shakes his head.
THE_WATCH_DVS427
SOMEONE and SOMEONE nod.
THE_WATCH_DVS428
He loads a handgun.
THE_WATCH_DVS429
He peers at SOMEONE up the length of a golf club. Now, SOMEONE joins the three watchmen as they march up the steps of a house. SOMEONE kicks the front door open. In slow motion, he raises his middle finger to his mother, who watches TV in the living room. Now, a bedroom door flies open. SOMEONE flips over a mattress, revealing a cache of weapons of all kinds.
THE_WATCH_DVS430
She cocks a handgun.
THE_WATCH_DVS432
He leers at her.
THE_WATCH_DVS433
They nod to her and leave.
THE_WATCH_DVS434
She blocks SOMEONE's exit.
THE_WATCH_DVS435
He kisses her forehead and touches her face.
THE_WATCH_DVS436
As he leaves, she blinks.
THE_WATCH_DVS437
Now, on the street, SOMEONE's car doors shut.
THE_WATCH_DVS438
The front tire burns rubber until the vehicle drives into the night.
THE_WATCH_DVS439
The crossover skids sideways to a stop in front of the Costco building.
THE_WATCH_DVS440
SOMEONE opens the driver's door and steps out, admiring the big Costco wholesale sign over the front doors.
THE_WATCH_DVS441
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE approach the building and peer inside through the glass-paneled rollaway door.
THE_WATCH_DVS442
An alien darts behind a display.
THE_WATCH_DVS443
Now, inside the warehouse.
THE_WATCH_DVS444
The stealthy quartet sneaks through the tire section.
THE_WATCH_DVS445
SOMEONE gives them pink plastic walkie talkies from the store shelves.
THE_WATCH_DVS446
They struggle to tear open the thick plastic packaging.
THE_WATCH_DVS447
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sneak through the produce department.
THE_WATCH_DVS448
Guns raised, SOMEONE and SOMEONE patrol another area.
THE_WATCH_DVS449
SOMEONE gestures to his friend to keep a lookout to their left.
THE_WATCH_DVS450
Now, SOMEONE spots something and tugs her husband's sleeve.
THE_WATCH_DVS451
SOMEONE sees something, too, and he and SOMEONE duck.
THE_WATCH_DVS452
An alien guards the grate near the refrigerated section.
THE_WATCH_DVS453
SOMEONE pulls out the pink walkie talkie.
THE_WATCH_DVS454
She smiles at SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS455
SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter.
THE_WATCH_DVS456
The alien's gone.
THE_WATCH_DVS457
SOMEONE hiccups.
THE_WATCH_DVS458
And alien fist clutching a human heart bursts from SOMEONE's chest.
THE_WATCH_DVS459
They watch the fist withdraw back inside SOMEONE. The fat man falls, revealing an alien.
THE_WATCH_DVS460
SOMEONE shoots it in the shoulder.
THE_WATCH_DVS461
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE unload on the alien. SOMEONE covers his ears.
THE_WATCH_DVS462
They stand over the gunned down creature. SOMEONE kneels over his partner.
THE_WATCH_DVS463
He grabs SOMEONE's heart off the floor, stuffs it back in his body, then tries to resuscitate the dead man.
THE_WATCH_DVS464
SOMEONE slaps him.
THE_WATCH_DVS465
As the others head off, SOMEONE stands over the gunned down alien, its body oozing green slime.
THE_WATCH_DVS466
It grabs his ankle, then flings him into a display of vitamin beverages.
THE_WATCH_DVS467
The others shoot the creature down again with a shot to the groin.
THE_WATCH_DVS468
SOMEONE stands over it.
THE_WATCH_DVS469
SOMEONE and SOMEONE take turns shooting the alien.
THE_WATCH_DVS470
SOMEONE and SOMEONE kneel at SOMEONE's side, finding a wound in his midsection.
THE_WATCH_DVS471
SOMEONE kisses her husband.
THE_WATCH_DVS472
SOMEONE lays his lips on SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS474
SOMEONE put two more bullets in the alien as he trots past. SOMEONE lifts the metal grate off the floor.
THE_WATCH_DVS475
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE peer down into the darkened basement.
THE_WATCH_DVS476
SOMEONE leads the way down a ladder.
THE_WATCH_DVS477
He steps onto the wet basement floor.
THE_WATCH_DVS478
Rounding a corner, he leads his friends past walls of steaming pipes.
THE_WATCH_DVS479
They spot a tower-like transmitter across the room.
THE_WATCH_DVS480
They prepare to shoot.
THE_WATCH_DVS481
SOMEONE steps out and SOMEONE lowers his weapon.
THE_WATCH_DVS482
Thorny spikes protrude from SOMEONE's forearms. The guys take cover.
THE_WATCH_DVS483
SOMEONE steps out and fires. SOMEONE hurls him into the wall of pipes.
THE_WATCH_DVS484
SOMEONE grabs a pipe and hits SOMEONE across the face. He takes out SOMEONE's legs, then strikes again.
THE_WATCH_DVS485
SOMEONE catches the pipe mid-swing, grabs SOMEONE by the crotch, and throws him into another wall.
THE_WATCH_DVS486
SOMEONE steps on SOMEONE's throat.
THE_WATCH_DVS487
SOMEONE, the silver orb, sits atop the tower under a ring of amber lights.
THE_WATCH_DVS488
SOMEONE walks up to the tower and aims his shotgun.
THE_WATCH_DVS489
Several aliens drop from the ceiling.
THE_WATCH_DVS490
SOMEONE and SOMEONE trade a look. They shoot, to no avail, even blasting a hole in one's head.
THE_WATCH_DVS492
An alien's crotch explodes. Another gets shot in the groin.
THE_WATCH_DVS493
A third goes down, then a fourth.
THE_WATCH_DVS494
The last of them falls and SOMEONE enters, peering over the barrel of a shotgun.
THE_WATCH_DVS495
With SOMEONE still stepping on his throat, SOMEONE reaches up through the young man's gym shorts and grabs hold of his genitals.
THE_WATCH_DVS496
SOMEONE grimaces in pain.
THE_WATCH_DVS497
SOMEONE's hand squeezes.
THE_WATCH_DVS498
SOMEONE yanks out a handful of green goo.
THE_WATCH_DVS499
SOMEONE collapses to his knees, then falls face down on the floor.
THE_WATCH_DVS500
SOMEONE rises to his feet.
THE_WATCH_DVS501
The alien's green, gooey genitals in his hand.
THE_WATCH_DVS502
He throws them down.
THE_WATCH_DVS503
SOMEONE lowers his gun.
THE_WATCH_DVS504
SOMEONE climbs.
THE_WATCH_DVS505
SOMEONE reaches the orb at the top of the transmitter.
THE_WATCH_DVS506
The last bar of an energy meter lights up and the orb emits a brilliant skyward beam.
THE_WATCH_DVS507
SOMEONE unplugs four cables attached to SOMEONE and the beam dies out.
THE_WATCH_DVS508
SOMEONE removes the orb from the tower, then looks around.
THE_WATCH_DVS509
The meter shows a lessening of power and the overhead amber lights go out.
THE_WATCH_DVS513
Dozens of aliens emerge from the tunnels, crawling on all fours. SOMEONE throws the orb down to SOMEONE. SOMEONE jumps to a thick cable and slides down to the floor.
THE_WATCH_DVS514
In slow motion, SOMEONE and SOMEONE pull out handguns. Walking backwards, they fire on the alien horde. SOMEONE with a pistol in each hand. As an alien lunges forward, a shot blasts open its groin. SOMEONE takes out another creature. In slow motion, SOMEONE tosses his pistols, then draws a single revolver. They all reach the ladder. As SOMEONE climbs up last, an alien grabs his ankle.
THE_WATCH_DVS516
SOMEONE shoots the alien and SOMEONE kicks it off.
THE_WATCH_DVS517
The guys climb out from the basement, then tip over a refrigerator, slamming the grate over another alien.
THE_WATCH_DVS520
As they run through the store, the alien reaches through the grate.
THE_WATCH_DVS521
A smoky blast launches the refrigerator across the room.
THE_WATCH_DVS523
The aliens scramble out of the basement, then race across the store, knocking over lawn furniture.
THE_WATCH_DVS524
The guys continue their dash to the exit, SOMEONE keeping hold of the orb.
THE_WATCH_DVS525
SOMEONE hits a red button on the wall.
THE_WATCH_DVS526
Gaining on them, the aliens round a corner.
THE_WATCH_DVS527
The guys sprint for the security door as it lowers. Before the door closes completely, they all slide underneath and into the parking lot. The aliens barrel into the corrugated metal divider.
THE_WATCH_DVS528
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hide behind a police car.
THE_WATCH_DVS529
With their fingers in the orb, a brilliant beam of light hits the store and a wave of energy encases the entire building.
THE_WATCH_DVS530
SOMEONE peeks over the car.
THE_WATCH_DVS531
A fiery blast rips through the walls, sending a shopping cart across the lot.
THE_WATCH_DVS532
The blast demolishes the Costco sign.
THE_WATCH_DVS533
SOMEONE sees a wall of smoke and SOMEONE envelop the guys.
THE_WATCH_DVS534
An aerial view shows the massive eruption of fire and smoke.
THE_WATCH_DVS535
In slow motion, SOMEONE's flaming Costco ID card, which bears his photo, rises into the night sky.
THE_WATCH_DVS536
A severed alien head flies through the air, its mouth open wide.
THE_WATCH_DVS537
Boxes spilling out foil-wrapped Magnum condoms soar amid the rising smoke.
THE_WATCH_DVS538
Boxes of detergent crash to the pavement.
THE_WATCH_DVS539
A refrigerator tumbles to a stop.
THE_WATCH_DVS540
SOMEONE looks over the hood of the police car.
THE_WATCH_DVS541
In slow motion, the guys emerge from the haze.
THE_WATCH_DVS542
SOMEONE spots them through the smoke, their figures defined by a backdrop of amber flame.
THE_WATCH_DVS543
She runs out from behind the police car and embraces her husband.
THE_WATCH_DVS544
SOMEONE holds her tight, closing his eyes.
THE_WATCH_DVS545
The group faces the burning wreckage.
THE_WATCH_DVS546
SOMEONE and SOMEONE kiss.
THE_WATCH_DVS547
Nodding, SOMEONE smiles at his friend.
THE_WATCH_DVS548
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS549
SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS550
SOMEONE nods softly.
THE_WATCH_DVS551
The four guys share a group hug.
THE_WATCH_DVS552
Emergency vehicles arrive.
THE_WATCH_DVS553
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS554
SOMEONE grabs him.
THE_WATCH_DVS555
SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE.
THE_WATCH_DVS556
Firefighters watch the group head into the wreckage.
THE_WATCH_DVS557
SOMEONE photographs Chelsea and her prom date.
THE_WATCH_DVS558
SOMEONE brings SOMEONE coffee.
THE_WATCH_DVS559
A girl jumps on their bed.
THE_WATCH_DVS560
SOMEONE knocks on a front door.
THE_WATCH_DVS561
Women in lingerie answer and he holds up Magnums.
THE_WATCH_DVS562
SOMEONE joins his guys.
THE_WATCH_DVS563
Wearing their matching jackets, the four guys strut in our direction. They become faceless cartoons with bright white skin as eggs splatter on their dark clothing.