Opening it, she finds earrings inside.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS20
Stifling a disappointed look, she holds them up and forces a grin.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS22
His five friends all turn and stare at him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS24
Cooking in her kitchen, SOMEONE gets a text: Mind if I hang with the guys? I'll pick up some pizza on the way home.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS26
He leans in too close.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS28
SOMEONE and SOMEONE trade places.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS29
The woman averts her gloomy gaze.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS30
With a smile, he turns away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS31
SOMEONE counts down on his fingers.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS32
He cocks his head at SOMEONE, then turns back to the pretty woman.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS34
Everyone but SOMEONE raises their beer.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS37
At the Ritz-Carlton.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS38
She watches from her treadmill in a kitchen.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS39
A young man with tattoos across his pecs, shoulders, and arms sleeps in bed. The woman from the coffee shop stands over him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS40
Stretching, he opens his eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS42
She gives him another quick kiss, then heads into the bathroom.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS43
He dresses hastily.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS45
She reemerges.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS46
She finds a note on the bed reading, Michelle, it was fun.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS50
People fight over copies.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS53
SOMEONE reads as she heads down a sidewalk. The successful business woman crosses paths with her and rolls her eyes. Now words type out: The Mama's Boy vs. The Single Mom
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS54
In a SOMEONE and Noble, SOMEONE spots the single mother two paces ahead of him in line.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS55
She hides her SOMEONE Harvey book under a kitten calendar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS56
He dawns glasses from a display and grins.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS57
SOMEONE steps up to the register. SOMEONE gives the next guy a pleading look, and he lets him cut ahead.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS58
Noting his disappointed look, SOMEONE turns away and collects her purchase.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS59
She faces him with a surprised expression, then allows a hopeful smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS60
At an open house: The Non-Committer vs. The Girl Who Wants The Ring
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS61
A pregnant couple enters.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS62
As the well-dressed husband helps his wife down a few steps, SOMEONE's friend's jaw drops.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS63
The guys play horse.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS64
Steadying himself on SOMEONE, SOMEONE lifts his leg and shoots the ball with one hand. It bounces off the rim.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS65
SOMEONE sneers at displayed toys and a bong.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS66
She knocks over a giant toy robot.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS69
SOMEONE arrives.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS70
Words appear: The Dreamer vs. The Woman Who Is Her Own Man
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS72
He and two friends eyed the successful woman.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS73
At the table, she sits with SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS75
She shows the book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS77
Now SOMEONE returns home to find bare walls and empty shelves.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS78
He drops his pizza box.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS79
A brown lumpy sofa with duct taped cushions
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS80
She shows some catalogs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS81
He kisses her cheek.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS83
He turns on the TV.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS84
With SOMEONE and a friend.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS85
SOMEONE approaches.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS86
The Player vs. The 90-Day Rule Girl
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS87
SOMEONE gives a downward twitch of her lip.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS89
SOMEONE stands nearby.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS91
As her friend chuckles, SOMEONE's face relaxes with a conceding smile. She shakes his hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS92
At the restaurant the chef approaches SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS93
Outside, SOMEONE approaches her car and hands over her valet ticket.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS96
SOMEONE watches her slide her jacket off revealing her silky smooth bare shoulders.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS97
With a little smile, she gets in behind the wheel.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS98
Keeping his eyes on her, SOMEONE opens the car's gull-wing door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS99
As SOMEONE drives away, he speeds off after her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS100
Now that Mercedes races around a corner. Stopped at a red light, SOMEONE watches it in her rear view mirror as it slows and pulls up to her right side.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS101
She lowers her passenger side window.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS102
SOMEONE searches the many buttons on the console.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS103
He self-consciously lifts a finger signaling her to wait.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS104
His gull-wing door slowly rises.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS106
She tosses it across the room.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS107
Sucking in her cheeks, she gazes out at the city through floor-to-ceiling windows. Her eyes slowly shift back toward it.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS108
Now SOMEONE highlights a question in SOMEONE's book,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS109
What are your short-term goals?
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS111
The guys play a half court three-on-three game. SOMEONE tries for a three-pointer, but it bounces off the rim and SOMEONE gets the rebound.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS112
SOMEONE rubs the ball against his crotch, then tosses it to SOMEONEt. He catches it in his shirt.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS113
Later, SOMEONE arrives at home to find it completely redecorated.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS114
Exiting a room, a well-dressed man almost collides with him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS115
He spots two guys moving a chair.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS116
He grabs his chair as movers carry it off.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS118
The designer turns away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS119
Now at SOMEONE's apartment, her friend grins as SOMEONE enters the living room wearing a tight black dress.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS120
SOMEONE returns to the living room in a form-fitting sheath dress, with a longer skirt.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS121
She examines her reflection in a full-length mirror.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS122
SOMEONE gives Sonia a disappointed look, then turns away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS124
At the Ritz-Carlton Residences, two suited men open the front double doors for SOMEONE as she strides out,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS125
dressed in the form-fitting cocktail dress.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS127
He holds a Town Car's door open and she climbs in. He gratefully blows kisses skyward.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS128
Sitting beside her, he gives her a rose.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS129
Dressed in a chauffeur's uniform, SOMEONE turns forward and drives off.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS130
Now as SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk toward his car, he hits the locks remote.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS131
He heads to the driver's side.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS133
He speeds off. SOMEONE stares after him, her jaw hanging.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS134
The car backs up, returning to the curb in front of her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS135
SOMEONE takes a steadying breath.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS136
She rolls her eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS137
SOMEONE climbs out of the car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS138
He opens her door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS140
Now his red Taurus sedan drives off.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS142
SOMEONE nods.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS143
She gives SOMEONE a frustrated look. He holds up a placating hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS145
At dinner with SOMEONE and SOMEONE
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS146
With SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS147
She sips wine.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS148
Lifting her brow, she drinks innocently.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS149
She offers a smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS150
He lifts his wine glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS151
Now lying back on the bed beside SOMEONE, SOMEONE exhales smoke.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS152
SOMEONE releases a stream of it as well.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS153
Furrowing his brow, he gives her a baffled look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS154
Later in the car with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS155
She looks away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS156
He hands her the case.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS157
She eyes his photo.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS158
He turns away thoughtfully.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS159
He hits a button on his steering wheel.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS160
He closes his eyes, then gazes at SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS162
As SOMEONE gazes off, his eyes forlorn, SOMEONE listens intently.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS163
He shifts his gaze to the stereo's display panel.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS164
SOMEONE scrutinizes him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS165
He locks eyes with her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS166
She glances away, then shoots him a contemplative look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS167
Now at SOMEONE's apartment, SOMEONE kisses her neck as she takes off his belt.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS168
He picks her up with her knees straddling his waist.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS169
He sets her down.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS170
She kisses him passionately. Now at SOMEONE's front door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS171
SOMEONE tentatively leans in for a kiss.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS172
She meets his lips with hers. As they separate, SOMEONE grins.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS173
The door opens.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS174
Watching him, SOMEONE grins.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS175
Duke slams the door. Outside SOMEONE's
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS176
Smiling, she gazes at him hungrily, then gives him a passionate kiss.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS177
With a cool look, she opens the door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS178
She flashes a smile, then closes it.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS179
SOMEONE turns away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS180
Inside, SOMEONE places a red X beside another on a monthly calendar. Morning.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS181
Our view drifts toward downtown Los Angeles where pale, pink light lines the horizon.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS182
In her apartment,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS183
SOMEONE stretches her arm across the bed as she awakes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS184
Finding the spot beside her vacant, she sits up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS185
Shirtless, SOMEONE enters the room.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS186
He offers a glass of orange juice.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS187
He takes her glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS188
She forks up a bite.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS189
He hands her the glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS190
Averting her gaze, she takes a sip, then returns the drink.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS191
He spots a framed photo with SOMEONE in it.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS192
He crawls onto the bed.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS193
He kisses her, then lowers himself on top of her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS194
Now, at his loft apartment,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS195
SOMEONE pads into the kitchen wearing only pajama pants.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS197
SOMEONE receives a text message.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS198
She reads.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS200
SOMEONE arrives
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS201
with SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS202
SOMEONE frowns.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS203
Now SOMEONE joins his friends at the bar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS207
She settles into bed.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS208
He does the same, but they both lie awake.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS209
SOMEONE plays a video game with Duke. Later, he shows a photo.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS210
Turning, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE in his underwear.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS211
Ron Artest approaches.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS214
He turns and slaps each of his reluctant friends' hands. Behind him, SOMEONE Leslie and three more NBA players approach.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS215
He turns.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS216
SOMEONE turns back to his friends, leaning his hands on his knees.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS217
SOMEONE tries to grab the ball out of Ron's hands. He hangs on it, pulling with his full weight, then falls to the floor.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS218
He points to SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS219
Now at a luncheon at a JW Marriott banquet room.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS222
As she goes to the podium, SOMEONE brings out a tray of salads. His jaw drops. As he turns to leave, he knocks over another server. SOMEONE sees him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS223
SOMEONE enters his mother's house.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS224
Wide-eyed, SOMEONE looks around.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS225
SOMEONE's mom glares over her wine glass, taking a long sip. SOMEONE notices a picture of SOMEONE as a boy.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS226
Frowning, his mom leaves.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS227
At a wall of photos,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS228
SOMEONE peeks into a room decorated with trophies and posters.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS230
SOMEONE shifts her wide-eyed gaze.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS231
Now SOMEONE reads a chapter titled, Mama's Boys. Snippets read, Excessively attached to their mother's. He doesn't want to grow up. They just can't compete.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS232
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in his car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS233
Now she leads the way into her apartment.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS235
As SOMEONE steps down the hall, SOMEONE flips through her collection of record albums.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS236
He flips a record between his hands, sets it on the player, and gently drops the needle.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS237
Stepping back,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS238
SOMEONE takes breath spray from his pocket and squirts some into his mouth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS239
He gets out two condoms and looks at their different wrappings,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS240
stuffing a gold one back in his pocket,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS242
unbuttons his shirt and peels off his jacket.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS243
SOMEONE returns with a tray.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS244
Now at the loft, SOMEONE rubs his fingers in between his toes, smells them, then wipes them on the arm of his leather chair.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS246
He takes two beers.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS247
With SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS248
They see SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS249
As he strides off, Sonia laughs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS250
With SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS251
The guys head out of the gym.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS252
She takes SOMEONE's wine glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS254
Inside, the guys toast with shots.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS259
She playfully waves a bite in front of his mouth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS260
He finds SOMEONE Harvey's book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS262
SOMEONE makes a call.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS263
SOMEONE enters.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS264
SOMEONE starts toward him, and SOMEONE quickly leaves.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS265
SOMEONE's eyes dart searchingly.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS266
SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE on a modern sofa.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS268
SOMEONE comes down the stairs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS269
SOMEONE sips some milk.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS270
SOMEONE spits out his water.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS271
Now SOMEONE opens the loft door for SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS272
With a little pout, she enters.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS273
Gazing around the expansive modern space, she mouths, Whoa.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS274
Wide-eyed, SOMEONE watches him pour a glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS275
He steps close, offering a glass.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS276
SOMEONE side-steps away from him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS277
SOMEONE stifles a smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS278
He moves closer. She toasts bluntly, then takes another side-step.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS279
Finishing her sip of wine, SOMEONE closes her eyes ecstatically.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS281
Before an impressive view of the city, an elegantly set table for two sits surrounded by candlelight.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS282
Keeping his gaze on here, SOMEONE gives a soft nod.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS283
The couple approaches the table and a nearby service cart.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS284
As SOMEONE wraps his arms around SOMEONE from behind,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS285
SOMEONE arrives bearing a covered tray.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS286
He fumbles the trays lid.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS287
As SOMEONE leaves the couple, he shoves one of the hors d'oeuvres into his mouth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS289
As they hold each other close, they gaze out at the city rooftops.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS290
Tucking her hair behind her ear, she gives him a little shrug.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS291
She closes her eyes for a moment,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS292
then faces SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS295
SOMEONE tosses away the rest of her hors d'oeuvre
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS296
and wraps her arms around SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS297
Now SOMEONE sits alone in his parked car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS298
Sitting on the closed toilet, SOMEONE consults SOMEONE Harvey's book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS300
Now SOMEONE answers her door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS302
Later, spotlights at L.A. Live shine into the sky as SOMEONE and SOMEONE stroll a bustling walkway.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS303
The couple looks expectantly at SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS304
SOMEONE eyes her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS305
SOMEONE glances at Xavier.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS306
He meets her surprised gaze.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS307
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE make out in his car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS309
Just as her granny panties come into view, she jumps back.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS310
She covers herself up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS311
She kisses him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS312
She hurries out of the car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS314
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE's phone.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS315
SOMEONE pulls out of the driveway.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS318
SOMEONE hits his car's remote, then leaves SOMEONE's side.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS319
He opens her door.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS322
SOMEONE stands at a street.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS323
SOMEONE helps Duke ride a bike.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS325
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie on the floor beside her bed, surrounded by rose petals.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS326
He kisses her, then runs his tongue along her knee.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS327
Reaching for a dish with raspberries and chocolate cake,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS328
he grabs some of the dessert and feeds it to her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS329
Now SOMEONE enters his living room, framed by one of SOMEONE's bare, bent legs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS330
He pauses and shakes his head.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS331
He sits beside her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS332
They kiss.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS333
She nuzzles his nose with hers.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS334
SOMEONE opens his eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS335
SOMEONE eyes him skeptically.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS336
With a disappointed look, she gets up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS337
Now SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE outside the Ritz.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS338
A battered sedan pulls up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS339
SOMEONE eyes the beat up silver car, with its missing front bumper, and exposed radiator as it peels out.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS340
A woman waiting in the valet area shoots SOMEONE a dubious look. The successful business woman meets her gaze with a challenging expression.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS341
A sleek black Porsche pulls into the valet area. SOMEONE's lips part in a lustful look as her eyes trail after the arriving car.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS342
In slow motion, a valet heads over.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS343
A gentle breeze lifts SOMEONE's hair as she watches a tall, handsome man exit the Porsche.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS345
Sliding on a suit jacket he turns and looks at SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS346
She stares, her jaw slack.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS348
He hugs her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS349
She heads off.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS350
She climbs into her silver Mercedes. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch The Jefferson's.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS351
She wraps her arms around his neck and kisses him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS352
Grinning, he retreats. SOMEONE leans against SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS353
She turns off the TV.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS354
Now at the Santa SOMEONE SOMEONE, SOMEONE stifles a smile as she strolls with SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS355
She breaks into a grin.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS357
As she embraces her, a horrified look crosses his face.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS358
Pulling away, SOMEONE gazes into his eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS359
Later, in his bedroom, SOMEONE strips off SOMEONE's vest.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS360
Kissing her, he backs her up against a dresser and knocks over a lamp.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS362
He gazes up at her as she slides her silky tank top over her head,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS363
then lowers herself over him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS364
On the wall behind her, a framed painting shows a boxer with both gloves raised triumphantly in the air.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS366
SOMEONE lies asleep in SOMEONE's bed.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS368
Waking up, she finds a note in the vacant spot beside her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS369
With a dejected look, she opens it and reads, SOMEONE, ran out for breakfast. Be right back. SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS370
She shifts her thoughtful eyes, then gives a pleased look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS371
Sitting up, she scoots to the edge of the bed.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS372
She opens a drawer in a bedside table.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS373
Finding a photo of SOMEONE as a boy, dressed in a football uniform and posing on one knee, she picks it up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS374
Returning it, she slides the drawer open farther.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS375
She finds a copy of SOMEONE Harvey's book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS376
She opens it to a bookmarked chapter with its heading circled: The 90-Day Rule.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS377
Later, she sits on the steps with the book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS378
SOMEONE enters, clutching a bag in his mouth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS379
He holds a box in one hand and a drink carrier in the other.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS380
He sets the food down.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS381
His smile fades as he sees the book in her hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS383
SOMEONE opens his mouth as if to speak.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS384
She pushes him away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS385
Now SOMEONE's caller ID flashes, Work.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS386
She heads outside where SOMEONE and Duke play basketball.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS387
SOMEONE's lips stutter.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS388
SOMEONE glances away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS389
He gives an injured look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS390
She hands him his keys and phone and he heads off.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS391
Later, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in an upscale restaurant.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS392
He hugs her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS393
She opens her mouth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS394
With a wry grin, he shakes his head and stands.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS395
Placing a hand on her shoulder,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS396
he kisses the top of her head, then leaves.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS397
She gazes after him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS398
Now SOMEONE enters his apartment.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS399
He sees his posters and action figures sitting on the couch and coffee table along with a copy of SOMEONE Harvey's book.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS400
A sticky note on it reads, Found this with your stuff.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS401
Boys shack, men build homes. I'm out, K.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS402
Between its pages, he finds a printout of his unsubmitted résumé where the words, Blah, blah, blah, filled the blurb for the professional development section.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS403
Dropping the book on the coffee table,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS405
he plops down on the couch. SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE drink at the bar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS406
Daytime. At Candace's, Duke sits on the stoop with a basketball and gazes off with forlorn eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS407
SOMEONE spots him from the doorway.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS408
Meanwhile, SOMEONE pushes a plate of half-eaten food away and rests his head on his hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS409
His mother looks on from the kitchen.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS410
As SOMEONE works at a valet station, a silver Mercedes, like SOMEONE's, pulls up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS411
He uncomfortably averts his eyes, then opens the driver's side door and a businessman climbs out.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS414
Later, SOMEONE gazes at a framed photo of himself and SOMEONE dressed as blue Na'vi from Avatar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS415
He sets it face down on a table.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS416
At an open house, SOMEONE stares off sadly.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS417
The pregnant couple enters.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS418
She flashes a tight smile, which fades to a glum look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS420
Following the bartender's gaze, SOMEONE sees a woman at the end of the bar. She offers him a smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS421
Now at her apartment, SOMEONE rips down her monthly calendar, which shows almost three weeks filled with red Xs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS422
Later, SOMEONE strolls down a street, stopping as he notices a for sale sign on a food truck's windshield.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS423
Now, in a dress shirt and slacks, SOMEONE joins his friends at the bar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS425
He stares at his phone.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS427
He turns to SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS428
As they clink their shots, SOMEONE stares off with wistful eyes. He shakes his head. The others drink.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS429
He downs his drink.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS430
Entering the bathroom, SOMEONE checks the stalls as he makes a phone call.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS431
In a kitchen, a full-figured woman answers the phone.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS432
Lowering the phone, he glances around.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS433
He hangs up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS434
He looks skyward.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS436
He claps a hand on SOMEONE's back.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS437
SOMEONE stares after the departing guy, who wears a pageboy cap.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS438
He checks the back of his shirt in a mirror.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS439
He glances at the vacated stall.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS440
Now SOMEONE returns to his friends' booth.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS441
A woman passes behind him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS443
SOMEONE enters his mother's house, catching her in her robe as she heads upstairs with a mug in each hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS444
Frowning, she looks away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS445
SOMEONE watches her resolutely.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS446
He gives a confused look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS448
He extends a bath-brush.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS449
Now at the open house.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS450
The pregnant couple.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS451
She leads him into the backyard.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS452
The couple listens in.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS453
SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS454
He drops to one knee.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS455
Gina and the wife gawk. The husband smiles. SOMEONE opens and holds out a jewelry box.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS456
SOMEONE blinks back tears.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS457
He frowns and SOMEONE stifles a smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS458
Taking the ring from its box, he slides it onto SOMEONE's finger.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS459
As she gazes at it,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS460
a tear trickles down her cheek.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS461
SOMEONE lifts his glistening eyes to hers.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS462
Shrugging her brow, she smirks.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS463
He eyes her questioningly.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS464
The three of them watch as the engaged couple kisses.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS465
Now Sonia and SOMEONE enter the cafe during another open mic event.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS467
Sonia sees SOMEONE taking the stage.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS468
SOMEONE looks over.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS470
She tears up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS471
SOMEONE plays guitar.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS472
As he glances at SOMEONE, some patrons follow his gaze.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS473
SOMEONE follows her outside.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS475
He gives a resigned look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS476
He gives a desperate look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS477
He locks his eyes on hers.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS478
He blinks earnestly.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS479
As she gazes at him,
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS480
her eyes filled with tears. SOMEONE steps forward and kisses her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS481
She wraps an arm around his neck.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS482
Now at her family reunion, SOMEONE sits at a picnic table with three women.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS483
As she eats, SOMEONE stares off with a distant look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS485
Duke drags SOMEONE over by the hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS486
He waves at the table.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS488
SOMEONE gives the crowd a bashful smile. Duke claps enthusiastically.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS489
SOMEONE lifts his brow at SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS490
She considers him.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS492
They kiss.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS493
Later, at her apartment, SOMEONE does her makeup.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS495
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS496
Now at dinner, a waiter serves her and James champagne.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS497
SOMEONE glances away with thoughtful eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS498
Shifting her gaze back to James, she shakes her head.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS499
She closes her eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS501
Stepping out of one, SOMEONE brings a tray to his friends and their significant others.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS502
He beams at the applauding group, then hands out food.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS503
Duke sits with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS506
She nudges the customer aside.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS507
He shakes his head at her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS508
He looks away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS509
She gives a pleading look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS510
Shaking out a bag, SOMEONE ignores her. She trudges away and the customer steps up.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS511
Entering the truck SOMEONE gives a determined look.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS512
He stares slack-jawed. She gestures at his staff.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS513
His two assistants leave.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS514
He hefty customer stares with wide eyes.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS515
Considering her, he shakes his head, then shrugs.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS516
She moves closer.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS517
Their lips rest mere inches apart.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS518
Nodding, he glances away with a smile.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS519
As he meets her gaze again, she leans in closer.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS520
He cups her face and kisses her.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS521
Their friends watch through one of the truck's windows.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS523
Now credits appear with scenes of the pickup game with the NBA players.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS524
Directed by SOMEONE Story
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS525
SOMEONE gazes up at SOMEONE Leslie.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS528
Now Leslie checks the ball to SOMEONE who raises an arm in a signal to his team.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS529
SOMEONE sets a pick and SOMEONE dribbles around him. As he shoots, Ron Artest smacks the ball away. Later, Leslie spins past SOMEONE and makes a shot.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS532
Leslie keeps her hand up as he fakes repeatedly.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS533
He goes up and she slaps the ball away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS537
Now SOMEONE smacks Leslie's legs as she looks to pass. Artest receives the ball, then elbows SOMEONEt into a padded wall. SOMEONE throws the ball at Artest.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS539
Now Shannon Brown dunks the ball.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS540
As he hangs from the hoop, his legs knock against SOMEONE who stands under the basket.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS541
SOMEONE steps toward him, blustering. SOMEONE leads him away.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS542
SOMEONE alley-oops to Butler who hangs from the hoop by one hand.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS543
High-fiving, the pros find SOMEONE amid their huddle.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS544
Butler tosses the ball down the court as he leaves with the others.
THINK_LIKE_A_MAN_DVS545
His friends give annoyed looks.