SOMEONE grabs the steering wheel with one hand, lightning arcs from the spinning column of dark vapor and strikes the ground around the truck. As the two women wrestle for control, the black-haired woman applies the brakes.
THOR_DVS27
The truck strikes a man who appears out of the fog.
THOR_DVS28
The truck spins to a stop. The two women stare at one another then scramble out of the truck with SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS29
SOMEONE kneels over the downed man who lies motionless. She glances around herself.
THOR_DVS30
Paramount Pictures and Marvel Entertainment present.
THOR_DVS31
A Marvel Studios production.
THOR_DVS32
A narrow ribbon of water slices between craggy peaks of snow and ice.
THOR_DVS33
Tonsberg, Norway, 965 A.D.
THOR_DVS34
Villagers stare up at the night sky.
THOR_DVS35
Flashes of white light shoot down beside a distant mountain.
THOR_DVS36
At the head of an army of bare chested humanoids, one frost giant opens a box which emits and icy blue light.
THOR_DVS37
Swirling winds sweep across the village splintering homes and extinguishing fires. A woman clutches a child to herself as they freeze solid.
THOR_DVS38
A fiery whirlwind knifes down out of the sky.
THOR_DVS39
Smoke clears to reveal a vast army of armored warriors wearing capes and holding spears.
THOR_DVS40
Separated by a few dozen yards, the leader of the warriors, a grey bearded man wearing a helmet with twisting horns,
THOR_DVS41
faces the red eyed, blue skinned leader of the frost giants.
THOR_DVS42
The two armies charge into one another, swords and spears clashing in the ensuing chaos.
THOR_DVS43
The warrior leader skewers a giant nearly twice his own height and flings him away. The giant's leader opens his box freezing two warriors solid,
THOR_DVS44
and then smashes them to pieces.
THOR_DVS45
A spiky ball of ice crystals forms in his hand, and he hurls it into a warrior’s face.
THOR_DVS46
Meanwhile, a flame shoots from the warrior leader’s spears.
THOR_DVS48
Snow blows around a city of towering crystalline structures.
THOR_DVS49
The grey bearded warrior thrusts his spear against the frost giant king’s throat.
THOR_DVS50
A warrior picks up the glowing box.
THOR_DVS51
A column of light speeds across outer space to a flat spiral of fluffy clouds.
THOR_DVS52
A colossal mountain peak topped by glowing crystals jets out of the center of the clouds.
THOR_DVS53
The mountain tips upside down, becoming the base of a landmass, supporting tall, rugged cliffs, separated by clear, glimmering water.
THOR_DVS54
Seemingly built into the rock.
THOR_DVS55
Large structures with sweeping terraces top many of the cliffs.
THOR_DVS56
Gleaming pyramids, statues, and columns surround an enormous peak resembling vertical crystals.
THOR_DVS57
Within Asgard, the grey bearded king leads a blonde boy and a black-haired boy to the glowing box.
THOR_DVS58
The blonde boy swings his fists.
THOR_DVS59
His right eye covered by a patch, the grizzled king studies the two boys with his piercing left eye.
THOR_DVS60
As the king strides off the boys exchange smirks then chase after him.
THOR_DVS61
A thick blocky hammer with a short handle rests nearby.
THOR_DVS62
Thousands of people crowd a cavernous palace room. At its center, a bearded blonde man wearing a winged helmet and a red cape holds up the blocky hammer.
THOR_DVS63
Smiling as he strides past lines of guards, the man casually flips the hammer and points to cheering onlookers.
THOR_DVS64
Nearby, a brunette woman rolls her eyes.
THOR_DVS66
A blonde woman bedecked with jewels scowls then smiles at the now white-bearded king who sits upon a high golden throne.
THOR_DVS67
The blonde man pumps his arm overhead as he strides toward the waiting king who watches expressionless.
THOR_DVS69
Stopping at the base of the throne's platform, the blonde man kneels and sets down his hammer and helmet.
THOR_DVS71
The blonde man winks at the bejeweled woman, who suppresses a smile and shakes her head slightly.
THOR_DVS72
The blonde man turns and smiles toward three men standing to the right of the king.
THOR_DVS73
The king stands and thumps his spear on the floor.
THOR_DVS74
For below the throne room in the heart of the palace, two guards wearing yellow capes march up a corridor with smooth stone walls.
THOR_DVS75
Various artifacts sit in recesses along the hall.
THOR_DVS76
The guards approach the glowing blue box which rests upon a pedestal of scored rock at the end of the corridor.
THOR_DVS77
Hidden in shadows, a blue hand slides across a thick column, leaving a thin layer of frost.
THOR_DVS78
Smiling, SOMEONE stares up at king SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS79
Meanwhile, in the corridor, one of the guards stoops to peer at a film of frost spreading across the floor.
THOR_DVS80
A frost giant grabs the guard by the throat and slashes him with an icy blade sprouting from one arm.
THOR_DVS82
Three frost giants run up the corridor to the translucent box, which contains a swirling orb of glowing blue mist.
THOR_DVS83
As one of the giants picks up the box, SOMEONE taps his spear against the floor.
THOR_DVS85
A spiked grid dissolves and releases a faceless guardian made of ribbed armor.
THOR_DVS86
Bright light shoots from the guardian’s visor and incinerates the fleeing frost giants.
THOR_DVS87
As SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE's black-haired brother step into the subterranean vault, the armored guardian steps back behind the spiked grid which closes.
THOR_DVS88
The bodies of the guards and the slain frost giants litter the vaults main corridor.
THOR_DVS89
SOMEONE surveys the corpses.
THOR_DVS90
SOMEONE glares at his father.
THOR_DVS91
SOMEONE meets his stare then walks away.
THOR_DVS92
Elsewhere, SOMEONE flips a long banquet table then sits on steps of shiny black stone.
THOR_DVS93
His black-haired brother steps out from behind a gold column and sits beside him.
THOR_DVS94
The brunette woman and three other warriors walk in.
THOR_DVS95
Chuckling, SOMEONE approaches the warriors.
THOR_DVS96
SOMEONE, his dark-haired brother SOMEONE, and SOMEONE's friends.
THOR_DVS97
Blonde-haired and bearded SOMEONE, black-haired and clean shaven Hogun, woolly-bearded SOMEONE, and the slender brunette SOMEONE,
THOR_DVS98
ride out of Asgard on horseback.
THOR_DVS99
With a panoply of stars strewn across the sky behind them,
THOR_DVS100
they gallop along an elevated roadway which resembles a thin ribbon of water suspended in the air.
THOR_DVS101
The road extends over the sea to a domed metal building sitting on an island.
THOR_DVS102
The riders slow as they approach the building,
THOR_DVS103
where a man dressed in gleaming gold armor and clutching a sword stands outside.
THOR_DVS104
SOMEONE and his friends dismount and walk up to the motionless sentinel.
THOR_DVS105
SOMEONE steps past SOMEONE and glares at SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS106
SOMEONE strides past SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS107
As his friends follow, SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS108
Inside the domed building, SOMEONE and his companions walk around a circular pit with a glowing disk at its bottom.
THOR_DVS109
SOMEONE steps onto a dayus behind them and slides his sword into a slot on the floor.
THOR_DVS110
Bolts of white lightning arc from the sword and a crackle around the chamber.
THOR_DVS111
Below them a large devise spins.
THOR_DVS112
Outside, the dome's exterior rotates more and more quickly.
THOR_DVS113
An elongated pyramid atop the dome tilts toward the horizon and opens like a flower. A beam of intense white light fires out of it.
THOR_DVS115
SOMEONE thrusts down his sword.
THOR_DVS116
SOMEONE and his companions shoot down a tunnel and vanish in a flash of light. The beam of light shoots straight from the dome into the starry reaches of outer space.
THOR_DVS117
Inside the beam SOMEONE holds his hammer.
THOR_DVS118
SOMEONE, out in front of himself as he hurdles headlong through vibrating streams of colored light.
THOR_DVS119
SOMEONE and his companions rocket towards the icy surface of Jotunheim.
THOR_DVS120
As thick smoke clears, SOMEONE gazes around himself at the inhospitable terrain.
THOR_DVS121
He and his companions stand at the edge of a cliff.
THOR_DVS122
Dark fingers of jagged rock jet upward like stalagmites.
THOR_DVS123
A light snow falls.
THOR_DVS124
SOMEONE sighs as he follows SOMEONE and the others.
THOR_DVS125
Carrying a thick ax on one shoulder,
THOR_DVS126
SOMEONE brings up the rear.
THOR_DVS127
Ahead of them a huge shard of black rock falls and splinters against the ground.
THOR_DVS128
Eyes darting as he surveys his surroundings, SOMEONE leads the group through distant structures resembling ruins of stone pillars and arches.
THOR_DVS129
Staying close together, the warriors make their way over uneven shelves of fractured ice.
THOR_DVS130
SOMEONE pulls his fur coat tighter around himself as fierce winds blow the falling snow nearly horizontal.
THOR_DVS131
Eventually, they near a large angular citadel, humed from black rock.
THOR_DVS133
A pair of twin towers rises like horns from the massive building.
THOR_DVS134
SOMEONE glances sideways at SOMEONE as they march.
THOR_DVS135
As SOMEONE and his allies approach the citadel's entrance, a frost giant watches from behind a shadowed boulder.
THOR_DVS137
High above them, red-eyed SOMEONE, the king of the giant SOMEONEs, sits upon a thrown of black stone.
THOR_DVS138
Thick spikes of ice form over frost giants fists as they step out of hiding.
THOR_DVS139
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE then gazes downward.
THOR_DVS140
SOMEONE grips SOMEONE's arm as a frost giant steps in front of them.
THOR_DVS141
SOMEONE stares at his brother then pulls his arm free,
THOR_DVS142
and with his teeth bared glares at the giant.
THOR_DVS143
Furrowing his brow, the frost giants glowers back at him.
THOR_DVS144
His chest heaving, SOMEONE continues to stare at the SOMEONE, then turns his back to him.
THOR_DVS145
SOMEONE smiles as he spins and smashes the giant with SOMEONE, sending the giant flying backward.
THOR_DVS146
SOMEONE swings his hammer into another frost giant then fends of several attacks.
THOR_DVS147
SOMEONE takes out a spiked mace as SOMEONE slashes with a double-bladed sword.
THOR_DVS148
SOMEONE laughs as he wields his sword.
THOR_DVS149
SOMEONE throws a weapon which shatters a giant's ice weapon, while SOMEONE swings his hefty ax into another giant's torso.
THOR_DVS150
SOMEONE kicks a giant across the ground and looks up at SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS151
More frost giants race out of the Citadel and leap down into the courtyard below.
THOR_DVS152
One SOMEONE punctures the ground creating a shockwave that thrusts a shard of ice up out of the rock and knocks SOMEONE off his feet. SOMEONE swings SOMEONE at an armored giant, but the feen grabs SOMEONE's wrist and headbutts him.
THOR_DVS153
The giant punches SOMEONE and sends him sailing backward.
THOR_DVS154
SOMEONE throws SOMEONE at the armored giant, striking his face. The hammer returns like a boomerang to SOMEONE's hand. Meanwhile, another giant knocks down SOMEONE, but SOMEONE dispatches him with a flying knife.
THOR_DVS155
SOMEONE retreats to the edge of a cliff as a burly SOMEONE races toward him.
THOR_DVS156
The giant leaps at SOMEONE, who turns translucent.
THOR_DVS157
Then passes straight through him before tumbling into a deep ravine.
THOR_DVS158
The real SOMEONE peaks out from behind a corner, and with a wave of his hand dispels the false image of himself.
THOR_DVS159
SOMEONE stabs another giant then shields herself against a bally of ice shards.
THOR_DVS160
SOMEONE grapples with an ice giant who grips SOMEONE's arm searing the flesh as it burned.
THOR_DVS161
SOMEONE smashes his war hammer into a giant's chest.
THOR_DVS162
Nearby, SOMEONE stabs a bare chested giant with a dagger.
THOR_DVS163
The giant grips SOMEONE's arm, which turns the same dark blue color as the giant's own skin.
THOR_DVS164
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
THOR_DVS165
He stabs the frost giant in the heart and wrenches himself free, then watches as his arm gradually returns to normal.
THOR_DVS166
Meanwhile, SOMEONE parries another giant's attacks.
THOR_DVS167
The giant knocks SOMEONE's sword out of his hand.
THOR_DVS168
SOMEONE retreats a few steps, then runs forward and slides through the giant’s legs.
THOR_DVS169
SOMEONE grabs his sword again and thrusts it into the giant's throat.
THOR_DVS170
As SOMEONE turns, long spikes of ice shoot up from the ground and impale him.
THOR_DVS172
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pull SOMEONE off the spikes.
THOR_DVS173
SOMEONE smashes another giant with SOMEONE, then hurls his hammer across the battlefield striking down several enemies.
THOR_DVS174
From his thrown, SOMEONE watches the conflict.
THOR_DVS175
He flicks his hand, sending out a bolt of blue energy which races through the rocky terrain.
THOR_DVS176
Flakes of frost fall from a huge creature encased in ice.
THOR_DVS177
SOMEONE's allies watch as the beast shakes its head free, revealing a wide mouth filled with fangs.
THOR_DVS178
Spinning like a whirlwind, SOMEONE continues to battle frost giants as his friends flee.
THOR_DVS179
Meanwhile, the heavily muscled creature breaks free of its icy shell.
THOR_DVS181
Carried by SOMEONE, SOMEONE looks back as the beast races toward them on four legs.
THOR_DVS182
Smashing through boulders of rock and ice in its path, twirling his hammer so fast that it blurs, SOMEONE flings chunks of the ground like projectiles. A huge column of black rocks topples behind the others as they flee the beast, which burst through the barricade as if it were made of matchsticks.
THOR_DVS183
The creature swings its spiked tail toward SOMEONE, but misses.
THOR_DVS184
Still twirling his hammer, SOMEONE watches as frost giants close in around him.
THOR_DVS185
He thrusts SOMEONE skyward imbuing it with a bolt of lightning, then slams the hammer into the ground. A huge shockwave ripples outward and sweeps away the giants in a swell of shattered earth.
THOR_DVS186
The shockwave spreads, toppling rock formations and collapsing the ground beneath the frost giant’s feet.
THOR_DVS187
The beast swipes at SOMEONE, but falls backward into a widening phisher.
THOR_DVS188
SOMEONE's fleeing companions race just ahead of the collapsing ice, which exposes an immense underground cavern.
THOR_DVS189
Upside down now, the creature clings to the underside of the ice as it races directly beneath SOMEONE and the others, as they leap over widening cracks in the unstable terrain.
THOR_DVS191
The warriors stop at the edge of a cliff as one of the beast's clawed hands reaches up in front of them.
THOR_DVS192
The creature pulls itself up, narrows its beady red eyes and roars.
THOR_DVS193
Spinning his hammer, SOMEONE leaps high into the air.
THOR_DVS194
As the beast rears up onto its hind legs, SOMEONE flies like a missile into the creature’s open mouth and out through the back of its head.
THOR_DVS195
The beast's eyes roll backward as it collapses onto the ground.
THOR_DVS196
SOMEONE lands in front of the dead creature as it slides over the edge of the cliff and disappears.
THOR_DVS197
Smiling, SOMEONE turns to his companions then frowns.
THOR_DVS198
Hundreds of frost giants close in around them.
THOR_DVS199
As the giants rush in, a bright beam of light shoots down from the sky. Sitting atop a black war horse,
THOR_DVS200
SOMEONE appears in full battle armor.
THOR_DVS201
Riding on a wave of ice and rock, SOMEONE glides up to SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS202
A dagger of ice forms in SOMEONE's hand as SOMEONE raises his silver spear. Bright light engulfs SOMEONE, knocking SOMEONE backward.
THOR_DVS203
The beam of light sucks up SOMEONE and the other Asgardians before shooting back into outer space and vanishing.
THOR_DVS204
Standing motionless, the frost giants stare after them.
THOR_DVS205
Back in Asgard, SOMEONE's golden dome spins to a stop.
THOR_DVS206
SOMEONE's friends usher SOMEONE away.
THOR_DVS207
SOMEONE stares at his son then slowly lowers his eyes.
THOR_DVS208
SOMEONE points one finger toward SOMEONE, who stiffens.
THOR_DVS209
SOMEONE slams down his spear, releasing bolts of white lightning.
THOR_DVS210
SOMEONE tears off SOMEONE's cape and two discs from his breastplate.
THOR_DVS211
SOMEONE stares into SOMEONE's eyes, then steps back a few paces.
THOR_DVS212
SOMEONE, his nostrils flared, frowns as he studies his father.
THOR_DVS213
SOMEONE stretches out his hand, SOMEONE flies into his grasp.
THOR_DVS214
SOMEONE's armor disintegrates.
THOR_DVS217
SOMEONE thrusts out SOMEONE, knocking SOMEONE backward into the Bifrost transport tunnel. SOMEONE vanishes in a flash of gold light.
THOR_DVS219
SOMEONE whispers to SOMEONE, then hurls the hammer into the tunnel after his son.
THOR_DVS220
Standing beside the tunnel, the blank faced SOMEONE turns and faces his father.
THOR_DVS221
Meanwhile, SOMEONE careens along the light beam through outer space.
THOR_DVS223
On earth, SOMEONE stares at black-haired SOMEONE, as their research vehicle strikes a man before skidding to a halt. Carrying flashlights, they scramble out of the truck.
THOR_DVS224
Lying on the ground, SOMEONE opens his eyes.
THOR_DVS225
SOMEONE stares up at SOMEONE backlit by the truck's headlights.
THOR_DVS226
He rolls onto his back and falls still.
THOR_DVS227
SOMEONE shrugs.
THOR_DVS228
Thrashing, SOMEONE stands and paces.
THOR_DVS229
A circular pattern marks the ground.
THOR_DVS230
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE with a taser. He falls backward.
THOR_DVS232
They slide SOMEONE into the back of the truck.
THOR_DVS233
As the truck pulls away, a glowing object drops out of the sky and crashes in the distance.
THOR_DVS234
Later, the research vehicle pulls into the county hospital, inside a nurses’ station.
THOR_DVS235
A blonde man bends over SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS236
Doctors and nurses try to restrain SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS237
SOMEONE pushes a doctor away and stands, then flips a man into a supply cabinet. Another man wraps SOMEONE in a bear hug, but SOMEONE shoves him away.
THOR_DVS238
More hospital personnel and security guards swarm around SOMEONE as he struggles.
THOR_DVS239
Three men grab SOMEONE and shove him against a door.
THOR_DVS240
A doctor gives SOMEONE an injection and he goes limp.
THOR_DVS241
In the desert, a red pickup truck drives up a dusty dirt road.
THOR_DVS242
Just over a hill, a large impact crater sits in a wide valley.
THOR_DVS243
A smaller crater lies in the center of the larger one.
THOR_DVS244
The red pickup truck pulls up to the lip of the large crater and stops.
THOR_DVS245
A burly man wearing a ball cap and brown jacket steps out and jogs down to the craters center, where SOMEONE sits embedded in a chunk of rock.
THOR_DVS246
The man pulls on the hammer's handle, but it doesn't budge.
THOR_DVS247
Elsewhere, a road sign stands at the edge of a small town.
THOR_DVS248
Puente Antiguo, city limit. Population: 2,175.
THOR_DVS250
In a research lab, SOMEONE and SOMEONE join SOMEONE at a bulletin board covered with pictures of the magnetic storm.
THOR_DVS251
In one photograph, the shadowy figure of a man drifts inside surging storm currents.
THOR_DVS252
Meanwhile, SOMEONE lies strapped to a bed in a white hospital room.
THOR_DVS253
SOMEONE struggles against his bonds, then lies still.
THOR_DVS254
He twists his left wrist, sliding it through the restraint.
THOR_DVS255
Outside, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE run into the hospital then hurry up a corridor past the wrecked emergency room.
THOR_DVS256
They step into a room holding an empty bed with loosened restraints.
THOR_DVS257
They hustle outdoors again and climb into their research truck.
THOR_DVS258
SOMEONE starts the truck, puts it into reverse, and backs into SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS259
SOMEONE falls motionless.
THOR_DVS260
Back at the crater, a man carrying a six-pack of beer trudges near two women sitting on a picnic blanket.
THOR_DVS261
Others lounge beside coolers as they watch about a dozen men gathered around SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS262
One of them tugs on the hammer to no avail.
THOR_DVS263
A bald man grilling hot dogs raises his tongs and cheers.
THOR_DVS264
Veins pop out on a burly man's neck as he pulls on the hammer's handle.
THOR_DVS266
A white pickup truck backs up to the lip of the crater, as men wrap a chain around SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS267
The truck drives forward, and the chain snaps taught.
THOR_DVS268
The truck's tires spin in the loose soil until the truck bed breaks off and flips backwards.
THOR_DVS269
A silver car pulls onto a ridge overlooking the crater.
THOR_DVS270
A man with short brown hair and wearing a black suit steps out.
THOR_DVS271
He takes off his sunglasses
THOR_DVS272
as he stares at the crater, then takes out a cell phone.
THOR_DVS273
Back at the research lab, bare-chested SOMEONE, now wearing jeans steps out of a bathroom.
THOR_DVS274
Bespectacled SOMEONE stares at him.
THOR_DVS275
SOMEONE walks up to a desk and examines some equipment.
THOR_DVS276
SOMEONE takes the equipment out of SOMEONE's hands, then writes in a notebook as he puts on a black t-shirt.
THOR_DVS277
SOMEONE removes a name tag from the shirt.
THOR_DVS278
SOMEONE folds his arms and stares at SOMEONE as he walks away.
THOR_DVS279
Back on Asgard, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE gather in a chamber with a large pile of burning rocks in the middle.
THOR_DVS280
SOMEONE flinches as SOMEONE rubs salve on his burned arm.
THOR_DVS281
Nearby, SOMEONE examines his own hand.
THOR_DVS282
SOMEONE turns and strides out of the room.
THOR_DVS284
Deep within the vault, under Asgard, SOMEONE approaches the glowing Jotunheim box, or casket,
THOR_DVS285
which still sits atop the stone pedestal.
THOR_DVS286
Shaking his head slightly, SOMEONE grips two handles on the sides of the small casket and picks it up.
THOR_DVS287
SOMEONE stands behind SOMEONE at the far end of the corridor.
THOR_DVS289
SOMEONE slowly sets the caskets back down again.
THOR_DVS290
SOMEONE turns and faces SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS291
SOMEONE strides toward his father.
THOR_DVS292
Scar-like lines SOMEONE the forehead of an infant with bluish skin.
THOR_DVS293
Collapsing to the floor, SOMEONE reaches up toward SOMEONE then falls motionless. SOMEONE crouches over SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS295
He places his hand over his father's hand.
THOR_DVS296
Two guards rush in and huddle over the king.
THOR_DVS298
Back on earth in a diner, SOMEONE shovels food into his mouth.
THOR_DVS299
SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare as SOMEONE eats more food, then sips from a coffee mug.
THOR_DVS300
SOMEONE slams the mug to the floor.
THOR_DVS301
SOMEONE picks up the broken mug.
THOR_DVS302
Behind SOMEONE two men walk into the diner.
THOR_DVS303
SOMEONE grins as SOMEONE snaps his photo.
THOR_DVS304
SOMEONE strides out.
THOR_DVS305
Cars swerve as SOMEONE walks into the street.
THOR_DVS306
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step away from SOMEONE to join SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS307
SOMEONE presses her lips together and glances away, then returns to SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS308
SOMEONE flinches as SOMEONE takes her hand and kisses it.
THOR_DVS309
She smiles.
THOR_DVS310
SOMEONE bows.
THOR_DVS311
SOMEONE returns the gesture.
THOR_DVS312
SOMEONE curtsies.
THOR_DVS313
Still standing in the middle of the street, SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE and the women leave.
THOR_DVS314
As they round a corner, SOMEONE pauses and glances back at SOMEONE, then hurries off.
THOR_DVS315
As she catches up with the others, a pickup truck loaded with scientific equipment passes in front of them.
THOR_DVS316
SOMEONE runs back to her lab now overrun with men in black suits.
THOR_DVS317
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a check.
THOR_DVS318
An agent snatches SOMEONE's notebook.
THOR_DVS319
SOMEONE holds SOMEONE back as SOMEONE and the other agents get into their vehicles and drive away.
THOR_DVS320
Later, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on the roof of their ransacked lab.
THOR_DVS321
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, then stares straight ahead.
THOR_DVS322
In Asgard, SOMEONE and her companions stride into the throne room.
THOR_DVS323
They freeze.
THOR_DVS324
Wearing a helmet with long horns that rise in a V, SOMEONE sits upon the throne.
THOR_DVS325
Placing one hand on his own chest, SOMEONE stands.
THOR_DVS326
SOMEONE and the others exchange glances.
THOR_DVS327
After a moment’s hesitation, SOMEONE raises his right fist to his own breast and kneels on one knee.
THOR_DVS328
The others do the same.
THOR_DVS329
SOMEONE lunges toward SOMEONE. Her friends restrain her.
THOR_DVS330
SOMEONE and the other men stand.
THOR_DVS331
They turn and leave, but SOMEONE remains rooted.
THOR_DVS332
Staring at SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS333
With a slight SOMEONE she finally turns,
THOR_DVS334
and follows her friends.
THOR_DVS335
Back on Earth, SOMEONE uses a library computer.
THOR_DVS336
He crosses the room and selects a book from a cart, then puts it down and opens a thicker volume beside it.
THOR_DVS337
SOMEONE smiles as he peruses images from Norse mythology.
THOR_DVS338
He pauses at an image of SOMEONE holding SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS339
Outside, SOMEONE sits in their idling research truck.
THOR_DVS340
She watches as SOMEONE walks into a store, Pet Palace, across the street.
THOR_DVS341
SOMEONE walks out.
THOR_DVS342
Later, he rides beside SOMEONE in the truck up a desert road.
THOR_DVS343
Smiling at SOMEONE, SOMEONE momentarily drives off the road.
THOR_DVS344
SOMEONE drives west toward the setting sun.
THOR_DVS345
In Asgard, SOMEONE and his mother SOMEONE sit on either side of SOMEONE, who lies in a bed beneath a translucent golden barrier.
THOR_DVS346
SOMEONE stiffens.
THOR_DVS347
On Earth, SOMEONE and SOMEONE drive through the desert at night.
THOR_DVS348
They approach the impact crater now lit by floodlights and swarming with SHIELD agents.
THOR_DVS349
Guards pace atop a square scaffolding which encloses the center of the crater,
THOR_DVS350
while scientist in white lab coats scurry around SOMEONE still embedded in stone.
THOR_DVS351
Outside the truck, SOMEONE gives his jacket to SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS352
SOMEONE stalks off.
THOR_DVS353
In the crater compound, computer screens flicker as lightning flashes overhead.
THOR_DVS354
Two guards in a cart approach the perimeter fence.
THOR_DVS355
A section of the fence is peeled back.
THOR_DVS356
SOMEONE pops up and punches one guard as SOMEONE watches through binoculars.
THOR_DVS357
SOMEONE grabs the other guard's rifle and butts him in the head with it.
THOR_DVS358
Wearing one guard's hooded poncho, SOMEONE dashes behind a large generator as an agent stumbles upon one unconscious guard.
THOR_DVS359
Lightning flashes above the crater compound.
THOR_DVS360
SOMEONE ducks behind a ridge as a spotlight sweeps past her.
THOR_DVS361
Meanwhile, SOMEONE hides in shadows.
THOR_DVS362
SOMEONE crouches as more agents armed with assault rifles join the search.
THOR_DVS363
Forks or lightning flash above SOMEONE as rain falls.
THOR_DVS364
SOMEONE looks up at the night sky and grins. He runs into a tunneled plastic sheathing leading to the crater's center.
THOR_DVS368
SOMEONE rushes an agent in the tunnel and flips him over his back. A second agent grabs SOMEONE from behind, but SOMEONE slips out of the poncho and yanks it over the agent's head.
THOR_DVS369
As the first agent stands, SOMEONE slams the second agent into him and flees.
THOR_DVS370
More agents join the pursuit as SOMEONE races through the tunnel.
THOR_DVS371
In an armory, a man reaches for a sniper rifle then grabs a composite bow instead.
THOR_DVS372
The man runs outside and climbs into a basket dangling at the end of a crane.
THOR_DVS373
Meanwhile, SOMEONE kicks an agent in the face sending him toppling down a ladder into his teammates.
THOR_DVS374
SOMEONE leaps down and kicks one agent, then ducks into a side tunnel as more agents give chase.
THOR_DVS375
With a flurry of punches, SOMEONE fights off two more agents then kicks a third.
THOR_DVS376
Through the tunnels plastic sheathing.
THOR_DVS377
Outside, the crane raises the man with the crossbow above the crater with a direct view of SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS378
Agent SOMEONE jogs into a command center.
THOR_DVS379
SOMEONE draws back his bow.
THOR_DVS380
SOMEONE dashes around a corner, then pauses.
THOR_DVS381
SOMEONE lies just a few yards ahead in the center of the crater. He smiles as he strides toward the hammer.
THOR_DVS382
A large agent steps out and punches SOMEONE to the ground.
THOR_DVS383
SOMEONE leaps to his feet and punches the agent in the face. Seemingly unaffected, the agent lands a series of jabs then tackles SOMEONE through the back of a tunnel.
THOR_DVS384
They land outside and wrestle in mud as SOMEONE aims his drawn bow at them from his vantage point overhead.
THOR_DVS385
The large agent puts SOMEONE into a headlock,
THOR_DVS386
but SOMEONE swings one elbow repeatedly into the agent’s stomach.
THOR_DVS387
As both men stand, SOMEONE jumps and kicks the agent in the chest with both feet.
THOR_DVS388
He kicks the agent again as he tries to rise.
THOR_DVS389
Standing over the motionless agent, SOMEONE wipes his muddy forearm across his chin, then stares at SOMEONE's silhouette.
THOR_DVS390
SOMEONE rips down a sheet of plastic, then walks up to SOMEONE and smiles.
THOR_DVS391
Standing in the rain, agent SOMEONE stares down at him.
THOR_DVS392
In slow motion, SOMEONE smiles as he reaches out and grabs the hammer's handle.
THOR_DVS393
His smile turns to a frown as the hammer remains embedded in the rock.
THOR_DVS394
SOMEONE grabs the handle with both hands, and pulls to no avail.
THOR_DVS395
SOMEONE staggers backward while staring at his hands, then faces skyward and squints into the falling rain.
THOR_DVS396
His face expressionless, agent SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE sinks to his knees,
THOR_DVS397
He bows his head.
THOR_DVS398
SOMEONE releases the tension on his bow and lowers it.
THOR_DVS399
An agent steps up and handcuffs SOMEONE, who offers no resistance.
THOR_DVS401
Rain splatters SOMEONE, as more agents pull SOMEONE to his feet and lead him away.
THOR_DVS402
On Asgard, SOMEONE's yellow eyes stare into the gashes reaches of outer space.
THOR_DVS403
In the dark research lab, SOMEONE holds open a book with an illustration of SOMEONE's hammer.
THOR_DVS404
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare at SOMEONE, who grimaces.
THOR_DVS405
SOMEONE interrogates SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS406
SOMEONE raises his eyes for the first time and glares at SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS407
SOMEONE checks his cell phone.
THOR_DVS408
As he steps out of the mirrored room and into the main command center, SOMEONE appears in front of SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS409
His brow furrowed, SOMEONE look down as a tear falls.
THOR_DVS410
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE, who wears a suit and tie,
THOR_DVS411
then lowers his eyes as his brother turns away.
THOR_DVS412
SOMEONE vanishes, as Agent SOMEONE walks back into the room.
THOR_DVS413
Meanwhile, technicians probe the area around SOMEONE with electronic devises.
THOR_DVS414
Apparently unseen by the workers all around him, SOMEONE grips the hammer's handle.
THOR_DVS415
He tugs with one hand, then bares his teeth as he pulls on the hammer with both hands.
THOR_DVS416
SOMEONE releases his grip and stares skyward, then adjusts his jacket as he turns and walks away.
THOR_DVS417
An agent steps into the interrogation room.
THOR_DVS418
Flanked by guards, SOMEONE waits outside as SOMEONE stands in the command center doorway.
THOR_DVS419
On a nearby computer screen, a driver's license baring SOMEONE's photo is marked falsified data.
THOR_DVS420
SOMEONE walks into the interrogation room.
THOR_DVS421
SOMEONE hurries SOMEONE out of the room. Eyes darting, he stays by SOMEONE's side as they walk outdoors.
THOR_DVS422
Passing a table filled with confiscated materials,
THOR_DVS423
SOMEONE snatches SOMEONE's notebook.
THOR_DVS424
Later, in a smoky club SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit at the bar.
THOR_DVS425
SOMEONE blinks at SOMEONE then nods.
THOR_DVS426
A bartender sets down two shots and two mugs of beer.
THOR_DVS427
SOMEONE pours the shots into the beers then touches his glass against SOMEONE's.
THOR_DVS428
The men nod to one another then drink.
THOR_DVS429
Eyeing one another over the tops of their glasses, both men guzzle.
THOR_DVS431
Traveling by means of a Bifrost bridge, a person rockets down onto the icy surface of Jotunheim.
THOR_DVS432
Later, amid the crumbled ruins, SOMEONE steps past frost giants as he approaches king SOMEONE, who sits on his throne.
THOR_DVS434
SOMEONE cocks his head to one side.
THOR_DVS435
SOMEONE jumps to his feet.
THOR_DVS436
The tunnel in SOMEONE's observatory flashes brightly as SOMEONE rides the Bifrost back to Asgard.
THOR_DVS438
Clutching the hilt of his sword, SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS439
Back on Earth, SOMEONE sits and read a book.
THOR_DVS440
Myths and Legions.
THOR_DVS441
She jumps up and opens the door to her mobile home.
THOR_DVS442
Outside, SOMEONE carries SOMEONE over one shoulder.
THOR_DVS444
SOMEONE grins as he collapses onto SOMEONE's bed.
THOR_DVS445
SOMEONE slaps SOMEONE's cheek.
THOR_DVS446
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step to the other end of her trailer.
THOR_DVS447
SOMEONE crams a dirty bowl into a cupboard.
THOR_DVS448
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange smiles.
THOR_DVS449
SOMEONE retrieves the bowl and places it in her sink.
THOR_DVS450
On the roof of the lab, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit beside a fire burning in a portable grill.
THOR_DVS451
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS452
He pats his pockets then hands her the notebook he recovered.
THOR_DVS453
SOMEONE smiles and nods.
THOR_DVS454
SOMEONE studies her notebook, then sighs.
THOR_DVS455
SOMEONE opens the journal to a sketch of stars and planets.
THOR_DVS456
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE as he draws lines dividing the cosmos into branching regions.
THOR_DVS457
Bands of dark clouds drift across the full moon.
THOR_DVS458
SOMEONE stares straight up at the sky then pulls a blanket snug over SOMEONE,
THOR_DVS459
who sleeps in a recliner beside him on the roof.
THOR_DVS460
In Asgard, SOMEONE paces as SOMEONE gnaws on a drumstick.
THOR_DVS461
SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
THOR_DVS462
Wide doors swing open and a guard enters.
THOR_DVS463
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE as the guard leaves.
THOR_DVS464
SOMEONE strides away.
THOR_DVS465
Propped in the control mechanism, SOMEONE's sword arcs with lightning.
THOR_DVS466
Elsewhere in the city, SOMEONE stands on a balcony.
THOR_DVS467
He watches as a Bifrost bridge shoots from the distant observatory into the sky. He turns and stalks off.
THOR_DVS468
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE appear in a desert.
THOR_DVS469
A SHIELD computer flickers as it displays a tornado-shaped anomaly.
THOR_DVS470
SOMEONE and several other agents climb into vehicles and speed off.
THOR_DVS471
At a table, SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE, who drops a digestive tablet into a glass of water.
THOR_DVS472
Behind them, SOMEONE helps SOMEONE prepare plates of eggs and toast.
THOR_DVS473
SOMEONE sets the plates in front of SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS474
On a rooftop across the street from the lab, SHIELD agents use binoculars and listening equipment.
THOR_DVS475
In the vault beneath Asgard, SOMEONE strides up to the casket and taps his spear on the ground.
THOR_DVS477
Behind the casket dissolves.
THOR_DVS479
The faceless guardian made of ribbed armor, the Destroyer, steps forward.
THOR_DVS480
On earth, townspeople gawk at SOMEONE's friends as they stride up the middle of a street while carrying exposed weapons.
THOR_DVS481
A young blonde boy holding a woman's hand points toward them.
THOR_DVS482
With SOMEONE leading, the Asgardians walk beneath two SHIELD agents watching from a rooftop.
THOR_DVS483
SOMEONE's mouth drops open as he turns toward his four friends standing outside the labs glass entrance. SOMEONE drops a coffee mug.
THOR_DVS484
SOMEONE's expression hardens into a mask.
THOR_DVS485
Back on Asgard, SOMEONE stands outside his observatory with his sword propped upright in front of himself as SOMEONE approaches.
THOR_DVS486
SOMEONE raised his sword, but SOMEONE unveils the casket and opens it. With the point of his sword inches from SOMEONE's throat, SOMEONE freezes solid.
THOR_DVS487
SOMEONE waves his hands and the casket vanishes.
THOR_DVS488
In the New Mexico desert, agent SOMEONE crouches on the ground beside a circular pattern in the sand.
THOR_DVS490
SOMEONE's clothes ripple as a brisk wind kicks up.
THOR_DVS491
Overhead, thick clouds swirl.
THOR_DVS492
In town, SOMEONE and his friends hurry outside and stare toward the funnel cloud forming on the horizon.
THOR_DVS493
Back in the desert, SOMEONE studies the sky as dust fills the air. A parked car shakes violently.
THOR_DVS494
The bottom of the funnel cloud touches down, sending out a circular shockwave across the desert.
THOR_DVS495
As the dust settles, SHIELD agents peek over a car at the Destroyer.
THOR_DVS496
Grabbing a bullhorn, SOMEONE steps out to meet the approaching Destroyer.
THOR_DVS497
The Destroyer's visor slides open revealing fiery light.
THOR_DVS499
As agents scurry for cover, the Destroyer incinerates several vehicles.
THOR_DVS500
In town, SOMEONE stares toward the distant conflict.
THOR_DVS502
SOMEONE runs into the diner.
THOR_DVS503
SOMEONE lifts children into the back of a pickup truck as the Destroyer walk into town.
THOR_DVS504
As a woman and a child run across the street an explosion rips through a nearby building.
THOR_DVS505
SOMEONE and the other Asgardian warriors march side by side toward the Destroyer.
THOR_DVS507
SOMEONE slips off as the Destroyer lowers its visor and incinerates a gas station with a beam of fire.
THOR_DVS508
The towering silver attacker walks unharmed through the flames.
THOR_DVS509
Gripping his ax, SOMEONE dashes toward SOMEONE, who flings him up the street toward the Destroyer.
THOR_DVS511
The Destroyer bats SOMEONE through the air, he crashes onto a parked car. SOMEONE and SOMEONE huddle behind a building as they watch the battle.
THOR_DVS512
The mechanical giant looms over SOMEONE, and opens its visor.
THOR_DVS513
SOMEONE leaps from a nearby rooftop and drives her double-bladed sword through the back of the Destroyer's neck.
THOR_DVS514
Light fades from the scenes of the automaton's ribbed armor as it slumps forward motionless.
THOR_DVS515
Sitting atop it's back, SOMEONE grins then frowns as the Destroyer's hollow head glows once again.
THOR_DVS516
It's rib segments twist and rotate until SOMEONE
THOR_DVS517
finds herself standing on the Destroyer's chest. She leaps away as it unleashes another blast of fiery energy.
THOR_DVS519
SOMEONE flees after the others as the Destroyer fires a beam that slices up the street behind them.
THOR_DVS520
She flies into the air in an explosion of pavement as the beam cuts across the facades of nearby buildings.
THOR_DVS521
As SOMEONE's friends attempt to rush to her aid, the Destroyer unleashes another blast and sends everyone flying.
THOR_DVS522
Inside the diner, SOMEONE staggers to his feet. He looks up as the Destroyer fires another beam.
THOR_DVS523
Balls of fire shoot out of the diner's windows. Broken glass pelts SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they run.
THOR_DVS524
Nearby, SOMEONE crouches behind a parked car as the Destroyer continues to advance. SOMEONE hides in the back of the diner while SOMEONE dashes to SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS525
SOMEONE puts one hand on the side of SOMEONE's face.
THOR_DVS526
They leap apart as an energy beam flips over the car they were hiding behind.
THOR_DVS527
SOMEONE and SOMEONE find SOMEONE amid the rubble and help him to his feet.
THOR_DVS529
The Asgardians hurry away with SOMEONE's group as SOMEONE stands his ground.
THOR_DVS531
Holding SOMEONE's shield, SOMEONE lets it fall to the ground.
THOR_DVS532
SOMEONE strides up the middle of the street toward the Destroyer.
THOR_DVS533
In slow motion, the Destroyer walks toward SOMEONE from the opposite end of the street.
THOR_DVS534
The Destroyer kicks aside a car like a toy as SOMEONE stops a few feet away.
THOR_DVS535
Sitting on his throne, SOMEONE strokes his chin.
THOR_DVS536
The Destroyer's visor slides down and its head glows with energy.
THOR_DVS537
SOMEONE lets his hand fall. The Destroyer's visor closes.
THOR_DVS538
SOMEONE smiles slightly.
THOR_DVS539
The Destroyer turns away from SOMEONE then backhands him into the air.
THOR_DVS541
SOMEONE flies several yards then tumbles to a stop on the pavement.
THOR_DVS542
SOMEONE runs to his side.
THOR_DVS543
SOMEONE strokes SOMEONE's bloody face then shakes her head.
THOR_DVS544
SOMEONE lies motionless with his eyes closed.
THOR_DVS545
In Asgard, SOMEONE stands in front of his throne,
THOR_DVS546
then turns and walks away.
THOR_DVS547
On earth, the Destroyer turns and walks away.
THOR_DVS548
SOMEONE shuts her eyes and sobs.
THOR_DVS549
Frowning, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch nearby.
THOR_DVS550
SOMEONE strokes SOMEONE’s face as the Destroyer recedes into the distance.
THOR_DVS551
Lying in his bed under the golden canopy,
THOR_DVS552
SOMEONE sheds a single tear.
THOR_DVS553
Back at the crater compound, a needle spikes on an electronic instrument as a technician holds it out toward SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS554
The stone around SOMEONE fractures.
THOR_DVS555
Computer screens flicker as technicians scurry about.
THOR_DVS556
The rock around SOMEONE flakes away as the hammer rockets straight up into the sky.
THOR_DVS557
Kneeling beside SOMEONE, SOMEONE glances toward the desert as a thin vapor trail rises then arcs toward them.
THOR_DVS558
SOMEONE runs to SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS559
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE away. SOMEONE's hand shoots up and snatches SOMEONE out of the air as a bolt of lightning strikes it.
THOR_DVS560
Shuddering with electricity, SOMEONE opens his eyes.
THOR_DVS561
The Destroyer pauses and looks back.
THOR_DVS562
Metal shards shoot onto SOMEONE's skin, becoming his armor.
THOR_DVS563
SOMEONE smiles broadly.
THOR_DVS564
SOMEONE's mouth hangs open as white forks of light surround SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS566
The Destroyer's visor slides open, but SOMEONE flies and smashes against its head, deflecting it's blast.
THOR_DVS567
The war hammer boomerangs back and strikes the Destroyer to the ground.
THOR_DVS568
Wearing his old battle armor and red cape, SOMEONE catches SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS569
Lifting its head, the Destroyer fires again, but SOMEONE flies into storm clouds swirling in the sky.
THOR_DVS570
SOMEONE and the others retreat as strong winds whip up loose SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS571
The Destroyer rises to its feet and gazes upward.
THOR_DVS572
High above, twirling his hammer over his head, SOMEONE hovers in the eye of the storm as lightning flashes around him.
THOR_DVS573
The winds intensify, pelting the Destroyer with chunks of concrete and flying cars.
THOR_DVS574
The whirlwind sucks the Destroyer into the sky.
THOR_DVS575
It fires energy beams at SOMEONE, who beats them away with SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS577
Holding the war hammer out in front of himself, SOMEONE dives and shoves SOMEONE into the Destroyer's open visor. A huge blast flashes over the town and radiates outward.
THOR_DVS578
The Destroyer plummets from the sky and smashes onto the street below.
THOR_DVS580
As the dust settles, SOMEONE casually strides up to SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS581
Stepping out of a car, agent SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS582
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE to his side.
THOR_DVS583
SOMEONE and SOMEONE shoot into the sky.
THOR_DVS584
Back in Asgard, SOMEONE pulls his spears out of the Bifrost mechanism.
THOR_DVS588
Standing with a host of frost giants, SOMEONE grins. They follow SOMEONE toward the city passing SOMEONE, still encased in ice with his face frozen in a scream.
THOR_DVS589
A hairline crack runs through the ice.
THOR_DVS591
Back on Earth, the research vehicle drives toward the location of the Destroyer's arrival.
THOR_DVS592
SOMEONE steps into the circular pattern on the ground.
THOR_DVS593
SOMEONE stares at the sky then furrows his brow.
THOR_DVS594
He glances at SOMEONE who stands at the circles edge.
THOR_DVS595
SOMEONE's icy cocoon fractures a little more.
THOR_DVS597
SOMEONE bursts free in a shower of ice crystals then quickly kills two frost giants guarding him.
THOR_DVS598
In the observatory, SOMEONE slides his sword into the Bifrost control mechanism.
THOR_DVS599
He sags as lightning arcs around the room.
THOR_DVS600
In the desert, SOMEONE smiles as a funnel cloud forms overhead.
THOR_DVS601
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE, who pulls her close to him.
THOR_DVS602
SOMEONE inches closer, then glances down as SOMEONE takes her hand and kisses it.
THOR_DVS603
SOMEONE nods.
THOR_DVS604
SOMEONE grabs his face and kisses him passionately.
THOR_DVS605
They both smile.
THOR_DVS606
SOMEONE steps away, then rises into the sky with the other Asgardians in a streak of light.
THOR_DVS607
They shoot through outer space along the Bifrost bridge then emerge in SOMEONE's observatory.
THOR_DVS610
SOMEONE jabs SOMEONE toward SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS611
Frost spreads across the doors to SOMEONE's chamber.
THOR_DVS612
SOMEONE draws a nearby sword as the SOMEONEs march in.
THOR_DVS613
She cuts one invader down, but SOMEONE backhands her to the floor.
THOR_DVS615
Outside, SOMEONE streaks toward the city as he flies with SOMEONE held out in front of himself.
THOR_DVS616
Standing over the ailing king, SOMEONE pulls one of SOMEONE's eyes open.
THOR_DVS617
As SOMEONE raises an ice dagger, a bolt of energy strikes him down. Standing in the doorway, SOMEONE lowers his spear.
THOR_DVS618
SOMEONE stirs. SOMEONE blasts him again.
THOR_DVS619
SOMEONE jumps up and hugs SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS620
Glaring at SOMEONE, SOMEONE hugs his mother.
THOR_DVS621
SOMEONE aims his spear at SOMEONE and blasts him through a wall.
THOR_DVS622
SOMEONE falls from the towering palace and disappears into clouds.
THOR_DVS623
SOMEONE rides on horseback to the observatory and slides SOMEONE's sword into the Bifrost control mechanism.
THOR_DVS625
The exterior of the domed building spins as a Bifrost bridge lances through outer space to the icy surface of Jotunheim, causing a glacier to explode.
THOR_DVS626
SOMEONE freezes the control mechanism.
THOR_DVS627
Frost spreads over the equipment as well as through the branching bolts of electricity, forming a flickering tree of ice in the center of the chamber.
THOR_DVS628
SOMEONE lands at the observatory.
THOR_DVS630
SOMEONE raises SOMEONE, but SOMEONE knocks him to the floor with a blast from his spear.
THOR_DVS631
On Jotunheim, frost giants flee as towering pinnacles of ice and stone crumble around them.
THOR_DVS632
Back on earth, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze up at a flashing storm cloud as they stand around a circular pattern on the ground.
THOR_DVS633
SOMEONE slashes SOMEONE's face.
THOR_DVS634
Swinging his spear, SOMEONE knocks SOMEONE to the floor.
THOR_DVS635
SOMEONE trembles.
THOR_DVS636
The two brothers leap at one another, their weapons meeting in a flash of light.
THOR_DVS637
SOMEONE tackles SOMEONE, who knocks SOMEONE away.
THOR_DVS638
SOMEONE stands and strikes at SOMEONE, but SOMEONE sweeps his feet out from under him.
THOR_DVS639
SOMEONE swings SOMEONE, but SOMEONE blocks it with the shaft of his spear.
THOR_DVS640
SOMEONE kicks free then unleashes a flurry of attacks.
THOR_DVS641
He leaps and drives the point of his spear into the floor just as SOMEONE rolls away.
THOR_DVS642
Swinging from the spear shaft, SOMEONE kicks SOMEONE with both feet.
THOR_DVS643
SOMEONE stuns his brother with an elbow to the chin.
THOR_DVS644
He tosses SOMEONE to the ground then leaps at him.
THOR_DVS645
SOMEONE fires a blast of energy as SOMEONE tackles him.
THOR_DVS646
The brothers tumble onto the bridge outside.
THOR_DVS649
SOMEONE rolls off the side of the bridge and hangs from the edge by his fingertips.
THOR_DVS650
A wild sea churns below him.
THOR_DVS651
SOMEONE stands over SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS652
SOMEONE reaches down a hand, but SOMEONE vanishes and reappears behind him.
THOR_DVS654
SOMEONE stabs SOMEONE in the gut. As SOMEONE falls, dozens of copies of SOMEONE encircle him.
THOR_DVS655
SOMEONE calls down a bolt of lightning that flings the copies away. The real SOMEONE flies backward and drops his spear as he falls onto the bridge.
THOR_DVS656
SOMEONE rises and stands over his brother.
THOR_DVS657
SOMEONE stoops and sets SOMEONE upon SOMEONE's chest, pinning him down.
THOR_DVS658
SOMEONE turns and staggers toward the observatory, his feet sliding on the slick bridge as tors of brilliant energy swirl around the building.
THOR_DVS659
SOMEONE stretches out his hand and SOMEONE flies into his grasp.
THOR_DVS660
He swings his hammer down upon the bridge, cracking it.
THOR_DVS661
Lying in his bed, SOMEONE opens his eyes.
THOR_DVS662
SOMEONE beats the bridge repeatedly, creating fracture lines which spiderweb through the glassy material.
THOR_DVS664
Behind SOMEONE, SOMEONE stands and runs at his brother with his spear in his hands.
THOR_DVS665
SOMEONE leaps at SOMEONE as he swings down his war hammer.
THOR_DVS667
The bridge shatters in a huge explosion that deforms the sea and creates a massive wave.
THOR_DVS668
The explosion carries SOMEONE and SOMEONE high into the air.
THOR_DVS669
As the end of the bridge collapses, flames rip apart the spinning observatory, which then crashes into the water.
THOR_DVS670
As SOMEONE falls he grabs SOMEONE's spear. Standing on the ragged edge of the bridge, SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's leg.
THOR_DVS671
The two brothers dangle over an endless expanse of deep space.
THOR_DVS672
Below SOMEONE, SOMEONE hangs onto his spear with one hand.
THOR_DVS673
SOMEONE stares up at his father.
THOR_DVS674
SOMEONE's hand slides down the shaft of his spear.
THOR_DVS676
Releasing his grip, SOMEONE falls into outer space toward a swirling cloud of flashing gas.
THOR_DVS677
The gas clouds stop swirling and expand slightly.
THOR_DVS678
Back on earth, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare up at a blue sky marbled with fluffy white clouds.
THOR_DVS679
SOMEONE lowers his head.
THOR_DVS680
SOMEONE shuffles back toward their truck.
THOR_DVS681
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE then turns and follows SOMEONE.
THOR_DVS682
SOMEONE stands motionless then slowly follows the others.
THOR_DVS683
High above them, beyond earth's atmosphere and far across the starry reaches of space,
THOR_DVS684
a low sun illuminates the glittering kingdom of Asgard.
THOR_DVS685
In the palace, SOMEONE's friends feast at a long banquet table.
THOR_DVS686
Sitting at the table, SOMEONE smiles then stiffens as SOMEONE passes through the crowd behind her.
THOR_DVS687
SOMEONE walks up to his mother and takes her hand briefly,
THOR_DVS688
then continues on.
THOR_DVS689
As SOMEONE watches her son walk away, SOMEONE steps up beside her.
THOR_DVS690
SOMEONE offers a small smile and touches SOMEONE's bare arm.
THOR_DVS692
SOMEONE walks to SOMEONE, who stands on a balcony and looks out over his sprawling kingdom.
THOR_DVS693
SOMEONE stares straight ahead then looks down.
THOR_DVS694
SOMEONE smiles then faces his son.
THOR_DVS695
He lays one hand on SOMEONE's shoulder.
THOR_DVS696
SOMEONE pats SOMEONE's shoulder and walks off.
THOR_DVS697
Later, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE, who stands gripping his sword at the ragged end of the bridge.
THOR_DVS698
Below him the sea pours over a cliff and falls into the vast reaches of outer space.
THOR_DVS699
On Earth, SOMEONE works in her lab.
THOR_DVS700
SOMEONE smiles.