Finding light spilling from an open door, he ventures through and finds a woman at a refrigerator.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS39
The boy lingers, staring at her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS40
She leans forward with an inviting smile.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS41
Her smile fades. The boy glances at a photo of himself with his mother.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS42
He advances, his lips unmoving.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS43
Holding her head, the impostor lowers her hands.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS44
Blue scales ripple over the figure in a wave as the stranger reveals her true form.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS45
A naked little girl with blue scaly skin, bright-yellow eyes, and slick dark-red hair that flips outward just above her shoulder.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS46
SOMEONE beams at her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS47
He warmly extends his hand. The girl shakes it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS48
SOMEONE beams gratefully.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS49
Her smile grows into a radiant grin
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS50
Now at the concentration camp.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS51
In an office, an aging hand sets a needle on a spinning record.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS52
The owner crosses to a desk.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS54
Understand this, SOMEONE. These Nazis, I'm not like them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS55
He sets a chocolate bar before him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS56
Wearing spectacles, he smiles at the thin boy through a graying mustache.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS58
He unwraps the candy.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS61
The aging man breaks off a hunk of chocolate and takes a bite.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS62
He slides the candy bar forward on his desk.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS64
SOMEONE eyes the chocolate, licks his lips, then meets the man's gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS66
The man sternly slides the chocolate back toward himself, then licks his finger.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS73
Holding the boy in a grave stare, he indicates a coin sitting on the desk before him..
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS75
SOMEONE sighs, shifts his gaze to the coin, and grits his teeth.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS76
His lean features SOMEONE and contort with effort.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS77
On the desk, the coin sits, unmoving, beside a little brass bell.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS78
SOMEONE extends his hands toward it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS79
His face flush, the boy lowers his arms apologetically.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS82
His gaze troubled, the doctor shifts thoughtfully in his chair.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS83
SOMEONE sighs remorsefully.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS85
The boy winces sheepishly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS87
The man rings the bell.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS88
A glass wall beside them reveals a medical lab equipped with gruesome-looking tool
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS89
Two guards bring SOMEONE's mother into the office.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS90
The boy rushes to her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS94
At the doctor's signal, the guards separate the two.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS100
He slides the coin toward SOMEONE, then turns his aim on the boy's mother.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS102
SOMEONE extends his hands.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS104
He faces his mother.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS106
He looks down at the coin, his hands shaking with effort.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS108
SOMEONE's mother gives a gentle nod.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS110
The boy bares his gritted teeth and stares between his hands at the unmoving coin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS111
His face flushes dark pink.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS112
The doctor eyes the coin coldly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS114
SOMEONE's mother collapses behind him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS115
He lowers his arms, staring as the doctor lowers the gun remorsefully.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS116
With hesitation, the boy turns and looks down at his mother.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS117
He faces the doctor with a wrathful glare.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS118
On the desk, the brass bell crumples as if squeezed by an unseen force.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS119
The doctor notices.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS122
A tall file cabinet in a corner ejects its drawers, then buckles. The doctor smiles approvingly at the boy.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS124
Tables in the medical lab quiver as SOMEONE faces the guard
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS125
They clutch their heads as the boy crushes their helmets into their skulls.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS126
The doctor stands staring at the rattling-steel lab tables.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS127
SOMEONE screams at the guards, who sink to their knees before him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS128
Facing the lab, he stretches his arms wide.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS129
The tables soar through the air and the medical instruments rip free from their posts.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS130
Every metal object in the room whips around chaotically. The doctor laughs.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS131
SOMEONE lowers his arms.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS132
His chest heaving.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS134
Bowing his head, he bursts into tear. His thin stooping shoulders quiver with sob
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS135
The doctor comes over, puts an arm around him, and surveys the devastated medical lab.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS138
Keeping an arm around the boy, he opens the lab door.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS140
He walks the weeping SOMEONE into the room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS142
The doctor puts the coin in SOMEONE's hand, pats his shoulder, and leaves him alone.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS144
SOMEONE looks down at the token.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS145
As the rest of the scene fades to black, the Nazi coin hovers in the darkness, then rotates.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS146
A large X stamps the other side.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS147
Words beneath read, "First Class."
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS148
Now the coin floats around the spread fingers of a grown man's hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS149
A concentration camp identification number mars his inner forearm.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS150
Now an athletically built man with broodingly handsome features, SOMEONE sits up on a bed, his back against the wall.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS151
Clad in a bathrobe, he stares ahead with a haunted expression.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS152
On the far wall, snapshots hang posted to various spots on a map.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS153
We take in the space and find it to be a modest hotel room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS154
Words appear. Geneva, Switzerland. 1962.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS156
His gaze hardens as it focuses on a sketch of his childhood tormentor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS157
With a flick of his hand, he sends the coin flying as fast as an arrow.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS158
It embeds in the forehead of the doctor's portrait.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS159
Now words appear over a campus. "Oxford University, England."
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS160
In a pub, a boyishly attractively young man approaches a pretty woman with one blue eye and one green eye.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS161
A beautiful blonde looks on.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS162
The blonde approaches the two as they raise their glasses.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS163
One of SOMEONE's eyes changes color.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS164
They leave.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS165
Now toothpaste squeezes out on a toothbrush.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS166
In her natural blue form, SOMEONE faces a mirror.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS167
Clad in a fuzzy robe, she brushes her teeth.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS168
She faces a doorway, which shows her adopted brother hunched over paperwork on a desk.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS169
SOMEONE leans over,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS170
spits, and faces her reflection morosely.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS171
She leaves the bathroom.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS172
Lingering near the doorway, she faces SOMEONE with a vulnerable gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS173
Looking up from his work, he takes in her natural scaly form.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS174
SOMEONE lowers her wounded gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS175
As he moves to a couch, she flops down next to him and nestles.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS176
In a European city, SOMEONE arrives at an austere building.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS177
Now we face a gold bar marked with a swastika.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS178
Possession of that gold is illegal. I should inform the police.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS183
In an office, The banker eyes SOMEONE warily.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS186
He notices a framed baby photo and smile
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS192
The banker reaches for an alarm button.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS193
SOMEONE uses the banker's watch to stop his arm, then makes him smack himself.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS195
He stands and steps around the desk.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS197
He looms over the banker.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS200
SOMEONE seizes him and leans over menacingly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS206
SOMEONE maintains his telekinetic hold on the banker's fillings, his face luminous with sadistic glee.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS207
His deep-set blue eyes gleam as the man's jaw wrenches helplessly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS208
From inside his victim's mouth, a metal crown springs from a molar. SOMEONE catches it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS210
He calmly strolls back around the desk, then faces the banker.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS212
He takes the gold bar, picks up a briefcase, and heads for the door.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS217
He leaves.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS218
Now as we travel along a strip of casinos, words appear: Las Vegas, Nevada. Outside an establishment marked "Atomic," a bespectacled man sits in a parked car with a lovely auburn-haired woman.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS219
They watch the club entrance.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS220
Women in bras and panties
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS221
his partner strips to her underwear.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS222
In a private room, an exquisite scantily clad blonde joins SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS223
The women arrive.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS224
SOMEONE leads them through a doorway, followed by the parade of lingerie-clad women.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS225
She leads the colonel down a stairway onto an opulently decorated casino floor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS226
Its patrons take notice as the women arrive behind them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS227
In the private room, the female agent picks up the rear.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS228
Wearing a black SOMEONE ensemble of bra, panties, and garter belt, she breezes past a bouncer, who follows her dutifully into the casino and shuts the door.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS229
Gazing over the gaming floor, the agent notices women joining men in private alcove
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS230
then drawing thick heavy curtain
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS231
At the end, SOMEONE shuts herself into an alcove with SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS232
The agent crosses the floor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS233
She squeezes past more gawking men.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS234
They gaze hungrily after her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS235
Reaching SOMEONE's alcove, she parts the curtain.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS236
It's empty.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS237
Wide eyed, the agent looks over her shoulder and scans the room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS238
She slips inside the alcove and draws the curtain.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS239
Now a record spins on a turntable.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS240
In a tux, SOMEONE's childhood tormentor leaves the record player, now 20 years younger.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS241
He takes a seat on a sprawling couch.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS242
SOMEONE sits near SOMEONE on a matching sofa positioned opposite.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS243
In the club alcove, the agent pats around the table edge, then presses an ashtray at its center.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS244
Her eyes widen as the alcove spin
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS245
It opens up on a warmly lit study furnished in polished wood and brown leather.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS246
The agent ducks out of sight, then cautiously ventures in.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS247
Noticing files on a desk,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS248
she hurries over and searches them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS249
Among the files, she finds a document typed in Russian.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS250
Her brow lifts and she gives an astonished smile.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS251
with SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS252
He stands.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS253
SOMEONE looks to a lanky man, with a mane of black hair, seated at a bar, and twirls his finger.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS254
The man opens his hand, producing a miniature cyclone.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS255
It quickly gathers size and strength.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS256
He releases it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS257
It grows to the size of a man as it reaches SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS258
The cyclone-maker flicks his hand and the whirlwind knocks the colonel into a wall.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS259
In the study, the agent ducks and faces a bookcase,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS260
then creeps toward it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS261
In the next room, SOMEONE addresses SOMEONE telepathically.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS262
In the study, the agent peeks through a gap between the bookcases and finds SOMEONE standing over SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS263
SOMEONE nods to his associate.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS264
Her flesh-and-blood form becomes crystalline like a diamond.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS265
The agent fearfully ducks out of sight, then steels herself and peers back in.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS266
SOMEONE whistles. A red-skinned man, with sharp devilish features and a tail, materializes beside SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS268
SOMEONE extends a crimson hand to SOMEONE, who stares.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS269
The colonel takes his hand and they vanish.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS270
A gray-haired man uses a phone.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS271
SOMEONE sits a few feet away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS272
MacTaggert faces her partner.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS273
At Oxford University,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS274
SOMEONE steps outside with SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS275
A few yards behind them, MacTaggert follow
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS276
Now words appear over a grassy hill with a view of a distant snow-capped mountain.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS277
Villa Gesell, Argentina.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS278
A tall athletically built man in white and khaki walks over the knoll, his jacket slung over his shoulder.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS279
He hikes toward an inn on the other side.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS280
Later he enters a tavern. It's SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS281
The broodingly handsome man hangs up his jacket and hat, and approaches the bar.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS282
Afternoon, gentlemen.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS283
Hot out there.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS284
Beer, please.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS285
He takes a seat.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS286
Two older men sit at a nearby table.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS287
On a wall, a photo shows the two men with a third between them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS288
It reads, "Caspartina, Miami."
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS289
SOMEONE notices it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS290
His expression hardens as he recognizes the third man as his Nazi tormentor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS291
He blinks and looks away with a tightened jaw.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS292
The bartender brings him a tall glass of beer.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS297
SOMEONE takes a long drink, keeping his back to the laughing patron.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS298
He lowers his glass and chuckles bitterly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS299
The best.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS300
With a cold scowl, he turns to face the stranger.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS303
His friend glances up from his drink.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS305
Since I was a boy, my father made the finest suits in Dusseldorf.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS306
SOMEONE extends a cordial arm. My parents were from Dusseldorf.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS307
He joins them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS311
He clinks his glass with the first man.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS313
He toasts the second man.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS314
As he raises his glass to his lips, the other two follow suit, swapping uneasy looks.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS315
SOMEONE takes a long drink and the others wait until he lowers his glass before they warily lower their
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS316
SOMEONE turns his arm over revealing his concentration camp number.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS317
The pig farmer reaches for a knife as his friend's eyes widen.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS318
He plunges the knife at SOMEONE, who disarms him, pins his wrist on the table, and reads an inscription on the blade "Blood and Honor".
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS323
He stabs the farmer's hand. The bartender aims a gun.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS326
SOMEONE glowers at his would-be shooter.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS327
The bartender's arm trembles and he stares at the gun. His aim sweeps toward the tailor and the trigger moves.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS328
SOMEONE sends the knife flying into the bartender’s chest, summons it back into his grip, and pins the farmer's hand to the table.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS329
He finishes his beer.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS330
SOMEONE faces him gravely.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS331
The Holocaust survivor turns.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS332
He gets to his feet, leaving the former Nazi pinned helplessly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS333
SOMEONE swaggers to the photo hanging on the wall and stares at it piercingly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS334
The gun floats to his hand and he aims at the farmer.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS335
On the wall, the farmer's shadow collapses.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS336
In a pub, young men and women cheer on SOMEONE as he drains a yard glass of beer.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS337
SOMEONE laughs and lifts her arms as he finishes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS338
A SOMEONE slaps his back.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS339
SOMEONE stumbles down off a chair and SOMEONE hugs him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS340
As he swaggers toward the bar, MacTaggert intercepts him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS341
SOMEONE lays fingertips against his temple and gazes thoughtfully at her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS342
Beyond the agent, the bar dissolves into images of SOMEONE, SOMEONE Frost in her diamond form, and SOMEONE appearing.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS343
SOMEONE lowers his hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS344
SOMEONE lowers her gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS345
Now words appear beneath a dock. Miami, Florida. On a yacht.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS346
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE, who reclines on a lounge chair.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS347
As the cyclone-making mutant approaches, SOMEONE produces a grenade.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS348
SOMEONE hooks his finger around the grenade's pin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS349
Peering at him through dark sunglasses, SOMEONE coolly strolls up to the military commander.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS350
He reaches out and pries the explosive from SOMEONE's grasp.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS351
SOMEONE gives a smirk.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS352
SOMEONE shifts anxiously on his feet as SOMEONE pulls the pin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS353
SOMEONE looks on calmly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS354
A fiery blast blots him from view, then shrinks. SOMEONE's clothes flutter as he contains the explosion between his hands, then absorbs it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS355
He taps SOMEONE's shoulder. From the point of contact, radiant energy expands and consumes his form. At CIA headquarters.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS357
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS358
He eyes SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS359
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap looks.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS360
Seated by SOMEONE, SOMEONE bolts to her feet and assumes the middle-aged jowly form of Agent SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS361
She smiles at the staring slack-jawed agent with his face.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS362
Dark scales flutter around her figure in waves as she shifts into her natural blue form.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS363
SOMEONE drily faces SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS364
A portly man in black, seated in a corner, speaks up.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS365
Later in a hallway,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS366
he freezes at a water fountain.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS367
The arching water grazes his nose.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS368
Now in a parking structure.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS369
Nighttime. SOMEONE's anchored yacht looms before us,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS370
its polished hull reading, "Caspartina."
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS371
From the rippling water below, SOMEONE's head emerge
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS372
He gazes intently at the extravagantly large luxury craft.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS373
Later in a wetsuit, he creeps onboard.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS374
Taking cover, he draws the Nazi's Blood and Honor knife from a boot sheath.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS375
SOMEONE stalks out onto the main deck.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS376
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the cyclone-maker stand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS377
Little SOMEONE Lensherr.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS378
SOMEONE grins at the intruder.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS379
SOMEONE's eyes narrow.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS380
SOMEONE clutches his head and drops to his knees, as memories of SOMEONE torturing him flood his mind.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS382
SOMEONE remembers his mother screaming.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS383
After all these year
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS384
he relives SOMEONE murdering her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS385
SOMEONE throws the knife.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS386
Taking her diamond form, SOMEONE catches it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS387
SOMEONE springs to his feet, but she punches him overboard.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS388
She turns back to flesh and blood.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS389
A military ship approaches.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS390
Ahead of the ship, three motorized inflatable boats carry armed soldiers toward the yacht.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS392
SOMEONE narrows her eyes and our view of her fragments.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS394
the motorized boats near the yacht, kicking up spray in their wake.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS395
The cyclone-maker steps to the edge of the yacht deck and a whirlwind springs from each of his hands. He hurls them at the oncoming boats.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS396
On the ship's deck, SOMEONE gawks.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS397
The whirlwind knocks the boats high in the air.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS398
In the water, SOMEONE lifts his arms. The yacht's anchor chains rise all around him. In a ship corridor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS399
Recovering, SOMEONE marches back out on the deck and points.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS400
One of the yacht's anchors rises high above its deck.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS401
SOMEONE thrusts a hand forward.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS402
The anchor swoops down, crashes through the smokestack, and plows through the upper deck. It rises high as SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the man in black stare.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS403
SOMEONE whips the anchor chain around the yacht's corridors.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS404
Inside, SOMEONE and SOMEONE flee down a hallway as the chain slices through the walls. The upper cabins collapse in its wake.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS405
SOMEONE flings an arm and the anchor snaps loose.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS406
Our view sinks beneath the water to find a hatch in the yacht's underside releasing a submarine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS407
Treading water, SOMEONE turns. As the underwater vessel pulls away, he grits his teeth and stretches his hands after it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS408
The submarine shakes, but continues through the water as SOMEONE and his followers reach an all-white state-of-the-art bridge.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS409
Water surges around SOMEONE's head as the vessel drags him in its wake.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS410
On the ship, sailors gather on the decks.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS411
The submarine drags SOMEONE beneath the water.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS412
Completely submerged, he bares his gritted teeth, and keeps a stubborn hold on the submarine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS413
On the ship, SOMEONE runs along the deck, then dives from the edge. He plunges into the water behind SOMEONE and wraps his arms around him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS414
Two veins throb in SOMEONE's forehead as SOMEONE drags him toward the surface. In the escaping submarine, SOMEONE shifts his smug gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS415
The two mutants surface.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS416
SOMEONE smiles warmly at him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS417
The haunted man regards him with a furrowed brow.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS419
As we drift over a sprawling complex, words appear: "Covert CIA Research Base."
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS420
On a lawn, a sphere stands on a pedestal, resembling a giant golf ball on a tee.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS421
At a bustling entrance, a black car pulls up.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS422
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, the man in black, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE get out.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS423
Now a bespectacled young man shows a model of the stealth jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS424
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS425
The man in black steps closer, his head cocked.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS426
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS427
The slim charmingly disheveled young man shifts his uncertain gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS428
He gives a little shrug of the head, then kicks off his shoes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS429
He peels off his socks,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS430
revealing large feet with long prehensile toes,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS431
including opposable big toes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS432
SOMEONE notices the blonde SOMEONE beaming radiantly at him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS433
He smiles pleasurably, then scoots past the group.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS434
He leaps up, backflips, and catches hold of the model jet with his feet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS435
He hangs upside down.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS436
He swings gently as his feet grip the model tightly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS437
He stares, slack-jawed.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS438
Smiling warmly, SOMEONE steps in close to SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS439
Now a TV in a living room shows a news broadcast.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS440
SOMEONE skeptically cocks her head.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS441
SOMEONE crosses to a large hard case sitting on a desk.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS442
He opens it and pulls out a sleek shiny helmet the color of pewter
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS443
designed to cover the entire head.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS444
Steel-hued trim frames its specialized facial opening.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS445
He puts it on, leaving only his eyes, nose, mouth, and chin exposed.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS446
As SOMEONE faces SOMEONE, she exhales and lowers her chin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS447
She stares piercingly at SOMEONE, her eyes narrowing.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS448
Relaxing, she tilts her head and cocks an eyebrow.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS449
SOMEONE beams gratefully.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS450
SOMEONE holds up a glass of liquor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS451
SOMEONE's smile fade
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS452
She takes the glass and crosses the stylish room to a hatch.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS453
Opening the door, she heads into the submarine bridge.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS454
SOMEONE and the cyclone-maker lower a ladder for her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS455
Now standing in an open upper hatch, SOMEONE's diamond hand cuts a plum-sized chunk of ice from a large formation.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS456
As it plops into SOMEONE's drink,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS457
we drift back and find the sub in the midst of a frozen sea.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS458
In a recess at the lab, SOMEONE sits facing SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS459
SOMEONE leans in close.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS460
She lays her forearm across his lap.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS461
SOMEONE rolls up her sleeve and swabs at a patch of her skin with a cotton ball.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS462
He picks up a syringe and injects the needle into her vein.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS463
SOMEONE winces.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS464
She brings her full parted lips in toward his.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS465
She straightens abruptly as SOMEONE strolls over.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS466
SOMEONE presses his lips shut and swallow
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS467
SOMEONE stares after SOMEONE as he saunters off, then faces SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS468
The young man licks his lips and shifts his uneasy gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS469
Now in a dimly lit office, SOMEONE searches a file cabinet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS470
He brings out a folder, glances over his shoulder, and studies its cover.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS471
It bears the CIA emblem,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS472
SOMEONE's name, and a file number.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS473
SOMEONE puts it in a briefcase.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS474
Later he exits
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS475
the complex, passing SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS476
SOMEONE keeps his back to SOMEONE, his gaze vulnerable.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS477
He smiles bitterly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS478
He faces the compassionate young man.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS479
SOMEONE stands motionless, his wary gaze fixed on SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS480
SOMEONE backs away a few feet, then turns and heads toward the building.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS481
SOMEONE looks away, uncertain.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS482
Now SOMEONE looks at the giant golf-ball-like structure.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS483
SOMEONE smile
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS484
With a nod, SOMEONE eyes the man in black.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS485
SOMEONE considers SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS486
The supervising agent gapes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS487
As the man in black holds SOMEONE's smug gaze, our view zooms out a window, which frames the transmitter.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS488
Now SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE find SOMEONE inside the transmitter's spherical room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS489
SOMEONE pulls on a helmet attached to a network of wire
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS490
SOMEONE flips switches on a control board as SOMEONE waits atop a circular platform at the room's center.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS491
Furrowing his brow, SOMEONE scrutinizes his telepathic colleague.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS492
As SOMEONE closes his eyes, SOMEONE watches with an anxious look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS493
SOMEONE flips more switches and a strip of paper begins to move like a conveyor belt under the arms of a chart recorder.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS494
White light glows down on SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS495
He clutches railings at his sides. His chest heaves as he envisions shooting into the air past hundreds of humans. Emerging on a blanket of clouds, his gaze sweeps from three girls, to a man reading a book, to a dark-skinned girl with white hair.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS496
He smiles.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS497
SOMEONE finds a girl being examined by an eye doctor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS498
In the transmitter, SOMEONE watches a printer.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS499
SOMEONE grins.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS500
His mind's eye zooms from person to person in the clouds,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS501
then focuses on a black-haired young woman in booty shoots and a bra with dangling fringe.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS502
The clouds clear away to show her standing on a bar in a night club.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS503
SOMEONE and SOMEONE now sit in front of her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS504
SOMEONE shows her some money.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS505
Later in a private room, SOMEONE and SOMEONE clink their glasses.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS506
SOMEONE snaps and an ice bucket with champagne rises.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS507
As they look at her, the young woman twitches a smile.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS508
Reaching behind her back,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS509
she unhooks her bra and a web-like tattoo of four dragonfly wings morphs into real ones. As they flutter rapidly, the young woman rises into the air.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS510
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange an amazed look, then return their attention to the hovering dancer.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS511
Back at the transmitter, the printer types more coordinates.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS512
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb into a cab.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS513
SOMEONE guides the meter's arm down. Later the recruiters walk a prison corridor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS514
The warden opens a cell.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS515
Sitting on a bench inside, a brawny young man with blonde hair lifts his gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS516
Now in an aquarium, a teenaged boy and girl face a fish tank.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS517
The pretty teen gives him a haughty look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS518
As she turns away, the shaggy-haired boy blows at the tank.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS519
The water inside ripples, driving the fish off.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS520
The girl turns back to the tank and finds all of the fish gone.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS521
With a perplexed look, she hurries off.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS522
As the boy turns back to the tank, SOMEONE and SOMEONE step up behind him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS523
Later the recruiters enter a pub where Logan sits at the bar.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS524
They approach the troubled man as he lifts a cigar to his lips.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS525
Logan puffs on his cigar and the two recruiters exchange a resigned look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS526
As they head out the door, he stares over his shoulder after them, then downs his drink and gestures for another.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS527
Now a view through a periscope sweeps across a vacant ocean.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS528
Inside SOMEONE's sub, SOMEONE removes her eyes from the viewfinder and turns to SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS529
Striding out of the bridge, she enters the adjacent living room and office area.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS530
She opens a small metal box on a desk and pushes a button inside.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS531
Two sections of wall separate to reveal a secret doorway.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS532
Entering a room covered in mirrored panels, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE staring down at a waist-high nuclear reactor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS533
SOMEONE's chest heaves and his eyes harden.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS534
Now on the steps of the SOMEONE Memorial.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS535
Nighttime. At the research base, SOMEONE and the young recruit sit in a rec room with a large window overlooking a courtyard.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS536
She morphs into the shaggy-haired boy.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS537
She transforms back.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS538
He strides over to a fish tank.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS539
As he sticks his head under water, gills appear on either side.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS540
He opens his mouth and breathe
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS541
He grins at the others, then lifts his head out.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS542
The shaggy-haired boy stares thoughtfully.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS543
With puzzled looks, the others press their hands to their ear
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS544
SOMEONE smiles, then releases a gust of sound.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS545
It hits the window and shatters it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS546
SOMEONE turns to the black-haired exotic dancer.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS547
She shows her wing.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS548
She spits a ball of fire, which soars out through the shattered window, and ignites the head of a statue in the courtyard.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS549
She gives SOMEONE a nod.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS550
He looks away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS551
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a smile.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS552
SOMEONE rises from his chair.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS553
SOMEONE climbs out the broken window and enters the courtyard.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS554
The others peer through the window at him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS555
They retreat behind the wall, then lean their bodies to look out the window again.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS556
They remain in position.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS557
Clenching his fists, he swivels his hips and shoulders.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS558
Red rings of energy swirl around him and shoot off like discs.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS559
One cuts the statue in half, leaving flames along the sever line.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS560
Now in a meeting with SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS561
Later at the research base.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS562
through the window into the rec room, they see SOMEONE dancing on a couch.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS563
Angel hovers in the air beside SOMEONE, who hangs upside-down from the ceiling.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS564
SOMEONE wears scaly armor as SOMEONE slams him with a piece of metal.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS565
With her hands on her hips, SOMEONE gapes at the rowdy youngster
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS566
SOMEONE and Angel stop dancing. SOMEONE flips down and SOMEONE's armor melts away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS567
She points at SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS568
She grins at SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS569
He gives the recruits a dry look. As he and SOMEONE leave, SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS570
SOMEONE stares dejectedly as he heads off.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS571
Now our view drifts away from a mansion on a vast countryside estate.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS572
Words appear: "Russian Military Retreat."
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS573
As a truck trundles down a road into a thick barrier of trees bordering the estate,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS574
SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride in back.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS575
Lifting a hatch, they peer into the cab, where SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS576
Craning his neck, SOMEONE looks down at the road and sees soldiers guarding a roadblock up ahead.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS577
He faces soldiers in back with him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS578
They arrive at the roadblock and a soldier approaches.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS580
A dog pulls a soldier toward the truck.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS583
As SOMEONE heads to the back, the soldiers inside raise their gun
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS584
SOMEONE touches his temple.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS585
The dog sniffs around the vehicle and SOMEONE leads a soldier to the truck's rear.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS586
Throwing open its doors, he finds it empty. Standing among the soldiers with drawn weapons, SOMEONE keeps his fingers on his temple.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS590
SOMEONE turns to the soldier
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS592
As he swings the doors closed, SOMEONE lowers his hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS593
His shoulders sag in relief and SOMEONE pats his knee.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS594
Later a view through binoculars shows a helicopter landing at the military retreat.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS595
Hidden behind a hill, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE watch as SOMEONE climbs off the chopper and heads toward the mansion.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS596
With puzzled looks, they lower their binocular
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS597
As he touches his temple, SOMEONE and SOMEONE raise their binoculars again.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS598
SOMEONE's mind's eye zooms past a barbed-wire fence protecting the mansion
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS599
to a soldier standing guard at its portico.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS600
The Russian man blinks as if dazed, then shifts his gaze to SOMEONE as she greets a mustached general.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS601
The general escorts her inside and SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS602
The telepath frowns.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS603
The violated Russian soldier gives a puzzled look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS604
He runs off.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS605
Meanwhile in a bedroom, the general toasts with SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS607
He drains his drink and SOMEONE sips her
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS608
They set down their glasses.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS609
With a seductive look, she rises from a couch.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS610
She undoes the belt on her dress.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS611
She lowers her zipper, which trails from her collar to the hem of her skirt.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS612
The general stares with hungry eyes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS613
Meanwhile, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE watch through binoculars as coils of the barbed-wire fence wrap around soldiers guarding it
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS614
and pull them to the ground.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS615
SOMEONE directs a gate to lift and sprints underneath. As the guards by the portico aim their weapons,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS616
SOMEONE extends his arms, drawing the soldiers toward him, then pulls his elbows down, causing them to fall.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS617
He kicks one as he races past.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS618
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS619
Now SOMEONE enters the mansion.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS620
As two soldiers aim their weapons, he commands the guns to disassemble, then hurls them into the ground.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS621
Outside, SOMEONE spots a soldier wrapped in barbed wire.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS622
He hurries over.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS624
He touches the soldier's cheek. Forget my face.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS625
The Russian's eyes close and his head drops.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS626
SOMEONE rushes to the mansion.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS627
In the bedroom, the general sits on the bed, with SOMEONE straddling him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS628
The real SOMEONE watches from the couch.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS629
Dressed in only her underwear, she nibbles a cracker.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS630
Bursting into the room, SOMEONE and SOMEONE find the mustached general fondling his imaginary woman.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS631
They exchange a look and SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS632
Coming out of his trance, the general glare.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS634
As he reaches for his gun, SOMEONE points at him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS635
The general falls back and passes out.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS636
Standing, SOMEONE morphs into her diamond form.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS637
With his eyes fixed on her, SOMEONE touches his temple.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS638
SOMEONE winces.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS639
He glances at SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS640
As SOMEONE sprints to the door, the men each grab an arm and wrestle her to the brass bed frame,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS641
where they hold her against the foot board.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS642
SOMEONE commands its bars to wrap around her wrists.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS643
He bends the frame to hold her tighter.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS644
His chest heaves. As SOMEONE struggles against her restraints, he directs a bar to wrap around her neck.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS645
He commands two more and they each bind an arm just below the shoulder.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS646
SOMEONE's brow creases in a pained look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS647
SOMEONE shakes his head.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS648
Sucking in ragged breaths, he controls the bar around SOMEONE's neck,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS649
making it squeeze even tighter.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS650
SOMEONE's chest heaves.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS651
The metal wrings SOMEONE's diamond skin, causing a crack around her neck.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS652
As SOMEONE releases the bar strangling her, the captive morphs back into her human form.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS653
He turns away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS654
He prepares himself a cracker.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS655
Gazing intently at SOMEONE, SOMEONE touches his temple.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS656
In her mind, he sees the United States on a world map.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS657
The focus shifts as SOMEONE places a magnet of a missile on top of Cuba.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS658
Warheads soar around a globe, launching from the United States and landing in Russia.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS659
As they detonate, missiles fly from Russia to the US and explode.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS660
A burst of fire gives way to a mushroom cloud.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS661
Another vision shows the Capitol building now in ruins amid a destroyed cityscape.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS662
SOMEONE lowers his hand, then turns to SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS663
He shifts his gaze back to SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS664
SOMEONE gives a troubled look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS665
Meanwhile, SOMEONE watches a score display as SOMEONE plays pinball in the rec room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS666
In the courtyard, two agents pass the window and look in at Angel, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS667
He mimes flying.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS668
SOMEONE stands.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS669
With a sarcastic salute, SOMEONE draws curtains over the window, then sits again.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS675
SOMEONE lowers her thoughtful gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS676
She returns her eyes to Angel, who looks away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS677
The recruits glance around.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS679
SOMEONE turns from the pinball machine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS681
As he strides to the window, SOMEONE follows.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS682
The others rise from their seats.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS683
SOMEONE opens the curtains. Meanwhile in the man in black's office,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS687
As the man in black steps toward his window, SOMEONE materializes behind him,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS688
grabs the subordinate agent, then disappears with him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS689
Reappearing, he grabs the supervising agent and teleports him into the sky above the base.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS690
The recruits watch through the window as SOMEONE releases the man in black, then disappear
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS691
The portly agent plummets to the courtyard.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS692
Now more CIA agents rain from the sky.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS693
One crashes through a skylight in the rec room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS694
As SOMEONE enters the building wearing the helmet, an agent talks into a radio.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS695
SOMEONE absorbs his bullets.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS696
SOMEONE lifts him by the throat. Meanwhile,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS697
the recruits watch through the window as SOMEONE appears in the courtyard.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS698
The agents open fire, but SOMEONE disappears.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS699
The mutant materializes next to an agent and forces him to fire into the room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS700
The young mutants see a cyclone pass by the transmitter. In the main atrium, the agent dangles in SOMEONE's grasp.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS701
A team of soldiers surrounding him cock their weapons. SOMEONE launches his captive into the air and the team fires.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS702
As he absorbs the bullets,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS703
SOMEONE's arms appear to split at the elbow, replicate into three forearms, then rejoin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS704
A soldier fires a rocket launcher. Flames engulf the SOMEONE, then shrink into his hands as he absorbs the energy.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS705
Meanwhile, the recruits watches SOMEONE slay agents in the courtyard.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS706
SOMEONE spears a man in the chest with his devil's tail.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS707
As the recruits race down a hall, soldiers stop them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS708
In the atrium, SOMEONE stomps his foot and a glowing pulse of energy cracks the floor underneath.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS709
It spreads to the wall, then surges around the room
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS710
taking out the balcony and the soldiers along with it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS711
In the hallway, the recruits and soldiers duck.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS712
Standing at the atrium's center, SOMEONE directs the roiling flames with his gaze
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS713
and the recruits retreat down the hall.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS714
Racing into a small lunch room, they see the cyclone through a window.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS715
The swirling wind engulfs the transmitter, ripping it apart.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS716
The recruits turn to the other window and find SOMEONE slaying soldiers and agents. Strangling a man with his tail, he uses him as a shield against an agent with a gun.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS717
The agent accidentally shoots SOMEONE's hostage and the teleporter vanishes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS718
The cyclone outside hurls a man into the window and shatters it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS719
At the other window, SOMEONE appears in front of a trembling agent.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS720
The mutant easily dispatches him, stabbing him in the back.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS721
The cyclone-maker climbs through the broken window.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS722
The recruits turn to see SOMEONE coming in from the other side.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS723
The door open
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS724
SOMEONE steps in and faces the huddle of terrified young recruit
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS725
He removes the anti-telepathy helmet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS726
Outside, a soldier aims.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS727
The devilish mutant materializes in the courtyard and kills him with a sword.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS728
He faces SOMEONE pointedly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS729
SOMEONE looks away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS730
SOMEONE's gaze falls on Angel and grows seductively tender.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS731
With a vulnerable pout, the young woman swallows and looks down at his extended hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS732
She accepts it and SOMEONE leads her to the shattered window.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS733
SOMEONE reaches out to her, but she turns away and continues out with SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS734
The young man lowers his arm as she steps through the window with SOMEONE and the cyclone-maker.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS735
SOMEONE lowers his woeful gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS736
He sighs heavily and his expression grows resolute.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS737
He faces SOMEONE who scowls as SOMEONE speaks. The young men trade angry shove
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS738
As he comes outside, Angel smirks. SOMEONE smiles and meets him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS739
Behind him, the other young mutants form a line.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS740
SOMEONE sweeps an arm behind him in a welcoming gesture.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS741
SOMEONE joins Angel at her side and faces the other
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS742
He shields her with his body and turns to stone.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS743
SOMEONE hurls an energy ring, but SOMEONE catches it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS744
He absorbs it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS745
SOMEONE swings at him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS746
SOMEONE blocks his punch, then grabs him by the jaw, forcing his mouth open.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS748
He forces a compact mass of the energy between SOMEONE's lips, then releases him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS749
Angel stares sadly at her friend as SOMEONE and his team join hands, then disappear with SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS750
SOMEONE convulses, his form turning metallic.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS751
It takes on the appearance of volcanic rock
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS752
with lava beneath the surface.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS753
SOMEONE steadies himself and becomes stone,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS754
appearing to subdue the combustion of his body.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS755
He faces SOMEONE, whose eyes widen.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS756
SOMEONE reaches out to him, resuming his flesh-and-blood form.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS757
Brilliant light shines out through cracks in his skin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS758
It consumes him, then overwhelms our view.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS759
In Moscow, the Russian general looks out at a military parade through from a balcony. He goes inside.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS761
He shakes SOMEONE's hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS762
Once again, my sympathies for your treatment at the hands of the CIA.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS763
These Americans are ruthless.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS764
Now they have their missiles placed in Turkey.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS765
He arrives at a world map highlighting the United States and Soviet Union, then points out the strategic location.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS770
He plants a missile-shaped crimson marker over a sizable island southeast of the Floridian coast.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS773
He steps in close to SOMEONE and removes the marker.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS775
The general stares at him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS777
He marches to a phone on one of the long tables and picks it up.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS779
SOMEONE, Angel, and the cyclone-maker appear before him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS781
He fearfully lowers the phone, then looks back at SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS782
The evil mutant leader smiles and holds out his hands.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS783
The general faces SOMEONE's menacing team.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS784
Now a black car arrives outside the devastated research facility.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS785
SOMEONE and SOMEONE rush out.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS786
They find the remaining teens on a bench.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS787
As SOMEONE embraces his adopted sister, SOMEONE joins the group.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS788
SOMEONE hangs his head and SOMEONE looks away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS789
All eyes turn on SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS790
SOMEONE takes him aside.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS791
SOMEONE faces the group, his angular features set in a grim frown.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS792
SOMEONE yields a faint comforting smile.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS793
Now SOMEONE sits in a small room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS794
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from an observation room,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS795
SOMEONE stands and strides confidently to the window.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS796
Her finger crystallizes and she uses it to cut a circle in the glass.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS797
The mutant lightly taps it and it drops out of the window.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS798
Now a massive Russian ship, named Aral Sea, slowly moves across the ocean.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS799
The captain and a few crew members stand vigilantly on the control bridge.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS800
Captain, no sign of any American ships.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS801
Maintain course. Full ahead.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS802
At the Pentagon.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS803
Around the ring-shaped table, officials raise their hands unanimously.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS804
Now on the Xavier estate's verdant grounds.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS805
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the teens stare up at the palatial manor house.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS806
SOMEONE gratefully kisses SOMEONE's blonde head.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS807
She leads the group off a gravel driveway and around the side of the mansion.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS808
Now words appear beneath a gray, overcast public square.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS809
Moscow, Russia. In the Soviet war room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS810
Dear comrades, the United States have dispatched warships for Cuba.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS811
This leaves us no choice.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS812
The general circles the packed room, indicating the map with a long pointer.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS813
He halts before a central table.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS814
Comrade First Secretary, we must send in our fleet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS815
A bald man whispers with two colleagues on either side of him, then gives a nod.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS816
Dispatch the fleet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS817
The scene freezes in a photo.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS818
Panels featuring newsreels and headlines fill the screen.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS819
Blossoming mushroom clouds fill the panels, which vanish.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS820
The remaining two converge to reveal SOMEONE aiming a gun on his estate.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS821
His hand shakes as he cocks it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS822
SOMEONE stands before him, the gun pointed at his head.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS823
SOMEONE takes a deep breath as his companion grins eagerly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS824
He takes the gun.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS825
Now in a long arched chamber,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS826
SOMEONE sets up a mannequin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS827
Now outside, SOMEONE shatters panes of glass.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS828
Now SOMEONE runs laps with SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS829
In the bunker.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS830
SOMEONE steps out and closes a heavy-duty hatch.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS831
He presses an ear to the door.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS832
Opening it, he finds the bunker's arch-shaped support beams in flames.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS833
He grabs an extinguisher and hurriedly puts out the fire.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS834
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE fit SOMEONE with cloth-wing attachments.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS835
At a window.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS836
Sitting on the window's ledge, SOMEONE crosses himself, then spreads his wings.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS837
He pitches off the window.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS838
He plummets.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS839
Now SOMEONE stands with SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS840
SOMEONE stretches his bare feet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS841
They race down the driveway.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS842
SOMEONE pulls in front, then disappears ahead of SOMEONE, who pumps his arms as he sprints.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS843
In a blur of motion, SOMEONE appears behind SOMEONE, then catches up and taps his shoulder.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS844
Stopping, SOMEONE shakes his head.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS845
SOMEONE saunters over.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS846
He slaps his back.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS847
SOMEONE trudges away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS848
Passing a window, he sees SOMEONE inside.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS849
She waves and he gives her a half-hearted smile as he returns the gesture.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS850
Now as SOMEONE does bench presses, the barbell lifts out of her hands.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS851
He releases the barbell.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS852
SOMEONE morphs into her true form as she catches it.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS853
SOMEONE stares after him as he strides away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS854
Now SOMEONE wears a vest with a circular panel on its chest.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS855
Facing three mannequins, SOMEONE shoots a shaft of energy from his chest.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS856
He destroys the one on the left.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS857
He tries again and the blast knocks him over.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS858
Only the middle mannequin remains standing. Later SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in a lab.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS859
Sitting on his lap, SOMEONE peers into his microscope.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS860
Now on top of a giant satellite dish.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS861
SOMEONE closes his mouth.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS862
SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE off the dish.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS863
The shaggy-haired boy plummets toward some trees.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS864
Rings of sound waves shoot out of his mouth, expanding in a cone shape.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS865
They propel SOMEONE high into the air.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS866
The boy dives back toward the satellite dish, then uses his sound rings to glide over dish's concave face.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS867
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a disapproving look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS868
SOMEONE marks a mannequin with an X.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS869
SOMEONE stands by the dummy.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS870
On the mannequin's other side, SOMEONE inches away from the target.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS871
SOMEONE shoots energy from his chest and the beam hits the dummy in a burst of flames.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS872
Unharmed, SOMEONE and SOMEONE move aside. SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS873
SOMEONE's grin fades.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS874
Now SOMEONE points at the satellite dish in the far distance.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS875
SOMEONE stare
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS876
He shoots an uncertain look and his friend nod
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS877
SOMEONE's shoulders heave.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS878
With his fingers spread wide, he aims his palms at the dish.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS879
It remains motionless.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS880
SOMEONE's hands tremble and his face flushes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS881
Lowering his arms, he drops his head.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS882
Raising his fingers, he wiggles them questioningly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS883
SOMEONE shakes his head and SOMEONE touches his temple.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS884
His eyes close briefly, then meet SOMEONE's.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS885
The landscape around the brooding man blur
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS886
In his mind's eye, SOMEONE sees a young SOMEONE lighting candle
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS887
His mother stands with him and they share a smile.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS888
Reaching out, she brushes his cheek with her finger.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS889
As the memory fades, SOMEONE blinks out a tear.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS890
He stares off, his chest heaving, then clenches his
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS892
SOMEONE opens his eyes and brushes a tear from his own cheek.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS893
He hold SOMEONE's gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS894
He pats him on the shoulder.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS895
SOMEONE faces the satellite dish.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS896
He bows his head for a moment, then extends his hand and fingers as if stretching to reach the dish.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS897
The dish shifts and SOMEONE knits his brow in concentration.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS898
His hand trembles.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS899
SOMEONE's shoulders heave as he controls the satellite dish, his face pulled into an expression of both sadness and triumph.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS900
He curls his fingers as if holding an invisible tennis ball,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS901
then turns his hand,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS902
rotating the dish toward the mansion.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS903
Breaking into a grin, he lowers his arm.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS904
SOMEONE sticks her head out a window.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS905
Now the group watches a TV.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS906
Now as the Russian cargo ship glides over the ocean, SOMEONE's sub follows underwater.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS907
SOMEONE watches the news.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS908
Beside him, Angel twitches a smile, then clinks her glass with SOMEONE's.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS909
Meanwhile in SOMEONE's room, SOMEONE enter.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS910
SOMEONE beams at him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS911
He holds out a case.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS912
Grinning, SOMEONE opens it and finds two syringes with needles inside.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS913
Her smile fades and she sits.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS914
SOMEONE sits across from her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS915
SOMEONE stares with a conflicted gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS916
She leans toward him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS917
With a determined smile, he takes one of the shots from the case.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS918
He taps the syringe's barrel, then prepares to inject.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS919
He gives her a puzzled look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS920
SOMEONE's face falls and he glances away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS921
She stares into his eye
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS922
Her eyes turn yellow.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS923
Her skin becomes blue and her hair morphs into its original color.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS924
SOMEONE gazes at her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS925
Changing back into the blonde teen, SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a heartbroken look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS926
He nods.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS927
She averts her outraged gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS928
Holding up the shot, he gives a firm nod, then stands and heads out of the room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS929
SOMEONE's betrayed eyes narrow as she watches him leave.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS930
Lowering her gaze to the case, she removes its remaining injection, and stares at the lime-green serum in the syringe's barrel.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS931
Now in a study, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit across from each other,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS932
their eyes fixed on a chess game between them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS933
SOMEONE rests his hand on his fist while SOMEONE sips a martini.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS934
SOMEONE sits back.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS935
SOMEONE lifts his gaze to his and frown
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS936
SOMEONE captures one of his friend's chess pieces
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS937
Leaning his elbows on his knees, SOMEONE folds his hand
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS938
SOMEONE stares at the floor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS939
He looks at SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS940
He holds the vengeful man's gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS941
SOMEONE gives a cool look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS942
Now sitting in the lab, SOMEONE taps a syringe,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS943
then holds his thumb over its plunger.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS944
He glances over his shoulder, then looks at the finger-like toes of his right foot.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS945
Steeling himself, the bespectacled young man takes a breath.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS946
Bending down, he injects himself near the ankle and presses down on the plunger.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS947
He removes the syringe and sits up, keeping his eyes fixed on his foot.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS948
The mutated appendage shrinks,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS949
forming the shape of an average human foot.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS950
SOMEONE wiggles his normal-looking toes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS951
Studying his new foot, the young man smiles, teary-eyed.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS952
He glances aside, then looks at his right foot again.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS953
The knuckles expand and the toes elongate.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS954
SOMEONE shakes his head.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS955
As the foot grows long and wide, things protrude from under the skin, which turns blue.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS956
Clutching his leg, SOMEONE grits his teeth.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS957
Things protrude on his mutating hands as well.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS958
As he clutches at his pant leg, it rises, revealing a thick coat of blue hair.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS959
His hand balloons in size and lands on a lamp table.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS960
Growing blue and furry, the giant arm topples the table.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS961
Reflected in a glass sphere, SOMEONE's human face morphs into that of a monster.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS962
Now SOMEONE steps through a door and stops with a slight smile.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS964
He shuts the door behind him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS966
SOMEONE lies in his bed.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS970
He crosses the room. SOMEONE turns on her side and shape-shifts.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS971
SOMEONE faces a sultry woman, slightly older, with wavy blonde hair.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS973
She returns to her regular human form.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS975
Starting at her hand, she shifts into her natural form, with scaly blue skin, slick dark-red hair, and pale-yellow eye
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS977
SOMEONE sits beside her on the bed.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS983
He leans in and kisses her on the lips, then gently raises his hand to her neck.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS984
Now SOMEONE's blue feet step onto a shag carpet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS989
Our view rises up the side of her naked body, revealing the hard rippled blue skin on her thigh, her forearm, and the side of her breast.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS993
She faces SOMEONE, who takes a bottle out of a refrigerator. He faces her, slack-jawed.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS997
She sits at a table.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1009
She leaves the table.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1010
SOMEONE watches her go, then lowers his gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1012
A note on one of the mansion's inner doors reads,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1013
"Gone to the airbase. Bring the crate marked 'X'."
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1014
SOMEONE pulls it down and enters the lab.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1015
SOMEONE and the other mutants follow him inside.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1016
SOMEONE steps past toppled workstations.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1017
SOMEONE glances back. SOMEONE looks on, wearing clothes but in her natural form. SOMEONE opens a crate marked "X." The whole team peers inside.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1019
SOMEONE shuts the lid, darkening our view.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1020
Now a hangar stands across an airfield.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1021
Inside, our view drifts down past the nose of a massive jet
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1022
and finds the five mutants staring up at the shuttle.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1023
Each wearing form-fitting blue-and-yellow jumpsuits, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and Mystique stand side by side.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1024
They share concerned looks.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1025
A broad-shouldered figure with thick forearms approaches.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1026
As he nears the group, SOMEONE lowers his gaze and SOMEONE and SOMEONE trade a look.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1027
The bespectacled mutant steps out of the shadows to reveal his pale-blue face framed by a coat of blue fur.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1028
She touches his cheek.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1029
He nods.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1030
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's throat and snarls.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1032
SOMEONE drops SOMEONE to the floor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1033
Now as the Aral Sea leaves a wide wake, a word appears:
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1035
On either side of the cargo ship, the opposing fleets face each other.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1036
The crafts become blips on a US battleship's radar screen.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1037
An admiral peers through binoculars.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1038
The admiral grimly lowers his binocular
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1039
The officers take off their hats and put on helmets and life vests.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1040
Meanwhile on a Russian battleship, the captain lowers a pair of binoculars, then crosses to a radioman, who shakes his head.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1041
An officer faces him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1044
The captain looks over the bridge
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1046
Battle stations.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1048
On the US-naval bridge, two triple-barreled cannons take aim.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1049
Fleet reports all weapons ready.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1050
The radioman speaks up. From the Kremlin sir, new orders.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1051
As of 10:25 hours, the cargo vessel Aral Sea is hereby ordered to reverse course and return to port in Odessa.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1052
Aral Sea, come in.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1054
The captain watches the cargo ship.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1055
They are not responding. She's not turning around. Aral Sea, you are ordered to turn around. Do not cross the line. On the US bridge.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1056
the admiral peers through his binoculars. Above, the mutants' sleek jet arrives. It soars low over the American fleet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1057
The admiral and his men watch the unique aircraft pass by.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1058
In the cockpit, Beast eyes the ships.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1059
The others ride in the cabin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1060
SOMEONE shifts his gaze. SOMEONE touches his finger to his temple and closes his eye
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1061
He envisions the cargo ship.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1062
Inside, a crew member lies on the floor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1063
SOMEONE kicks him. In the jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1064
The jet soars over the opposing fleets.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1065
SOMEONE touches his temple and closes his eyes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1066
On the Russian ship, an officer suddenly lifts his head.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1067
With wide eyes, he crosses the bridge, pushes a fellow officer out of his way, and presses a button.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1068
A rocket launches from the ship.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1069
The admiral looks on from the USS Independence.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1070
Beast notices the rocket heading their way.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1071
The jet barrel rolls for it to pass over.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1072
The cabin turns upside-down, startling the mutants on board.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1073
In the cockpit, Beast bares his fangs. The passengers brace themselves. As the rocket heads for the cargo ship, SOMEONE notices and disappear
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1074
The ship erupts in a fiery blaze. On the submarine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1075
On the jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1076
On the USS Independence.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1077
On the Russian ship, the captain faces the possessed officer.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1082
Now on the submarine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1083
SOMEONE sits in a leather chair.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1084
He glances at his cohorts.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1085
He puts on his helmet. Now in the jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1086
SOMEONE's nostrils flare.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1088
SOMEONE and SOMEONE take of their headsets. Beast grins. Now in the submarine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1089
SOMEONE steps through a doorway. In the jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1091
Beast works the controls and the jet steadies itself.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1092
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1093
SOMEONE show his hands.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1094
Trapdoors swing open, giving the mutants a view of the passing sea below.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1095
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE. SOMEONE looks on.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1096
SOMEONE jumps out of the jet, opens the winged arms of his suit, then soars off his sound waves high into the air.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1097
The young man brings his arms in at his sides and shoots head first into the sea.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1098
Under water, he peers through the murky deep.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1099
In the jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1100
SOMEONE screams and a sound wave shoots across the ocean floor to the submarine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1101
SOMEONE's dark-haired cohort grabs his headphones. SOMEONE turns. A sound wave travels back to the mutant.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1102
SOMEONE touches his temple.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1103
SOMEONE and SOMEONE face each other.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1104
The jet banks right, heading for the fleet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1105
Now in the mirrored chamber, a doorway opens revealing SOMEONE's office.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1106
The SOMEONE enters and as the passage closes behind him,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1107
it blends in seamlessly with the rest of the wall.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1108
The waist-high pillar rises from the blue-lit floor.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1109
holding several glowing rods.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1110
SOMEONE flips three switches, then grips a lever and slides it upward.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1111
Two rods rise from the pillar and SOMEONE clutches them with both hands. Subtle waves of energy pulsate through the SOMEONE's body.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1112
The needle on a meter indicating reactor-energy state falls.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1113
Now hovering over the sea,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1114
the jet's landing gear lowers.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1115
Perched on one of the wheels, SOMEONE scans the ocean below.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1116
He holds out his hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1117
The admiral peers through his binoculars, watching the hovering jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1118
SOMEONE keeps his palm turned down to the sea.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1119
Peeking through an opening above, SOMEONE notices a change in his partner.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1120
SOMEONE tightens his jaw.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1121
His hand trembles.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1122
Straining, he grimaces. SOMEONE touches his temple.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1123
A calm overtakes SOMEONE's face. He grits his teeth.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1124
Beyond the outstretched fingers of his trembling hand,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1125
the submarine rises from the deep.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1126
The submarine's spinning propellers emerge from the water,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1127
followed by four tail fins.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1128
As the propellers rise, sea water rains down.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1129
SOMEONE shakes from the strain of lifting the vessel.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1130
The entire craft leaves the sea and rises into the air alongside of the jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1131
In the cockpit, Beast notices the submarine on his left.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1132
Through his binoculars, the admiral watches the vessel rise.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1133
He lowers the lenses, his jaw slack.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1134
An American radioman lowers his headset.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1135
The submarine floats past the Russian ship, where several sailors watch from the deck.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1136
The captain looks on.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1137
In the cockpit, Beast pushes a lever, firing the jet's twin engines.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1138
SOMEONE holds his position on the landing gear.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1139
While the jet and the submarine fly side by side, en route to a shoreline miles ahead.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1140
On board the Independence, the admiral and his men peer through windows encasing the bridge.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1141
A hatch on top of the sub opens and SOMEONE's dark-haired cohort climbs out wearing a tailored purple suit.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1142
SOMEONE peers at the SOMEONE, who twirls, engulfing himself in a cyclone, which grows tremendously in size and crosses onto the surface of the sea.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1143
SOMEONE holds his focused gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1144
Beast eyes the twister.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1145
The cyclone swallows the jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1146
On board, SOMEONE and SOMEONE brace themselves.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1147
SOMEONE loses control and the submarine drops to the edge of the sandy shore, landing on its side.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1148
SOMEONE clings to the landing gear.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1149
Tumbling across the beach, the submarine mows down several palm trees, creating a cloud of sand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1150
As it comes to a stop, sand blots out our view.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1151
A wing breaks from the aircraft igniting a fiery blaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1152
SOMEONE eyes the cockpit, where Beast works the controls.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1153
SOMEONE dangles from the jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1154
SOMEONE pulls him into the cabin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1155
The jet crash lands on the beach.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1156
SOMEONE hits the floor and SOMEONE covers him, securing them both to the metal hull as the jet rolls upside-down.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1157
The aircraft tumbles to a stop and lies belly up.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1158
Inside, SOMEONE levitates down with SOMEONE on his chest.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1159
A cloud of black smoke rises from the jet's burning wreckage.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1160
The beached submarine lies nearby.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1161
SOMEONE crosses the cabin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1162
SOMEONE frees SOMEONE from her chair.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1163
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look outside.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1164
Beast, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE step outside and spot SOMEONE's cohorts by the submarine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1165
As Angel takes flight, the dark-haired mutant forms a cyclone in each hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1166
SOMEONE blasts him against the submarine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1167
As SOMEONE attacks Beast, his tail grabs SOMEONE's throat.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1168
They all reappear in the sky. SOMEONE falls.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1169
Beast grabs SOMEONE's arm with his foot, then clutches SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1170
They disappear, then land safely on a ship.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1171
With a flick of his hand, SOMEONE rips off a chunk of the sub, crushing the cyclone-maker. He runs on board.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1173
On the ship's deck, SOMEONE dodges SOMEONE's blast and strangles him with his tail.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1174
Beast tackles SOMEONE and they disappear.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1175
Armed sailors surround SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1176
The admiral and his men peer down from the bridge. SOMEONE crosses the submarine and reaches a control panel.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1177
SOMEONE lowers the lever.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1178
SOMEONE lets go of the glowing rods and his doubled form gradually reverts to normal.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1179
He shifts his troubled gaze. On the ship's deck.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1180
SOMEONE stands up and faces the sailors with his hands up.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1181
He spots Angel fluttering above the ship.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1183
She spits fireballs, knocking him off of his feet, and scorching the disc on his chest.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1184
He removes the burning disc, then looks up.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1185
Flapping her wings, Angel scans the deck.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1186
SOMEONE flies up from the water and sends Angel tumbling off course with a sonic scream.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1187
She regains her balance, then chases the young mutant across the sky.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1188
In the submarine, SOMEONE crosses the office.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1189
Behind him, the wall parts, revealing the secret chamber.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1190
SOMEONE cautiously approaches the doorway.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1191
Meanwhile, Angel chases SOMEONE past a battleship.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1192
Staying on his tail, she spits several fireballs, strafing the sea.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1193
SOMEONE corkscrews over a ship, then glides down near the water.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1194
The American officer looks on.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1195
Meanwhile, SOMEONE steps into the mirrored chamber.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1196
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE in the face, which multiplies momentarily.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1197
The SOMEONE stands upright, unharmed, and SOMEONE gapes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1198
On the deck, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE flying his way and covers his ears.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1199
The young mutant screams and the sailors fall to their knees.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1200
SOMEONE sprints across the deck, leaps, and grabs onto SOMEONE's hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1201
The young mutant carries his friend over the water.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1202
Angel chases after them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1203
Dangling underneath SOMEONE, SOMEONE eyes a ship below.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1204
Angel spits a fireball, which tears through one of SOMEONE's fabric wings.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1205
Losing control, the young mutant descends, dipping SOMEONE's toes into the water.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1206
Reaching the shoreline, the two mutants crash land and tumble across the beach.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1207
In the chamber.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1208
He touches SOMEONE's forehead, sending the mutant crashing into a mirror.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1209
Our view shoots through the cracked glass and across the beach to SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1210
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1211
The SOMEONE flings SOMEONE across the room, shattering another mirror.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1212
Angel flutters over the sea.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1213
SOMEONE kneels at SOMEONE's side.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1214
As the villainess approaches, SOMEONE hurls an energy disc past her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1215
Flailing wildly, Angel falls to the sand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1216
SOMEONE sighs and SOMEONE laughs. In the chamber.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1217
SOMEONE rises from the floor and sends metal beams crashing through the chamber between them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1218
SOMEONE touches a girder SOMEONE holds between them. He calmly backs the mutant against a wall.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1219
On the deck, Beast throws SOMEONE over a railing, but the devilish mutant teleports and tackles him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1220
They both disappear, then land on the beach.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1221
As the point of SOMEONE's tail nears Beast's left eye, SOMEONE steps out of the sub.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1222
SOMEONE rises from Beast and faces his leader. SOMEONE holds his gaze. Beast throws SOMEONE, then strikes his chest, dropping him face down on the sand. He looks at SOMEONE, who shifts into Mystique.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1223
In the reactor chamber.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1224
Pressed against the wall, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE, who grins, baring only his top teeth.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1225
A cable snatches the helmet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1226
SOMEONE freezes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1227
The girder trapping SOMEONE falls and he steps around the SOMEONE to face him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1228
SOMEONE stands frozen, arm outstretched, reaching for his helmet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1229
The helmet descends into SOMEONE's hands.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1230
SOMEONE puts on the helmet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1231
He takes two steps toward SOMEONE and tilts his head
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1232
Gazing into the villains eye
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1233
He walks away.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1234
Across the room from SOMEONE, SOMEONE holds up the Nazi coin, aligning it to the SOMEONE's frozen gaze. Sharp focus switches from the coin's swastika to SOMEONE's plain expression.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1235
The coin floats from his hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1236
SOMEONE keeps a finger to his temple.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1237
The coin drifts toward SOMEONE's frozen form.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1238
In the X-Jet, SOMEONE breathes strenuously. Concentrating.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1239
SOMEONE looks on behind him. Back in the sub.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1240
The coin approaches SOMEONE's forehead.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1241
As SOMEONE expels strained breaths, SOMEONE stays focused on SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1242
The coin pierces SOMEONE's forehead.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1243
SOMEONE screams as the coin disappears into SOMEONE's skull.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1244
A side-on view that tracks the coin's path switches between SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1245
Now the coin emerges from the back of the SOMEONE's head and falls to the floor, splotched with the SOMEONE's blood.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1246
Framed by the metal helmet, SOMEONE's parted lips and glistening eyes show his gaze to be strangely tense and tranquil. In the war room.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1247
On the beach, SOMEONE and SOMEONE step outside.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1248
SOMEONE's body levitates out of the submarine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1249
As the mutants gather around, SOMEONE's body floats above, arms outstretched.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1250
Blood leaks from the wound on his forehead.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1251
SOMEONE lets him drop onto the sand. The mutants look on.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1252
SOMEONE, Angel, and their dark-haired cohort approach SOMEONE's body.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1253
With open arms, SOMEONE levitates down from a blast hole near the top of the submarine.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1254
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step forward as he lands on the beach.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1255
SOMEONE points to the battleships.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1256
SOMEONE parallels SOMEONE's strides.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1257
He touches his temple.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1258
Crossing the beach, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE all face the distant fleet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1259
The triple-barreled cannons aim at the shore.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1260
SOMEONE lowers his fingertips from his temple, breathing heavily.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1261
He looks at SOMEONE and nods. She runs to the crashed X-Jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1262
Onboard, she radios the American ship.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1263
New orders: fire on the beach. The Russian Captain holds.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1264
SOMEONE lowers a headset from her ear, her mouth agape.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1265
On the beach, SOMEONE shifts his gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1266
The American commander peers sternly.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1267
The Russian Captain seconds.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1269
Heavy artillery fires from both fleets.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1270
The mutants watch from the shore.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1271
Dozens of missiles race toward the Cuban coast
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1272
streaking the sky with lines of smoke.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1273
The mutants hold their positions. Our view follows the rockets. SOMEONE eyes them, his mouth slightly agape.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1274
With the mutants behind him, SOMEONE raises a hand and the rockets stop in mid-air within a 100 feet of the shore.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1275
He peers at them, his eyes framed by the helmet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1276
All of the missiles remain suspended in the sky.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1277
Through his binoculars, the admiral spots them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1278
His men gather behind.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1279
The Russian captain watches from his ship.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1280
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand before the hovering missiles. As SOMEONE slowly twists his left hand,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1281
the rockets rotate to face their points of origin.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1282
The rockets complete their rotation.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1283
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1284
SOMEONE thrusts his open hand and the missiles head for the ships.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1285
SOMEONE holds his merciless gaze. The rockets soar toward the American and Russian fleets.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1286
SOMEONE tackles SOMEONE. The rockets fall from the sky,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1287
a few exploding. SOMEONE reaches for SOMEONE's helmet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1288
SOMEONE elbows him and sends the other mutants flying across the beach.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1289
As he holds SOMEONE down, he regains control of the missiles. The American and Russian commanders each watch them returning.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1290
As SOMEONE punches SOMEONE in the face, a few more rockets explode. The remainder skew chaotically.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1291
SOMEONE holds out his hand again, cuing the rockets back on course toward the ships.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1292
Comrades, thank you for your service.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1293
The rockets hone in on the ships. As the American admiral and Russian captain observe resignedly, SOMEONE fires a bullet at SOMEONE's helmet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1294
The shot ricochets, distracting him, and the rockets fall. SOMEONE deflects each bullet fired by her and one strikes SOMEONE in the back.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1295
As the telepath collapses, a stunned SOMEONE lowers her pistol and SOMEONE sadly sees his friend fall.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1296
The wounded mutant hits the sand, belly down.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1297
SOMEONE covers her mouth.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1298
SOMEONE hurries to SOMEONE and holds a hand over the wound.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1299
SOMEONE grimaces as SOMEONE extracts the bullet, which rolls into his palm.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1300
Over the sea, the rockets fall from the sky, some bursting in mid-air,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1301
others landing in the water.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1302
In slow motion, both the Russians and Americans celebrate. SOMEONE runs over to SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1303
The others halt. SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1304
He strangles her with her own dog tags. Gripping the chain, she steps backward.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1305
SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE, who lies in his arms.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1306
He lowers his hand and SOMEONE drops to her knee
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1307
As they hold eye contact, SOMEONE mournfully tightens his jaw.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1308
SOMEONE holds his tender gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1310
he looks at SOMEONE and curtly beckons her to approach.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1311
As SOMEONE kneels over SOMEONE, SOMEONE addresses the other mutant
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1312
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, Beast and SOMEONE look on as one group.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1313
Angel, SOMEONE, and the cyclone master stand in another.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1314
SOMEONE peers in SOMEONE's direction, then reaches out to her.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1315
She limps forward, leaving Beast and the others behind.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1316
As SOMEONE crosses the beach, she glances at SOMEONE and SOMEONE, then sets her gaze on SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1317
She looks to SOMEONE again.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1318
SOMEONE kneels down beside SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1319
SOMEONE observes.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1320
He kisses the back of her hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1321
She kisses his forehead, then looks to SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1322
SOMEONE rises and takes SOMEONE's hand.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1323
While SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and Beast stay put across the beach
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1324
SOMEONE, Angel, and the cyclone master join SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1325
They stand in a line, all holding hand
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1326
Beast averts his gaze.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1327
In a series of fiery poofs, beginning with SOMEONE and ending with SOMEONE
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1328
SOMEONE's faction disappear
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1329
The remaining mutants rush to SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1330
As a bird's-eye view withdraws from the group,
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1331
the sprawling shore soon dwarfs them.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1332
Smoke rises from the crashed submarine and X-Jet.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1333
Black-and-white footage of SOMEONE F. Kennedy appear
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1334
Now outside SOMEONE's mansion.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1335
SOMEONE pushes his wheelchair, then stops and faces him.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1336
She leans down, meeting his gaze squarely.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1337
He kisses her lips, then raises his fingers to his temple.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1338
Fade to white.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1339
In a conference room, SOMEONE addresses a dozen suits.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1340
The room shakes and everyone stands. One man grabs a phone.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1341
As SOMEONE peers out a window, our view descends to SOMEONE's cell.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1342
Clad in white, the blonde mutant rises from her bed and faces a metal door.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1343
The door rips open and SOMEONE shifts into her diamond form.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1344
SOMEONE ambles into the cell.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1345
He wears a red helmet and black cape.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1346
SOMEONE looks to his right, as does SOMEONE.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1347
His four cohorts stand in the doorway.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1348
SOMEONE returns her gaze to her initial visitor, then changes back to her human form.
XMEN_FIRST_CLASS_DVS1349
Our view roves in close to his face framed by the gladiator-like helmet.