She minimizes her word processor program and opens an email inbox.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS26
The woman clicks on a message titled
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS28
She blinks slowly then opens another email with an attached photo of a newborn baby.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS29
It reads "Look who's arrived. Come join us at our home."
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS31
The woman leans forward and studies the baby's face.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS32
Absentmindedly tugging on a lock of hair, she clicks on the Print button.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS33
The computer begins processing the command then stops.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS34
The woman opens her printer and removes a toner cartridge.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS35
She drools spittle onto the cartridge and rubs it in,
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS36
She shakes the cartridge then replaces it.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS37
The printer spits out a barely legible copy of the baby notice.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS38
Later, she sits on her balcony and stares at the notice.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS39
She picks up a nearby cellphone displaying a new message alert and holds it to her ear.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS40
Holding the notice, SOMEONE lunches with a black haired woman.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS41
Back in her apartment, SOMEONE lies on a sofa as reality program plays on the television.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS42
Her white dog sits on the couch at her feet.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS43
Later, inside an Office Depot, two teenage clerks stock shelves as SOMEONE browses printer cartridges.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS44
SOMEONE types on her home computer.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS45
She opens the email of the baby announcement and stares at the infant's photo.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS46
SOMEONE browses through outfits in her closet. Later, in a dimly lit restaurant, SOMEONE wears a cocktail dress as she sits with a brown-haired man.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS47
Nodding her head, SOMEONE smiles.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS48
Later, SOMEONE awakes in bed beside the brown-haired man who sleeps beside her with his arm draped over her stomach.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS49
She glances sideways at the man and slowly slides her right arm free.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS50
SOMEONE raises her head and stares at the birth notice sticking out of her purse on the floor.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS51
She lies backward and stares at the ceiling.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS52
SOMEONE slides out of bed and stands.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS53
She pulls a suitcase out of her closet and tosses some clothes into it.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS54
SOMEONE rummages through dresser drawers and plastic bins then opens a cardboard box.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS55
She takes out a cassette tape titled Mad Love, Buddy.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS56
She unzips a pet carrier and releases her small white dog,
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS57
then places the dog into a hand bag.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS58
Leaving her date asleep in her bed,
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS59
SOMEONE totes her luggage out of her apartment.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS60
Driving a red Mini Cooper, she pulls to a stop, takes out the cassette tape, and inserts it into a dashboard player.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS61
As the sun rises over distant skyscrapers, SOMEONE drives across a bridge out of town.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS72
At a rest stop, SOMEONE walks her dog on a leash.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS73
SOMEONE rewinds the cassette tape.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS74
Written by Diablo Cody, directed by SOMEONE Reitman.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS75
SOMEONE pulls into a Hampton Inn beside a strip mall.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS76
She walks into the lobby, steps up to a blonde-haired desk clerk
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS77
and sets her handbag on the counter.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS78
SOMEONE hands the woman a credit card.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS79
SOMEONE' handbag shakes.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS80
SOMEONE glares at the clerk.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS81
Later, she walks into her hotel room and turns on the light.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS82
She sets down the handbag and lets out Dolce.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS83
She opens her suitcase and drops some clothing onto the floor.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS84
She takes out her laptop computer, places it on a desk, then plugs it into an outlet.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS85
SOMEONE carries an armful of toiletries into the bathroom and drops them onto the counter.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS86
She places her jacket and several dresses onto hangers.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS87
SOMEONE sits on the end of her bed with her hands on her lap.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS88
Dolce licks her fingers and waddles off.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS89
SOMEONE takes out her cellphone and makes a call.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS90
Wearing sweatpants and a hooded sweatshirt, SOMEONE runs across a busy road.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS91
Inside a convenience store, she opens a freezer case
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS92
and peruses containers of ice cream.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS93
Dolce wags his tail as SOMEONE returns to the hotel room eating ice cream straight from the container.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS94
She turns on the television and climbs into bed.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS95
She grunts as Dolce steps across her stomach.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS96
Later, she sits on a sink and holds her cellphone to her ear.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS97
Chewing her bottom lip, SOMEONE stares at her phone.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS98
She takes a dress off a hanger, puts on a coat, then drives in her car.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS99
SOMEONE stares at a Chili's restaurant as she drives past, then at a Staples store.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS100
She stares at a combination KFC, Pizza Hut, and Taco Bell, and shakes her head as she drives past.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS101
SOMEONE parks her car in from of Woody's Village Saloon and walks toward the entrance.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS102
She stops and takes out her phone.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS103
SOMEONE smiles broadly.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS104
At his home, SOMEONE fills several baby bottles and places them into a refrigerator.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS105
SOMEONE smiles as she ends the call and walks into the saloon.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS106
Inside, Christmas lights and neon signs illuminate a short bar and pool table.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS107
SOMEONE sets her purse at the end of the bar and sits beside a short brown-haired man.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS108
A bartender nods and fixes her drink.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS109
He sets it in front of SOMEONE as she checks her phone.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS110
The short man stares at her.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS111
She glances sideways at him then sips her drink.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS112
She sets down her glass and studies her phone and turns to the short man.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS113
Later, several empty glasses line the bar in front of SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS114
as the bartender pours her another shot of whiskey, She downs it in a single gulp.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS116
SOMEONE glances down at a crutch resting against the bar between SOMEONE and herself.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS117
SOMEONE bends his hand then waves dismissively. SOMEONE takes a swig of bottled cider.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS118
SOMEONE motions with one finger. SOMEONE leans close to her.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS119
He nods.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS120
SOMEONE glances toward the door then back at SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS121
They walk into the back parking lot.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS122
SOMEONE gets into the back of a taxi cab.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS123
The next morning, SOMEONE lies face down on her hotel bed still wearing the clothes from the previous night.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS124
She opens a bottle of diet soda and clutches it with both hands as she drinks.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS125
Wearing her sweatshirt and sweatpants, she walks up a side walk.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS126
Sitting on a public bench, she types on her laptop then checks her cellphone.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS127
At a salon, SOMEONE plops into a cushioned recliner.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS128
A pedicurist removes the nail polish from her toes.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS129
SOMEONE soaks her feet in bubbling water.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS130
The pedicurist buffs her nails and rubs lotion over her feet and legs.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS131
She drips oil unto her cuticles and trims them.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS132
SOMEONE peers down at her feet and frowns.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS133
Back at the hotel, she shaves her legs in the bath tub.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS134
Standing in a mirror, she rubs foundation onto her face then smooths it with a make-up brush.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS136
She puts on eye shadow and powders her face with a make-up sponge.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS137
SOMEONE examines herself in the mirror and smiles. Sitting on her bed, she glances at the alarm clock.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS138
5:29 PM.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS139
She stands.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS140
She picks up her purse, and smooths down her skirt. the dog stands on the unmade bed and watches SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS141
SOMEONE pulls into the parking lot of Champion O'Malley's and parks near a side entrance.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS142
She walks into the sports bar and scans the patrons as she slowly makes her way toward the front. SOMEONE sits at a table in the center of the room.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS144
A server sets down a napkin and silverware.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS145
SOMEONE glances at two men drinking beers at the bar, then at two men sitting at a table near the front windows.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS146
She looks down and pulls up the front of her dress.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS147
SOMEONE picks up her phone and types on the keypad.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS148
The screen displays a string of nonsense letters.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS149
She slowly lowers the phone as a man with brown, wavy hair and a sparse beard walks into the bar.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS150
He smiles at her and approaches her table.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS151
SOMEONE stands as SOMEONE hugs her.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS152
SOMEONE jerks his thumb toward the bar.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS153
SOMEONE smiles as SOMEONE steps away from the table.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS154
Her smile gradually fades as she stares at him.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS155
Standing at the bar, SOMEONE raises one finger.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS156
SOMEONE walks up to SOMEONE' table.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS157
SOMEONE glances at the bar.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS158
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE, who glares at him.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS159
SOMEONE waders off.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS160
SOMEONE furrows his brow.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS161
SOMEONE narrows her eyes.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS162
SOMEONE smiles and drops her eyes. Later, they walk outside.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS163
SOMEONE gets into his car.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS164
Smiling, SOMEONE leans toward SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS165
She smiles and tilts her head.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS166
Grinning, she turns away and bites her lower lip.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS167
SOMEONE shuts his door and starts his car.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS168
SOMEONE stares at him as she slowly backs away.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS169
Back in her hotel room, SOMEONE watches a young woman sing on television.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS170
SOMEONE pulls a hair out off the back of her head then sets it down beside several other hairs.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS171
A blond woman eats pizza in the next room as SOMEONE answers his home telephone.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS172
Wearing her sweatshirt and sweatpants SOMEONE walks across a suburban lawn to a brick house
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS173
and presses the front door bell.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS174
SOMEONE's sister opens the door.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS175
SOMEONE stares open-mouthed and then nods.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS176
SOMEONE's sister gestures to the side of the house.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS177
SOMEONE turns and walks off.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS178
SOMEONE's sister frowns after her then shakes her head and shuts the door.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS179
SOMEONE slowly walks toward the garage and peers in through a window.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS180
Inside, SOMEONE wears safety goggles as he uses a blowtorch.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS181
SOMEONE knocks on the window.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS182
SOMEONE looks up and takes off the goggles.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS183
He opens the garage door revealing an elaborate contraption of pipes, hoses, tanks, valves, and buckets.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS184
SOMEONE brings over a flask of whiskey.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS185
SOMEONE chugs the whiskey.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS186
She takes another pull.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS187
He takes back the flask then pour SOMEONE a drink from a bottle.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS188
SOMEONE pours more liquor into her glass.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS189
Tilting back her head, SOMEONE drains her glass.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS190
He refills her glass.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS191
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE as she slowly sips her drink.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS192
She smacks her lips and nods.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS193
SOMEONE slams down her drink.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS194
SOMEONE sniffs a bottle of glue.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS195
She touches a figurine on SOMEONE's desk.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS196
SOMEONE drops the figurine.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS197
SOMEONE drives slowly through a suburban neighborhood then rolls to a stop across the street from a two-story house.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS198
SOMEONE rolls down her window.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS199
In the passenger seat, SOMEONE chews on a cookie.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS200
SOMEONE gazes at the house.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS201
Lights glow behind window blinds.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS202
SOMEONE closes her window again.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS203
Back in her hotel, SOMEONE opens her bathroom door and turns on the light.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS204
She stands on the
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS205
doorway and stares at her own reflection.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS207
A half dozen cars sit in a Macy's parking lot.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS208
With her purse slung over one shoulder,
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS209
SOMEONE shuffles across the lot toward the department store.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS210
Inside, she inspects shirts on hangers.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS211
A brown-haired saleswoman approaches SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS213
The saleswoman stares at SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS214
Later, SOMEONE strides through the young adult section of a bookstore.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS215
She steps up to a dark-haired employee writing on a clipboard.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS216
He points toward a nearby table covered with paperback books.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS217
SOMEONE opens one book and signs the title page.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS218
SOMEONE glares at him.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS219
She taps her name on the bottom of the inside dust jacket.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS220
SOMEONE stares at the stock boy.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS221
As he walks off, she grabs more books from the clearance table.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS222
SOMEONE walks off.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS223
Elsewhere, a salon worker clips and buffs SOMEONE' fingernails.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS224
Standing in a mirror, SOMEONE clips a blonde weave onto the back of her head and blends it in to her own hair with a brush.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS225
Later, she pulls into SOMEONE's driveway.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS226
Sitting on his front steps, SOMEONE assembles a baby sling.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS227
He stands as SOMEONE parks.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS228
Holding a signed book, SOMEONE trots across the lawn.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS229
They hug.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS230
Holding a baby, dark-haired SOMEONE steps outside.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS231
SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS232
SOMEONE smiles and furrows her brow. Inside, SOMEONE rocks her child in a baby seat.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS233
SOMEONE crouches near SOMEONE and the baby on the living room floor.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS234
SOMEONE and the baby stare at each other.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS235
SOMEONE hands a beer to SOMEONE and a bottled water to SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS236
SOMEONE gazes around the room.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS237
SOMEONE taps SOMEONE with her foot.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS238
A chart of cartoon faces expressing various emotions.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS239
SOMEONE furrows her brow.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS240
Later, at Champion O'Malley's SOMEONE stands at the bar.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS241
Tuning an electric guitar, a red-haired woman, turns to the dark-haired bassist.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS242
SOMEONE kicks SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS243
SOMEONE glances towards SOMEONE who adjusts her drum set.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS244
SOMEONE sprinkles salt onto the side of SOMEONE's hand.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS245
They each lick the salt off their own hands then drink the tequila shots.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS246
SOMEONE works at a nearby table.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS247
The red-haired guitarist steps up to the microphone.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS248
SOMEONE turns her back to the stage.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS249
SOMEONE stares at the band open-mouthed.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS250
SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE who smiles and nods his head as he watches the band.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS251
SOMEONE gazes downward, glances at SOMEONE, then watches the band.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS252
She looks across the room.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS253
SOMEONE watches her from the kitchen doorway.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS254
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE then gulps down her drink.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS255
SOMEONE points to SOMEONE's crotch. Furrowing his brow, he nods.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS256
SOMEONE buries her face on SOMEONE's chest.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS257
Sighing, SOMEONE turns away.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS258
SOMEONE looks from the band to SOMEONE then back again.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS259
SOMEONE glares at the band.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS260
SOMEONE bounces in her seat as she plays the drums and sings.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS261
After the show, SOMEONE storms into the back parking lot.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS262
She strides toward SOMEONE who loads the band's equipment into a station wagon.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS263
SOMEONE steps next to SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS264
SOMEONE watch as SOMEONE and SOMEONE kiss.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS265
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE' keys.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS266
The band members watch SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk away.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS267
Later, SOMEONE's jeep pulls into his driveway.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS268
SOMEONE and SOMEONE get out.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS269
As SOMEONE steps toward his house, he stumbles and SOMEONE catches him.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS270
She grasps his wrists.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS271
They both lean forward and kiss.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS272
A short-haired man steps out of the house.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS273
SOMEONE turns and walks inside.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS274
Without facing her, SOMEONE waves and disappears inside.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS275
Later, sitting at a table with SOMEONE at Woody's, SOMEONE gulps down a drink.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS276
A man using a wheelchair shoots pool.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS277
SOMEONE glances over her shoulder at the dark-haired man.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS278
SOMEONE leaves them.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS279
Smiling at one another, they touch glasses then finished their drinks.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS280
Later, SOMEONE drives into the hotel parking lot.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS281
She turns into a parking space and smashes into a lamp post.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS282
The light goes out.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS283
Clothes and papers litter SOMEONE' hotel room floor.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS284
Still dressed, she lies sideways across her bed.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS285
Dolce hops up and climbs over her back.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS286
SOMEONE lifts her head.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS287
Later, she grimaces as she pulls the weave out of her hair.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS288
SOMEONE walks across the parking lot to her car.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS289
She stares at the front SOMEONE then crouches and inspects the damage.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS290
SOMEONE stands and walks off.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS291
Later, in the Kentacohut,
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS292
SOMEONE eats as she types on her laptop.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS293
Two girls chat at the counter.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS294
SOMEONE' phone lights up. She picks it up and checks the caller ID.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS295
Later, SOMEONE carries Dolce as she walks through town.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS296
A black sedan slowly follows her as she turns a corner.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS297
SOMEONE stops beside a brick building.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS298
The car slows to a stop along the curb.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS299
SOMEONE bends forward and peers in to the car.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS300
The driver, a brown-haired woman, stares at SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS301
Later, SOMEONE and her mother drive along a country road.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS302
SOMEONE furrows her brow.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS303
Later, SOMEONE follows her mother, Hedda, into her home.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS304
SOMEONE' gray-haired father, SOMEONE, kisses her.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS305
Later, SOMEONE steps into her old bedroom.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS308
She sits on the narrow bed then gazes toward a wall. She fingers strings of beads hanging from a desk lamp,
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS309
inspects small containers of make-up,
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS310
picks up a cassette tape, and chooses a red hair scrunchie
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS311
from a small container of fabric.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS314
Standing in front of a mirror, She fits the scrunchie around a small bun of hair at the back of her head
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS315
She then gazes at her reflection. She reaches into the top shelf of a closet and pulls out a green sweatshirt.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS316
The name Slade is handwritten beneath the words Mercury Injuns
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS317
and the logo of a Native American.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS318
SOMEONE smells the sweatshirt.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS320
Putting it on, she strolls down a hallway
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS321
She stops to gaze at framed photographs hanging on the wall.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS322
In one photo, a younger SOMEONE stands in her wedding dress with her ex-husband, SOMEONE, as they are about to cut their wedding cake.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS323
Peering closely at the photo, she shakes her head.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS324
SOMEONE joins her father at the kitchen table.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS325
SOMEONE slouches and tugs at the hair at the back of her head.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS326
SOMEONE hands a plate of food to SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS327
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE then sips his drink.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS328
Later, SOMEONE pulls a small red car into SOMEONE's driveway.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS329
Working with his distilling equipment, SOMEONE slips his arm into his crutch then limps toward the driveway.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS330
SOMEONE walks off.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS331
Later, they walk across an athletic field.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS332
SOMEONE sips from a bottle as they walk near woods.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS333
SOMEONE leans against a tree.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS334
They stare at each other.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS335
SOMEONE steps away.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS336
SOMEONE walks off.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS337
Later, SOMEONE stands at a fast food counter as a worker loads her tray with food.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS338
She types in her hotel.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS339
At a beauty salon, a manicurist scrubs black polish from SOMEONE' fingernails then applies clear polish.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS340
She rips hair removal tape from SOMEONE' upper lip.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS341
Wearing a towel around her head, SOMEONE lies with her eyes closed
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS342
as a person sprays steam at her face.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS343
Back in her room, SOMEONE pins up her hair.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS344
She applies lipstick, puts on pearl earrings.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS346
She slips on high heels, then walks to her car.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS347
She gets in and checks herself in the mirror.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS348
She drives off. Later, she strides into a Buy Buy Baby store where she walks through the clothing department.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS349
She passes a rack of items resembling teddy bears then rows of pink dresses.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS351
She stops and grabs a package of plain white burp cloths. Later, she walks toward SOMEONE's house where guests stand in the driveway or walk into the backyard.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS352
Carrying a gift bag, SOMEONE climbs the front steps
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS354
and walks into the crowded house.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS355
She takes off her sunglasses then slowly moves through the living room.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS357
Carrying a plate of food, SOMEONE passes SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS358
SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS359
SOMEONE throws her arms around SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS360
A small boy runs into SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS361
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE through a doorway then up several steps.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS362
She glances over her shoulder.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS363
SOMEONE and the babysitter stare at her from across the room.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS364
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step into the baby's room.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS365
She shuts the door.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS366
She touches his head, then his chest.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS367
She tries to kiss him but SOMEONE pushes away.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS368
SOMEONE holds her hand to her face and stares at SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS369
SOMEONE shakes her head slightly as she stares wide-eyed at SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS370
SOMEONE walks out.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS371
SOMEONE watches him go.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS372
As SOMEONE walks downstairs, SOMEONE steps up with the baby.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS373
SOMEONE watches from the landing as SOMEONE gently cradles his daughter.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS374
SOMEONE pulls at the hair on the back of her head.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS375
SOMEONE leaves with the baby.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS376
SOMEONE steps to a table in the living room and picks up a bottle of Maker's SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS377
She fills half a plastic cup, drinks it down.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS378
She drinks that too.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS379
SOMEONE wipes her mouth on a napkin then grabs another drink and walks outside.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS380
People gather on the front lawn.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS381
SOMEONE strides through the crowd, flinging bits of fruit from her drink.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS382
SOMEONE turns into SOMEONE and spills red punch on her shirt.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS383
SOMEONE covers her face as the garage door opens.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS384
SOMEONE plays a new drum set. Written on the bass drum, Nipple Confusion.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS385
SOMEONE holds up the drumsticks and faces the crowd.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS386
He drops the sticks then hurries toward SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS387
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE and stares at her.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS388
She glances at the other guests, then back at SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS389
SOMEONE walks away.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS390
SOMEONE walks toward her car.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS391
SOMEONE puts his arm around SOMEONE.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS392
In his bedroom, SOMEONE paints a figurine.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS393
SOMEONE walks into his house.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS394
SOMEONE shuts the door then follows her into his bedroom.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS395
Still wearing the stained dress, SOMEONE stares at him.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS396
She hangs her head.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS397
SOMEONE takes off her sweater and dress and drops them on the floor.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS398
Silicon breast enhancers stick to her chest.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS399
SOMEONE nods.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS400
SOMEONE frowns then sets down his crutch and takes off his plain white T-shirt.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS401
He hands the shirt to SOMEONE who hugs it to her chest.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS403
SOMEONE steps forward and wraps his arms around her.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS404
She leans her head against his shoulder.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS405
SOMEONE embraces SOMEONE as he rubs her back.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS406
They sway in one another's arms then slowly shuffle sideways.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS407
SOMEONE lays SOMEONE down on the bed. He lies beside her and stares into her eyes.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS408
SOMEONE reaches down and tugs on his pajama bottoms.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS411
As he slips them off, SOMEONE pushes them down with one foot.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS412
Wearing striped boxer shorts, SOMEONE rolls on top of her.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS413
She wraps her legs around him as they kiss.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS414
Various action figures stand motionless in the dimly lit room.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS415
SOMEONE lies on his back beside SOMEONE who stares at the ceiling.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS416
She turns toward SOMEONE then lays one hand against his face.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS417
SOMEONE smiles and nods at her.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS418
She smiles weakly.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS419
Out in the living room, faint morning light shines in the windows and illuminates an upright piano.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS420
In the bedroom, SOMEONE sleeps beside SOMEONE with one arm draped over her stomach.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS421
She opens her eyes and glances at him then slowly slides out of bed.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS422
Standing with her back to the bed,
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS423
SOMEONE puts on her stained dress and sweater.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS424
She walks upstairs into the kitchen where SOMEONE's sister stands at the sink.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS425
SOMEONE picks up a coffee pot.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS426
SOMEONE fills her mug then her own.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS427
SOMEONE nods.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS428
She stares at SOMEONE's sister then looks away.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS429
SOMEONE cries.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS430
SOMEONE shrugs.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS431
SOMEONE leans backward and tilts her head.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS432
SOMEONE grins.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS433
SOMEONE nods.
YOUNG_ADULT_DVS434
SOMEONE stands and walks toward the door.