Little girl zombies cling to her car as she speeds across an empty lot.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS25
Bumps and turns knock them off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS26
The woman hits a truck and flies through her windshield.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS27
She skids across the road past the words, Rule Number 4, seat belts.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS29
As titles appear, images move in slow motion.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS30
An inmate throws a prison guard off a watchtower past the title.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS35
A fleeing woman spills her strawberry milkshake high into the air.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS36
Zombies accost a man wearing a sandwich board that reads, The End Is Near.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS38
In more super slow motion vignettes, a guy flings away a briefcase full of money
ZOMBIELAND_DVS39
as two of the infected chase him from a burning car.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS41
A bride tackles her groom.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS42
With a crowbar, a man smashes a window that reads, Zombieland.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS43
Law enforcers try to fend off blood-spewing zombies with riot shields.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS44
An infected stripper hunts down some businessmen while tassels flail on her breasts.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS49
A father and son team runs away from their infected competitors during a three-legged race.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS52
A man engulfed in flames pursues a firefighter.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS56
A guy in a white tuxedo fires a barrage from a sub machine gun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS58
A flying zombie drips blood onto a windshield before crashing into it and knocking away the title.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS61
At a gas station.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS62
He reaches for a bathroom door then notices a bloody fingerprint on the handle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS63
A zombie bursts out.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS64
The narrator's shotgun discharges. With toilet paper trailing from his shoe, the infected man chases him toward his car.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS65
A female zombie emerges from behind the pumps.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS66
The narrator shoots her in the chest but she keeps coming.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS67
She barrels through the last letter in the hovering words, Rule Number 1,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS69
Circling back to his car door, the narrator drops his keys.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS70
He ditches them and leads the zombies in another lap around the parking lot.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS71
Rule Number 1, Cardio, blinks on the asphalt.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS72
Reaching his car again, the narrator grabs his keys and notices that the door is already unlocked.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS73
He climbs in and locks it just as the zombies arrive.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS74
Fastening his seat belt, he speeds off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS75
The zombies chase after him but quickly fall far behind.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS76
The rear view mirror shows another one in the back seat.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS77
The car weaves as the narrator fends him off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS78
He crashes into a planter sending the zombie flying out the windshield and into a building.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS79
Words lock together, Rule Number 4, Seat belts.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS80
The zombie reappears spitting out a mouthful of flowers.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS81
As the narrators opens his shotgun's chamber, the infected man grabs at him through the hole in the windshield.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS82
The narrator turns on his wipers to keep him at bay, then finishes reloading and shoots him in the shoulder.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS83
The zombie topples off the car.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS84
Staggering over, the narrator plugs him once more.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS86
Words ping out from his shotgun's smoking barrel, Rule Number 2, Double Tap.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS88
He slides down onto his butt with a small SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS89
The picture fades to black.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS90
Now a suitcase gets wheeled down a highway.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS91
A black Cadillac Escalade speeds around a curve with a snow plow on its front bumper.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS92
The narrator hurries for an abandoned hatchback on the grassy median.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS93
The Escalade's front doors bear the number 3 written it white spray paint.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS94
Its snow plow clips another car as it barrels into the median and speeds past a line of vehicles stopped on the road.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS95
The narrator ducks behind the hatchback.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS96
Pulling around in front of him, the Escalade comes to a stop.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS97
The narrator stands up a motorbike for cover and points his shotgun over the seat.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS98
The Escalade's front door opens and a pair of legs in cowboy boots and jeans steps out,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS99
a long holster strapped to his thigh.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS100
The thick jawed newcomer stares at the narrator through shades.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS101
The shotgun trembles in the young man's hands.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS102
The newcomer removes his shades under the brim of his canvas tarp hat
ZOMBIELAND_DVS103
and tosses them over his shoulder into his car.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS104
As he draws a sawed off shotgun from his holster,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS105
the narrator rises.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS106
The newcomer quickly cocks his weapon.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS107
The two men take aim at each other, the narrator trembling.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS108
The newcomer sneers and cocks his head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS109
The narrator lets go of his shotgun's stock and extends a shaky thumb like a hitchhiker.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS110
The newcomer nods toward his Escalade.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS111
As the narrator wheels his suitcase around to the passenger side,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS112
the thick jawed man kicks over the motorbike.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS113
The narrator climbs into the Escalade's passenger seat then eyes the back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS114
Sitting at the wheel, the newcomer notices.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS115
Check the backseat.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS116
Under the thick jawed man's stern gaze, the narrator nods.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS117
He draws a hunting knife, bumping a liquor bottle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS118
The stranger uncaps the bottle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS119
He fills a shot glass and hands it over.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS120
The young man flings its contents out the window and pretends to drink.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS121
The newcomer swigs from the bottle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS122
He buckles himself in.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS123
The Escalade pulls away.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS124
A passenger jet's wreckage litters the road ahead.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS125
In a flashback, he wields chainsaws.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS126
Now, by a roadside ditch.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS127
SOMEONE passes through a break in the guard rail and peers into the steep ditch. He pauses, facing SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS128
The young man performs squats and knee lifts, working his arms with his shotgun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS129
A rule, Limber Up.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS130
The text mimics his movements.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS131
SOMEONE furrows his brow.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS132
SOMEONE nods. With one last stretch of the neck,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS133
the young man follows him down into the ditch.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS134
The older man readies his gun as they near the abandoned delivery truck.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS135
With a nod from SOMEONE, he kicks the rear door.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS136
As the young man aims his shotgun at it, SOMEONE yanks it open.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS137
Hundreds of double serving packages spill out, all containing pink round snack cakes.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS138
SOMEONE takes one.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS139
SOMEONE stomps on them.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS140
SOMEONE eats one. SOMEONE picks one up then drops it.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS141
As he steps away, SOMEONE swipes another snack cake.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS142
Now outside a rest stop bathroom, SOMEONE practices knife attacks.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS144
with the butt of his gun, SOMEONE whacks the stalls open one by one.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS145
Now perched on a toilet, he tenses.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS146
He grabs his gun. A clown crawls under the door.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS147
It vanishes in a puff of smoke and SOMEONE relaxes.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS148
A flashback.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS149
He spills on himself.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS150
He cleans up at a sink.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS151
He opens up. A gorgeous blonde rushes in, locks the door, and embraces him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS152
Later, SOMEONE pours bright red soda into a mug and offers it to his neighbor.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS153
She gratefully accepts it.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS154
As she drinks, he sits beside her with a resealable plastic bag filled with cereal.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS155
She shakes her head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS156
She sips her drink.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS157
She kisses his cheek and rests her head on his shoulder.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS158
He reaches out but she looks up.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS159
He quickly moves his hand to his hoodie and fidgets with it.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS160
406 nestles into his chest and he gently lays his hand on her back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS161
Fade to black.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS162
Later, SOMEONE wakes to find himself seemingly alone. A zombified 406 lunges close.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS163
She tilts her head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS164
She slobbers vomitus goo.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS165
He backs off of the couch and she leaps after him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS166
406 swipes at him then chases him into the kitchen.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS167
Cornered against the refrigerator, SOMEONE grabs a blender.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS168
The pitcher falls off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS169
406 lunges and he flees. The zombie chases SOMEONE down the hall to his room.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS170
He tries to shut her out but she blocks the door with her foot.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS171
He makes repeated efforts, smashing her ankle until a bone juts out.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS172
She squeezes in and chases him to a bathroom.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS173
As SOMEONE struggles with the door, she flings him to the ground.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS174
He takes the shower curtain with him, yanking it from the rod.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS175
406 pounces on him and he wraps the plastic curtain tightly around her head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS176
Turning, he sits up and slams her against the wall.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS177
The zombie's teeth chomp through the curtain and her tongue slithers out, dripping black slime.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS178
Reaching into a cabinet, SOMEONE hurls cotton balls at her then toilet paper. He sprays her with an aerosol can and frees himself from her grasp.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS179
As she crawls after him, he whacks her with the toilet tank lid.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS180
He rushes from the bathroom, slamming the door behind him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS181
He holds the tank lid ready.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS182
Now the zombie's hands shoots up and twists the bathroom door knob.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS184
The door swings open and 406 pulls herself up.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS185
SOMEONE gapes fearfully as she takes a step closer and convulses.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS186
Her head leans back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS187
She hobbles at him, her broken ankle dragging behind her.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS188
SOMEONE whacks her with the lid.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS189
As her head spins toward us, the scene freezes and Rule Number 2 appears, Double Tap.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS190
She falls. Now cars block a road.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS191
As the guys approach a wrecked car, SOMEONE carefully checks the interior. Later, they push it down the road.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS192
Later, they drive down the cleared lane.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS194
He spots FedEx packages on the side of the road.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS195
Blocking the road, a zombie devours the innards of a corpse.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS196
The zombie snaps a bone in two and slurps out the marrow.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS197
SOMEONE pulls forward, veering slightly to the side.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS198
As he passes the zombie, he bashes her with his door.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS200
Outside a grocery store, SOMEONE takes out a pick ax.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS201
He returns it to a weapon stash.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS202
He considers a ground tiller.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS203
Now they face the entrance.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS204
Loaded with weapons, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE inside.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS205
SOMEONE plays a banjo.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS206
The two gaze down a deserted aisle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS207
An obese zombie trots into view and advances on them.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS208
Wielding the banjo like a club, SOMEONE rushes to meet it.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS209
He bashes the zombie in the face. As it goes down, he swings repeatedly at it, splattering our view with blood.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS210
Another fat zombie arrives and chases SOMEONE toward his companion who now wields a bat.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS211
He slides on his knees.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS212
SOMEONE's bat catches the zombie's face. As the infected man lands at his feet, he smashes its head in.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS213
He tosses his bat aside and they proceed down the aisle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS214
A corpulent zombie blocks their path.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS215
SOMEONE offers his shotgun but SOMEONE takes out pruning shears.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS216
The narrator edges back as he looks on, his chest heaving.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS217
The shears slide across the floor, their blades dripping blood.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS218
A doe-eyed young woman with auburn hair marches out from the back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS219
SOMEONE follows her toward the back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS220
Finding an exit door, SOMEONE props it open with a box.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS221
The rule appears over the door. In the back, SOMEONE finds the young woman comforting a 12 year old girl.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS222
SOMEONE approaches him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS223
SOMEONE brings him over.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS224
He points to the young woman then the girl.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS225
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE and SOMEONE aside.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS226
She eyes his shotgun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS227
He sees a bite on her arm.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS228
Behind SOMEONE, SOMEONE hangs her head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS229
SOMEONE stares at her.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS230
She jerks her head toward SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS231
He gravely steps forward, accepting the weapon.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS232
SOMEONE moves away and Little SOMEONE's shoulders sag.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS233
SOMEONE gently strokes her hair.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS234
SOMEONE bites her lip.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS235
SOMEONE stands with his back to them as SOMEONE takes aim.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS236
SOMEONE lifts the barrel away from the girl.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS237
Stepping forward, SOMEONE lays her hand on the weapon and gives SOMEONE a pleading look.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS238
He grimly relinquishes it.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS240
Turning away, SOMEONE plugs his ears with his fingers.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS242
SOMEONE looks to her little sister who gives a brave nod.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS243
The young woman kisses the girl's forehead.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS244
Stepping back, SOMEONE checks the double barrel chamber and finds it fully loaded.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS246
She aims at her sister who bites her lip in a suppressed sob.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS247
SOMEONE steps forward.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS248
She aims at him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS249
Little SOMEONE takes his sawed off shotgun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS250
Holding the men at gunpoint, the sisters leave. SOMEONE flips them off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS251
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch the sisters drive off in the Escalade.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS252
With the sisters.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS253
SOMEONE flips up her sun visor.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS254
The sisters share a wistful smile.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS255
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE hike through a deserted town.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS256
He throws rock through its windows.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS257
He attacks it with a crowbar.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS258
From the minivan's roof, SOMEONE tosses the crowbar aside,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS259
hops down, and limps over to SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS260
Rule Number 18 appears on the bumper, Limber Up.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS261
The words topple over, landing on the pavement.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS262
He jogs to a yellow Hummer.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS263
SOMEONE follows, toting their bags. The older man slows wearily as he nears the vehicle which has crashed near a house.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS264
The driver's side window shows hands gripping the steering wheel.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS265
SOMEONE cautiously opens the door and finds the hands gnawed off at the forearm.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS266
Using a rag, he tugs at one of the disembodied appendages.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS267
He pries it loose. Facing SOMEONE, he extends the middle finger.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS268
SOMEONE checks the back as SOMEONE hot wires the engine.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS269
Rule Number 31 appears over a large canvas bag, Check the Back Seat.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS271
Opening the sack, the guys find it loaded with guns.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS272
He picks up a rifle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS273
Now SOMEONE stands behind the Hummer, firing an automatic into the air.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS274
As SOMEONE waits patiently in the passenger seat, the rear window shows his companion jumping giddily up and down.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS275
Later, the older man paints a black 3 on the driver's side door.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS276
As the wide bodied vehicle backs away from the house, it takes out a beam supporting an overhang.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS277
The roof collapses as the Hummer speeds off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS278
A flashback shows him serving a terrier mutt pancakes, giving him a bath, and swaying as he cradles the dog in his arms.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS279
Now on a country highway, the Escalade sits parked with its hood up. SOMEONE studies it through binoculars.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS280
He grabs a rifle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS281
He chambers a round.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS282
He swaggers off and SOMEONE steps behind the Hummer's open door.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS283
As SOMEONE nears the Escalade, he finds the word, Help, painted on the side, using the 3 as an HELP.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS285
He scans the surrounding fields and the cylindrical hay bales dotting them.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS287
Aiming the gun inside the vehicle, SOMEONE peeks through the Escalade's open driver's window then yanks open the rear door and checks the back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS288
He finds it empty and bends over to survey the undercarriage.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS289
A flannel shirt hangs from the hood, flapping in the breeze. He unhooks it then tosses it on the steaming engine.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS290
Slinging the rifle over his shoulder with its strap, he cups his hands to his mouth.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS291
Grinning, he waves SOMEONE over.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS292
The Hummer pulls forward and SOMEONE strides back to meet it.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS293
He opens the passenger door and gets in.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS294
SOMEONE nods uneasily.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS295
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE who's gaze darts. SOMEONE frowns.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS296
Little SOMEONE aims her shotgun at him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS297
She shoots out the moon roof.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS298
He hands over his rifle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS299
SOMEONE emerges from behind a hay bale.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS300
SOMEONE waves. Aiming at him, SOMEONE gives a mocking wince.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS301
He unbuckles his seat belt.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS302
As she lowers the gun, he and SOMEONE climb out.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS303
SOMEONE gets behind the wheel and swaps grins with her sister in back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS304
Later, SOMEONE drives. SOMEONE thinks to himself.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS305
She eyeballs him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS306
In a flashback, at a Gas N Gulp, the pasty blonde man from the toilet attack notices SOMEONE outside
ZOMBIELAND_DVS307
crawling around on her hands and knees.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS308
As he heads out of the station, she peeks under her red convertible.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS309
Her tight skirts shows the curves of her toned rear.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS310
She hands him a business card. He grins.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS311
Behind the wheel, SOMEONE gives a disarming smile.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS312
The manager waves and she drives off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS313
As the convertible pulls toward the street, the manager scans the ground by the pump. Later, he uses a phone.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS314
Little SOMEONE finds the ring outside. The girl grins.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS315
He marches out to her.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS316
Now he hands her cash.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS317
Little SOMEONE stares at the ring then hands it over.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS318
She eats a candy bar.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS319
She strolls out, leaving the manager grinning.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS320
Now on a suburban street, Little SOMEONE strides up to the convertible and gets in.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS321
She opens the glove box.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS322
The young con artist pours a handful of rings out of an envelope.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS323
The convertible speeds off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS324
Back the present, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS325
SOMEONE steals his gun back and aims at Little SOMEONE. SOMEONE stops then aims at him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS326
SOMEONE lowers his gun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS327
SOMEONE averts her aim as well, setting her handgun in her lap.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS328
She glares at SOMEONE through the rear view mirror and irritably shakes her head
ZOMBIELAND_DVS329
then grips the wheel and drives off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS330
SOMEONE glares at him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS331
Little SOMEONE gives a wounded look.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS332
SOMEONE thoughtfully arches his brows.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS333
SOMEONE taps her shoulder with the tip of his sawed off shotgun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS335
She looks back at him and he pointedly glances at SOMEONE who sits gaping.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS336
SOMEONE nods.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS337
He bobs his head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS338
He grows thoughtful.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS340
He shifts his stare to the window.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS341
The Hummer speeds past a desolate farm.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS343
As Little SOMEONE and SOMEONE sleep in the back seat,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS344
SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze blankly through the windshield.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS345
SOMEONE glances over her shoulder at her sister.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS346
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE then looks away just as she turns to face him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS347
She notices an abandoned pickup.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS348
She slows to a stop in front of it and lets her hands drop from the wheel.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS349
She offers a weak smile.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS350
SOMEONE glances away and unlatches his seat belt then slowly guides it off his chest.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS351
As he opens the door, SOMEONE uneasily licks her lips then locks eyes with him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS352
SOMEONE shuts the door, remaining seated, and SOMEONE smiles.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS353
He pulls his seat belt back across his chest and fastens it.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS354
SOMEONE takes the wheel and motors off, driving away from the pickup.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS356
Now as the horizon glows dimly, the Hummer moves through a low fog.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS357
SOMEONE reads a billboard.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS358
Later, they pull into native American trading post themed rest stop that a sign labels, The Kemosabe. Lights glow within.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS360
SOMEONE struts up to the porch, munching a snack.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS361
He halts the others.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS362
He eyes the open door.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS364
SOMEONE thinks. The rule appears. Don't be a hero.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS365
SOMEONE taps a bell above the doorway with his sawed off shotgun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS366
Staying out of its line of sight, SOMEONE shoots a zombie as it runs out.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS367
It gets back up. SOMEONE takes it out.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS368
As SOMEONE calmly tugs a rope and enters a building, a piano plummets onto a zombie running after her.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS369
Back at Kemosabe's, SOMEONE smells a bottle of cologne.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS370
Nearby, SOMEONE tries on an embellished felt sombrero.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS371
He waves at her through a mirror and she waves back then doffs the hat.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS372
SOMEONE spritzes his upraised wrist with cologne,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS373
sniffs it, and rubs it on his neck.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS374
As SOMEONE ambles to a postcard rack behind him, SOMEONE sniffs another bottle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS375
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE's gaze to SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS376
He sniffs SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS377
As heads off, SOMEONE sprays him with cologne.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS378
SOMEONE whirls around, fuming. SOMEONE stutters.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS379
SOMEONE punches him. He stumbles.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS380
SOMEONE steps over. Chest heaving, SOMEONE grins and knocks over a vase.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS381
He drops another. SOMEONE slides a mug off of a display.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS382
SOMEONE kicks a figurine. SOMEONE swings her gun like a bat downing a pyramid of rawhide drums.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS383
SOMEONE hurls a statue into a glass counter and Little SOMEONE smashes a snow globe.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS384
SOMEONE shatters a glass shelf.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS385
Wearing an Indian headdress, Little SOMEONE romps as feathers rain down around her.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS386
SOMEONE and SOMEONE toss handfuls of beads at each other and SOMEONE bashes a mannequin. Its arm flies off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS387
SOMEONE and SOMEONE overturn a table of beads as SOMEONE hacks at a cowboy mannequin's neck with an ax.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS388
SOMEONE pitches a stuffed animal at him and he bats it away then smashes the glass over an educational Arizona display.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS389
He and SOMEONE bowl over a shelving unit which topples three more units like dominoes.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS390
Later, SOMEONE muses.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS392
The rule dangles from a chandelier. Later, the Hummer drives away.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS393
SOMEONE drives and Little SOMEONE rides shotgun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS394
SOMEONE drives.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS395
Little SOMEONE drives.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS397
SOMEONE drives.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS399
now Little SOMEONE sleeps on SOMEONE's shoulder. SOMEONE unbuckles his seat belt.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS400
Daytime. They pass the California border.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS401
Later on a highway, the Hummer passes a Welcome to Los Angeles sign.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS402
Cars and rubble lie strewn on the road and skyscrapers dot the horizon.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS403
The four survivors stare soberly at their surroundings, SOMEONE behind the wheel.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS404
SOMEONE sighs at the crammed together buildings. Behind him, SOMEONE's hair blows in the wind.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS405
The thoughtful young man contemplatively cocks his head as they drive through an industrial area.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS406
Later, they pass theaters in Hollywood.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS407
As zombies stagger nearby, they drive up to Gromlin's Chinese Theater. A sign reads, Stop Contagion.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS408
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE hop out, a zombie dressed as SOMEONE runs at them.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS409
They blast two others and SOMEONE grabs a star map.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS410
They get back in.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS411
SOMEONE shuts the door as a group of zombies reach the vehicle. Later on a street lined with palm trees,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS412
the Hummer pulls onto a fenced in drive in front of a sprawling mansion.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS413
Golden initials adorn a security gate.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS414
Later, the companions enter the foyer. Six foot urns bookend the door and a grand staircase leads to a second story.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS415
Crystal chandeliers hang from the ceiling.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS416
Later in a sitting room, a pop art painting shows tiled images of SOMEONE's face in bright candy colors. The survivors enter.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS417
He sneers.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS418
Now in a kitchen, Little SOMEONE opens a nearly empty cupboard.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS419
They split up.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS420
Later, SOMEONE and Little SOMEONE creep down a hallway.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS421
The slink into an anteroom with a baby grand piano and a popcorn machine.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS422
Open doors reveal a home theater.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS423
SOMEONE gapes and the girl grins.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS424
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter a bedroom.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS425
He jumps toward the canopy bed.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS426
The zombie killer flops down and crawls off of it.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS427
In the home theater, a movie plays.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS428
Little SOMEONE nods skeptically.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS429
Now a figure lies on a four column bed.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS430
His pale hand twitches, stroking the furry bedspread
ZOMBIELAND_DVS431
and a stocky man with scraggly hair sits up.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS432
He lowers his feet to the leopard print carpet
ZOMBIELAND_DVS433
and shifts around in his oxford shoes then steps off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS435
In the sitting room, SOMEONE dances.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS436
He plops onto a couch.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS437
As he waves his booted feet in the air, SOMEONE drifts away.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS438
He tugs off his boots.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS439
Now the oxfords make their way down a hall.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS440
The scraggly haired man stiffly shifts one shoulder then turns a corner.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS441
In the sitting room, SOMEONE swings a golf club, practicing her drives.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS442
SOMEONE dances.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS443
A ricocheted ball whacks the back of his shaved head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS445
The zombified SOMEONE staggers in, arms outstretched, mouth bloodied.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS446
He reaches toward SOMEONE. SOMEONE clubs him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS447
SOMEONE mimes fanning away tears.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS448
SOMEONE excitedly punches the air then shakes the movie star's hand.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS449
He kisses his hand.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS450
SOMEONE bows and mouths, "Thank you."
ZOMBIELAND_DVS451
SOMEONE eyes him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS452
He lifts his wig.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS453
Now SOMEONE lights a bowl of marijuana atop a hookah pipe while SOMEONE and SOMEONE each draw in a hose. Smoke rises to a crystal chandelier.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS455
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hurry over, pretending to be Ghostbusters.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS456
SOMEONE wears a full costume. SOMEONE wields a vacuum cleaner.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS457
The electricity fizzles out, surprising them both.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS459
In the home theater, SOMEONE nonchalantly dumps their popcorn bowl.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS460
SOMEONE puts on his scraggly wig and plods ahead like a zombie.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS461
SOMEONE and SOMEONE crack up as SOMEONE enters the home theater.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS462
SOMEONE springs up and shoots SOMEONE in the chest.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS463
SOMEONE collapses into a seat.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS464
SOMEONE gawks. SOMEONE hangs on SOMEONE whose argyle sweater now bares a bloody hole.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS465
SOMEONE touches the wound.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS466
SOMEONE turns his sad wry gaze on SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS467
They nod.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS468
Dying, SOMEONE exhales.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS469
SOMEONE and SOMEONE eye SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS470
Later, they haul SOMEONE outside.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS471
They bump his head on a door frame.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS472
They carry SOMEONE wrapped in a blanket across a balcony,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS473
but drop him before they reach the railing.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS474
Now they give a four gun salute.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS475
SOMEONE stops to reload.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS477
They roll SOMEONE off the mansion balcony.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS478
At night, they play Monopoly by a fancy fireplace.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS479
SOMEONE's face seizes tearfully
ZOMBIELAND_DVS480
then we see him in a sunny kitchen.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS481
He serves a fresh pancake to a towheaded little boy in a high chair.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS482
The tot smiles and points and SOMEONE adds syrup.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS483
As Buck takes a bath, SOMEONE playfully scoops mounds of suds onto the boy's head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS485
Outside by a blossoming tree, he twirls the happy boy in his arms.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS486
Now back with the survivors.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS487
The open wallet contains two cherished snapshots of the bright faced boy.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS488
SOMEONE takes a close look.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS489
SOMEONE pats his arm.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS490
He dabs his tears with real cash from the Monopoly board.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS491
The four survivors sit pensively by the hearth.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS492
Now a porcelain vase explodes.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS493
At the edge of an empty indoor pool, SOMEONE shoots valuables.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS494
Little SOMEONE joins him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS495
She lies on a chaise next to him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS496
As she reaches for a gun, he targets another objet d'art
ZOMBIELAND_DVS497
Little SOMEONE takes aim with a pump action shotgun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS498
Little SOMEONE irritably lets her gun droop.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS499
SOMEONE looks at her.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS501
Little SOMEONE lines up a shot.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS502
A dinner plate explodes. Little SOMEONE grins. SOMEONE returns a rugged nod.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS503
Now gripping a bottle of wine, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE on the sly as he straightens some wall art
ZOMBIELAND_DVS504
and sniffs a knick knack.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS505
She taps the bottle on the door frame,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS506
getting SOMEONE's attention,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS507
then flourishes a hand in front of the unopened bottle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS508
SOMEONE tweaks another trinket then approaches.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS509
She leads the way.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS510
SOMEONE shoots a glance back then follows. Later, he reads a label by candlelight.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS511
SOMEONE swigs from the bottle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS512
ZOMBIELAND_DVS513
He takes another drink.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS514
She sets the wine aside.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS515
She offers her hand.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS516
SOMEONE swigs more wine.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS517
SOMEONE tugs his hand, pulling him to his feet.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS519
Affecting the awkwardness of a middle schooler, SOMEONE plunks her wrists on SOMEONE's shoulders and stands at arm's length from him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS520
He copies, holding her shoulders,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS521
but SOMEONE wryly cocks her head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS522
She sways her shoulders, prompting his hands to her waist,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS523
then smiles through an exhaled laugh.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS525
They sway stiffly then SOMEONE draws him a tiny bit closer.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS526
In reply, he lets his hands move from her hips to the small of her back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS527
Soon they touch tummies and their heads nestle cheek to cheek.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS528
They separate enough to look into each other's eyes.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS529
He nods. Gradually, in tiny starts and stops, their faces come closer and closer together.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS531
SOMEONE caresses his neck and their lips hover less than an inch apart.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS532
SOMEONE leaves them in the awkward aftermath.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS533
They exchange a collegial nod.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS534
She leaves him in the candlelit room.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS536
Cloth lies draped over several high backed chairs.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS537
SOMEONE sleeps under the makeshift fort.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS538
As does SOMEONE in his boxers and t-shirt.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS539
As the yellow Hummer speeds off, SOMEONE and SOMEONE look on.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS540
With the girls.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS541
Now the Hollywood sign shows in the distance as the Hummer follows a boulevard past an old tank and some rubble.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS542
Later, roller coasters and a SOMEONE wheel peak above a lush horizon.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS543
At dusk, the Hummer crosses a vast parking lot.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS544
Both girls smile as they drive forward.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS545
The sun hangs low in the sky
ZOMBIELAND_DVS546
and the silhouettes of the dormant rides loom before them.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS547
Headlights gleaming, the dusty Hummer halts inches before the park's main gate.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS548
SOMEONE smiles at her sister then shifts gears.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS549
The chain locked gate yields easily. Little SOMEONE beams as they pull onto the grounds. Back in SOMEONE's mansion, SOMEONE boxes up some supplies.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS550
SOMEONE holds a surfboard.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS551
He wears a double beer can sipping helmet.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS553
On foot, SOMEONE advances with her gun and a flashlight.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS555
She opens a door labeled with a voltage sign. She checks the room first, eyes a row of utility boxes and swings a lever on each one to its downward position.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS556
The park lights up, section by section.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS557
Outside, Little SOMEONE smiles at the wonderland of mini lights decorating trees, buildings, and fences.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS558
A roller coaster banks low on its tracks.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS559
SOMEONE smiles at her happy sister.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS560
In a nearby town, four scavenging zombies look toward the electrified amusement park.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS561
Bloody ooze pours from a female zombie's mouth.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS563
As they lope off in the direction of the park, other zombies by a broken down semi notice the park too.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS564
Meanwhile, the uninfected girls ride on the rear most seat of a swinging pirate ship with an Egyptian pharaoh head on one end.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS565
Now zombies cross the play land parking lot, but the girls remain oblivious.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS566
By the dozens, the ghoulish cannibals pour through the park gates and climb the fences.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS568
As they swarm over a go-cart track, the girls spot them from the swinging pharaoh ship.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS569
Little SOMEONE's smile evaporates.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS570
The zombies draw closer. Now in SOMEONE's mansion.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS571
SOMEONE moves out.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS572
Now the girls run from a pack of zombies. SOMEONE drops one with a keen shot.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS573
She blows away a second one as they approach the Hummer.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS574
As SOMEONE pegs another, Little SOMEONE barely makes it into the passenger seat.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS575
A crazed zombie slobbers on her window.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS576
SOMEONE climbs safely behind the wheel.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS577
Zombies swarm the Hummer.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS578
The passenger side window shatters. As Little SOMEONE kicks at her attacker, SOMEONE throws the Hummer into drive and speeds off,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS579
leaving several zombies on the ground.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS580
A few still cling to the roof.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS581
Both girls leap from the vehicle which races on with the zombies still aboard.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS582
The girls watch the runaway Hummer plow through a prize booth and nosedive into a lake.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS583
SOMEONE checks on Little SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS584
As they retrieve their guns, more zombies come after them.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS585
SOMEONE fires. Little SOMEONE points nearby.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS586
A multi-story drop tower ride glitters yards across the park.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS587
SOMEONE lays down defensive fire as she and Little SOMEONE head for it.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS588
The older girl unleashes a deadly series of shots.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS589
Back at SOMEONE Murray's, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE who sits astride a customized motorcycle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS590
SOMEONE pats him on the shoulder.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS591
SOMEONE straps on a helmet and hits the kick starter.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS592
As SOMEONE rolls out of SOMEONE's garage, SOMEONE stares solemnly after him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS593
SOMEONE wavers on the chopper, accelerates into the bushes, and falls off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS594
As SOMEONE pushes himself up, SOMEONE pulls an SUV out of the garage.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS595
He rolls down the passenger side window.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS596
Clutching his shotgun and suitcase, SOMEONE climbs in.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS597
Meanwhile, SOMEONE and Little SOMEONE race through the gate of the drop ride.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS598
As SOMEONE fires, blood spurts from the chest of a pursuing zombie.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS599
As Little SOMEONE hurries toward a row of seats at the base of the tower,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS600
SOMEONE presses a button on a nearby control panel.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS601
The two sisters pull the ride's safety harnesses over their shoulders
ZOMBIELAND_DVS602
then blast away several charging zombies.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS603
The seats launch up the tower then gently drift back down.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS604
They stop halfway and launch again.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS605
A crowd of zombies circles the tower base, six bodies deep.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS606
They uselessly grab at the air.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS607
As the ride pauses at the top of the tower, SOMEONE and Little SOMEONE's feet dangle over the growing crowd of zombies below.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS608
As the seats slowly drift back toward the crowd, the crazed zombies reach for the sisters.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS609
SOMEONE fires into the clawing zombie mass. One zombie grabs the metal frame by Little SOMEONE's seat.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS610
As the ride's base shoots into the air, the zombie plummets, striking the tower on his way down.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS611
Blood splatters our view. Little SOMEONE faces her sister.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS612
As the base begins to descend, Little SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare down at the waiting zombies.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS614
Little SOMEONE hastily aims her rifle and fires.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS615
The bullet ricochets off the control box. She fires again and blood spews from a zombie's head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS616
SOMEONE eyes Little SOMEONE who lets out a breath.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS617
Sparks fly from the control box.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS618
The seats stop moving.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS619
The sisters share a relieved grin.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS620
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE pull into the play land parking lot.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS621
With wide eyes, SOMEONE surveys the swarm of zombies. SOMEONE buckles his seat belt.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS622
SOMEONE drives toward the park entrance.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS623
As they speed into the park, a crowd of zombies staggers toward them.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS624
SOMEONE spins the wheel and fires out his window.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS625
The zombies convulse as they fall to the ground.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS626
SOMEONE proudly eyes his smoking gun then reverses the SUV.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS627
As he spins it around, he runs over two zombie bodies.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS628
He breaks, backs over the already crushed bodies, then drives forward over them.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS629
Words appear, Rule Number 2, Double Tap.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS631
Back on the ride, Little SOMEONE points as she spots the SUV. SOMEONE blinks.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS632
She stares disbelievingly.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS633
Little SOMEONE grins.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS634
On the ground, SOMEONE stops the SUV by the lake.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS635
SOMEONE jumps out, his shotgun in hand, and jogs to a railing bordering the water.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS636
He spots the partially submerged yellow Hummer.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS637
He stares desperately.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS638
Behind him, SOMEONE hefts a bag of weapons onto the hood of the SUV.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS639
Atop the ride, the sisters wave.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS640
SOMEONE looks toward the tower.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS641
He smiles then turns to SOMEONE who wears a tactical vest loaded with weapons.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS642
SOMEONE raises portable air horn above his head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS643
He jogs away from SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS644
A swarm of zombies chase after him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS645
From the tower, Little SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch as the zombie crowd below disperses and joins the swarm.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS646
SOMEONE stops running.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS647
He tosses aside the air horn and pulls out a machine gun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS648
As he mows down a group of zombies, SOMEONE watches.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS649
A hoard of zombies approach him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS650
He runs.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS651
Meanwhile, SOMEONE jumps a fence for a ride of swings gliding around in a circle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS652
He grabs a swing and raises his gun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS653
Hanging off the swing by one arm, he shoots the zombies as they approach the fence. SOMEONE glances around frantically as he races from the zombies. He pauses to fire at a group of oncoming attackers.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS654
He kills one then heads toward the entrance of a haunted house.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS655
He loads his shotgun as he races down a cave-like passage. A zombie follows close behind.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS656
A reptilian monster thrusts its head out of the wall,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS657
catching the zombie between its jaws.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS658
SOMEONE shoots twice.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS659
The animatronic monster retracts, taking the zombie with it.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS660
At the drop ride, zombies climb the tower's frame.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS661
SOMEONE fires at the closest zombie and sends her sprawling backwards.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS662
The zombie plummets, splattering blood on the cement.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS663
A zombie in a track suit closes in on the sisters.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS664
SOMEONE shoots as he climbs a staircase to a roller coaster platform.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS665
He shoots a zombie woman in the head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS666
As a roller coaster car pulls up beside him, he jumps in.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS667
The car glides down its track.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS668
SOMEONE fires his shotgun as he passes zombies.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS669
A zombie jumps onto the back of the car.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS670
SOMEONE swivels around and shoots. The zombie falls off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS671
The car jerks around a corner where another zombie waits next to the track.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS672
Blood sprays from the zombie.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS673
At the haunted house, SOMEONE enters a dusty room.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS674
He looks around nervously.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS675
Fake bloody animal carcasses hang from the ceiling.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS676
A ghost pops out of a closet.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS677
SOMEONE recoils. Bobbing his head at the sheet covered prop, he passes the closet and heads into a room resembling a dingy cellar.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS678
A zombie attacks him from behind.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS679
She wrestles him to the floor.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS680
As she claws at him, SOMEONE shoots her in the stomach.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS681
She jerks backwards and he shoots again. She falls on top of him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS682
At the drop ride, Little SOMEONE fires at the advancing zombies.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS683
SOMEONE glances at her sister as the blood covered zombie climbs closer.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS684
Meanwhile, as SOMEONE exits the roller coaster, he shoots an approaching zombie.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS685
He leaps over the counter of a games hut then slides barred metal gates across the windows. As the hoard of zombies rush closer,
ZOMBIELAND_DVS686
SOMEONE knocks game prizes from a shelf and lines it with ammunition clips.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS687
With a gun in each hand, he spreads his arms, shedding the tactical vest.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS688
He aims one gun out each window at his side.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS689
Dozens of zombies close in.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS690
Each of SOMEONE's shots takes out an attacker.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS691
A couple climb onto the roof and SOMEONE shoots them through the ceiling.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS692
One zombie breaks the glass of a back door's small window.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS693
SOMEONE twirls around with both guns. In slow motion, he releases the clips from his guns, turns to the counter behind him, and pounds the handles over new ammo clips.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS694
Meanwhile, SOMEONE races from the haunted house exit with three zombies on his tail.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS695
At the drop ride, SOMEONE frantically kicks the zombie in the track suit clinging to her leg.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS696
SOMEONE fires his guns over his shoulder and behind his back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS697
SOMEONE sprints past a huge swinging ride.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS698
As the ride swings back, it takes out the zombies behind him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS699
SOMEONE hits the zombie in the track suit with the butt of her rifle.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS701
He falls. He flails helplessly as he descends. Meanwhile, dead zombie bodies lie in a pile outside the games hut.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS702
SOMEONE calmly stands inside.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS703
He twirls his guns then kisses one.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS704
SOMEONE sprints toward the drop ride.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS705
He slows as he reaches the tower and stares up at the sisters.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS706
A zombie climbs close to them.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS707
SOMEONE's mouth drops as he thinks to himself.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS708
Trembling, he raises his shotgun at a clown zombie.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS709
He searches for more shells.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS710
He tosses down his empty shotgun.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS711
Rule 17 changes from Don't be a hero to Be a hero.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS712
The clown grins. SOMEONE notices a giant rubber mallet at a strength testing game.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS713
He pushes out a breath as he eyes the clown. It rushes him and SOMEONE sprints to the mallet.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS714
He swings it down into the clown's
ZOMBIELAND_DVS715
gut, taking the zombie down.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS716
SOMEONE raises the mallet once again and smashes the clown's head.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS717
Blood splatters our view.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS718
SOMEONE tosses the mallet away.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS719
Up on the tower, a zombie draws dangerously close to SOMEONE and Little SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS720
SOMEONE hurries to the ride's control box and presses a button.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS721
The zombie grabs SOMEONE's leg.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS722
SOMEONE notices a lever labeled, Emergency Break Release. He lifts it and the seats descend the tower.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS723
The zombie falls off.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS724
As the ride comes to a stop, SOMEONE rushes over and helps the girls out of their seats.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS725
SOMEONE hugs him.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS726
She rests her face on SOMEONE's shoulder.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS727
As he pulls away, she meets his gaze with a smile.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS728
She blinks then leans closer, bringing her lips near his ear.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS729
She draws back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS730
SOMEONE tilts his head, his questioning eyes on hers.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS731
He raises his brow.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS732
He gently brushes SOMEONE's hair out of her face and pushes it back behind her ear.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS733
Cupping the back of her neck with his hand, he pulls her in for a kiss.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS734
As they separate, SOMEONE opens her eyes and gazes at SOMEONE.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS735
He stares back with a dazed look.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS736
He swallows then shifts his attention to Little SOMEONE who rolls her eyes.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS737
SOMEONE and Little SOMEONE exchange a look.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS738
SOMEONE watches from the roof of the games hut.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS739
He smiles.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS740
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE as they walk side by side through the park.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS741
She stops abruptly, her eyes narrowing.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS742
SOMEONE's gaze drifts past a sign for fried Twinkies.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS743
He strolls toward a snack shop.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS744
He enters to find SOMEONE destroying the store.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS745
SOMEONE throws objects at the Twinkie sign.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS746
He hurls a plastic container against the wall.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS747
SOMEONE glares.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS749
SOMEONE fires two shots at a door in the corner.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS750
He glances at SOMEONE and they cautiously advance.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS751
Using the end of his gun, SOMEONE pushes open the ajar door and peers into a dark room.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS752
He turns on the light and jumps back.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS753
Three rats scamper out of the room. SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE finds a box with a Twinkies label and a hole blown out of its side.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS754
SOMEONE reaches through the hole and extracts a fistful of crumbled, blown up Twinkie.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS755
He stares angrily.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS756
He raises a finger.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS757
SOMEONE drops the Twinkie remnants.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS758
SOMEONE turns to the exit.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS759
He rushes outside as SOMEONE drives the SUV away.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS760
As the vehicle stops, SOMEONE stares desperately.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS761
Little SOMEONE tosses SOMEONE a wrapped, intact, Twinkie.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS762
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE head to the SUV, it pulls away then stops.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS763
As they drive off, SOMEONE takes out a zombie.
ZOMBIELAND_DVS764
As the SUV pulls away, our view rises over the sparkling lights of the amusement park.