He enters a store called Smart Tech carrying his front bicycle tire and bag. Wearing a grey Smart Tech polo shirt, SOMEONE nods to a tall woman with short blonde hair.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS14
A busty customer approaches.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS15
At a TV display, a SOMEONE McDonald concert plays on dozens of screens.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS16
Nearby, SOMEONE stands behind a half door and puts on a nametag. A tattooed stock guy, SOMEONE, arrives.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS17
He scratches his head.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS18
SOMEONE pretends to blow out his brains at the TV display.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS19
As SOMEONE steps away, the salesman lurches.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS20
Later, the cocky salesman, SOMEONE, stands with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS21
As SOMEONE leaves, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS22
Outside his apartment, SOMEONE bypassed a pool.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS24
At Smart Tech. Now inside, SOMEONE plays poker with SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS25
He puts down his cards beside a can of Fanta.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS26
The guys stare blankly.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS27
SOMEONE's lips tense as his gaze moves around.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS28
Now on his bike, SOMEONE pedals.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS29
As sunlight slowly brightens the room, SOMEONE lies awake in the same position.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS30
Now, carrying his bike tire, SOMEONE gets stuck in Smart Tech's door.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS31
He angrily yanks it free.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS32
SOMEONE's cautious gaze relaxes as he rounds a merchandise divider.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS33
salesman approaches.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS34
SOMEONE springs after him.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS35
door but it's locked.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS36
He plays video games.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS37
Nighttime at SOMEONE's building. Inside, SOMEONE turns off his bedside light and curls up under his black and white comforter set.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS38
The screen whites out to a flashback. A younger SOMEONE faces a brunette teen.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS39
The girl's braces glint. She licks the steel parts and kneels.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS40
A different girl.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS41
She licks his big toe.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS42
Her mouth engulfs it.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS43
Now with the guys at Smart Tech, SOMEONE wears a butter-colored polo shirt.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS44
Later in a club, young patrons lounge and dance. One woman laps booze from another.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS45
As two other ladies make out, SOMEONE watches with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS46
The longhaired blonde downs a hefty shot.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS47
The party girl wraps her arms around him and kisses him hungrily. Her eager fingers muss his hair, then squeeze his ass. As they separate, SOMEONE smiles goofily.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS48
Party girl pounds two more shots.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS49
SOMEONE follows her to the door. SOMEONE slaps him a low five. Outside, the party girl stumbles
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS50
and SOMEONE buckles up.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS51
SOMEONE puffs into a breathalyzer. The reading comes up 0.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS52
The woman cheeks briefly bulge
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS53
and pukes in his face.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS54
The guys smash a fluorescent light bulb.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS55
leaves the woman with SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS56
She writes on a business card.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS57
She walks off.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS58
Morning, dressed for work, SOMEONE uses tongs to put a waffle on a plate with some bacon. As he opens the fridge, he notices
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS59
Hangs up. Now at Smart Tech, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE in an armchair watching a wall of TVs.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS60
Now they enter in a salon.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS61
SOMEONE exposes his extremely hairy chest.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS62
As SOMEONE lies on a table, the beautician spreads wax above his left nipple.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS63
She presses a three-inch cloth strip onto the wax.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS64
She grabs one end of the cloth.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS65
The beautician applies more wax.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS66
She lays down another cloth.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS67
She readies the cloth on the other side of his chest.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS68
The hairless patches on the
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS69
SOMEONE takes his hand.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS70
a pool on the bare patches.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS71
His hairless patches resemble a face.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS72
In a window, the salesgirl bends over revealing her thong.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS73
They see the hot salesgirl working nearby.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS74
She yawns as she places books on shelves.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS75
SOMEONE slowly approaches her, his mouth slightly agape.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS76
He closes his mouth and stuffs his hands in his pockets. The salesgirl glances at him as she sets down the last of her merchandise.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS77
He eyes SOMEONE who pretends to browse around.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS78
SOMEONE stares at the hot employee.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS79
She leans on a shelf. SOMEONE does the same.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS80
They indicate their employee nametags.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS81
SOMEONE watches excitedly.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS82
SOMEONE rejoins his co-worker.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS83
The swimming pool glimmers outside SOMEONE's apartment. Inside.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS84
in Trish’s home.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS85
SOMEONE answers the door and finds SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS86
SOMEONE plops down and
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS87
SOMEONE disappears into the next room. Slowly leaning back into view, he peers around the corner at the box of porn. Later, he lights nearly a dozen candles of varying sizes and colors.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS88
He eases under the covers and presses a remote control.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS89
SOMEONE fast-forwards. She quickly bounced.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS90
Now he watches Everybody Loves Raymond.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS91
SOMEONE shows a customer a TV displaying close-ups of butterflies.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS92
SOMEONE approaches the stock room.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS93
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sign in at the registration.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS94
SOMEONE slaps on a nametag.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS95
SOMEONE Sips a drink. A woman sits down at his table.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS96
Later, the guys head for the exit.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS97
SOMEONE tosses his drink over his shoulder and hurls away a cigarette. Now SOMEONE walks his bike past SOMEONE's door. Later at work.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS98
Now SOMEONE and a slender woman approach SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS99
SOMEONE wrestles SOMEONE to the ground.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS100
The TVs cut to the SOMEONE's concert.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS101
He approaches a cute young woman.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS102
SOMEONE turns to an old man.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS103
Indian co-worker approach.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS104
Now in a hotel corridor, SOMEONE walks past a maid and knocks on a door.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS105
He opens it and peeks his head inside. Entering the suite, he looks around and steps into an empty sitting area.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS106
SOMEONE faces an open bedroom door.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS107
A tall African American woman steps into view.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS108
Now in the Smart Tech home theater.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS109
SOMEONE watches the Bourne Identity.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS110
Bourne approaches SOMEONE at a desk.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS111
He glances over his shoulder.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS112
A pudgy boy holds a pair of boots.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS113
In the bathroom, SOMEONE sits on the counter and dials his phone. Lifting it to his ear, he swallows hard.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS114
In her kitchen, SOMEONE chops lettuce.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS115
SOMEONE takes a hit of a pipe.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS116
SOMEONE points to a figure.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS117
Inside his empty apartment, SOMEONE answers the door.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS118
She looks around him.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS119
the steakhouse, the chef cooks tableside.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS120
Now outside SOMEONE's house light glows in the windows. Inside SOMEONE and SOMEONE embrace on the bed.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS121
As they kiss, she wraps her legs around him.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS122
He presses his lips against hers.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS123
She enters her bathroom in her black bra and panties. SOMEONE opens the nightstand.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS124
SOMEONE takes out a ceramic dish full of condoms.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS125
He tosses the broken condom.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS127
He rubs a wet condom, then licks his finger. Grimacing he shakes his head.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS128
He throws another condom away.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS129
He blows into another condom. He takes it under the covers and moves it
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS130
SOMEONE spots the condoms.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS131
She covers her face. As SOMEONE pulls the condom of his toe, the teenage boy watches.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS132
SOMEONE eyes him sternly then leaves the room. Now in his apartment
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS133
bathroom he pulls down his shorts and sits
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS134
Now at Smart Tech he stands on the sales floor. SOMEONE approaches with her arms folded.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS135
His eyes widen.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS136
As she eyes him seductively, SOMEONE returns an uneasy stare.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS137
As SOMEONE walks past a couch, she kicks the back. SOMEONE sits up with mussed hair. SOMEONE faces SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS138
He pings a die cast figure.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS139
Nighttime. SOMEONE steps outside his apartment.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS140
Now at a restaurant a waitress serves drinks.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS141
His eyes widen.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS142
out on SOMEONE's couch.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS143
They kiss hungrily.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS144
At the door SOMEONE
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS145
covers a younger girls eyes.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS146
SOMEONE uncovers her own eyes.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS147
SOMEONE lights a cigarette.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS148
At Smart Tech.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS149
SOMEONE storms away.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS150
She stares distantly, then faces SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS151
stares inches from his face.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS152
As she pulls away, SOMEONE's brow lifts slightly.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS153
Now SOMEONE faces a black customer.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS155
In the break room, as the two guys hug SOMEONE rubs SOMEONE's back. Their Indian coworker enters.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS156
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride in one seat on a low two-seater bicycle.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS157
SOMEONE and SOMEONE play with SOMEONE's collectible figures.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS158
She kisses him. They ride a bike.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS159
He watched the couple kiss. She give him his lunch.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS160
Now, outside her house, she she removes her hands on his eyes to reveal a new mountain bike.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS162
SOMEONE rides his new mountain bike down the road. His front tire hits a pothole when he gets launched over the handle
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS163
A smile spreads across SOMEONE's lips.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS164
Now the state puffed marshmallow man sit neatly in its box.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS165
Grimaces behind its plastic casing. The invisible man dog casts a shadow.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS166
SOMEONE takes the last packaged figures of the high shelf and places them in a box
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS167
Later, he lifts an Aqua man figure.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS168
SOMEONE lifts a 12-inch Six Million Dollar Man figure.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS169
He holds the doll's head up and looks through its bionic eye.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS170
He look at the doll gently in his hands.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS171
He places the figure in a bubble.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS172
He pulls into SOMEONE's driveway on his bike.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS174
SOMEONE eyes a softball.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS175
the two piece model open.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS176
Woman faces a group of teenagers and their parents.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS177
He points to a chubby boy.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS178
SOMEONE raises her hand, then lowers it
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS179
Now SOMEONE drives SOMEONE in her mother's car.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS180
Wipers sweep rain of the windshield.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS181
At Smart Tech the cute stock girls wheels a box.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS182
She flashes a big smile as she passes.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS184
At SOMEONE's house.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS185
SOMEONE sits on his lap.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS186
She kisses him. His eyes stay wide open.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS187
He struggles over his boxed toys.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS188
As he leaves, SOMEONE buries her face in her hands outside
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS189
the red light he cuts into the left turn
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS190
intersection cars nearly hit him.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS191
A break with him and SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS192
SOMEONE sets his drink down. SOMEONE flicks his friend in the crotch.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS193
SOMEONE in the groins slaps him and punches his shoulder.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS194
SOMEONE tugs on SOMEONE's ear, then gives a tightlipped nod.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS195
SOMEONE downs two shots, one after the other. Sitting beside him with a beer in his hands, SOMEONE furrows his brow.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS196
Near the dancefloor SOMEONE and Bernadette make out.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS197
As they resume kissing, SOMEONE approaches the bar.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS198
SOMEONE grins at him.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS199
Now SOMEONE cuts open a taped box at her dining table.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS200
SOMEONE hides a smile.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS202
He gapes at his patchy chest. SOMEONE keeps his eyes open.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS203
SOMEONE keeps his eyes open. Her mouth pinches his lower lip and stretches it as she lets her head loll
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS204
She lets her satiny robe drop.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS205
with soaps in her arms and faces SOMEONE.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS206
She lifts a handheld showerhead attachment off its bracket
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS207
spray with her hand then submerge
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS208
SOMEONE plants one foot on the bathtub rim.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS209
With her eyes shut she waves her hands through the suds. SOMEONE stares tensely.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS210
She beams and her eyes open briefly. SOMEONE exhales.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS211
He shakes his head.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS212
his lips and his gaze falters
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS213
He leaves the bathroom.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS214
As SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE clear out, SOMEONE steers into the bathroom, then enters and waves hello.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS215
takes off his shirt. Now SOMEONE
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS216
apartment. He finds SOMEONE at a book
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS217
She holds up pornos.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS218
As SOMEONE rides, SOMEONE runs to him.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS219
He sits up then gets to his feet.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS220
She pulls herself into his arms and they kiss eagerly.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS221
SOMEONE grins at his earnest gaze, laughs a little, and steps into a kiss.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS222
The potbelly custodian resumes pushing the buffer.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS223
Now under luxurious bedding SOMEONE lies on top of SOMEONE as they embrace and kiss. They look into each other’s eyes.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS224
SOMEONE gives him a kiss. As SOMEONE's face hovers over her, he smiles.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS225
He gets under the silky covers.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS226
Fade to black. Words appear one minute later. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie side-by-side
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS227
As SOMEONE stares wide eyed at the ceiling.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS228
SOMEONE runs her fingertips between the straps of her white camisole. As SOMEONE beams.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS229
SOMEONE rolls on top of her.
40_YEAR_OLD_VIRGIN_DVS230
They kiss. Fade to black. Words appear two hours later. Now SOMEONE rests with her hair in a messy pile above her bare shoulders. SOMEONE stares off, transfixed.