SOMEONE the enforcer down and punches him in the face sending him crashing into the water.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS28
As SOMEONE's mother and father help the boys to their feet, a pipe smoking man steps out. He wears a top hat and sunglasses.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS29
As SOMEONE approaches, the pipe smoking man stops him with the butt of his cane.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS30
He grabs the cane revealing its handle as a secret pistol aimed at his chest.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS31
SOMEONE returns to his family.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS32
Grinning, SOMEONE pokes his tongue between his teeth.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS34
Smoke plumes from the chimney of a log cabin.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS35
Inside, writing in his journal.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS36
SOMEONE peeks down from a loft glimpsing his parents asleep in bed.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS37
His candle blows out.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS38
Watching the front door open, he inches back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS39
As the door opens wider.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS40
SOMEONE's shadow spreads across the wall.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS41
SOMEONE ducks down.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS42
As SOMEONE heads inside, the shadow leaves the wall.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS43
Lying on the floor, SOMEONE reaches for the edge of a rug.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS44
He pulls back the rug and peeks through a hole in the floorboards for a partial view of the floor below.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS45
He watches SOMEONE kneel at his mother's bedside.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS46
Her open hand hangs off the edge of the bed, her wrist exposed to the intruder.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS47
SOMEONE looks at his mother's sleeping face.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS48
On returning his attention to her bedside, he finds SOMEONE gaze on him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS52
Her eyes roll back. The veins of her forearm show through her pale skin.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS53
The priest heads off and SOMEONE follows leaving his wife alone in bed.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS54
SOMEONE climbs down from the loft.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS55
He lies down beside his mother, his leather bound journal in hand.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS56
She smiles at him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS57
SOMEONE shows her one of the pages.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS58
His mother stops reading along.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS59
She gazes absently.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS60
The boy's gaze remains fixed on the open journal.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS61
SOMEONE looks at his unresponsive mother.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS62
Now in a snow dusted cemetery, the boy and his father stand at her grave.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS63
SOMEONE lowers his gaze. Now, in a tavern, a tall young man writes in his journal.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS67
SOMEONE slaps the drunk’s back. A pistol falls out of SOMEONE's jacket and onto the floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS68
He glances at the stranger then picks up his weapon and stumbles off.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS69
Gazing thoughtfully, SOMEONE sips his drink.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS70
Now on the dock, SOMEONE hurries after a couple.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS71
In a boat, SOMEONE hides underneath the dock.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS72
SOMEONE spies on the couple as they head off.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS73
SOMEONE leans against a pole watching his superior set on a rowboat with two others. A sign above a warehouse store reads J. SOMEONE Shipping.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS74
As SOMEONE heads inside, SOMEONE climbs up a ladder to the dock.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS75
He reaches into his jacket pocket and takes out his pistol.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS76
As SOMEONE walks unsuspectingly, SOMEONE takes aim at his back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS78
A puff of smoke rises from the misfired gun.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS79
SOMEONE flees.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS80
SOMEONE marches after him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS81
SOMEONE hides in a shed but can't lock the door.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS82
He tears open a packet of gunpowder and dumps it down his gun's barrel.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS83
He readies the hammer.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS84
As he loads a bullet, a shove of the door jostles him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS85
The bullet rolls near the body of a young woman.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS86
SOMEONE kicks open the door and SOMEONE fires the retrieved bullet at pointblank range. The murderer falls to his back his top hat landing several feet across the dock.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS87
Catching his breath, SOMEONE lowers his pistol.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS88
He looks at SOMEONE, the bullet now lodged in the dead man's right eye.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS89
Leaving, he steps over the body and ambles around a corner of the dock.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS90
SOMEONE glances back at SOMEONE who remains flat on his back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS91
He marches on across the dock through a dense fog.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS92
Turning to the river, he chucks his pistol into the water.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS93
He lingers for a moment then continues on.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS94
Glancing back down the dock, he notices SOMEONE body now missing.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS95
As he turns, SOMEONE faces him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS96
As the vampire bares his sharp fangs, SOMEONE falls to his back. SOMEONE lifts the young man overhead then slams his face through the dock. He rips open SOMEONE's shirt, scratching his chest.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS97
SOMEONE stands over them.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS98
He grabs SOMEONE by the hair and flips him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS99
The vampire crashes through the dock then gets thrown up along the warehouse shattering the wall. As he ascends towards a huge full moon above, the vampire disappears. Amid the falling shards of wood, SOMEONE reaches towards SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS100
Now in bed, SOMEONE jolts awake.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS101
Daylight shines in through a window.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS102
The weary young man feels his wounded brow.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS103
Water drips into various pots surrounding the bed.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS104
Sitting up, he notices a bandage on his forearm and another on his bicep.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS105
As he gazes at a wall, portraits of a man and woman come into focus.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS106
Getting out of bed, SOMEONE steps in one of the pots of water.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS107
The young man rises from the bed and braces himself on a mantle.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS108
Weakly clutching his bruised side, he crosses to a desk where he finds his journal.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS109
He opens it then turns his attention to a window.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS110
SOMEONE steps out into a hall and peers towards a doorway.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS111
He heads up a staircase, stopping after only a few steps to peek at an upper floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS112
Hearing the sounds, SOMEONE hurries back down the steps and presses his ear to a door.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS113
He grabs a three-foot candlestick, gathers himself then barges into the next room.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS114
He finds a naked woman straddling SOMEONE in a bathtub.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS115
The naked woman steps out wrapped in a white sheet.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS116
She looks SOMEONE over then continues on down some stairs.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS117
SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE out of his way.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS118
SOMEONE leads him down a staircase.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS119
He gets dressed.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS120
SOMEONE pours himself a drink from a crystal decanter and downs it.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS121
SOMEONE swipes items from his desk, finds sunscreen and puts it on.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS122
SOMEONE hands him a boot.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS123
SOMEONE sucks on a hookah.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS124
Crossing to a front door, SOMEONE puts on sunglasses. SOMEONE blocks the door.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS125
SOMEONE takes off his shades.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS126
Now SOMEONE selects a gun.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS127
He shows a modified rifle.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS128
A broad-barreled rifle.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS129
SOMEONE notices an ax outside.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS130
Now he carries the ax over his shoulder as SOMEONE leads him through the woods.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS131
Wearing his sunglasses, SOMEONE's new mentor stops at a tree and gazes up the towering trunk.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS132
The young man's gaze darkens.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS133
SOMEONE plants his feet staring at the tree trunk.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS134
His powerful swing cuts only a few inches in.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS135
He tries again, but only chips the trunk.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS136
Twisting his whole body, SOMEONE slices through the massive trunk. Woodchips fly from the cut and the tree topples to the ground.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS137
As SOMEONE steps away, SOMEONE lingers thoughtfully.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS138
Now, light pours into a dark room as SOMEONE opens its door.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS139
SOMEONE enters with his ax.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS140
SOMEONE kicks the door shut rendering the room pitch black.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS142
In the light of the now open door, SOMEONE holds the ax while SOMEONE crawls toward the door his face beaten and bloody.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS143
He pauses at the threshold.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS144
He slams the door. Now SOMEONE nimbly twirls the ax. Practicing later, SOMEONE swings the ax in swirling patterns around his tall, lean frame, gaining speed with proficiency. He finishes with a mighty upward swing.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS146
Now balanced on logs, SOMEONE spars with an unarmed SOMEONE. The protégé falls then springs to his feet. Later, SOMEONE throws the ax. SOMEONE catches it and splits a tree trunk. SOMEONE writes in his journal.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS147
At a forge.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS148
SOMEONE pours silver on the ax.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS149
Now in a tavern, they stand at a bar.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS150
A mirror shows SOMEONE a shadow with no one before it.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS151
SOMEONE turns.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS152
SOMEONE starts to go. SOMEONE slams him down on the bar.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS153
Later, he shows a gallery of images.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS154
A cold-eyed man with Regan curls.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS155
An image shows tribal lands.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS156
A map highlights the southern states.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS157
Springfield, 1837.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS158
A man tumbles out of a shop. The keeper comes out and takes his coat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS159
As the shopkeeper storms back in, SOMEONE follows. Finding himself in a well-kept general store, he faces the owner who puts on a smile.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS160
SOMEONE nods pleasantly.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS161
With a polite smile, he goes. SOMEONE turns the thief’s inside out coat back the right way then shakes out the wrinkles. He faces the window thoughtfully.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS162
As SOMEONE reaches his horse, SOMEONE approaches.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS163
At night, SOMEONE writes at a desk.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS164
Now, as SOMEONE stocks high shelves behind the shop counter.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS165
A petite brunette with doll-like features comes in.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS166
She shows a list written on a card.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS167
SOMEONE hops down before her.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS168
She stares up at his angular features.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS169
A well-dressed gentleman with ginger blonde hair enters.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS170
He gives SOMEONE a cool smile.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS171
Douglas scrutinizes the younger man.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS172
Douglas faces him and his condescending smile fades.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS173
SOMEONE stares admiringly at SOMEONE as SOMEONE arrives.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS174
It bears a wax seal. SOMEONE watches SOMEONE as he takes it behind the counter and rips it open. Small, tidy handwriting fills half the compact page.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS175
SOMEONE hands her list to him with a friendly smirk. At dusk.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS176
As Joshua leaves, SOMEONE locks up then throws down his apron and hurries to action. In his room, he slaps down the letter, dons an overcoat and gets his ax.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS177
He unsheathes the silver dagger.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS178
At night, we swoop low over the streets of Springfield passing smoking chimneys as lightning flashes in the distance. At the end of the street, SOMEONE approaches a pharmacy in his long coat and stovepipe hat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS179
Clutching the letter, he peers in through a window.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS180
The young man steps inside and lets the door swing shut behind him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS181
He crosses the floor between two service counters quickening his pace as he nears the back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS182
In the pharmacy workroom, a bespectacled man with sizable sideburns grinds a pestle in a mortar.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS183
As he turns, SOMEONE narrows his eyes. Stibble rests the pestle against the mortar's rim. As SOMEONE reaches in his coat, Stibble bears his fangs. SOMEONE charges, but the vampire throws powder.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS184
The dust clears revealing Stibble's distorted, monstrous features. He knocks SOMEONE back then activates a trapdoor. The vampire hunter plunges through and a rope snare catches him around the ankle.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS185
Nearby, a naked man hanging upside down shows no sign of life. We pull back to find SOMEONE in a room full of victims, each suspended upside down. The young hunter futile reaches for the floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS186
Beside him, blood streams from a dying man into bowls set on the floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS187
His ax lies beside them.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS188
Arriving, Stibble kicks it away and strikes him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS189
He binds SOMEONE's wrists.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS190
As the trapped hunter looks on, the vampire opens a gleaming straight razor, turns it over and touches the blade. SOMEONE resumes his struggle to free himself as Stibble sharpens the blade against the porcelain bowl's ornate rim. Crouching low, the vampire slips the bowl beneath the hunter.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS191
SOMEONE's dagger slips from his belt. He catches it in his feet then slashes the vampire's throat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS192
Contracting his abdomen, he curls upward and cuts through the snare rope. SOMEONE falls to the floor, frees his wrists and retrieves his ax. As Stibble charges, he delivers a mighty upward blow.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS193
Spraying blood soaks half his face. Using his hand, SOMEONE wipes it away with a horrified expression.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS194
Later, in the misty woods, the vampire hunter digs a grave.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS195
Silhouetted against the moonlit mist, SOMEONE puts on his stovepipe hat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS196
Daytime. In the general store, SOMEONE uses a hand mirror as he applies sap to a swollen bruise on his cheek.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS197
SOMEONE bursts in energetically.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS198
He tosses SOMEONE a parcel.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS199
SOMEONE pulls out dress pants.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS200
Wearing a tuxedo with his stovepipe hat, SOMEONE follows SOMEONE into a mansion.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS201
SOMEONE slips away.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS202
From across the room, SOMEONE catches his gaze as she ignores her chattering fiancée.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS203
SOMEONE joins the couple.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS204
Facing SOMEONE, SOMEONE discreetly jerks his head aside.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS205
She turns and scans the room.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS206
Beyond a circle of waltzing couples, SOMEONE sits snacking on nuts.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS207
As SOMEONE approaches, he puts the remainder back in a bowl and dusts his hands off on his pants.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS208
She looks down at him with a sweet, coy smile.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS209
Douglas notices her absence then spots her dancing with SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS210
SOMEONE twirls her. Now at the store, SOMEONE drops a letter before him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS211
In a vault, SOMEONE sneaks up on a banker. As he swings his ax, the man turns and vanishes. He briefly reappears baring his fangs. SOMEONE reaches in his pocket and throws a handful of grain. It falls to the floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS212
He notices a door sliding open and throws another handful.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS213
It hits an invisible mass. The banker reappears just long enough to strike SOMEONE's midsection.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS214
The hunter reaches in his pocket, but finds no more grain.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS215
In the dusty air, he spies a shape approaching and throws his ax. Dodging it, the charging vampire reappears. SOMEONE sidesteps and decapitates him on a vault shelf.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS216
Later, the banker’s head lies upside down in a grave.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS217
SOMEONE buries him amid several other graves. In a smithy, a powerfully build vampire blocks SOMEONE's attack and bends him back over the forge. The hunter stomps on a bellows and the blazing flame sends the vampire reeling back. SOMEONE grabs him and thrusts his head into the fire repeatedly stomping on the bellows. Now on a picnic with SOMEONE, SOMEONE dozes off spilling a cup of tea.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS218
She nods. SOMEONE takes her cup and sets it down then takes her hands in his.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS219
He leans forward, staring up at her earnestly.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS220
SOMEONE turns her head away and presses her lips together suppressing a smile.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS221
She smiles playfully.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS222
With a modest smirk, he gives a dismissive wave.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS223
That night, as SOMEONE trots down a sidewalk, SOMEONE follows clapping the picnic basket lid like a yapping mouth.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS224
The reach a house gate and face each other, sharing a warm smile.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS225
Beaming hopefully, SOMEONE steps closer and rises up on her toes leaning her face toward his.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS226
Considerably taller.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS227
SOMEONE takes a deep breath and makes no move to meet her.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS228
SOMEONE removes his hat, sets it on the ground and steps up on it.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS229
As she leans in, he turns his cheek to her lips.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS230
SOMEONE nods.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS231
Taking a deep breath, she steps down and picks up his hat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS232
She manages a bright smile and heads for the house.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS233
Gazing after her, SOMEONE trips.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS234
From across the street, a one-eyed SOMEONE leers at the tender scene.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS235
Stepping forward, he sees SOMEONE pause at the door to watch her suitor go.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS236
Now in the deep South, a veiled woman rides a horse up a dirt path to a plantation house. Trees dripping with Spanish moss provide a canopy overhead.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS237
Later, she strides into a dining room where SOMEONE sits alone at a table.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS238
She slaps a newspaper down before him and sits.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS239
SOMEONE ignores it. She slides the paper closer and he turns.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS240
Boasting strawberry blonde tresses and sultry features, SOMEONE puffs a pipe.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS241
Frowning, SOMEONE takes up the paper and reads a headline.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS242
Six headless bodies found near Springfield. SOMEONE Stibble Jr among the dead.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS243
Smirking, SOMEONE lifts his brow.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS244
Now in the general store, SOMEONE reads a book. An African-American man steps inside, takes off his hat and shuts the door.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS245
SOMEONE eyes the visitor from his desk
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS246
Noticing a scar on the visitor's cheek, SOMEONE remembers.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS247
He hops over the counter and hugs him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS248
He takes off his apron.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS253
SOMEONE ducks a swipe from the first man then SOMEONE strikes again. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in a jail cell. SOMEONE paces outside the bars.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS254
She reaches through the bars and turns SOMEONE's head.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS255
Daytime. On a street corner, SOMEONE addresses a crowd from a soapbox.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS256
SOMEONE rides up in a carriage.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS257
SOMEONE steps down from his soapbox and the crowd gathers around him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS258
He walks with an older man wearing sunglasses.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS259
SOMEONE opens a carriage door and the man hands him his card.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS260
SOMEONE climbs into his carriage then shakes SOMEONE's hand.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS261
The carriage rides off revealing SOMEONE. He and SOMEONE walk together.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS262
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS263
SOMEONE presents a silver pocket watch with an engraving.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS264
A SOMEONE. Time waits for no man. SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS265
SOMEONE glances at his mentor then heads off.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS266
He turns back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS267
The tall young man hurries away.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS269
Gin Creek. Our view roves toward the shipping warehouse across the dock.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS270
SOMEONE sidles around the exterior of the building, his silver tipped ax in hand.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS271
He stops at a corner.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS272
Returning from a corral, SOMEONE throws down a pitchfork.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS273
He stops and sniffs the air.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS274
Grimacing, he takes of his sunglasses.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS275
SOMEONE attacks.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS276
SOMEONE backs away.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS277
He flees among his frightened horses. An aerial view shows the herd crossing a riverside field. As the vampire runs up ahead, SOMEONE mounts one of the horses.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS278
SOMEONE leaps forward between two horses, grabs onto their necks and hangs between them.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS279
He slams the horses into the ground and they tumble across the dirt obstructing SOMEONE's path. As SOMEONE jumps one of the horses, he falls off his own. He rolls to a stop and stands up to find himself facing the oncoming stampede. A horse brushes past him and he staggers. A second and third knock him around. He spots SOMEONE leaping over the herd.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS280
The vampire tackles him and bares his fangs.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS281
SOMEONE blocks him with the shaft of his ax. They both see a horse charging straight for them.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS282
The stallion knocks SOMEONE off SOMEONE sending him tumbling across the dirt. The vampire rises to his feet. He boldly grabs the front leg of an oncoming horse, flipping the steed on its back. Using the horse like a track and field hammer, he hurls it at his enemy knocking him to the ground. Amid the chaos of the stampede, the horse rises with SOMEONE on its back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS283
The vampire hunter rides on leaning down for his ax as he passes. Up ahead, SOMEONE bounds off the back of two horses and mounts a third. SOMEONE nears his target holding his ax at the ready. SOMEONE glances back over his shoulder.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS284
He ducks the swing of the ax. SOMEONE leans back as SOMEONE throws a roundhouse kick. The vampire grabs the ax and flips SOMEONE on to the back of another horse. As SOMEONE mounts the horse, he sees SOMEONE run off across the backs of the herd. SOMEONE attempts to stand on his horse's back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS286
He rises to his feet then runs after the vampire landing on a new horse's back with every daring step. Through a veil of wafting dust, we glimpse SOMEONE as he looks back and grins.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS287
SOMEONE lunges at him swiping at his legs, but the vampire jumps, flips and lands on a horse behind SOMEONE. He tries to bite SOMEONE's exposed neck, but the vampire hunter blocks the bite with his ax and pushes them off the horse. SOMEONE clings to SOMEONE's boot as the herd runs alongside a bluff. He lets go.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS288
SOMEONE falls off the horse and tumbles down the face of the bluff. Rolling to a stop, he loses his ax. SOMEONE pounces on him and bares his hideous fangs. SOMEONE's spots his weapon and reaches for it, but SOMEONE stomps the handle flipping the ax into the air.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS289
The vampire grabs the ax and nearly splits SOMEONE's face. SOMEONE grabs the shaft, extends it to reveal a hidden trigger, then shoots SOMEONE through his good eye. SOMEONE lands on his back. Standing over him, SOMEONE collapses his modified weapon and readies himself for a final strike.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS290
SOMEONE brings down his ax. Now at night, a man forces a young woman through a narrow alley.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS291
He slams her against a brick wall clutching her throat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS292
Behind the man, SOMEONE steps out from a shadowy recess across the alley.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS293
With a calm, deliberate gaze, he nears the rapist's exposed neck and takes a bite.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS294
As the vampire brings his flailing victim down, the young woman escapes down the alley.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS295
SOMEONE steps out from around a corner and catches his bloodsucking mentor in the act.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS296
SOMEONE meets his gaze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS298
He rises from his victim and holds up his hands.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS299
Cautiously, he approaches SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS300
SOMEONE throws his ax, but SOMEONE catches it.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS301
SOMEONE kicks him down and swing, but SOMEONE grabs the ax once more.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS302
In a flashback, on a tree-lined road, SOMEONE hops out of his carriage and takes a look at its wheel.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS303
As he kisses a woman leaning out of the window, he notices a team of riders approaching.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS304
The dark haired woman sits back and SOMEONE hands her a gun.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS305
He draws a dagger.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS306
As SOMEONE approaches the group, a rider hops down from his horse and disappears. As the others look on, the unshaven man holds his ground awaiting the imminent attack.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS308
The vampire appears and SOMEONE dodges a swipe. He ducks another, then slashes his attacker's masked mouth creating a spectacular spray of gore.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS309
A mildly frustrated SOMEONE dismounts. SOMEONE tries to stab his attacker, but the vampire clutches his wrist. He drops his dagger, catches it with his free hand, then slashes and leg sweeps his foe. He slashes a second attacker's kicking leg, then drives his blade through the vampire's palm and flips him onto his back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS310
SOMEONE nears. SOMEONE attacks, but the seasoned vampire deflects his every strike. He kicks the human in the face. In slow motion, SOMEONE twirls through the air and lands at SOMEONE's feet. The vampire takes off his sunglasses revealing his puffy eyes. SOMEONE kicks out SOMEONE's shin and the vampire almost falls on his dagger. From behind, SOMEONE's love attacks SOMEONE, but two minions seize her. SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE from behind, exposes his neck and sinks his teeth in.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS311
SOMEONE looks up from his trembling victim, his mouth dripping with blood.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS312
He grabs a tuft of SOMEONE's hair and lowers him to his knee.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS314
As SOMEONE crosses to the dark haired woman, a dazed SOMEONE rises to his feet but struggles to maintain his balance. He watches SOMEONE wrap his arms around her.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS315
Sinking his teeth into her neck, he spins her around lifting her off her feet.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS316
SOMEONE's eyes roll back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS317
He watches the attack in a stupor, his jaw hanging slack.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS318
SOMEONE slows his spin to a stop then let's his victim sink to the ground.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS319
Trembling, face down, SOMEONE watches his dead love.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS320
With his boot, SOMEONE rolls her on her back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS321
SOMEONE shakes his head.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS322
Baring his newfound fangs, SOMEONE grabs his dagger and charges the vampire. He goes to strike, but his arm stops mid-stab. With both hands, he swipes at SOMEONE and attempts to stab him in the heart, but an unseen force holds the blade back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS323
SOMEONE lowers his demoralized gaze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS324
SOMEONE leaves him standing alone.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS325
SOMEONE glances back at the riders then goes to his love's side.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS326
He gently turns her face to his own and kisses her on the lips.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS327
Back in the present.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS328
Beside SOMEONE, SOMEONE rises to his feet.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS329
The seated vampire meets his gaze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS330
As SOMEONE walks away, a flash of lightning brightens the alley's walls.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS331
Now through a downpour, the tall, young man crosses a street.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS332
Wearing his top hat and overcoat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS333
He steps onto a curb and crosses a sidewalk heading for the general store.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS334
As he unlocks the front door, someone approaches him from behind.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS335
As SOMEONE looks up from the door, a hooded figure nears.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS336
Pulling his ax from his jacket, he turns to strike.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS337
SOMEONE reaches into his jacket.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS338
SOMEONE watches as he takes a knee and holds up a ring.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS339
Gazing at the ring, she takes a deep breath.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS340
As SOMEONE offers her hand, SOMEONE rises to his feet and puts the ring on her finger.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS341
They share a loving smile then SOMEONE cradles SOMEONE's cheeks.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS342
She rests her hands on his shoulders and they kiss.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS343
The tall, young man lifts his fiancée into his arms.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS345
He carries her off leaving his ax behind.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS346
Now at an intimate wedding ceremony.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS347
Holding hands, SOMEONE and SOMEONE kiss.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS348
Later, the smiling bride and groom clink their glasses and sip champagne.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS349
SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS350
SOMEONE looks on.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS351
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE on the cheek.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS352
He and SOMEONE step aside.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS353
At a dock, SOMEONE runs his gloved hand over the top of a wooden casket.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS354
SOMEONE stands nearby, as do several masked vampires.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS355
SOMEONE opens the casket revealing SOMEONE inside.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS356
He removes a red rose petal from one of the slain vampire's eyes then notices something in his hand.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS357
SOMEONE turns SOMEONE' hand palm up and pries his fingers from SOMEONE's pocket watch.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS358
He slams the casket's lid.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS359
The vampires wait as their brooding leader steps away from the casket.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS360
SOMEONE stops and gazes thoughtfully.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS361
He turns back and ambles over to SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS362
Now a carriage arrives at a building.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS363
SOMEONE rides inside wearing a veil.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS364
SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE with a book.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS365
As he heads off, SOMEONE reads from the book leaning against the wall.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS366
One of the two men steps down beside SOMEONE then clubs him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS367
Now SOMEONE finds SOMEONE in his study.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS368
SOMEONE takes a seat and hands SOMEONE the book.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS369
He finds a flowery invitation inside. SOMEONE quickly gathers his jacket and hat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS370
Now on a boat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS371
They stand on the deck of their humble vessel as it approaches a fleet of steam-powered riverboats crowding a bustling harbor. Pillars of black smoke plume skyward for miles.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS372
New Orleans.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS373
Now, Spanish moss hangs low from the branches of surrounding trees as SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride a modest horse drawn carriage up a narrow path.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS374
On either side, wooden shacks show no sign of inhabitance.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS375
A pot hangs over a stack of firewood.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS376
From inside a shack, a mocha-skinned woman with a head-kerchief wields a rifle as she peers out through a gap in the wood slat wall.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS377
At night, the carriage approaches the plantation house.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS378
The moonlit Spanish moss over their head sways eerily in a breeze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS380
Now, a window reflects burning candles and frames SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they walk up to the house.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS381
Peering in, they find white people waltzing with slaves at a ball.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS382
Among them, SOMEONE recoils from SOMEONE as she holds him tight.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS383
SOMEONE draws his ax.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS384
He hurries away. Inside.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS385
SOMEONE lunges at SOMEONE baring her fangs.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS386
As SOMEONE stares, the vampires attack the slaves. SOMEONE wrenches free, but the shy woman succumbs to a vicious bite. SOMEONE watches pleasurably.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS387
As SOMEONE fight off the attacker, slaves all around him fall victim to the vamps. Two grab SOMEONE. SOMEONE kicks open the door and races in as a few survivors flee.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS388
Seated in a chair, SOMEONE smirks while two of his underlings hold SOMEONE on his knees. One story up, two vampires in a mural turn. They leap from a ledge in front of the painting and claw the wood floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS389
Charging, they disappear. SOMEONE throws his hat at one then strikes him down. He takes down the other in a single strike.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS390
Swinging at a third, SOMEONE drops his ax. He delivers a powerful roundhouse kick as more and more vampires join the fray, a staring SOMEONE backs away from the window. One vampire seizes SOMEONE's ax. The hunter kicks him away and twirls it into an upward swing taking out one vamp after another. Looking on, SOMEONE discreetly works through ropes binding his wrists. An invisible vampire grabs a sword then materializes to attack. SOMEONE disarms him, but three more surround him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS391
As he swings at one, it vanishes. Another swipes his claws. SOMEONE ducks them then embeds his ax in the creature's abdomen.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS392
In slow motion, he wrenches the weapon out sending a splash of blood through the air.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS393
As he finishes the vampire off, SOMEONE frees himself and fights off his captor. SOMEONE kicks him into a pillar splintering its wood. Propelling himself off another pillar, SOMEONE takes out two vamps in a single swing. SOMEONE stalks towards him as he fights a third. SOMEONE beheads his foe and finds SOMEONE in pants, swirling her long skirt like a cape. Slicing through it he finds her gone.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS394
From behind, she kicks him to the floor as SOMEONE throws her a chair. She backflips through the air catches it and lands in the seat on top of SOMEONE. Straddling the chair, she peers down at his face.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS395
She pins his arms beneath her boot.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS396
The high mural becomes an animated depiction of slavery throughout world history.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS397
He crouches beside SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS398
Standing, SOMEONE steps away.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS399
A vamp holds SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS400
SOMEONE struggles.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS401
SOMEONE puts a dagger to SOMEONE's throat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS402
The horse drawn carriage crashes through a window.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS403
SOMEONE fights free as SOMEONE drives in. The carriage skids in blood knocking SOMEONE off of SOMEONE. He grabs his ax.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS404
He and SOMEONE catch up to the carriage and climb on to the back. It loses a wheel as it speeds out, but continues down the dirt path. Later, they run.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS405
They halt in their tracks.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS406
A team of horsemen approach.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS407
The mocha-skinned woman rows a raft.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS408
The three man dash from the riverbank and find the raft waiting for them. Trees hide them as the horsemen ride past with a colony of bats swooping overhead. On the raft, the men and their rescuer duck low.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS409
As the danger passes, SOMEONE stands and takes up the long poled oar.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS410
At dawn, we gaze out over the winding bayou.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS411
Later, the raft arrives at a shore facing a stately brick church.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS412
SOMEONE gets off first and helps the others.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS413
He and SOMEONE pull the raft up on shore then follow the woman with SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS414
A pastor comes out to meet them.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS415
Now as SOMEONE climbs into an attic.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS416
SOMEONE offers a hand to help him up.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS417
Runaway slaves fill the cramped, dusty space.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS418
Many slumber, lie down on unused pews while some curl up on the floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS419
A baby lies in a makeshift cradle.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS420
SOMEONE and SOMEONE go to a shuttered window and peer through while Tubman takes up her rifle.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS421
SOMEONE bumps a bell.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS422
Outside, SOMEONE looks up.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS423
As SOMEONE looks on anxiously, SOMEONE waves the search team on.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS424
He relaxes and faces Speed who sighs.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS425
SOMEONE bounces the baby, soothing it.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS426
Craning her neck, Tubman regards the newcomers with a furrowed brow.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS427
Now in the rain, protesters hold up pro- and anti-slavery signs. SOMEONE works his way through the crowd. Inside, SOMEONE debates Douglas.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS428
Later, SOMEONE stands by as SOMEONE paces the empty chamber.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS429
The men turn. SOMEONE comes in and greets the men with a crisp smile.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS430
SOMEONE shoots a cutting look at SOMEONE who lowers his gaze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS433
SOMEONE twirls his ax.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS434
SOMEONE lays the ax in a chest.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS435
Now, our view spirals from sideways to upright as a door opens and a tall, silhouetted figure strides through.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS436
Clad in a trim long coat and the famous stovepipe hat, SOMEONE marches resolutely towards us. As he draws near, we find him aged and distinguished.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS437
Sporting his trademark presidential beard. Now before the Capitol with its dome under construction.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS438
As a canon fires, words appear: Fort Sumter, 1861. Within the fort, Union and Confederate troops clash in a chaotic battle as smoke fills the air. A bearded Union General leads a charge. Now, the wall of a toy fort topples as a young boy plays in the Oval Office.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS439
As SOMEONE reads a letter, SOMEONE arrives.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS440
The men turn and the boy looks up from his play.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS441
SOMEONE lowers his troubled gaze and SOMEONE steps away.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS442
A gracefully aging SOMEONE approaches the desk with a meal on a tray.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS443
She plants her hands on her hips and her gaze falls on a headline.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS444
20,000 soldiers dead.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS445
SOMEONE shifts his sorrowful gaze and SOMEONE heads out.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS446
The young boy follows his mother.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS447
The child pauses.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS448
Turning around, he returns to his father's desk and kisses his sunken cheek.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS449
The boy goes to his namesake who kisses his cheek.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS450
Beaming shyly, the little boy leaves with a jaunty stride.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS451
SOMEONE gazes after him lovingly as SOMEONE tosses down a paper.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS452
The Emancipation Proclamation lies before him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS453
He signs it. Now before Congress.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS454
Outside the Capitol.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS455
Now in the White House, a maid uses a feather duster on a clock. It's SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS456
Later, she smiles and nods demurely as she passes SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS457
SOMEONE pauses briefly looking over her shoulder at the sultry woman.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS458
SOMEONE slips into a bedroom where SOMEONE wears a Union uniform as he plays with toy soldiers.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS459
She shuts the door.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS460
Coming close, SOMEONE lays down on her stomach.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS461
Props herself on her elbows and chats sweetly with the child.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS462
As he answers her, she glances over her shoulder.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS463
SOMEONE blows a toy horn and they share a mirthful smile.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS464
His hand close to hers, he presents a gleaming toy sword made of silver.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS465
She takes his hand and kisses his wrist. The toy sword drops to the carpet.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS466
Now SOMEONE comes in as SOMEONE lies sick in bed.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS467
Sitting with SOMEONE on the bed, he notices dark, swollen veins branching from a bite on the boy's wrist. SOMEONE's eyes widen and he stands. Watching him, SOMEONE notices his stricken gaze as he looks away.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS468
Stepping away, SOMEONE crosses to a sunlit window.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS469
SOMEONE turns and faces him questioningly.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS470
Staring off, SOMEONE remembers his dying mother writhing as her eyes rolled back in her head.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS471
Now the President wakes in a chair at SOMEONE's bedside.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS472
Stretching, he finds SOMEONE sleeping on the bed cradling their son in her arms.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS473
Moving gingerly, SOMEONE gets to his feet.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS474
His gaze lands on a spot on the carpet.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS475
He drapes his jacket over SOMEONE like a blanket.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS476
Then crouches at his toys. The silver pocket watch gleams among them.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS477
SOMEONE picks it up and opens it revealing SOMEONE's personalized inscription.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS478
He lifts his stunned gaze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS479
Now, SOMEONE steps out onto a balcony on a beautiful day and pauses.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS480
Turning, he finds SOMEONE sitting on the concrete.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS481
His long legs stretched out before him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS482
He slumps dejectedly against a pillar.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS483
SOMEONE crosses to his lifelong friend and drapes his jacket around his shoulders.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS484
Stepping in front of SOMEONE, he crouches and touches his arm.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS485
SOMEONE offers a sympathetic gaze, then straightens and stands over him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS486
The President looks up at him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS487
SOMEONE draws a deep knowing breath and gazes off.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS488
Nighttime. A carriage rides past the mist-enshrouded White House.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS489
In the presidential home, SOMEONE kneels at SOMEONE's bed in prayer.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS490
Before him, the lifeless child wears a dark suit.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS491
His hands clasped demurely.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS492
SOMEONE comes in and sinks to his knees at the other side of the bed.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS493
The President lifts his head staring off as he rubs his thumbs together.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS494
Looking past SOMEONE, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE arriving in the doorway dressed in mourning.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS495
SOMEONE stands. SOMEONE nods wearily.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS496
She beats his chest.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS497
Overwhelmed with sobs, SOMEONE rushes from the room.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS498
SOMEONE starts to go then pauses in the doorway.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS499
SOMEONE's eyes widen and he lowers his remorseful gaze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS500
Now a photographer stands in the middle of a field littered with the bodies of Union soldiers.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS501
In the Oval Office.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS502
Leaving the room, he hands over a telegram order.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS503
On SOMEONE's plantation, we zoom up the path leading to his door.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS504
It opens as he walks out a man with a bearded chin.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS505
A servant brings red beverages.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS506
SOMEONE takes up the goblets.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS507
SOMEONE returns a goblet.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS508
Sipping his drink, SOMEONE spits it out. Splotches of red stain a war map in his hand.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS509
Our view zooms in on a red stain north of Gettysburg which becomes a smoking field beneath an overcast sky. Swooping low, we find Confederate soldiers charging recklessly over the grass as cannon balls touch down all around them.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS510
Union soldiers fire the canons from a high ridge.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS511
As a cannonball touches down with a stories high blast, Confederate soldier march straight towards it. A row of cannon barrels amid smoke and sparks as they fire. In the infantry below, a thin Union soldier clutches a photo of a woman as he stands by the bearded General.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS512
The thin soldier aims a rifle with his brothers-in-arms.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS513
A cannon ball blasts behind the Confederates.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS514
One or two fall, but the rest charge on seemingly unharmed by the bullets. They drop their rifles. The thin soldier faces his General.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS516
A pale Confederate runs on despite a blood spraying chest wound and a bullet through his hand. Another bears his fangs. As the General shoots, the Confederates vanish. A force knocks his head off and his men fall behind him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS517
A Confederate flag topples to the ground.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS518
The General turns and finds the thin soldier spitting up blood beside him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS519
He holds up a shaking hand and a shaft of light shining through a hole in his chest hits his palm.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS520
He sinks to his knees then keels over.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS521
Turning, the General finds every man in his unit sprawled on the ground.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS522
The thin soldier's photograph of his sweetheart flutters down to the grass. The General stares at the departing Confederates.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS523
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE dine at opposite ends of a long table.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS524
SOMEONE's sips her drink and takes up her soupspoon.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS525
SOMEONE turns the silver utensil in his hand.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS526
SOMEONE watches him with wide eyes. The President springs up from his seat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS527
He shows the utensil.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS528
Now, Union soldiers move in and out of wealthy residences bringing out bulging sacks and armloads of silver items. As we peer down through the clouds, we find carts loaded with silver twinkling in the sunlight as they travel through the streets. SOMEONE enters his house and peers out a window through his sunglasses. Now, Speed rides in a carriage with SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS529
SOMEONE eyes the vampire uneasily.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS530
In a factory, SOMEONE watches workers melt the silver.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS531
SOMEONE joins him at a high railing overlooking the work floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS532
The molten silver churns in enormous vats. SOMEONE faces his old friend who looks down with a thoughtful gaze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS533
Now fog drifts over the White House lawn at dusk.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS534
In SOMEONE's room, SOMEONE lies in the small bed in a demure white nightgown.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS535
She keeps her melancholy gaze averted as SOMEONE arrives.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS536
He sits close, his back to her.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS537
SOMEONE's expression softens as she stares towards the windows, one hand tucked behind her head.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS538
She rolls her head to face him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS539
SOMEONE sits up, her long hair hanging loose around her shoulders.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS540
SOMEONE turns over his shoulder to meet her gaze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS541
Wearing a vulnerable frown, she takes a deep breath.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS542
SOMEONE slumps regretfully then puts his arms around her.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS543
The aging couple lies back on the bed in a warm embrace.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS544
SOMEONE fingers SOMEONE's toy sword as SOMEONE cups her hand in his.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS546
SOMEONE hosts her in the dining room.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS547
Now the attic door opens.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS548
Light pours in past SOMEONE as he stands in the doorway staring at the now dust coated chest.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS549
He crosses to it slowly taking out a key.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS550
Unlocking it, he lifts the lid and gazes in.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS551
SOMEONE pensively takes out his specialized ax and finds the silver along the blade untarnished.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS552
Tipping it, he holds it firmly in both hands and regards it nostalgically.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS553
SOMEONE slowly twirls the weapon in both hands.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS554
Gaining confidence, he builds speed until the ax spins in a blur.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS555
It slips from his grasp.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS556
Bracing one hand on the chest, SOMEONE clenches a fist and softly pounds the chest lid.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS557
In a battle tent.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS558
Wearing his broad-brimmed hat, SOMEONE leans forward, his hands on a table.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS559
With SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS560
In Gettysburg, SOMEONE strides to the open flap of his tent where SOMEONE stands post.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS562
SOMEONE slides his pocket watch over a trajectory marked on a map. It becomes a locomotive speeding along a track in the darkness.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS563
Sidling along the engine's outer railing.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS564
SOMEONE reaches the front and wipes off the headlamp.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS565
He climbs back into the engine car where SOMEONE writes in his journal.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS566
Pausing, the President looks up at his old friend.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS567
Heading further into the car, a soot-smeared SOMEONE catches SOMEONE watching him and pauses with a frown.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS568
He shifts his gaze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS569
SOMEONE regards his old friend solemnly. A net of chains rattles over SOMEONE's head as he returns the gaze with a faint smile.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS570
Removing a pair of spectacles, the President takes up his ax and turns away. Now on a narrow path in the woods, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and a few underlings approach on horseback. Facing them, Ms. Tubman stays SOMEONE who draws up her cloaks hood.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS571
Riding ahead, SOMEONE passes Ms. Tubman and looms over SOMEONE on her horse.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS572
She halts close to the First Lady who keeps her face hidden.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS573
SOMEONE draws a long, slim blade and points it at her head.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS575
She pushes her hood back a few inches.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS576
SOMEONE reluctantly obeys.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS577
SOMEONE stares as the vampires ride off from whence they came.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS578
Behind the First Lady, dozens of African-Americans emerge from hiding with sacks and baskets.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS579
They join SOMEONE on the path out of Washington.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS580
Meanwhile, the locomotive races through the darkness.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS581
Stepping into the car behind it, SOMEONE slides its door shut.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS582
Stacks of crates fill both sides of the car.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS583
Stepping past, SOMEONE pauses, raises his ax and turns.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS584
From the engine, SOMEONE leans out a window and spots several vampires leaping onto the freight cars.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS585
He lunges back into the car with a smile. In a freight car, SOMEONE loads his six-shooter with silver rounds.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS586
Pausing, he looks up.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS587
SOMEONE frowns and gets to his feet, readying his gun.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS588
A lantern swings from its post over his head as he steps over the wood plank floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS589
Turning, he raises his weapon.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS590
He moves to a shuttered hatch and slides it open, aiming into the darkness.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS591
SOMEONE slides it shut then turns to face another shuttered hatch. He takes aim and reaches out to open it.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS592
Hands burst through the baseboards and grab his ankles. SOMEONE falls back and the vampire starts to pull him out.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS593
He fires a gun in each hand then scrambles free.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS595
SOMEONE limps to a crate.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS596
As he looks up, a vampire leaps from the shadows. Grabbing his guns, SOMEONE fires taking him down. He puts his back to the wall and aims in either direction. Arms burst through the wood and hug him from behind. The wounded vampire rises, but SOMEONE shoots him through the forehead. His guns fall from his grasp as he struggles against the vampire holding him. He fights his way free then grabs a huge pistol and blows the monster away. The kickback sends SOMEONE to the floor beside the dead vampire. He opens a door behind the monster letting him fall away.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS597
As he slides it shut, countless more vampires leap onto the roof. SOMEONE hobbles to another car.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS599
SOMEONE goes.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS600
Now between two rail cars.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS601
SOMEONE glances at the barrel of his ax.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS602
SOMEONE gives him a bullet then shakes his hand. SOMEONE heads back inside as his friend climbs up to the rail car's roof. Inside, SOMEONE stabs a vampire with a bayonet attached to the butt of his ax. He pulls the weapon out then ducks past another lapping off his head. On the roof, SOMEONE draws two pistols and shoots a vampire. In slow motion, the monster flies past him spraying blood. Another charges and SOMEONE fires. In slow motion, the shot rips through the vampire's shoulder.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS603
Baring his fangs, he lunges at SOMEONE. SOMEONE flings him aside, but loses his balance nearly stepping over the roof's edge.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS604
He regains his footing and hurries on to a vampire turning a hand wheel. Sparks fly from a wheel of the train. SOMEONE's guns misfire. The vampire bares his hideous fangs. SOMEONE lunges pushing the ghoul to the next rail car ahead.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS605
Rising to his knees, he turns the hand wheel, disengaging the brake. Meanwhile, SOMEONE wedges his ax into a ceiling beam and dropkicks a vampire away. He goes to finish his enemy but finds only shards of wood on the floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS606
The vampire jumps on his back. Forced toward an open door, SOMEONE braces himself with his ax. The vampire tries to bite his neck, but he flips his foe out of the rail car decapitating him as he shuts the door. The vampire's head lies at his feet. SOMEONE boots it out. On the roof, still turning the hand wheel, SOMEONE watches his enemy rise to his feet.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS607
SOMEONE turns his head.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS608
The vampire falls aside revealing SOMEONE standing halfway through a hatch, his modified ax in hand. SOMEONE spots a vampire climbing on to the roof. He grabs his partner's weapon and attacks the new arrival knocking the monster over the edge. He tosses the ax back to SOMEONE who chops into another. With SOMEONE's blade stuck in his fallen foe, a vampire attacks with kicks and punches. As SOMEONE fends off the attacker, SOMEONE lifts his ax, twirls it, releasing a spray of blood, then slashes off the vampire's head. In the same swing, he strikes another vampire's midsection. He massacres another, slashing his face several times, then passes the ax to SOMEONE. SOMEONE takes out two vampires then twirls the ax behind his back to SOMEONE who spins the versatile weapon and strikes another vampire with its butt. Through a veil of wind-swept steam, SOMEONE vanquishes yet another vampire. He brings his ax down once more.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS609
The steam dissipates to reveal SOMEONE clutching the ax handle. He kicks SOMEONE, sending the President back. SOMEONE lands between the railcars in a tangle of chains. SOMEONE breaks the ax-handle over his knee. As SOMEONE climbs back onto the roof, SOMEONE hurls a knife.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS610
The knife's tip nears SOMEONE's face, but the calm vampire tilts his head and dodges the blade. SOMEONE charges SOMEONE, but gets knocked off his feet.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS611
As he slides head first over the edge, SOMEONE grabs his ankle.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS612
Revolvers fall from the dangling man's pockets. As the train speeds alongside a wall, SOMEONE nearly crashes into some jutting rocks.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS613
SOMEONE clutches SOMEONE's collar.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS614
SOMEONE sinks his teeth into flesh, but finds himself biting SOMEONE's arm.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS615
He kicks off the passing rock wall and lands facing his rival. As SOMEONE ducks a punch, the pair gets jostled atop the last railcar. Meanwhile, SOMEONE exhales a puff of thick smoke.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS616
With a match, she lights a rope sending flames up a beam.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS617
As she marches off, a massive fire consumes the entire support structure of a bridge. SOMEONE catches SOMEONE's arm then flips him. Grabs his leg and slams him through the roof. With an avalanche of broken wood, the vampires crash land on the floor of the railcar. SOMEONE rises to his feet and slams SOMEONE's face through the top of a wooden crate.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS618
SOMEONE lifts the laughing vampire from the box then shoves him aside and peeks in the hole himself.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS619
He pulls out a common rock.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS620
Then looks up from the stone with a knowing gaze.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS621
He tosses the rock and crosses to another crate. Inspecting the cargo, he finds more rocks in place of the silver.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS622
SOMEONE angrily paces away. He kicks open another crate, spilling rocks on the floor.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS623
SOMEONE boots SOMEONE back into a corner. The evil vampire glares.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS624
As the train nears the burning bridge, SOMEONE eyes the blaze from the locomotive. He pulls back a lever, uses a piece of wood to keep it in place then leaves the controls. He enters the first railcar and staggers past the dummy cargo.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS625
Meanwhile, SOMEONE helps SOMEONE onto the roof. They rise to their feet and spot the burning bridge up ahead. They start for the locomotive but stop short.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS626
They turn back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS627
They run back across the rooftops.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS628
Making his way through the railcars, SOMEONE finds a floor strewn with broken wood. He spots SOMEONE unconscious on his back, then looks up through the open ceiling.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS629
Turning around, he finds himself face to face with SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS630
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's throat.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS631
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive to see SOMEONE bite into SOMEONE's neck.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS632
The vampire looks up at them. Now, as the train passes over the burning bridge, the track splits and the last railcar breaks loose from the train. Left behind, the railcar teeters over a ledge sending SOMEONE and SOMEONE sliding down its roof. About to fall into the blaze below, they daringly leap across the divide and land on the next rail car's roof.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS633
As what's left of the train races onward, the burning bridge collapses in its wake. Jostling inside a railcar, SOMEONE braces himself and SOMEONE rises to his knees. Their railcar breaks free from the train crashing into the support structure below the track.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS634
SOMEONE leaves the downed railcar. Emerging from thick smoke, he crosses the support structure and kicks out a beam.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS635
The track under the last railcar gives out and the railcar flips forward forcing SOMEONE and SOMEONE to run on to the next. SOMEONE kicks out another support beam. SOMEONE and SOMEONE fall to the structure under the track then hurry along its beams.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS636
SOMEONE looks back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS637
SOMEONE marches towards them.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS638
He vanishes. SOMEONE slings the silver pocket watch's chain around his fingers.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS639
He drives his fist through the vampire's chest then pulls it out awash with blood. His mouth agape, SOMEONE falls flat on his back.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS640
SOMEONE and SOMEONE notice the track collapsing above them. Each clings to a pillar as the locomotive lands on the lower level. They jump into the open trailer of the locomotive's coal car. As the remaining bridge buckles, the locomotive struggles to climb the increasingly inclined track. SOMEONE peeks over the side glimpsing the burning structure underneath. He and SOMEONE make their way across the engine. The locomotive’s wheels spin kicking up sparks. Before the engine reaches the end, the bridge underneath it splits from the final portion of the track. SOMEONE and SOMEONE brace themselves, clinging to the engine. More sparks fly as the train begins to slide backward. Just before it slips off the edge, the locomotive starts to climb the angled track.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS643
A massive black cloud of smoke rises from the abyss and blots out our view of the play.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS645
Drawing back, we find SOMEONE lying on the twisted end of the track.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS646
SOMEONE hobbles over to him.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS647
He reaches out and gives him a hand.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS648
The President helps his mentor to his feet, then they both remain hunched over, catching their breath.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS649
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look at SOMEONE.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS650
In the daytime, at a bustling military camp, SOMEONE opens a box filled with silver blades.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS651
She joins a few soldiers at another.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS654
Our view raises from their tent, ascending a flagpole for a glimpse of the entire camp as runaway slaves arm the Union soldiers with the silver-outfitted weaponry. SOMEONE walks through the camp.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS655
Clutching her left arm and breathing heavily, she notices a crate of garlic.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS656
Chatting with the commander, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE peeking around a tent.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS657
She grabs a nearby rifle and heads after the vampire.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS658
SOMEONE comes out of hiding and faces her squarely standing about ten yards away.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS659
SOMEONE rips a silver chain with SOMEONE's miniature sword from her neck.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS661
As the vampire charges, SOMEONE drops the chain down the barrel of her gun. She takes aim at her fanged assailant.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS663
She shoots SOMEONE and the vampire lands on her back, the silver sword dangling from a hole in her head. Now, a soldier loads a silver ball into a cannon.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS664
A Union infantry fires on a Confederate blitz, their bullets tearing through the vampires bodies. The infantry commander shout, "Charge!" and his men engage the enemy with silver bayonets.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS665
Amid the chaos of battle, a soldier stabs the top of a vampire's head, then pulls his blade out and runs on. A line of cannons fire and a number of explosions erupt across the battlefield. One rips a vampire apart.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS680
As the carriage fades away, the finished Washington monument appears in the distance. Marine One descends to the White House lawn.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS681
Our view draws back from the screen of a smartphone as a live news report shows the helicopter touching down.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS682
Sitting at a bar, a man thumbs a text message on the device.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS684
He downs a shot then gestures to a bartender.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS685
Beside him, SOMEONE takes off a pair of dark sunglasses.
ABRAHAM_LINCOLN_VAMPIRE_HUNTER_DVS687
He slaps them on the back and a pistol falls on the floor.