Later, they drive past a forest.
CHRONICLE_DVS21
The young man grins.
CHRONICLE_DVS23
They pull into a bustling high school parking lot.
CHRONICLE_DVS24
Now with the car parked, the camera stays on the driver.
CHRONICLE_DVS25
Now in a hallway.
CHRONICLE_DVS26
Several students walk by.
CHRONICLE_DVS27
A jokester waves his arms in front of SOMEONE's camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS28
Campaign posters show a smiling young man. A girl brings SOMEONE one.
CHRONICLE_DVS30
A cheerleading squad practices nearby waving green and white pom-poms.
CHRONICLE_DVS31
SOMEONE sets up his camera on a bench behind him.
CHRONICLE_DVS32
Watching the girls, he grabs a bag of chips.
CHRONICLE_DVS33
Beyond him, a circle of field hockey players stretch out on the 50-yard line.
CHRONICLE_DVS34
The teenager glances back at his camera and eats another chip.
CHRONICLE_DVS35
Now, a dark-haired cheerleader marches over and faces him from a lower railing.
CHRONICLE_DVS37
A shaggy-haired guy grabs the camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS38
A dark-haired bully holds SOMEONE in a headlock.
CHRONICLE_DVS39
The bully smacks him in the face several times.
CHRONICLE_DVS40
The camera finds SOMEONE standing across the hall.
CHRONICLE_DVS41
The camera slides across the floor and tips on its side.
CHRONICLE_DVS42
SOMEONE picks up his camera then peers at its lens.
CHRONICLE_DVS43
In his friend's car again, he points his camera at the side mirror.
CHRONICLE_DVS44
The mirror shows him peering through the eyepiece.
CHRONICLE_DVS45
He videotapes his friend.
CHRONICLE_DVS46
At a little corner park, three guys meet up toting bottles and brown bags.
CHRONICLE_DVS47
They notice SOMEONE.
CHRONICLE_DVS48
SOMEONE's camera whirls. Later.
CHRONICLE_DVS49
A stationary view shows SOMEONE sitting at a desk in his bedroom.
CHRONICLE_DVS50
The pale teen connects a light attachment to his camera,
CHRONICLE_DVS51
switches it on, and smiles to himself.
CHRONICLE_DVS52
SOMEONE's father barges in and the nervous teen quickly acts busy at his computer.
CHRONICLE_DVS53
He smacks SOMEONE upside the head, lifts him from his chair, and throws him down.
CHRONICLE_DVS54
He lowers his pointing finger.
CHRONICLE_DVS55
The bearded man storms out, leaving the bedroom door ajar.
CHRONICLE_DVS56
SOMEONE sits up.
CHRONICLE_DVS57
Bracing himself on the desk, he returns to his chair.
CHRONICLE_DVS58
He reaches to the camera, switches off the light attachment, then lowers his defeated gaze and licks his lips.
CHRONICLE_DVS59
He sits back a bit and expels a shaky breath.
CHRONICLE_DVS60
He reaches to shut off the camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS61
Later in his cousin's car.
CHRONICLE_DVS62
They approach a building.
CHRONICLE_DVS63
SOMEONE returns his camera to SOMEONE, then videotapes several teens heading inside.
CHRONICLE_DVS65
Now, ravers wave glow sticks overhead as lasers beam across the dance floor. The camera catches a glimpse of a jumping girl's breasts, then returns to the chaos of the crowd.
CHRONICLE_DVS66
A DJ works a set of digital turntables. Across the dance floor, SOMEONE finds a blonde, young woman with a video camera of her own. Through her viewfinder, we glimpse partygoers at an upper railing, then spot SOMEONE with his shoulder-mounted camera. She waves to him.
CHRONICLE_DVS67
SOMEONE glances at his feet, then heads off through the crowd.
CHRONICLE_DVS68
She approaches him.
CHRONICLE_DVS69
SOMEONE joins them.
CHRONICLE_DVS70
SOMEONE records him.
CHRONICLE_DVS71
SOMEONE shrugs.
CHRONICLE_DVS72
She heads off.
CHRONICLE_DVS73
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE the finger. Later, surrounded by partygoers, an attractive, young woman dances on a table. Through his camera, SOMEONE looks the young woman up and down. A guy wearing a brimmed hat steps down to the floor and confronts the cameraman.
CHRONICLE_DVS74
He wipes his mouth.
CHRONICLE_DVS75
The guy splashes the camera with his drink, spits on SOMEONE, then walks away. Outside with a blurry lens, SOMEONE's camera captures footage of a lawn near a line of parked cars.
CHRONICLE_DVS76
SOMEONE leans into view, then wipes the lens with his shirtsleeve.
CHRONICLE_DVS77
SOMEONE shuffles over.
CHRONICLE_DVS78
Crouching, SOMEONE extends his hand.
CHRONICLE_DVS79
SOMEONE gets up and follows him.
CHRONICLE_DVS80
SOMEONE switches on the light.
CHRONICLE_DVS81
SOMEONE leads him through the woods.
CHRONICLE_DVS82
They find SOMEONE down a hill standing over a wide hole in the ground.
CHRONICLE_DVS83
SOMEONE and SOMEONE get down on the ground and peer down the deep hole. SOMEONE grabs the cameraman.
CHRONICLE_DVS84
SOMEONE aims his camera down the hole.
CHRONICLE_DVS85
They all back away, but quickly return.
CHRONICLE_DVS86
SOMEONE jumps on the hole and slides out of view.
CHRONICLE_DVS87
SOMEONE steps down.
CHRONICLE_DVS88
Halfway in, SOMEONE glances up.
CHRONICLE_DVS89
The young man slides out of view.
CHRONICLE_DVS90
SOMEONE follows.
CHRONICLE_DVS91
His camera's light shines dimly into a dark tunnel.
CHRONICLE_DVS92
His foot withdraws from a murky puddle.
CHRONICLE_DVS93
SOMEONE jumps out in front of him.
CHRONICLE_DVS94
SOMEONE slips.
CHRONICLE_DVS95
He follows SOMEONE around a corner.
CHRONICLE_DVS96
As we enter a chamber with a giant glowing crystalline structure inside, the video image flickers.
CHRONICLE_DVS97
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step up to the sunburst-shaped structure.
CHRONICLE_DVS98
They lay their hands on the crystals which pulsate with light.
CHRONICLE_DVS99
SOMEONE touches a crystal spike. Vine-like tendrils inside move.
CHRONICLE_DVS100
The crystal's glow changes to a shade of pink.
CHRONICLE_DVS101
SOMEONE touches his face and finds blood streaming from his nose. He collapses.
CHRONICLE_DVS102
The camera's view jostles, showing the illuminated crystalline sunburst, then goes black.
CHRONICLE_DVS103
Light flashes in the darkness.
CHRONICLE_DVS104
We see a backyard.
CHRONICLE_DVS105
SOMEONE holds a baseball in one hand.
CHRONICLE_DVS106
SOMEONE steps into frame.
CHRONICLE_DVS107
SOMEONE throws the baseball right into SOMEONE's face, then runs over to him.
CHRONICLE_DVS108
He overhands the ball into the lawn and it bounces into SOMEONE's face.
CHRONICLE_DVS109
SOMEONE throws off to the side, but the ball curves around and hits SOMEONE in the head.
CHRONICLE_DVS110
SOMEONE throws. The ball slows down as it approaches SOMEONE.
CHRONICLE_DVS111
The ball hovers in front of SOMEONE.
CHRONICLE_DVS112
SOMEONE points at the floating ball.
CHRONICLE_DVS113
The ball drops as it touches his nose.
CHRONICLE_DVS114
Later, in a bedroom.
CHRONICLE_DVS115
Moving his hands, SOMEONE levitates two Lego pieces which bounce off each other.
CHRONICLE_DVS116
SOMEONE texts on his phone as SOMEONE struggles to connect the floating Legos.
CHRONICLE_DVS117
As SOMEONE flicks his hands, several completed structures rise off the floor and connect to create the Seattle Space Needle.
CHRONICLE_DVS118
SOMEONE gives him a high-five.
CHRONICLE_DVS119
SOMEONE goes up for a high-five, but topples the Legos instead.
CHRONICLE_DVS120
Now, in SOMEONE's car.
CHRONICLE_DVS121
They walk through the woods.
CHRONICLE_DVS122
SOMEONE jumps at him.
CHRONICLE_DVS123
They find the hole filled with soil.
CHRONICLE_DVS124
The park ranger watches from a hill.
CHRONICLE_DVS126
Now, in SOMEONE's bedroom.
CHRONICLE_DVS127
Filming himself in the mirror, he lowers his arms from the camera and lets it hover in front of him.
CHRONICLE_DVS128
He backs away.
CHRONICLE_DVS129
Our view circles around the room.
CHRONICLE_DVS130
We find a proud grin on SOMEONE's face.
CHRONICLE_DVS132
SOMEONE lies awake in bed.
CHRONICLE_DVS133
As he nods off, the camera falls.
CHRONICLE_DVS134
On another day, his mother holds it as they sit at a waterfront cafe.
CHRONICLE_DVS135
She films him.
CHRONICLE_DVS136
SOMEONE gives a worried look, then drops his gaze.
CHRONICLE_DVS137
He gives a bashful smile, then lifts his heavy-lidded eyes and stares directly at us.
CHRONICLE_DVS138
Now at a park, SOMEONE telekinetically lifts a rock off the grass and skips it across the lake.
CHRONICLE_DVS139
Another plops right in the water.
CHRONICLE_DVS140
SOMEONE zooms in on him.
CHRONICLE_DVS141
SOMEONE looks over, then gives a shrug.
CHRONICLE_DVS143
We pan over to three girls chatting by a leaf blower. It levitates and blows one girl's skirt up.
CHRONICLE_DVS144
Chips fly from a Pringles can into his mouth.
CHRONICLE_DVS145
Now, they drive through a shopping center's parking lot.
CHRONICLE_DVS146
In a store.
CHRONICLE_DVS147
The camera tapes SOMEONE pointing a toy light saber at woman's shopping cart.
CHRONICLE_DVS148
As she checks an item on a shelf.
CHRONICLE_DVS149
He directs her cart down another aisle and makes stuffed animals flip inside it.
CHRONICLE_DVS150
The woman chases after her runaway cart.
CHRONICLE_DVS151
In another aisle, a little girl takes a plush giraffe from a display cubby.
CHRONICLE_DVS152
A bear floats off a top shelf.
CHRONICLE_DVS153
As SOMEONE stares at him, the guy's head suddenly snaps back. He flies forward, knocking a shelf over.
CHRONICLE_DVS154
SOMEONE races away.
CHRONICLE_DVS155
At a diner.
CHRONICLE_DVS156
He stabs a fork at SOMEONE's hand.
CHRONICLE_DVS157
SOMEONE holds it up, showing its bent tines.
CHRONICLE_DVS158
SOMEONE displays his unharmed hand.
CHRONICLE_DVS159
Our focus shifts at a window to a girl's tight dress.
CHRONICLE_DVS161
A woman gets out of the red car.
CHRONICLE_DVS162
Facing the parked car, SOMEONE telekinetically drags it out of its spot.
CHRONICLE_DVS163
He turns it around to face a different space.
CHRONICLE_DVS164
He guides it in.
CHRONICLE_DVS165
SOMEONE bounces excitedly, then pops his vest collar.
CHRONICLE_DVS166
His nose bleeds.
CHRONICLE_DVS167
He holds a bloody tissue out at SOMEONE.
CHRONICLE_DVS168
The owner of the red car heads for her now vacant parking spot.
CHRONICLE_DVS169
The woman glances around.
CHRONICLE_DVS170
As the woman finds her car in its new space, SOMEONE nudges his shoulder against SOMEONE's.
CHRONICLE_DVS171
Later, SOMEONE pounds SOMEONE's dashboard.
CHRONICLE_DVS172
SOMEONE films a tailgating truck.
CHRONICLE_DVS173
It suddenly veers through a guardrail.
CHRONICLE_DVS174
Now they find the truck nose down in a river.
CHRONICLE_DVS175
The truck starts to move.
CHRONICLE_DVS176
Shedding his jacket and shoes, SOMEONE dives into the water. SOMEONE moves to the riverbank.
CHRONICLE_DVS177
SOMEONE swims to the trucks.
CHRONICLE_DVS178
He plunges below the water surface.
CHRONICLE_DVS179
SOMEONE whips off his jacket.
CHRONICLE_DVS180
Rain pelts the water surface.
CHRONICLE_DVS181
SOMEONE surfaces with the truck driver.
CHRONICLE_DVS182
SOMEONE helps him drag the unconscious man onto the muddy riverbank.
CHRONICLE_DVS183
The driver lies limp with a long cut up his forearm and a streak of blood staining the corner of his mouth.
CHRONICLE_DVS184
Kneeling with his arms around the injured man, SOMEONE lifts his gaze to SOMEONE's viewfinder.
CHRONICLE_DVS185
SOMEONE grabs at SOMEONE's phone.
CHRONICLE_DVS186
Later, on the road.
CHRONICLE_DVS187
With the police.
CHRONICLE_DVS188
An officer points at us.
CHRONICLE_DVS190
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pace before SOMEONE.
CHRONICLE_DVS191
As SOMEONE faces SOMEONE, SOMEONE turns away.
CHRONICLE_DVS192
Now in his room, the troubled teen lies on his bed, one hand outstretched toward us.
CHRONICLE_DVS193
As we peer down at him through the airborne camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS194
He pensively floats the camera side to side, then above him.
CHRONICLE_DVS195
Our bird's eye of SOMEONE drifts higher. Now, in SOMEONE's car.
CHRONICLE_DVS196
The mind-controlled camera view shows SOMEONE seated close to us, looking in our direction.
CHRONICLE_DVS197
He faces SOMEONE.
CHRONICLE_DVS198
The troubled teen gives a small solemn nod.
CHRONICLE_DVS200
They approach mounds of sawdust.
CHRONICLE_DVS201
SOMEONE digs out a cellphone.
CHRONICLE_DVS202
He reads the display.
CHRONICLE_DVS203
SOMEONE floats above them.
CHRONICLE_DVS204
SOMEONE leaps six feet up, then falls on his face.
CHRONICLE_DVS205
SOMEONE does a high, rapid back flip, and slams to the ground.
CHRONICLE_DVS206
SOMEONE spreads his arms.
CHRONICLE_DVS207
Rocks and dirt float up around him as he rises.
CHRONICLE_DVS208
SOMEONE flexes and bends his legs as he rises.
CHRONICLE_DVS209
SOMEONE takes his hand.
CHRONICLE_DVS210
Our view jostles.
CHRONICLE_DVS211
Now, we corkscrew past clouds. A teen in an orange hooded parka and gloves soars into view just beneath us.
CHRONICLE_DVS213
He grins at us and executes a roll.
CHRONICLE_DVS214
He accelerates.
CHRONICLE_DVS215
In his sporty black and white parka, SOMEONE pulls ahead of us.
CHRONICLE_DVS216
They fly 10 thousand feet above populated terrain.
CHRONICLE_DVS217
We quickly come up on SOMEONE who hovers as though standing.
CHRONICLE_DVS218
We pass him by, then he overtakes us again.
CHRONICLE_DVS219
Now, SOMEONE holds the camera out to record himself and SOMEONE in action.
CHRONICLE_DVS220
Later, still in the sky, SOMEONE levitates a football. SOMEONE kicks it to SOMEONE who catches it 50 yards away.
CHRONICLE_DVS221
He hurls it back at astounding speed. SOMEONE throws.
CHRONICLE_DVS222
SOMEONE makes the two-handed catch above his shoulder.
CHRONICLE_DVS223
A passenger jet passes between the teens.
CHRONICLE_DVS224
The tumbling camera gives us a dizzying, rolling view of the ground, then the sky, the ground, the sky. As it steadies, we glimpse one of the boys plummeting.
CHRONICLE_DVS226
A second guy whisks him out of his free fall.
CHRONICLE_DVS227
As we near a cloud, SOMEONE emerges head-on toward us with SOMEONE in one arm.
CHRONICLE_DVS228
With his free hand, he grabs the camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS229
Sharing his point-of-view, we peer out from the rippling folds of SOMEONE's coat while making a controlled descent toward the landscape below.
CHRONICLE_DVS230
Our view rolls, landing in the grass.
CHRONICLE_DVS231
SOMEONE lies before us, nose bleeding.
CHRONICLE_DVS232
Behind him, SOMEONE sits up.
CHRONICLE_DVS233
SOMEONE helps SOMEONE up, hugs him, and spins him around.
CHRONICLE_DVS234
He falls with the shy teen then kisses him.
CHRONICLE_DVS235
SOMEONE plunges down and lands in a roll. SOMEONE grabs him.
CHRONICLE_DVS236
As SOMEONE leads them toward the camera, SOMEONE checks on SOMEONE who dabs his nose.
CHRONICLE_DVS237
Later, SOMEONE lies back.
CHRONICLE_DVS238
SOMEONE drags SOMEONE into the camera's view.
CHRONICLE_DVS239
Now in a boy's room, we view a vast collection of trophies.
CHRONICLE_DVS240
A certificate award bears SOMEONE's name.
CHRONICLE_DVS241
SOMEONE and SOMEONE grin at us through SOMEONE's camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS242
Now in a dark living room, the shy teen lies back on a pillow.
CHRONICLE_DVS243
Peering up at us, he releases the camera into the air.
CHRONICLE_DVS244
As it floats upward, he folds his arms and watches it contentedly.
CHRONICLE_DVS245
At his head and feet, SOMEONE and SOMEONE each lie in separate makeshift beds.
CHRONICLE_DVS246
Seen through the hovering camera, the boys' heads form the three points of a triangle.
CHRONICLE_DVS247
Now in a library, the camera frames SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
CHRONICLE_DVS248
Now from an angle over SOMEONE's shoulder, we see her open her front door. SOMEONE's on the porch.
CHRONICLE_DVS249
She jerks her thumb toward us.
CHRONICLE_DVS250
SOMEONE removes his backpack and digs inside.
CHRONICLE_DVS251
He gives her an envelope.
CHRONICLE_DVS252
SOMEONE checks his cellphone.
CHRONICLE_DVS253
SOMEONE wearily creases his lips.
CHRONICLE_DVS254
SOMEONE shrugs.
CHRONICLE_DVS255
She shuts the door on him and smiles.
CHRONICLE_DVS256
Now on a skyscraper's ledge.
CHRONICLE_DVS257
SOMEONE autopilots the camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS258
Each has a fast food drink.
CHRONICLE_DVS259
Later, still on the ledge.
CHRONICLE_DVS260
SOMEONE looks into our hovering camera view.
CHRONICLE_DVS261
Now, SOMEONE models a suit and skinny tie.
CHRONICLE_DVS262
Later, we share the camera's perspective as SOMEONE carries it downstairs.
CHRONICLE_DVS263
We catch sight of his father who lounges in a recliner, watching TV.
CHRONICLE_DVS264
Slipping past him, we near the door.
CHRONICLE_DVS265
Facing the tired man, we spy empty beer bottles beside him.
CHRONICLE_DVS266
His dad sits up.
CHRONICLE_DVS267
The bearded man grins.
CHRONICLE_DVS268
Now, in a school auditorium.
CHRONICLE_DVS269
The blurry image sharpens.
CHRONICLE_DVS270
Now, before a packed student audience, a teen rock band backs up a blonde singer clad in black.
CHRONICLE_DVS271
Later, brightly clad girls execute synchronized dance moves.
CHRONICLE_DVS272
Later still, a teen soprano performs as her fellow students heckle her.
CHRONICLE_DVS273
Sharing another camera's perspective, we approach SOMEONE.
CHRONICLE_DVS274
He turns and smiles.
CHRONICLE_DVS275
We view SOMEONE through his camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS276
SOMEONE re-trains his camera on the stage.
CHRONICLE_DVS277
SOMEONE walks onstage.
CHRONICLE_DVS278
A spotlight hits a stage flat painted like a stone carving of a great cat.
CHRONICLE_DVS279
SOMEONE emerges from its roaring mouth.
CHRONICLE_DVS280
He gives a shy wave, then fumbles in his jacket pocket, produces a deck of playing cards, and faces SOMEONE. As the shy teen fans the cards, the more popular boy sips an energy drink.
CHRONICLE_DVS281
SOMEONE starts to cross the stage with the cards.
CHRONICLE_DVS282
Then trips and falls. The cards go flying and land in a scattered heap. SOMEONE makes exasperated gestures at SOMEONE who stands and worriedly eyes the cards. SOMEONE raises a finger then holds out his hand. The cards float up and collect in his palm.
CHRONICLE_DVS283
Later, he juggles four balls. He pauses, and they hover over his head.
CHRONICLE_DVS284
SOMEONE nonchalantly takes a sip of SOMEONE's energy drink. As his friend reaches for it, the balls drop on his head.
CHRONICLE_DVS285
Now, SOMEONE checks a tightrope.
CHRONICLE_DVS286
Later, he stands by as SOMEONE edges uneasily down the tightrope with his arms spread for balance.
CHRONICLE_DVS287
The shy teen falters forward.
CHRONICLE_DVS288
He slowly straightens.
CHRONICLE_DVS289
He balances easily.
CHRONICLE_DVS290
With small heel-toe steps, he crosses the rope nimbly.
CHRONICLE_DVS291
Next, he hops from its end to a point three feet in.
CHRONICLE_DVS292
He does turns.
CHRONICLE_DVS293
Later, SOMEONE tosses balls to SOMEONE who's still on the tightrope.
CHRONICLE_DVS294
SOMEONE encourages applause. Juggling, SOMEONE lifts one leg behind him and catches a ball on his heel.
CHRONICLE_DVS295
The ball drops and rolls along the rope after him.
CHRONICLE_DVS296
Later, SOMEONE presents SOMEONE, triumphant and beaming, to a standing ovation.
CHRONICLE_DVS298
Teens gather outside the mansion.
CHRONICLE_DVS299
The camera viewfinder now follows SOMEONE. As they near a pool, SOMEONE approaches.
CHRONICLE_DVS300
SOMEONE grins from ear-to-ear as he's greeted with handshakes and pretty smiles.
CHRONICLE_DVS301
The camera view rose to a DJ.
CHRONICLE_DVS302
Indoors, it focuses on SOMEONE on a couch.
CHRONICLE_DVS303
A girl with pink-dyed hair approaches.
CHRONICLE_DVS304
Our view drops onto a coffee table and records SOMEONE and SOMEONE on a couch.
CHRONICLE_DVS305
Kids play beer pong.
CHRONICLE_DVS306
Now, SOMEONE picks up the camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS307
He films the beer pong match.
CHRONICLE_DVS308
A guy in a varsity jacket takes a drink.
CHRONICLE_DVS309
His opponent, SOMEONE, gets a high-five from SOMEONE and a flirty squeeze from SOMEONE.
CHRONICLE_DVS310
SOMEONE tosses two balls from one hand.
CHRONICLE_DVS311
Both go in.
CHRONICLE_DVS312
Next, he simultaneously tosses a ball from his left hand and his right. Travelling parallel, the balls bounce once and land in side-by-side cups.
CHRONICLE_DVS313
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a long, eager kiss.
CHRONICLE_DVS314
Later, SOMEONE faces our view.
CHRONICLE_DVS316
Another camera view slyly records SOMEONE talking into SOMEONE's camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS317
SOMEONE approaches.
CHRONICLE_DVS318
Now, SOMEONE films himself on a stairway landing.
CHRONICLE_DVS319
SOMEONE storms into view, her shoulder covered in vomit.
CHRONICLE_DVS320
SOMEONE enters the bedroom.
CHRONICLE_DVS321
SOMEONE quickly pulls up his pants.
CHRONICLE_DVS323
SOMEONE lies belly-down on his bedroom floor, half-propped on his elbows with his hands folded.
CHRONICLE_DVS324
He watches a spider crossing in front of him.
CHRONICLE_DVS325
SOMEONE aims a hand at the creature and levitates it.
CHRONICLE_DVS326
As he holds it in suspension, the spider's legs all helplessly splay outward, pulled taut.
CHRONICLE_DVS327
The animal briefly struggles.
CHRONICLE_DVS328
SOMEONE spreads his fingers wide.
CHRONICLE_DVS329
Telekinetically tearing it apart.
CHRONICLE_DVS330
He holds the dismembered bits frozen in the air.
CHRONICLE_DVS331
Then, distracted, relaxes his hand.
CHRONICLE_DVS332
The parts drop.
CHRONICLE_DVS333
Now, a camera view from atop SOMEONE's dresser records his bedroom.
CHRONICLE_DVS334
His father enters.
CHRONICLE_DVS335
The ragged man searches through SOMEONE's belongings.
CHRONICLE_DVS336
He leaves a coat hanging on an armoire door and steps directly toward the camera. He reaches for it.
CHRONICLE_DVS338
They sit in a basement. SOMEONE slouches downcast as his father points fingers.
CHRONICLE_DVS339
His father overturns a table between them and slaps SOMEONE down. He pounces on the boy.
CHRONICLE_DVS340
He pulls the boy to his feet, but SOMEONE forces him up against the wall.
CHRONICLE_DVS341
SOMEONE throws his father several feet.
CHRONICLE_DVS342
The angry drunk crashes, tumbling across the dirty concrete floor. SOMEONE stands observantly by as the older man rolls on to his stomach.
CHRONICLE_DVS343
His feet upset some piled newspapers.
CHRONICLE_DVS344
As the retired firefighter catches his breath lying face down, SOMEONE remains standing.
CHRONICLE_DVS345
His shoulders heave as he catches his own breath.
CHRONICLE_DVS346
He stares off intensely.
CHRONICLE_DVS347
The view swings to SOMEONE who dabs his bloody nose.
CHRONICLE_DVS348
He playfully reaches for her camera. Now among dark clouds at night, lightning flashes.
CHRONICLE_DVS349
The city gleams far below.
CHRONICLE_DVS350
SOMEONE flies up.
CHRONICLE_DVS351
A zapping flash blots out everything. Our view tumbles.
CHRONICLE_DVS352
Daytime. Walking legs pass clad in black.
CHRONICLE_DVS353
A female cellist bows her instrument, performing on a lawn strewn with dead leaves.
CHRONICLE_DVS354
Mourners gather, many of them African-American.
CHRONICLE_DVS355
A dozen teens, each hold a white rose.
CHRONICLE_DVS356
The camera view rose to SOMEONE who returns a stoic look.
CHRONICLE_DVS357
SOMEONE clings to him, weeping.
CHRONICLE_DVS358
Afterward, SOMEONE films the gravesite.
CHRONICLE_DVS359
SOMEONE hovers the camera out of both their hands. SOMEONE looks around.
CHRONICLE_DVS360
Our vantage rises like a helium balloon, but stays trained on the two young men.
CHRONICLE_DVS361
SOMEONE childishly turns his back on SOMEONE and rockets skyward.
CHRONICLE_DVS362
At night, puddles retreat away from SOMEONE's footsteps.
CHRONICLE_DVS363
By day, photos of SOMEONE, small gifts, and wilting flowers rest on the new grave.
CHRONICLE_DVS364
Now, at his isolated lunch spot on the bleachers.
CHRONICLE_DVS365
SOMEONE sits motionless watching the cheerleaders practice.
CHRONICLE_DVS366
Later, in the school, between periods.
CHRONICLE_DVS367
His jostling camera view heads down some stairs.
CHRONICLE_DVS368
The pink-haired SOMEONE notices him as she chats with friends.
CHRONICLE_DVS369
One girl pretends to retch.
CHRONICLE_DVS370
Further along, the bully makes a face at him.
CHRONICLE_DVS371
The bully bumps the lens with his elbow. Later, SOMEONE follows the unsuspecting thug down the hall.
CHRONICLE_DVS372
SOMEONE makes a pulling motion and the bully lurches, his mouth spurting blood.
CHRONICLE_DVS373
The camera resumes in a bathroom.
CHRONICLE_DVS374
SOMEONE holds up three bloody teeth.
CHRONICLE_DVS375
SOMEONE tosses the teeth into the toilet.
CHRONICLE_DVS377
In a junkyard.
CHRONICLE_DVS378
He sits cross-legged on an old icebox.
CHRONICLE_DVS379
He cracks his knuckles.
CHRONICLE_DVS380
SOMEONE straightens his back and holds out a hand. As he slowly makes a fist, a rusty car behind him implodes.
CHRONICLE_DVS381
Later in his bedroom, he sits at his computer.
CHRONICLE_DVS382
He gets up swiftly and puts on his coat.
CHRONICLE_DVS383
SOMEONE arrives.
CHRONICLE_DVS385
SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE who shoves back.
CHRONICLE_DVS386
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE by the lapel and throws a punch, but SOMEONE telekinetically arrests it inches from his face.
CHRONICLE_DVS387
The two stand in a stalemate, SOMEONE's fist trembling in suspension. He disgustedly lets go of his cousin and glares at him.
CHRONICLE_DVS388
SOMEONE turns away and flies out the window.
CHRONICLE_DVS389
Left alone, SOMEONE grabs his backpack and heads out.
CHRONICLE_DVS390
From the hall, he views his agonizing mother lying in bed.
CHRONICLE_DVS391
As he swivels a hand aimed in her direction, her body gently turns and a blanket slides up to cover her.
CHRONICLE_DVS392
Now, a crooked view shows a pharmacist’s nametag.
CHRONICLE_DVS393
Back in his room, SOMEONE heaves a bulky red duffel bag onto his bed.
CHRONICLE_DVS394
He opens it up and lifts out a firefighter's helmet and eye guard.
CHRONICLE_DVS395
Next, he pulls out a pair of fireproof and waterproof suspender pants.
CHRONICLE_DVS396
He kicks off his sneakers.
CHRONICLE_DVS397
Wearing the pants, he puts on both rubber boots.
CHRONICLE_DVS398
SOMEONE fetches the rugged coat from the duffel.
CHRONICLE_DVS399
Its sleeves and body bear reflective yellow-green bands.
CHRONICLE_DVS400
He puts it on.
CHRONICLE_DVS401
Now, he unzips the side panel on the bag and retrieves a full-face mask.
CHRONICLE_DVS402
SOMEONE sets it over his head.
CHRONICLE_DVS403
The breathing apparatus built into it covers his mouth and nose.
CHRONICLE_DVS404
Only his eyes show behind the curved window on the face shield.
CHRONICLE_DVS405
SOMEONE tweaks the straps,
CHRONICLE_DVS406
then adjusts the mask.
CHRONICLE_DVS407
Now, we approach the park thugs.
CHRONICLE_DVS408
SOMEONE aims a finger like a gun.
CHRONICLE_DVS409
He mimes shooting and the thug flies backward.
CHRONICLE_DVS410
As the others run, SOMEONE gestures sending one of them smashing into a car's rear window, and another cartwheeling down to the pavement.
CHRONICLE_DVS411
Launches himself high, he lands in front of the last remaining thug. The teen sends him flying back into the camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS412
As our view tilts downward and glides over the asphalt, we glimpse two of the unconscious thugs.
CHRONICLE_DVS413
SOMEONE telekinetically drags one side-to-side, leaving bloody smears on the pavement.
CHRONICLE_DVS414
We lift high overhead as he moves on to the other,
CHRONICLE_DVS415
takes out his wallet, and pilfers the cash inside.
CHRONICLE_DVS416
Returning to the first thug, he takes his money, too.
CHRONICLE_DVS417
SOMEONE launches himself into the air and grabs the camera.
CHRONICLE_DVS418
Now, he sits with his back to a fence and his respirator mask off, counting out the cash.
CHRONICLE_DVS419
He puts it in his backpack, heaves a deflated sigh, and shifts his thoughtful gaze.
CHRONICLE_DVS420
Grimly licking his lips.
CHRONICLE_DVS421
he zips up the backpack.
CHRONICLE_DVS422
Now wearing the mask again, he marches into a gas station's food mart.
CHRONICLE_DVS423
He punches the air, knocking the clerk back against the cigarette case. Surveillance footage shows SOMEONE taking off his backpack.
CHRONICLE_DVS425
From his camera, we watch him float cash from the register into his bag. The doors open behind him as he zips up his backpack and heads out.
CHRONICLE_DVS426
The security footage shows the clerk hopping over his counter with a shotgun.
CHRONICLE_DVS427
SOMEONE halts by the gas pumps and turns back to find him taking aim.
CHRONICLE_DVS428
The teen sweeps a hand sideways.
CHRONICLE_DVS429
Security footage shows the gun flying from the clerk's grasp and discharging into a propane tank.
CHRONICLE_DVS430
A huge explosion rocks the gas station.
CHRONICLE_DVS431
As the flames settle, we find both SOMEONE and the clerk lying on the ground in flames.
CHRONICLE_DVS432
Now, a hospital surveillance camera shows a policeman walking Mr. SOMEONE to a guarded room.
CHRONICLE_DVS433
Inside, a heavily bandaged SOMEONE lies unconscious.
CHRONICLE_DVS434
A surveillance camera shows the cop leaving the room.
CHRONICLE_DVS435
Another camera sits on a tripod near the foot of SOMEONE's bed.
CHRONICLE_DVS436
Through the high-angle surveillance camera, we watch Mr. SOMEONE cross to a large window and remove his jacket.
CHRONICLE_DVS437
He takes a seat at his son's bedside.
CHRONICLE_DVS438
The tripod camera shows him taking SOMEONE's hand.
CHRONICLE_DVS439
He bends over, resting his head on it, then lays a hand on his son's blanketed knee.
CHRONICLE_DVS440
The heavily bandaged teen lies motionless and unresponsive.
CHRONICLE_DVS441
Later, Mr. SOMEONE sits with a hunched posture, his hands in his lap.
CHRONICLE_DVS442
His brow furrowed, he hangs his head and swallows.
CHRONICLE_DVS443
Mr. SOMEONE stands.
CHRONICLE_DVS444
The surveillance camera shows him leaning over SOMEONE and jabbing a finger at him.
CHRONICLE_DVS445
SOMEONE grabs his wrist. An explosion blast out the windows.
CHRONICLE_DVS446
Now, a boy blows out candles on a birthday cake.
CHRONICLE_DVS448
SOMEONE's nose starts to bleed.
CHRONICLE_DVS449
We follow him as he hurries out of the room.
CHRONICLE_DVS450
He holds paper towels to his nosebleed.
CHRONICLE_DVS451
In the living room, everyone watches TV.
CHRONICLE_DVS452
We get in SOMEONE's car with SOMEONE. Later.
CHRONICLE_DVS453
There's a roadblock up ahead.
CHRONICLE_DVS454
Now, as SOMEONE drives amongst speeding emergency vehicles, a police car cuts him off. Later, they arrive near a crowd.
CHRONICLE_DVS455
Through SOMEONE's camera, we follow SOMEONE's gaze up the hospital building and find the smoking blast site.
CHRONICLE_DVS456
SOMEONE flies out from the smoke, holding his father by the ankle.
CHRONICLE_DVS457
He drops him.
CHRONICLE_DVS458
SOMEONE suddenly takes flight.
CHRONICLE_DVS459
He catches Mr. SOMEONE.
CHRONICLE_DVS460
SOMEONE rescinds out of view.
CHRONICLE_DVS461
SOMEONE carries his limp, soot-covered uncle to the ground.
CHRONICLE_DVS462
Later in the speeding car.
CHRONICLE_DVS463
A news helicopter descends rapidly, spinning out of control.
CHRONICLE_DVS464
It crashes in front of them.
CHRONICLE_DVS465
SOMEONE breaks to a stop.
CHRONICLE_DVS466
A cop suddenly gets flung away from their car.
CHRONICLE_DVS467
The car rises several stories high.
CHRONICLE_DVS468
We fly past skyscrapers.
CHRONICLE_DVS469
The car slams down on top of the Seattle Space Needle.
CHRONICLE_DVS470
We peer through the windshield as the car rocks precariously.
CHRONICLE_DVS471
The neon lights on the spire burst.
CHRONICLE_DVS472
Floating nearby, SOMEONE uses his power to blast out the windshield and suck SOMEONE from the car.
CHRONICLE_DVS473
We tether backwards off the roof, then plummet.
CHRONICLE_DVS474
SOMEONE flies down and pulls us out.
CHRONICLE_DVS475
We watch the falling car exploding on impact, then look up at our savior.
CHRONICLE_DVS476
He floats us safely to the street and sets us down.
CHRONICLE_DVS477
He flies back toward the needle.
CHRONICLE_DVS478
A Fox News graphic reads, "Downtown High Alert. "
CHRONICLE_DVS479
From the needle's observation deck, onlookers record the events on their cellphones.
CHRONICLE_DVS480
Floating just outside, SOMEONE glowers at them.
CHRONICLE_DVS481
SOMEONE drifts up behind him, but his cousin hurls him back.
CHRONICLE_DVS482
SOMEONE shatters the windows of the observation deck and sucks up all of the bystanders' cellphones and cameras.
CHRONICLE_DVS483
They hover around him in the helicopter's spotlights as he spreads his arms and faces his cousin.
CHRONICLE_DVS484
A police helicopter records them.
CHRONICLE_DVS485
SOMEONE grimaces.
CHRONICLE_DVS486
SOMEONE straightens and glares at his cousin.
CHRONICLE_DVS487
A bus hits SOMEONE head on. The vehicle flies through the air and careens into a building's fifth story.
CHRONICLE_DVS488
SOMEONE lands clumsily on another building's rooftop.
CHRONICLE_DVS489
A few bystanders back away from the bandaged and bloody young man.
CHRONICLE_DVS490
He pukes as he stumbles to his feet.
CHRONICLE_DVS491
SOMEONE flies in and swoops him off the roof.
CHRONICLE_DVS492
A bank's black and white security footage shows them smashing through a wall in its lobby.
CHRONICLE_DVS493
Now, from inside a speeding police cruiser, we watch the pair land in the street before us,
CHRONICLE_DVS494
creating an eight foot crater.
CHRONICLE_DVS495
SOMEONE lifts his hand and the cruiser rises over the boys, landing on its roof.
CHRONICLE_DVS496
In an apartment overlooking the street.
CHRONICLE_DVS497
SOMEONE flies up through the apartment's floor and ceiling. SOMEONE follows.
CHRONICLE_DVS498
From a few blocks away, we see dirt and SOMEONE billow up from a roof as the boys bust through.
CHRONICLE_DVS499
Now, SOMEONE flies backward above the street, throwing parked cars.
CHRONICLE_DVS500
As SOMEONE dodges them, SOMEONE flies back into a lamppost. Sparks fly as he drops onto a parked car and rolls to the street.
CHRONICLE_DVS501
As SOMEONE lands nearby, a helicopter searchlight shines down on him.
CHRONICLE_DVS502
He drags his unconscious cousin away from the car.
CHRONICLE_DVS503
Two cruisers arrive. The cops take aim behind their open doors. SOMEONE lifts his arms.
CHRONICLE_DVS504
The street lamp falls.
CHRONICLE_DVS505
SOMEONE wakes and tries to lift his head.
CHRONICLE_DVS506
As SOMEONE slowly gets to his hands and knees, bits of glass strewn around him rise off the pavement.
CHRONICLE_DVS507
SOMEONE stands up behind SOMEONE, the glass shards hovering around him.
CHRONICLE_DVS508
An officer shoots. SOMEONE flinches, then lowers his bloody right hand.
CHRONICLE_DVS509
SOMEONE waves his arms forward, sending the two cruisers flying back. SOMEONE flings the fallen streetlamp into a parked car.
CHRONICLE_DVS510
Both boys shoot straight up into the air.
CHRONICLE_DVS511
Now, as panicked bystanders flee, a camera tries to follow the movements of a body as it smashes through a billboard, then bounces between two buildings.
CHRONICLE_DVS512
The police chopper's camera shows the boys landing in a plaza near a statue.
CHRONICLE_DVS513
Both lie face down on the stone tiles as several police cars surround the area.
CHRONICLE_DVS514
SWAT team members in black helmets train rifles on them.
CHRONICLE_DVS515
SOMEONE tries to crawl forward, the skin on his uncovered arm raw and bloody.
CHRONICLE_DVS516
A half-dozen laser dots cluster near his head and shoulder.
CHRONICLE_DVS517
SOMEONE's leg twitches and he lifts his head.
CHRONICLE_DVS518
As SOMEONE unsteadily gets to his feet, SOMEONE stays low to the ground. SOMEONE wobbles around the plaza like an injured animal. With an arm shielding his eyes, he gazes skyward toward the chopper. Laser sight dots dance on his back.
CHRONICLE_DVS519
The teenager turns to face the semi-circle of police.
CHRONICLE_DVS520
Lunging forward, he sends a giant wave of energy toward them.
CHRONICLE_DVS521
The car skid backwards and the humans fly through the air.
CHRONICLE_DVS522
As SOMEONE tries to prop himself up on his elbows, SOMEONE shakes both fists overhead in a primal scream.
CHRONICLE_DVS523
Windows shatter in the buildings around them.
CHRONICLE_DVS524
SOMEONE looks on helplessly as huge glass shards rain down on frightened pedestrians.
CHRONICLE_DVS525
Blood trickling from his nose, SOMEONE squints and looks around.
CHRONICLE_DVS526
His gaze lands on a nearby statue which depicts a shirtless warrior aiming a spear.
CHRONICLE_DVS527
With a quick wave of his hand, SOMEONE sends the spear straight through SOMEONE's back.
CHRONICLE_DVS528
Wearing an emotional SOMEONE, SOMEONE collapses.
CHRONICLE_DVS529
His impaled cousin hangs limp from the spear, now lodged in the ground at a 60-degree angle.
CHRONICLE_DVS530
From the helicopter's view, searchlights illuminate the two unmoving boys as the uniformed officers and SWAT members cautiously make their way to the center of the plaza.
CHRONICLE_DVS531
As the authorities move in, SOMEONE's eyes snap open. He jumps to his feet and shoots up into the air.