He takes out a stack of cash.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS15
SOMEONE kisses the cash and tucks it away.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS16
SOMEONE looks out the window.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS17
Later, SOMEONE shakes hands with the driver.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS18
The car backs out of a driveway as SOMEONE approaches a house. The front door opens and a doll faced brunette woman appears
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS19
in the doorway. As SOMEONE approaches, he hangs his head. The woman frowns. Reaching the front steps, SOMEONE bobs his head soberly. As the woman lowers her gaze, he breaks into a smile.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS20
She runs into his arms.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS21
and holds a younger boy.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS22
Later, the boxer sits on a patio in the night air. With an adoring smile, his wife brings two snifters of brandy and hands him one.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS23
She sits. SOMEONE puts down his glass
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS24
SOMEONE leans forward and pulls his wife closer.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS25
She stands over him in her silky white midi blouse.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS26
She raises his arms overhead. Letting them back down, she grabs him by the collar and kisses him.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS27
Their lips still locked, SOMEONE rises and holds her in his arms.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS28
Towering over him, she smiles as they
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS29
SOMEONE looks around cautiously. Behind them, lights glow on string of colorful lanterns.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS30
off into the darkness. Later, in a bedroom, SOMEONE stands at a dresser.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS31
The boxer takes off a Catholic cross necklace and drapes it over his framed wedding photo.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS32
He removes a wristwatch, then drops a stack of cash across an open jewelry box.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS33
A second wad plunks down in a money clip. On the lacquer dresser, another box sits filled with earrings, rings, and necklaces.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS34
As our view moves across the flower print wallpaper, the picture goes dark. Now our view keeps moving to a white washed dresser top lined with a simple lace runner. Words appear, September 25th, 1933.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS35
Four years into the Great Depression. A man's fingers reach for a folded straight razor near the Braddock's unframed wedding photo.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS36
SOMEONE squints at his reflection in a mirror.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS37
He runs a hand down his cheeks.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS38
He picks up a jagged hooked strip of metal with an ivory nub angled down from one end. Wincing, he fits it into his mouth. He checks his fake tooth in a mirror rubbing it with a forefinger.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS39
Scratching his belly through his t-shirt, he steps around a wall of exposed lathe.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS40
A girl sits up in bed.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS41
His wife removes a pair of socks from an oven.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS42
As she holds them out to the groggy boxer, he grabs her arm and pulls her in for a kiss.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS43
holds the socks to his face.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS44
She kisses her daughter's head as SOMEONE puts on his shoes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS45
As he lifts SOMEONE onto his lap, his wife brings over a meat slice on a plate.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS46
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS47
He sits her at the table,
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS48
sets the plate in front of her. Outside before sunrise, SOMEONE heads upstairs to an
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS49
Two empty milk bottles sit in a basket. A notice around one reads, Past Due. SOMEONE picks it up. Wearing suspenders over his t-shirt, he grabs the bottles. Now he returns to the basement apartment. As his wife looks over from the stove, he shows her the past
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS50
SOMEONE puts the empties on a shelf.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS51
He adds the notice to a stack of bills.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS52
His wife adds water to a milk bottle only one-eighth full.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS53
She stabs it into the last morsel of
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS54
The bottle's now three-quarters full.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS55
As she pours a glass of milk, SOMEONE returns to the table.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS56
He gives his daughter his single piece of meat.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS57
As SOMEONE eats with her hands, her father leans over the table and kiss his wife.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS58
He grabs a coat and heads to the door.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS59
His round faced wife watches him go.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS60
In the early morning darkness, people stir in a parked car. As one of its doors opens, SOMEONE crosses a dingy lot nearby where a crude tent sits near campfires.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS61
Two children run out from the car.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS62
Wearing a floppy cap, SOMEONE warms his hands over one fire then stuffs them in his pockets and walks off.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS63
Later, he heads down a sidewalk of darkness.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS64
He meets SOMEONE's gaze. SOMEONE's finger points away from the boxer.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS65
Glowering, SOMEONE turns away.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS66
Past a dirt smudged newspaper
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS67
that reads, Unemployed hits record 15 million. Now, a boy jumps on a rusty box spring mattress left out on a staircase balcony. Twirling, he sees SOMEONE arrive in the gravely courtyard below.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS68
SOMEONE climbs out of a makeshift fort.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS69
She runs over to SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS70
In the basement apartment, SOMEONE's oldest son sits against a wall with his arms folded. SOMEONE descends the stairs toward the open door holding SOMEONE. He faces SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS71
SOMEONE nods.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS72
Facing her husband, SOMEONE shakes her head. SOMEONE glowers.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS73
Sulking, SOMEONE stays still.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS74
The boy gets up and grabs the salami off the
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS75
SOMEONE eyes his wife then follows SOMEONE to the stairs.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS76
The boxer musses his younger son's hair.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS77
Now a woman exits the shop.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS78
Plucked chickens hang in the window which frames a view of SOMEONE handing the salami over a counter to a butcher.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS79
SOMEONE puts his arm around his son and brings the boy outside. A sign reads, Speagle's Meat and Poultry Shop.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS80
Another sign mounted below the window displays the Coca Cola logo.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS81
SOMEONE and SOMEONE follow the busy sidewalk. The straight haired boy looks up at his father.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS82
Arms shaking, SOMEONE glances down at him and swallows. The boxer looks around, shifting on his feet.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS83
SOMEONE leans down to his wide-eyed son, propping his hands on his knees.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS84
SOMEONE nods then gulps hard.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS85
Crouching below his son's eye level, SOMEONE rubs his hands together.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS86
SOMEONE holds out his hand.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS87
SOMEONE hugs him.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS88
He picks up his son.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS89
SOMEONE clings to his father who carries him down the sidewalk patting his back.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS90
September 25th, 1933. In a locker room, SOMEONE tapes up SOMEONE's left hand.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS91
SOMEONE shoots him a harsh look. It goes unnoticed by SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS92
SOMEONE's face glistens with sweat.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS93
He rubs SOMEONE's untaped right hand.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS94
SOMEONE feels around his fighter's wrist. SOMEONE forces a wince into a smile.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS95
With a solemn look, SOMEONE shifts his draw.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS96
SOMEONE stops him then looks back down at his wrist.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS97
SOMEONE punches the air
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS98
then evades body blows by swiveling with
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS99
head lulls forward, SOMEONE's
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS100
shatter. As SOMEONE looks away, SOMEONE's
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS102
The husky fellow halts, inches in front of SOMEONE's manager.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS103
The promoter turns away, leaving SOMEONE under the stark overhead light.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS104
SOMEONE bites down on a cigar. Now, SOMEONE exits into an alley, his right arm wrapped in a towel.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS105
SOMEONE jogs up to the promoter.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS106
SOMEONE follows.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS107
SOMEONE nods with a meager smile.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS108
SOMEONE gets into his car.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS109
SOMEONE watches the chauffeur driven car pull away. Shifting on his feet, he works his jaw then swaggers past SOMEONE. The manager stays put, staring somberly after the promoter. Behind him, SOMEONE sidles through a turnstile and gives it an angry shove as he clears through.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS110
Now, in their drab basement apartment, SOMEONE sits in an armchair sewing a shirt. She sits up and glances toward the door. SOMEONE enters and sets down his bag.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS111
to her feet and gazes attentively at her husband who approaches with a neutral expression on his face.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS112
As SOMEONE takes her in his embrace,
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS114
They separate and gaze into each other's eyes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS115
In bed, SOMEONE wakes up.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS116
SOMEONE shuts the door on a potbelly stove.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS117
SOMEONE gets out a leather-handled box.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS118
SOMEONE returns to his chair facing SOMEONE and takes a rag from the box. Unseen, SOMEONE steps up to a curtain doorway
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS120
His wife looks tenderly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS121
As she caresses the
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS122
cast, he looks into her eyes. SOMEONE's chin trembles. He briefly bows his head, then forces words out.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS123
She shakes her head.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS124
As SOMEONE bows his head again, SOMEONE keeps her tear-moistened eyes on him. She leans close, nearly pressing her forehead to his, and drives her gaze squarely at him.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS125
She cups his cheeks and kisses him. SOMEONE watches.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS126
SOMEONE sits on SOMEONE's lap. They share a deep kiss then warm smiles. SOMEONE rests his head on her shoulder.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS127
Closing his eyes, he wraps his arms around her. Daytime. Water droplets sag off the gate at the docks.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS128
The eager men point.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS129
SOMEONE watches the foreman pace a few feet away.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS130
The foreman steps closer.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS131
view shows him choose another. He points again. The view focuses on SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS132
SOMEONE nods.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS135
SOMEONE and SOMEONE start loading another dolly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS136
They move another sack. SOMEONE doubles over briefly and flexes his fingers.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS137
As SOMEONE reaches for another sack, SOMEONE joins him. The foreman notices SOMEONE's cast, painted to match his coat sleeve.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS138
SOMEONE looks from the supervisor to SOMEONE. SOMEONE straightens his cap under the foreman's stern gaze and hooks the next sack.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS139
SOMEONE and SOMEONE resume hauling sacks onto the dolly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS140
SOMEONE smiles.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS141
Later, they enter a bar.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS142
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS143
The two men find a table.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS144
A title. December 1933. As a man shovels snow outside a dress shop, SOMEONE arrives.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS145
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk down the alley to the Tenement Courtyard and halt.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS146
A man tinkers with an electric meter.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS147
He adjusts the utility box. In the light snowfall, SOMEONE gazes up.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS148
Later, by candlelight, SOMEONE stacks coins onto a two-dollar SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS149
SOMEONE serves dinner on a plate.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS150
SOMEONE joins him at the table.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS151
SOMEONE nods and fidgets with her wedding ring.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS152
SOMEONE chuckles and smiles.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS153
SOMEONE holds out her hands, palms up, and SOMEONE takes them in his own
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS154
and they both look toward the children's bed.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS155
SOMEONE frowns then SOMEONE leads them in prayer. As she bows her head, SOMEONE opens his eyes and shifts restlessly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS156
SOMEONE lifts her gaze to his.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS157
He lets go of her hands.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS158
A billboard shows a rosy-cheeked lady smiling over her steering wheel next to a chipper dog. It reads, Buy at the Esso sign for happy motoring. In the snow beneath the sign,
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS159
SOMEONE and the children pull lattice boards off its base.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS160
Nearby, a woman hurries after a man who marches away with luggage.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS161
Later, SOMEONE stokes their stove.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS162
SOMEONE reads to SOMEONE. SOMEONE sleeps near the stove.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS163
SOMEONE takes a mug in hand and leans over SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS164
weakly rolls his head to face her. A knit cap frames his flushed complexion.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS165
She adjusts his blankets.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS166
SOMEONE stays at his side. Her lips crease into a deep frown.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS167
As SOMEONE trembles, SOMEONE looks to her eldest son.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS168
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch her exit quickly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS169
In her sweater and scarf, SOMEONE crosses the snow to an alcove between buildings. Indoors, SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap a look. Outside, SOMEONE shifts on her feet, her face seizing with grief. Sheltered from the lightly falling snow, she turns toward the building.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS170
She leans on the brick wall.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS171
Later, inside, a coalscuttle sits empty next to the stove whose open grate reveals dying embers. SOMEONE paces nearby, rubbing her hands together.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS173
SOMEONE remains by the wood stove. SOMEONE marches deeper inside and finds the two beds empty.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS174
SOMEONE stands still before her. His green eyes lift.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS175
SOMEONE squares her chin and swallows hard.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS176
SOMEONE walks away.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS177
He drops change on the table.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS178
SOMEONE shrugs then lowers his head and walks to the door.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS179
SOMEONE races after him.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS180
Outside, SOMEONE pulls his coat tight and walks off. With snow steadily falling, SOMEONE stands alone in the white courtyard.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS181
SOMEONE heads down a street.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS182
protruding from his cast. Later, indoors, a sign reads, Emergency relief administration of New Jersey. A man faces a clerk's grid wire window.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS183
window, a chestnut haired clerk counts out
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS184
a few five and two dollar bills for SOMEONE. As she slides it into an envelope, the clerk looks into SOMEONE's eyes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS185
He shifts his eyes uneasily.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS187
He's on a boat, heading to New York City. A sign on its stern reads, Weehawken Ferry.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS188
street, SOMEONE passes two children collecting water from a hydrant.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS189
Men and women in elegant attire carry wrapped presents as they cross from under an awning to a Rolls Royce.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS190
The unemployed boxer makes his way past them, his gaze fixed.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS191
SOMEONE stops and stares across the street. His eyes scan the marquee for Madison Square Garden.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS192
His hands slung in his pockets, he heads toward the entrance.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS193
inside, he lightly taps on a door and enters a boxing club. He nods to a man in a suit and walks into the smoky lounge. SOMEONE passes businessmen at tables and makes his way to the front of the room by a bar.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS194
Men in sofas and armchairs fix their attention on the decommissioned boxer. SOMEONE watches gravely.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS195
More men face SOMEONE. With his head lowered, he takes a deep breath.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS196
SOMEONE removes his cap and shrugs.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS197
The humble father looks at the men then drops his gaze.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS198
A man in a vest bows his head.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS199
SOMEONE's gaze sinks.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS200
With tears in his eyes, SOMEONE swallows.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS201
Keeping still, the businessmen eye the man standing before them. A hefty patron looks around the room then gets up.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS202
He reaches into his pocket and signals for SOMEONE to step forward. The hefty man places a SOMEONE in SOMEONE's cap.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS203
An older gentleman adds a few coins.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS204
As another member contributes, SOMEONE's face brightens. He looks at two more gentlemen. They turn their heads and walk away.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS205
Seated at a desk, SOMEONE gazes off and rubs his lips. SOMEONE steps toward a sofa in the club where SOMEONE stands up. The promoter reaches into his pocket then lets a handful of coins slide into the hat. Another gentleman drops in a few bills. As SOMEONE lowers his gaze, a seated patron reaches out.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS206
SOMEONE looks on solemnly and presses his lips together. The decommissioned boxer meets his gaze.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS207
SOMEONE glances around the room then heads toward SOMEONE. Passing framed pictures and a mirror, he reaches his old manager at the desk.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS208
SOMEONE rises from his chair.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS209
SOMEONE's tear-filled eyes dart away from SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS210
SOMEONE picks through his cap and counts the donations.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS211
He shakes his head.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS212
SOMEONE reaches into his pocket.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS213
Now at the basement apartment,
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS214
them, SOMEONE sets down their luggage. In the bedroom, SOMEONE jumps on a bed.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS215
takes a seat at the kitchen table and watches his boys. He shifts his attention to SOMEONE playing with a doll. Springtime.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS216
Bright sun, several families gather around a birthday cake.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS217
a dozen children blow out the candles.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS218
As the children devour cake slices, a priest approaches.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS219
Across the street, a woman follows SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS220
SOMEONE stands slack jawed.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS221
SOMEONE runs after her husband. Now in the Tenement Courtyard, a woman sweeps dust out of a garage set up as an apartment. While SOMEONE bounces a ball off a wall, SOMEONE crouches facing SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS222
slides her fist into his cheek. As SOMEONE approaches, SOMEONE throws punches into her dad's hand.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS223
SOMEONE's arrival distracts SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS224
SOMEONE's next punch hits SOMEONE's cheek.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS225
kisses SOMEONE then runs off.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS226
They shake hands.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS227
SOMEONE studies SOMEONE's face.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS228
As SOMEONE stops, SOMEONE shakes his head.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS229
SOMEONE hugs him. Nighttime. A sign reads, Primo Carnera versus Max Baer, World's Heavyweight Championship. Words appear. Madison Square.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS230
SOMEONE holds up a pair of bright red boxing shoes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS231
SOMEONE looks up.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS232
SOMEONE walks out. With a bowl of hash sitting in front of him, SOMEONE paces. He scans the locker room then leans over and eats out of the bowl.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS233
As a balding man signals to SOMEONE, the boxer looks back at his surprise visitor.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS234
SOMEONE wipes his face with a towel.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS235
As the boxer walks out, the chuckling reporter puffs a cigarette. Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk side by side down a hallway leading to the arena. Sporty enters the press box.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS238
At SOMEONE's bar, SOMEONE approaches the radio.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS240
A sign reads, Round 3.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS241
In the locker room, SOMEONE uses a spoon to finish the hash. SOMEONE enters.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS242
SOMEONE softens his gaze.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS243
The winner smiles and nods.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS244
SOMEONE opens the door to a crush of reporters.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS245
Now in the basement apartment, a nightstand lamp shines next to the kids' bed. Lying on their backs, their eyes remain wide open.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS246
They quickly lift their heads.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS247
As they patter into the kitchen, SOMEONE walks in. SOMEONE emerges in her bib front apron and watches her husband shut the door behind him.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS248
SOMEONE sits wearily, his gaze turned downward. He reaches into his vest pocket, takes something out, and palms it.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS249
SOMEONE cranes to see. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare. SOMEONE stands behind the children wringing
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS250
A tentative smile settles on her
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS251
SOMEONE holds up some money. The children
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS252
SOMEONE meets her worried glance.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS253
As SOMEONE nods and smiles, SOMEONE lifts his lips to hers. Pressing against him, SOMEONE puts her free hand on his shoulder as she turns the meat. Daytime. At the docks, SOMEONE flexes his right hand and glances at the padlocked gate.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS254
SOMEONE peers through the gate.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS255
SOMEONE smiles.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS256
Later, a man hands SOMEONE a pair of meat hooks. SOMEONE heads toward the dock.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS257
Motioning SOMEONE aside, SOMEONE shows him a sports page headline. Amazing! Braddock KOs SOMEONE in Three.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS258
SOMEONE regards the paper, nods and smiles.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS259
SOMEONE and SOMEONE load the bales onto
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS260
Each bundle fills a worker's dolly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS261
As they hook another bale, SOMEONE nods.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS262
Now in SOMEONE's neighborhood.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS263
In his parked car, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE and SOMEONE walking forward. SOMEONE sees him drive off.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS264
SOMEONE runs down the alley past SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS265
SOMEONE and SOMEONE play in a decrepit car parked by the courtyard garages. SOMEONE and a friend go to her fort.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS266
SOMEONE shrugs.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS267
Pacing with aimless steps, SOMEONE smiles over a wad of bills.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS268
SOMEONE's worried gaze shifts to the money.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS269
SOMEONE gives her the money.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS270
He strokes her hair, steps back, and folds his arms with a smile.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS271
SOMEONE lifts SOMEONE up.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS272
he gazes up into her eyes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS273
Suspended off her feet, SOMEONE blinks thoughtfully as she eyes him. SOMEONE grins and kisses her. With their arms wrapped around each other, SOMEONE gently sets her down.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS274
SOMEONE sadly lowers her gaze then lifts it. SOMEONE strokes her chin.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS275
He slings SOMEONE over his shoulder.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS276
Pouting slightly, SOMEONE resolutely juts out her chin. Now, SOMEONE marches across a busy street. The square roofed automobiles that pass have chromy grills and bug eyed headlights. SOMEONE rounds a corner wearing a dressy russet blouse and a brown cloche hat. Behind her, two vendors sit at a folding table and men in business suits and fedoras follow different paths. SOMEONE crosses a carpet to a residential building's posh entry. Inside, she faces an apartment door.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS277
SOMEONE lifts her knuckles to the wood again.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS278
Inside, SOMEONE walks to the door and checks the peephole.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS279
SOMEONE stays put.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS280
As a woman inside approaches, SOMEONE lifts a shushing finger.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS281
The door remains shut.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS283
SOMEONE steps into an elegant and virtually empty room. Under a crystal chandelier, a card table and folding chairs sit on a parquet floor.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS284
Later, SOMEONE pours tea. The ladies each sit with a blossom patterned china cup.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS285
SOMEONE gives the door a dismissive wave.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS286
He puts up his dukes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS287
Mrs. Gould bites her lip and shifts her gaze.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS288
SOMEONE shakes his head.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS289
SOMEONE gives his wife a dapper half smile.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS290
As the women smile, SOMEONE glances at each then leaves them. Mrs. Gould watches him disappear behind the doorway
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS291
then lets her smile fade. Her gaze shifts uneasily and settles on Mrs. Braddock.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS292
Sunlight silhouettes the two women.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS293
Mrs. Gould looks away, smiles, and shakes her head.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS295
Two classical columns support an empty mantle.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS296
Now in the promoter's office, SOMEONE puffs a cigar.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS297
SOMEONE scoots his chair closer.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS298
SOMEONE leans back in his chair.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS299
As SOMEONE draws on his cigar, the tips glows bright orange. He removes the stogie from his lips and glances about the dimly lighted room.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS300
Sleeves rolled up, he cocks his head.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS301
SOMEONE dampens a brief smile.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS302
Later, Jeanette, SOMEONE's trainer, watches the bulldog.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS303
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE to a corner.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS304
SOMEONE nods.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS305
He meets SOMEONE's gaze.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS307
At home, SOMEONE packs SOMEONE's trunks into a brown paper bag as he straightens a tie tucked under his vest. She faces him sadly as he approaches.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS308
SOMEONE musters a smile.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS309
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE on the cheek.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS310
Grinning, he backs out the door.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS311
His wife's gaze sinks heavily to the floor.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS312
Now in a ring, SOMEONE faces an African-American boxer. As they advance on each other in slow motion.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS313
Madison Square Garden. November 16.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS314
blows, then SOMEONE counters with a right hook.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS315
Circling left, SOMEONE jabs at SOMEONE's head. SOMEONE dodges.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS316
SOMEONE takes a barrage of hits.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS317
SOMEONE moves in, slugging SOMEONE's head.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS320
The sports writers applaud.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS321
SOMEONE's view blurs.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS322
His opponent goes for his face
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS323
Staggering, SOMEONE remembers his children sleeping in one bed and eating in a soup kitchen. Quick flashes show SOMEONE frowning and the past due notice on the milk bottle. SOMEONE looks up at Lasky who appears to sink away. His mouthpiece tumbles across the canvas leaving a trail of spit. Fans rise from their seats. Remembering his children's bed lying empty, SOMEONE looks up at his opponent's swollen face. The bulldog grins, blood trickling from his mouth as he crosses the ring.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS324
his nimble footwork.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS326
the crowd covers their mouth as SOMEONE throws more punches.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS327
Card reads, Round 13.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS328
SOMEONE looks around.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS329
The pudgy well-dressed passenger steps out into a hotel hallway.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS330
As Baer glares back at his two scantily clad guests, the well-dressed man rolls his eyes. The bare chested champion faces Baer.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS331
Baer shuts the door in his face.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS332
Now at the relief office, SOMEONE stands in one of the many long lines. A few people notice him and crowd close, whispering.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS333
His face bruised and swollen, SOMEONE eyes the gossipers. He gives them a shy wave. Later, at the chestnut haired clerk's window, he places a form on the counter then sets down a roll of cash bound in rubber bands. A note around the money lists the amount, $323. 60. SOMEONE drops some coins on the form and slides it all to the clerk. Picking up the roll of bills, she eyes him strangely. He smiles. Now at home, SOMEONE peers through the front door's window at SOMEONE. He enters with a bouquet of roses.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS334
He holds the flowers out over the kitchen table. SOMEONE reads the attached note and smiles.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS335
She runs her hand over her husband's. He removes his cap.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS336
SOMEONE enters.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS337
takes a seat. SOMEONE stands hunched over the table.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS338
Shadows mask SOMEONE's troubled face.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS339
Later in the dark, men flee past SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS340
He moves through an array of crowded shacks.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS341
Words appear. Hooverville. Central Park, New York City.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS342
SOMEONE eyes a poster of Little Red Riding Hood and the Big Bad Wolf.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS343
A man hurls a bottle.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS344
A resident vomits.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS345
SOMEONE turns, looking all around. Three men eye him coldly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS346
SOMEONE wanders between the shanties.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS347
Seeing a group of cops beating a man with clubs, SOMEONE hides back against a wall.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS348
Policemen hold back a crowd.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS349
Beyond an overturned wagon, men try to put out a fire.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS350
SOMEONE watches medics carry a body away on a stretcher.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS351
A man lies on the ground, his chest heaving.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS353
The boxer kneels to him.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS354
Two ambulance workers fold SOMEONE's arms across his chest and hoist him onto a stretcher. Fire glows on SOMEONE's face
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS355
as he watches them carry SOMEONE away.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS356
SOMEONE stands in the open pit, wiping his hands.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS357
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE stand with other mourners.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS358
Behind the priest, gravediggers idle near a truck filled with several more of the simple wood caskets. SOMEONE and another worker climb out from the grave which is filled with a long row of coffins.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS359
Wearing a black vest and tie, the boxer joins his family.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS360
SOMEONE holds onto her black shawl as it billows in the wind.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS361
SOMEONE watches her sadly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS362
SOMEONE's wife looks down at SOMEONE's plain pine coffin. Now at a press conference,
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS363
SOMEONE and SOMEONE strain to keep smiles on their faces.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS364
SOMEONE sits next to them.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS365
The boxer leans into a row of radio station microphones.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS366
His wife watches closely.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS367
SOMEONE leans closer to the bank of microphones.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS368
SOMEONE gapes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS369
Later, a woman shows SOMEONE and SOMEONE into an office. They wear their suits from the press conference.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS370
SOMEONE picks up a newspaper.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS371
He sets it down on the corner of his desk for SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS372
He closes the window blinds.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS373
Furrowing his brow, SOMEONE trades look with his fighter.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS374
Scowling, SOMEONE's manager watches Mills cross the room.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS375
He closes the drapes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS376
SOMEONE starts a film projector. On a screen, black and white footage of a fight flickers in and out of focus.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS377
He fights, hunched forward.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS378
SOMEONE looks over at SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS379
In the film, Baer hits Campbell repeatedly in the head, knocking him to a corner.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS380
Light flickers on SOMEONE's sober face. Baer nails Campbell with series of hooks.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS381
Baer knocks his opponent down.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS382
The referee checks Campbell and waves frantically at the officials. The fighter's corner men rush to his side.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS383
SOMEONE stops the projector. SOMEONE keeps his eyes glued to the screen as the promoter rewinds the reel.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS384
Campbell rises up from the canvas. SOMEONE rises from his seat.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS386
SOMEONE and SOMEONE give him surprised looks. The promoter starts the projector again, playing the reel forward. As the two fighters square off, SOMEONE steps closer, studying the footage intently. Baer hits Campbell repeatedly in the head, knocking him to a corner. SOMEONE shifts his jaw as the giant slugger nails his opponent with a series of hooks. A quick color drained flash takes us into the fight. As Campbell leans over against the ropes, Baer winds up his right arm and knocks the fighter down with a haymaker. His body rolls back with a lifeless gaze.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS387
The footage shows the referee checking the downed fighter and his corner men rushing in. As Baer towers over them, SOMEONE swallows. Back in the ring, Baer adjusts his gloves as he looks at us. The projector's light flickers on SOMEONE's face. Now Baer approaches with a vacant trance-like stare. One side of SOMEONE's face twitches. The footage shows Baer's trainer throwing a towel over the slugger's shoulder.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS388
The film stops.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS389
He opens the drapes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS390
SOMEONE looks at his manager who gives him a grim look.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS391
Blinking, he faces SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS392
Squinting, SOMEONE shifts on his feet.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS393
a smile, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS394
The promoter stands near a window.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS395
Bathed in sunlight, SOMEONE looks down at his lawyer who nods.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS396
Now, a waiter carries a covered silver tray into an elegant club.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS397
formal wear dance at the center of the dining area.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS398
follows Mrs. Gould to their table.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS399
SOMEONE holds a cigar as he reads.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS400
A waiter starts to clear the table.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS401
wraps the rest of her steak in her napkin.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS402
Baer arrives and shakes hands with the SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS403
The Cinderella Man follows his wife's gaze. As a waiter removes Baer's fur coat.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS404
SOMEONE turns in his seat, facing the large man fully.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS405
winks as he crosses the room with a group of well-dressed friends. The Braddock’s and Gould’s watch
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS406
SOMEONE cocks an eyebrow.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS407
SOMEONE brings a bottle of champagne.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS408
waiter sets out glasses. SOMEONE straightens his suit jacket.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS409
As his fighter crosses the room, SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a reassuring gesture. At the bar, Baer stands and shakes SOMEONE's hand.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS410
He cocks his head and nods.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS411
As the photographers crowd before them, Baer poses.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS412
She slams the glass down and stomps off.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS413
Jaw tensed, SOMEONE shifts on his feet. A smile crosses his face.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS414
nears the exit. His smile fades.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS415
Now in the apartment, SOMEONE cleans a skillet.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS419
Staring fearfully, the children nod. SOMEONE yanks off her apron and marches out.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS420
SOMEONE leans to his children.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS422
SOMEONE closes the apartment door behind him.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS423
Light shines down on the couple standing close together.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS424
The overhead lamp highlights SOMEONE's pained face.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS425
SOMEONE sits on the ring's edge with a towel draped over his neck.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS426
At a railing above the ring, Jeanette frowns. SOMEONE joins him.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS427
A man whispers up to them.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS429
appear. Day of the fight, June 1935.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS430
SOMEONE packs a book-sized kit into a bag
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS431
She meets his gaze.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS432
Later, outside the rundown tenement, a man hurries to a railing overlooking the alley. SOMEONE and his family walk to the curb.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS433
As the fighter reaches for a car door stops.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS434
Other families watch from the sidewalk.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS435
Standing by the car's open door, SOMEONE looks back at his wife.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS436
hat cocked stylishly on her.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS437
His shoulders shift beneath his crisp blue suit as he takes a few steps toward her and kisses her pale cheek.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS438
As she closes her eyes, SOMEONE regards his three children standing in a row. He smooths SOMEONE's hair and kisses her.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS439
His daughter looks up at him seriously.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS440
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE's forehead.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS441
Stepping before SOMEONE, SOMEONE extends his hand. The young boy gives it a firm shake and his father proudly pats his cheek.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS442
SOMEONE extends his hand.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS443
it, arching his brow and smiling.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS444
His smile fades as he notices SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS445
She presses her lips into a tight smile and nods slightly. SOMEONE's lip part and they share a long look between shallow breaths.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS446
SOMEONE's jaw clenches shut.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS447
SOMEONE ushers her children away.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS448
SOMEONE leans on the car's door as he
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS449
Another family and four women huddled in a doorway.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS450
Now, SOMEONE jostles slightly in a taxi's back seat as it passes a sign advertising the fight. Arriving patrons wave to him. The men and women
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS451
stadium, some dressed in suits, others in everyday clothes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS452
SOMEONE waves back. Elsewhere, a woman opens a door for SOMEONE and her children.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS453
As SOMEONE walks off, the children wander into their aunt’s house. SOMEONE eyes a boxy wooden radio as an older man waves to SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS454
makes the sign of the cross and
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS455
then steps beside their priest.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS456
He nods then looks forward.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS457
SOMEONE turns her stunned gaze from the priest.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS458
Our view follows to the many pews filled with working class families.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS459
The priest smiles brightly. SOMEONE stares thoughtfully.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS460
An overhead view shows people crowding through the stadium entryway.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS461
Madison Square Garden Bowl, Long Island City, New York. Our view lifts over the rim of the stadium to the rows of sparsely filled seats surrounding the brightly lit boxing ring. The New York skyline looms in the distance.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS462
In the locker room, SOMEONE drops some cash on his bag.  He sets down his wedding ring by his pocket watch.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS464
SOMEONE lies on a bench nearby tapping his fingers on his chest and whistling at the ceiling. SOMEONE slides down his suspenders.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS466
He peels off his dress shirt and grabs a coat hanger.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS467
SOMEONE briefly lifts his head off a bunch of towels serving as a pillow
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS468
He again gazes at the ceiling.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS469
SOMEONE saunters around the room
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS470
finds a rolls of tape in SOMEONE's mouth.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS471
As SOMEONE stands, SOMEONE bounces on his feet.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS472
He sits on the empty bench and SOMEONE feels his outstretched hand.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS473
SOMEONE rounds a corner.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS474
Both men look up and stare.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS476
As SOMEONE goes to address his manager, halts his open mouth with his palm.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS477
then walks out past SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS478
They share a smile and SOMEONE exits.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS479
his feet, SOMEONE leans on the wall.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS480
SOMEONE shrugs his brow.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS481
She nods, smiling broadly. SOMEONE crosses to her and she meets him halfway. She grips his shoulders and looks into his eyes.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS482
Her strained grin fades to a misty
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS483
as she pats his chest.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS485
She gently strokes his face then pulls back with a weak smile.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS486
As SOMEONE's gaze lowers, she turns around and walks out.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS487
Now, filaments in a vacuum tube glow to life.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS488
In the church, the Father tunes in a radio.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS489
Reaching the aisle, SOMEONE wears a silky blue robe, his name printed across the back arcs above a bulldog emblem. With SOMEONE just behind him, the fighter passes two guards and looks around the packed arena.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS490
Seated fans crane for a look. A man points. SOMEONE takes a deep breath.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS491
SOMEONE eyes the staring crowd. With a nervous look, he glances back at SOMEONE then starts toward the ring.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS492
A few cameras flash.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS493
Following his manager, SOMEONE climbs the stairs to the ring. As SOMEONE stretches the top rope high, he winks. Our view tilts and sidles under the rope into the ring where a referee and several gentlemen wait. A tall balding man removes his hat and SOMEONE nods. As SOMEONE faces the crowd, his wife grins in a bright red hat and waves. The manager smiles at her. SOMEONE jogs in place.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS494
Now inside her dark house, SOMEONE heads down a hallway and opens a door.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS495
Standing on the basement stairs with the radio, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE look up innocently.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS497
The defending champion lingers in the hallway.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS498
Smiling, SOMEONE looks at the packed stands.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS499
SOMEONE waves an arm over the rope. Now Mr. SOMEONE takes a seat. As the timekeeper raises a mallet, Sporty looks toward SOMEONE's corner.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS500
As SOMEONE glares fiercely at SOMEONE, the timekeeper hits the bell.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS501
The fighters move to the center and shuffle around each other. SOMEONE's face grows smug and he winks at SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS502
He hits SOMEONE's chest. They clinch and punches SOMEONE in the face.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS506
The opponent rams his stomach.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS508
A needle on a timer ticks around.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS509
As SOMEONE jabs SOMEONE flat on the nose,
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS511
SOMEONE glares at his opponent.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS513
As the boxers face off, SOMEONE hits below the waist.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS514
SOMEONE rushes his opponent.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS515
the champ's ribs.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS516
SOMEONE's manager sponges water on him.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS517
As SOMEONE drinks, he sees men and women in the crowd eyeing him dubiously. The timekeeper slaps the mat.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS518
SOMEONE stands and glares, his brow hard set over a vengeful gaze. In the opposite corner, SOMEONE rolls his neck. The champ eyeballs SOMEONE with a vacant trance-like stare.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS519
SOMEONE's right hook hits SOMEONE's chin.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS520
SOMEONE returns two jabs.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS521
SOMEONE's view turns blurry.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS522
SOMEONE dodges three hooks. As they clinch.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS523
SOMEONE's right hand winds up. SOMEONE's jaw takes the hit. His upper body torques. Sneering through blood,
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS524
lets bloody water dribble out his mouth.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS525
At Alice's, several ladies listen to the radio.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS526
SOMEONE arrives.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS527
SOMEONE looks to his sibling and SOMEONE frowns.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS528
SOMEONE approaches.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS529
Reaching the basement doorway, she eyes her huddled children, then SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS530
Her children peer earnestly up at her. SOMEONE leaves the gathering.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS532
Listening, SOMEONE covers her mouth. At the fight, SOMEONE pounds SOMEONE's side. SOMEONE shuts her eyes and presses her knuckles to her lips.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS533
SOMEONE moves in, swinging wildly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS534
Dozens listen intently at the bar, at the church, and Aunt SOMEONE's.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS535
As SOMEONE stands alone, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE in his corner.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS536
assails SOMEONE with three jabs and a right hook then ducks
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS538
At Alice's, SOMEONE frowns sadly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS539
At the arena, a spectator shouts through his cupped hand.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS540
Ref SOMEONE circles past SOMEONE's corner.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS542
The corner men insert each fighter's mouthpieces. SOMEONE sways and huffs in his corner.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS543
As SOMEONE stands, he leans over with his mitts propped on his knees. He lifts his gaze to SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS544
In a grainy blurred focused view from SOMEONE's corner, SOMEONE rubs his head and shakes his arms down. SOMEONE loosens his ankles with a little footwork.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS545
Ringside, the timekeeper raises his mallet.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS546
The fighters move to the center of the ring. SOMEONE seethes his head and shoulders hunched forward. SOMEONE's thoughtful gaze
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS547
mitts come together.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS549
SOMEONE lands a right hook right and wallops him. SOMEONE punches SOMEONE's face.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS550
Now SOMEONE pounds at SOMEONE's rib cage.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS552
SOMEONE joins the others near the radio.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS553
SOMEONE delivers a left jab. As SOMEONE swings
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS554
and slugs him hard.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS555
As SOMEONE gapes, SOMEONE staggers into the ropes. SOMEONE and Mrs. Gould stare fretfully. Dozens of spectators stand, craning for a look.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS556
At Alice's, SOMEONE looks to his mother. At SOMEONE's Bar, SOMEONE hangs his head. In the ring, SOMEONE hunches forward. With a sidelong gaze, he squints toward SOMEONE. As the defending champ closes in, SOMEONE envisions a hazy blanched view of Campbell crumbling under SOMEONE's
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS557
blow. The fallen fighter's gaze drains of life. Back in the actual arena, SOMEONE stays doubled over as
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS558
SOMEONE cock his arm back.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS559
lands a left punch to SOMEONE's midriff and a hook
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS560
SOMEONE into a clinch.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS561
with left and right hooks followed by an uppercut.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS562
SOMEONE reels then resumes his stance. Facing SOMEONE.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS563
In the arena, SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE. Jeanette puts a towel around the fighter's neck.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS564
SOMEONE eyes the crowd.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS565
man unlaces SOMEONE's gloves.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS566
As SOMEONE sobs, SOMEONE comforts her.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS568
crosses toward the judges, SOMEONE faces Jeanette.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS569
They watch the judges confer with the ref.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS570
A white mustached judge gestures adamantly.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS571
The radio. In the ring, SOMEONE looks around.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS572
Women pray over their rosaries. In the arena,
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS573
into the center of the ring. As the fighters in their corners
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS574
The microphone lowers. The announcer removes his hat and lifts his face toward the mic.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS576
turns and shakes hands with a gentleman in a suit.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS577
It shows a packed arena.
CINDERELLA_MAN_DVS578
They join the champion.