The bare-chested soldier watches the students halt at the end of the SOMEONE. A live young woman with wavy, corn silk hair, sets her purse on the railing.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS26
A boyish guy sits on the railings, sending her purse plunging into the water.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS27
As SOMEONE jogs up the SOMEONE toward the beach, the soldier jumps off the railing and plummets 15 feet into the water. The blonde's jaw drops. Underwater, the soldier swims down along the SOMEONE's barnacled supports. The purse stirs in the current, on the SOMEONE strewn ocean floor. The soldier seizes it, then kicks off the bottom and shoots back to the surface.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS28
The soldier swims toward the beach.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS29
On the sand, SOMEONE kicks off his flip-flops, and trots into the water, meeting the soldier in the surf.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS30
The soldier delivers it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS31
The smiling woman shakes her drenched bag.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS32
SOMEONE ambles off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS33
SOMEONE halts and walks back toward them.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS34
He grabs his surfboard.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS35
As SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE, he accidentally bangs his board on the SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS36
They head off side by side.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS37
The setting sun casts long shadows over the sand.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS38
Dear SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS39
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE Porter, and SOMEONE Jenkins.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS40
Now a date appears. Spring 2001.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS41
Guests mill about a SOMEONE beach house's natural un-landscaped yard. SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in an unlit fire pit.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS42
SOMEONE notices a bulky ring on SOMEONE's finger.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS43
SOMEONE brings SOMEONE a beer.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS44
SOMEONE mimes throwing punches.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS45
SOMEONE eyes him, coolly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS46
SOMEONE salutes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS47
He leaves.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS48
SOMEONE hangs his head with a subdued smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS49
SOMEONE regards SOMEONE candidly. Then allows a smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS50
He looks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS51
A tow-headed boy hugs her from behind.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS52
The young boy beams.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS53
SOMEONE peers downward.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS54
A bearded man joins them.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS55
SOMEONE plays with some driftwood.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS56
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS57
SOMEONE climbs over a log bench, and heads off with his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS58
He looks over his shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS59
SOMEONE gapes, and SOMEONE gives a stunned smirk. SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit back down.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS60
SOMEONE drops his gaze, and SOMEONE studies him with a warm smile. They lock eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS62
SOMEONE and SOMEONE ramble toward the water.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS63
They halt among tufted beach grass, and gaze up at the moon.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS64
As he demonstrates, she copies him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS65
She covers the moon with her thumb.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS66
SOMEONE watches enviously from the fire pit.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS67
Later, SOMEONE whacks a striker bar against a magnesium strip key-chain, instantly igniting a small campfire.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS69
Holding a hotdog on a stick, SOMEONE grins.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS70
SOMEONE bashfully glances at the fire and turns away. Then faces SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS71
She nods, beaming.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS72
He missteps, almost tripping into the fire. Then affects a cool recovery.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS73
Later, SOMEONE hobbles down a deserted road in his flip-flops, carrying his surfboard under one arm.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS74
A pickup slows beside him. It's SOMEONE. SOMEONE ride shotgun.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS75
He stumbles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS76
SOMEONE loads his board into the bed of the truck. Later they drive.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS77
SOMEONE points at SOMEONE with a nod.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS78
SOMEONE sways capriciously and tickles the men's necks. Now the truck stops before a modest home with a bushy tree in the front yard. SOMEONE climbs out.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS79
SOMEONE heads off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS80
He carries his board toward the house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS81
Now, SOMEONE opens the front door and enters a room veiled in shadow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS82
In a study, a balding man wearing a single white glove examines a coin under a magnifying glass. SOMEONE lifts the edge of a window shade covering the room's French door, and peeks inside at his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS83
The oblivious man's gaze remains locked on his coin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS84
SOMEONE lets go of the shade and walks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS85
His father glances over his shoulder, then stares off glumly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS86
SOMEONE heads into his room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS88
Outside, laundry whips on a line in the wind.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS89
In the kitchen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS90
SOMEONE's father purses his lips into a thoughtful frown, and digs in his pocket. He pulls out a set of keys and hands them to SOMEONE, who ambles toward the door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS91
Later, a sign on a shabby seaside building reads, Bowens Island Restaurant.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS92
Loitering men spot SOMEONE and swap looks. A goateed guy speaks up.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS93
SOMEONE inches over to him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS94
SOMEONE joins a puzzled SOMEONE a few steps ahead of him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS95
Later in the restaurant.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS96
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE blankly, and offers a fleeting grin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS97
She smiles back.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS98
At twilight, two men fish on the dock outside the restaurant. Back inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS99
She smiles quizzically.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS100
He munches some food. Eyes the rosy-cheeked young woman, then shyly bows his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS101
SOMEONE locks her in his sudden sobered gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS102
Later, they stroll toward his front door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS103
They head inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS104
SOMEONE's father looks up from his desk.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS105
He stands to greet them.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS106
She extends a hand.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS107
He bashfully shakes it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS108
She notices a coin collection.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS109
He takes a coin from her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS110
He rubs it vigorously on his shirt. Then peers at her through his glasses.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS111
He gives her a white cotton glove.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS112
He covers a wheel printed on the coin with a silver dollar.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS113
He brings out more.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS114
Now the SOMEONE family car pulls up in front of SOMEONE's house. Riding with SOMEONE, she beams.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS115
SOMEONE chews his pursed lips. Leaning over, SOMEONE gives him a kiss on the cheek. Then gets out of the car.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS116
SOMEONE grins at him and shuts the door. He happily gazes after her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS118
At the beach, SOMEONE paddles his surfboard out over the breaking waves. He crests one, then swims farther out.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS119
Later, he paddles with a flow of a swelling wave, as its foaming crest reaches his board, he gets to his feet and surfs it until it breaks. Later, he sits straddling his board, gazing at the houses along the shore.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS120
Later still, he paddles out past a stone jetty.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS121
At her house, SOMEONE steps out on her screened-in porch, and gazes toward the beach.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS122
Now she walks with SOMEONE, as he carries his board from the water.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS123
They stroll toward her home.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS124
Now they approach a partially constructed house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS126
Later, she leads him through the house's framework.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS127
It starts to rain.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS128
She leads him under a cluster of boards supported by a beam.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS129
They stand close together.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS130
She strokes his eyebrow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS131
Looking away, SOMEONE works his mouth.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS132
SOMEONE shrugs.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS133
SOMEONE rests his cheek against the side of the beam.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS134
SOMEONE gazes tenderly at SOMEONE. He leans his face closer to her, and she smiles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS135
She lifts her chin and her nose brushes against his.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS136
Opening her mouth, she kisses him hungrily.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS137
SOMEONE drapes her arms around his neck, as they passionately make out. He lifts her up, and she wraps her legs around him. As SOMEONE lowers himself to the floor, she straddles his lap.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS138
Now, as they walk down a sidewalk, SOMEONE clasps SOMEONE's hand to his chest. At the sun dappled construction site, SOMEONE arrives to find him working at the top of a ladder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS139
She stops, watching him appreciatively.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS140
He spots her, and they share a warm smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS141
Now, SOMEONE holds his surfboard, tucked under his arm as they trod into the ocean. Later a wet-suit clad SOMEONE, crouches low on the board as she awkwardly rides a wave.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS142
Tumbling into the shallow water, she grins. From the shore, her female friend pouts beside SOMEONE, who sullenly watches the couple. Trying another wave, SOMEONE manages to stand briefly as SOMEONE cheers her on.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS143
Now, she hugs his arm as they walk hand in hand past a cafe. At the SOMEONE house, the young couple enjoys a meal with SOMEONE's father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS144
Later, silhouetted by a dusky sky, SOMEONE frolics on the beach, playfully evading SOMEONE's grasp.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS145
He finally catches her in his arms. Lifts her and spins. At the construction site, the couple adds a plywood board to a wall. She swats her hand in front of him, as he hammers it in place.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS146
In a living room, SOMEONE sings and plays guitar for SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS147
In a hallway, SOMEONE sneaks up on her as she shuts a door. He turns her to face him, and they share a tender kiss.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS148
SOMEONE peeks around a corner.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS149
As his father paces in the living room, SOMEONE carries his girlfriend upstairs. Now they tumble unto his bed.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS151
Mr. SOMEONE slows, blinking.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS152
He gives a startled turn, then stares off. His brow knitted.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS153
Upstairs SOMEONE rolls off the bed, then scrambles to a closet and shuts herself in.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS154
She pulls at the door knobs, but he yanks the doors open.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS155
Pouncing at her side, he tickles her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS156
As our view drifts upward, his armed uniform obscures them from view.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS157
Back in the living room, SOMEONE smiles as she plays the guitar.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS158
Reclining beside her, SOMEONE beams appreciatively.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS159
Now, tall reeds wave in a breeze as the young man hikes into view, and gazes ahead. On the beach, a small group plays volleyball amidst a boisterous party. Near a grill, SOMEONE pats SOMEONE's shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS160
Another group sits around two young men playing acoustic guitars.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS161
SOMEONE hangs back, pensively taking in the cheerful scene.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS162
Turning, he spots a solitary figure sitting alone at the base of a grassy dune.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS163
At the volleyball net, SOMEONE pauses. He watches his rival cross to the dune, then turns back to his game.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS164
SOMEONE hikes along a grassy ridge towards SOMEONE, and sneaks down behind her. He playfully grabs her side, startling the live young beauty.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS165
She smiles contentedly in his arms.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS166
SOMEONE lowers her troubled gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS167
Pulling her closer, SOMEONE kisses her brow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS168
He rocks her in his arms.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS169
Her lips creep into a faint smile, and he kisses her brow again.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS170
Turning, SOMEONE wraps her arms around him and lays him back against the dune.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS171
Later, they stroll toward the party.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS172
SOMEONE trots ahead a few paces and bends to pick up a seashell. As she straightens and pockets it, SOMEONE drapes a loving arm around her shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS173
He stops and faces her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS174
SOMEONE lowers her gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS175
SOMEONE starts to speak, then turns away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS176
He sulks off, leaving his girlfriend behind.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS177
Reaching the party, he heads up a boardwalk.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS178
SOMEONE tosses him a can.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS179
SOMEONE chucks it aside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS180
SOMEONE pulls him aside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS181
He touches SOMEONE's chest. The soldier flings him to the ground. His buddy runs over, and SOMEONE punches him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS182
SOMEONE rushes up behind the soldier. SOMEONE elbows him in the face.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS183
Glaring lividly, SOMEONE smacks his arm. SOMEONE faces her briefly, then leaves. SOMEONE cups a hand over his nose.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS184
SOMEONE crouches to him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS185
At dusk, SOMEONE hikes along a dirt road. His feature obscured by shadow. An SUV rounds a turn, pulls up beside him, and continues on.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS186
Silhouetted against the gray sky, SOMEONE bows his head. His stride unbroken.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS188
Daytime, SOMEONE stands on SOMEONE's porch, knocking on the screen door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS189
In the next yard, SOMEONE takes out the trash, sporting a black eye and a swollen nose.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS190
SOMEONE approaches him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS191
SOMEONE shrugs his hand and steps forward.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS192
Getting a look at his face, SOMEONE slows.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS193
SOMEONE fishes a scrap of paper from the trash bin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS194
SOMEONE meets the kind man who hands him the paper with a pen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS195
SOMEONE nods, and steps away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS196
Now an oven door opens, revealing two pans of lasagna.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS197
A pair of hands and oven mitts take them out and sets them on a stove. SOMEONE wanders into the kitchen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS198
SOMEONE shuffles into the dining room. His father closes the oven door, crosses to an island counter and watches him. The young man clears one of three place settings from the dining room table. Taking it into the kitchen, he sets the plate, place mat and glass on the island. His father looks on as he starts to put the silverware away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS199
SOMEONE puts the silverware back down.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS200
As he steps away, Mr. SOMEONE methodically sets the silverware aside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS201
He picks up the plate in both hands. Sets it at a precise angle in a wooden case, and slides a glass door close in front of it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS202
Later, we watch through a doorway, as father and son eat at the dining room table. SOMEONE gazes off as he chews, then looks down at his plate.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS203
His father picks at his food.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS204
SOMEONE watches him with a concerned expression.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS205
With a melancholy stare, Mr. SOMEONE scoops a large fork full of lasagna into his mouth and chews.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS206
He turns, facing a window. SOMEONE follows his gaze to find SOMEONE's car pulling up outside. Standing, he leaves the table.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS207
He goes outside and jogs down off the porch. Getting out of her car, SOMEONE faces him with an affectionate smirk.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS208
They embrace.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS209
He caresses her corn silk hair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS210
He kisses her smooth forehead.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS211
She warps her arms around him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS212
She gives him an envelope and he starts to open it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS213
He drapes an arm around her shoulder and she hugs his waist as they head inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS214
Now they eat dinner with SOMEONE's father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS215
Later as SOMEONE sits in her car, SOMEONE leans through the window and playfully grapples with her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS216
She turns her face toward his and kisses him. In the house, Mr. SOMEONE looks up from his coins. A window shows SOMEONE's car pulling away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS217
SOMEONE gazes after her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS218
His image recedes as she drives away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS219
With glistening eyes, SOMEONE watches him through her rear-view mirror.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS220
She tearfully looks away, and watches the road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS221
Now at a bus station.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS222
He takes two bags from his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS223
The young man boards a waiting bus.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS224
Its long side window shows Mr. SOMEONE lingering on the spot, staring off as he stuffs his hands into his pockets. The bus pulls away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS225
On the bus, SOMEONE reads SOMEONE's letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS226
Now amongst sleeping soldiers, SOMEONE reads by flashlight.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS227
Daytime at an airfield.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS228
The soldiers file off a plane in their camouflaged uniforms. Each carrying a duffel.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS229
SOMEONE exits the aircraft, squinting in the sun and proceeds across the tarmac.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS231
He eyes one of his peers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS232
The dark-haired soldier stares defeatedly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS233
Their mustached superior leaves. SOMEONE lowers his gaze. At dusk, the platoon crosses the airfield and climbs the boarding steps of a cargo plane. On board, SOMEONE writes a letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS234
Now a helicopter descends. SOMEONE rides on board among the others.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS235
He gazes at passing trees.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS236
The soldiers hop out of the landed chopper, one by one. Now they enter a crude village where a calf drinks from ruts of sitting water.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS237
He hands a letter to a pilot.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS238
SOMEONE watches the helicopter take off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS239
Now multiple letters travel along four conveyor belts. One of them addressed to SOMEONE Curtis. Letters flip vertically through a machine. A bin of bundled letters slides down a track, and a postal worker sorts the letters into cubbies. On a college campus, a mailman takes a few letters from his satchel and places them into one of many PO boxes. From inside the PO box, we see SOMEONE take out her mail.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS240
On finding SOMEONE's letter, she smiles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS241
She reads on her way to class. SOMEONE instructs African troops.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS242
In a lecture, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE reading.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS243
SOMEONE's dark-haired buddy goes through the newly receive mail.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS244
SOMEONE reads.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS245
Now, African women play drums and dance. Soldiers walk among merchants set up along a dirt road. A soldier in sunglasses chats with two local men. Another soldier exits a house and pats SOMEONE, who sits on a porch reading.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS246
SOMEONE leaves a horse and runs across the front yard to greet SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS247
She picks him up and twirls.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS248
Now they ride horses.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS252
She grins at the boy.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS253
Leaning on a fence, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch SOMEONE feed a horse.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS254
SOMEONE writes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS255
SOMEONE reads attentively. Nighttime in a tent.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS256
SOMEONE grabs the letter from him. Now SOMEONE receives another.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS257
She gazes at the moon.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS258
She covers the moon with her thumb.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS259
Her cheeks flushed. She holds her gaze steady.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS260
Now at Mr. SOMEONE's house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS261
He hesitates at the door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS262
He retrieves a small case from a lower drawer.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS263
Then takes out a coin, which he holds under a magnifying glass.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS264
Flipping the nickel over, he reveals the back of a penny.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS265
He glances around the desk, and finds another coin. SOMEONE smiles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS266
Riding in the bed of a transport truck, SOMEONE reads "What's the story?".
DEAR_JOHN_DVS268
He stares off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS269
In a flashback, a boy receives a handful of change from an ice-cream vendor.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS270
Leaving the van, the boy studies his change.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS271
Young SOMEONE licks his ice-cream cone.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS272
Later his dad's fingers rinse the peculiar coin under the faucet.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS273
In the kitchen, a younger Mr. SOMEONE studies the coin and shakes his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS274
He glances at the boy.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS275
Now at a pawn shop.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS276
SOMEONE brightens, his grin missing a couple baby teeth.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS277
Mr. SOMEONE collects the coin and tugs his son away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS278
Mr. SOMEONE hurries down a sidewalk and briefly stops for SOMEONE to catch up.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS279
In another store.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS280
The clerk sets the coin on a square napkin. Bends down and digs under his counter to retrieve a pamphlet titled, The Four Thousand Dollar Mule.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS281
Mr. SOMEONE looks at his son.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS282
SOMEONE nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS283
The clerk grins.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS284
Now at another coin shop.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS285
They view coins on display.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS286
We tour a collection.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS287
Now older SOMEONE takes milk out of the fridge.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS288
He drinks from the carton.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS289
He tosses the carton back inside and shuts the door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS290
His father opens the door and stands the carton upright.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS291
Now Mr. SOMEONE studies a coin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS292
SOMEONE goes to a stereo in the living room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS293
His father looks up from a coin. Seen distantly through the doorway, SOMEONE leaves the stereo and walks out of sight.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS294
His dad glances over his shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS295
On campus, a passing student bumps into SOMEONE as she reads. At the bottom of a staircase, she reaches a walkway where frantic peers gather and talk on cellphones. A confused SOMEONE holds SOMEONE's letter with both hands as she observes the anxious activity.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS296
As SOMEONE remains frozen, our view is sent to take in a bird's eye view of the chaos. Now wearing plain clothes, SOMEONE walks alone on a busy street in an eastern European town. A horse-drawn cart, a woman on a bicycle, and a man on a scooter crosses path. SOMEONE approaches a cafe, where pedestrians gather outside. Reaching the entrance, SOMEONE joins his dark-haired buddy to watch television news coverage. Black smoke billows from one of New York City's Twin Towers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS297
SOMEONE breathes heavily as he watches SOMEONE falling off the building.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS298
Fade to black.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS299
Now in a hanger, the soldier’s superior approaches.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS300
SOMEONE packs.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS301
SOMEONE's friend rises.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS302
SOMEONE, the only one left seated, lowers his gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS303
Later in a conference room, he shakes hands with two soldiers then grabs his bag.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS304
He eyes his dark-haired friend.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS305
Now a gray cargo plane lands on an airstrip.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS306
Inside a crowded airport, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE on the other side of a security gate.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS307
She ducks under a dividing rope, and hurries around to the other side. SOMEONE notices her and beams. She runs to him and leaps into his arms.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS308
As he spins her around, they kiss.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS309
A heavy-set traveler eyes them as he takes off his belt.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS310
Another man eyes them, holding out his arms for a guard.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS311
Later while SOMEONE drives, SOMEONE raises her free hand to his lips. He rubs her hand with his chin, then she strokes the back of his head, fondle his ear, and caresses his cheek.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS312
SOMEONE brushes her long blonde hair behind her shoulder. As he gazes at her, thumbing her hair around her ear, she meets his gaze and smiles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS313
Now, outside his father's house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS314
They approach the front door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS315
Inside, Mr. SOMEONE sits on a chair and buttons a suit jacket.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS316
Behind him, the front door opens, and the couple enters.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS317
SOMEONE walks off, then returns to the sitting room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS319
They follow him into the kitchen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS320
He takes out the pan.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS321
Now Mr. SOMEONE sits in the back seat of SOMEONE's blue Volkswagen, as they drive away. On a country road, he nervously stares at the foiled wrapped meatloaf nestled in a cardboard box on his lap.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS323
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE. Mr. SOMEONE squeezes his brow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS324
Grimacing, he grabs at the door. SOMEONE reaches back. The car stops and Mr. SOMEONE gets out. A disheartened SOMEONE remains in the passenger seat, and rests his elbow on the window sill.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS325
Mr. SOMEONE slouches at the side of the road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS326
She touches his back, and he walks off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS327
He walks a few paces away, then halts and hunches forward, catching his breath.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS328
Now at the SOMEONE house, they get out of the car.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS329
Mr. SOMEONE goes to the front door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS330
His father pauses.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS331
He enters the house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS332
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, rolls his eyes, then returns to the car.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS333
Later on the road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS334
SOMEONE meets her gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS335
They both stare ahead somberly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS336
Now SOMEONE's car pulls onto a private road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS337
A stylish brunette woman in a white dress, crosses the front porch of a colonial plantation home, and greets arriving guests as she passes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS338
She hugs SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS339
Well over a dozen cars sit parked on the front lawn. Inside, guests mingle over drinks and hor d'oeuvres.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS340
SOMEONE offers his hand. SOMEONE ignores him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS341
SOMEONE returns and offers SOMEONE a drink.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS342
SOMEONE takes the drink and averts his gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS343
SOMEONE nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS344
A cigar-smoking man approaches SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS345
As her father leaves, SOMEONE joins them.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS346
A blonde woman joins them.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS347
The woman and SOMEONE leave.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS348
The boy collects hor d'oeuvres on a plate.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS349
SOMEONE looks around self-consciously.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS350
SOMEONE sips his bourbon.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS351
SOMEONE nods and glances off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS352
SOMEONE nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS353
SOMEONE eyes him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS354
SOMEONE deflates.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS355
Now on the porch, SOMEONE paces behind SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS356
She leans on the railing, gazing out over the lawn as departing guests find their cars. He stands behind her, and she lowers her gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS357
She flinches and shifts away from him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS358
SOMEONE bows his head and faces her from the side.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS359
She looks at him ascant, then faces him fully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS360
She grimaces, agonizing and SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS361
She storms past him and disappears down the front steps, leaving him alone on the porch. SOMEONE watches her go, then swallows hard and hangs his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS362
Now as guests stroll around the Curtis' expansive grounds, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE siting alone on a bench overlooking a marsh. His pace slows as he draws closer.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS363
He gazes out at the wetlands as he waits a few feet away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS364
SOMEONE clasps SOMEONE's head in her hands, then wraps her arms around his neck and pulls him into a tight embrace. She rests her chin on his shoulder as he holds her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS365
She meets his gaze, then draws his face closer and kisses his forehead.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS366
Leading him by the hand, SOMEONE takes SOMEONE to her family's stables. Inside, she leans back against a wall as she unbuttons his dress shirt.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS367
He caresses her hair, then lovingly kisses her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS368
Dim blue light outlines SOMEONE's corn silk hair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS369
SOMEONE nuzzles the top of her head, as he sweeps her long blonde locks behind her back.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS370
She parts his shirt, and slips it off his shoulders. Then wraps her arms around his neck and kisses him hungrily.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS371
As SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE's neck, she lowers her dress and presses her body against his.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS372
Now, SOMEONE's toned upper body hovers above SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS373
Propped up by his arms, as she pulls his undershirt over his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS374
She then removes her bra.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS375
He lowers himself on top of her, and meets her lips with a passionate kiss.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS376
The muscles in his shoulders ripple as he and SOMEONE make love.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS377
He kisses her shoulder, then trails his lips from the tip of her chin, down her neck, and gently caresses her hair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS379
He lies beside her, his arm reaching across her body, to stroke her corn silk tresses with his fingertips.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS380
They kiss sweetly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS381
She stares distantly. Her hand clasping SOMEONE's smooth freckled shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS383
With a wistful look, she closes her eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS384
A tear slides out.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS385
Glistening in the light.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS386
And rests at the corner of her eye.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS387
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold hands as they stroll outside the stable into the daylight.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS388
SOMEONE carries her heels, and she wears his jacket over her dress.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS389
A wider view shows warm sunlight glinting through Spanish moss on a tree, as the couple embraces in front of the stables.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS390
Now wearing his fatigues, SOMEONE enters the airport with SOMEONE by his side.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS391
He spots his father waiting at a security checkpoint.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS392
As the couple draws closer, a grin crosses SOMEONE's face.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS393
Mr. SOMEONE smiles briefly, but avoids his gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS394
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, who grins at Mr. SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS395
SOMEONE shares a quick look with SOMEONE, who turns away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS396
He faces his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS397
They exchange smiles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS398
Mr. SOMEONE shifts his gaze uneasily.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS399
SOMEONE extends his hand. With his eyes averted, Mr. SOMEONE shakes it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS400
The soldier awkwardly watches his father, then turns to SOMEONE, who waits a few steps away. As she faces SOMEONE, Mr. SOMEONE walks past them and exits the airport. SOMEONE bends down and wraps his arms around SOMEONE's waist.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS401
They embrace tightly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS402
SOMEONE straightens.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS403
Clasping his neck, SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE, then rests her forehead against his.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS404
He lifts his lips and kisses the top of her head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS405
She looks up at him, tearfully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS406
Tears shine in her red rimmed eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS407
The corner of SOMEONE's mouth twitches into a tiny smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS408
He and SOMEONE kiss desperately.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS409
She cups SOMEONE's face in her hands as she kisses him one last time, then turns away and strides out of the airport.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS410
SOMEONE clenches his jaw as he watches her leave.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS411
Outside, she glances over her shoulder and smiles at him, then continues away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS412
Now in a military plane, SOMEONE lies on some cargo netting as it takes off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS413
Later in the hanger on base.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS414
The captain observes his men.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS415
Sitting on a crate, SOMEONE furrows his brow thoughtfully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS416
He rises and stands at attention, joining the rest of his team.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS417
The captain nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS418
As the captain heads off, our bird's eye view of his men swings down to watch them collect their belongings.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS419
Now, an image of SOMEONE's address handwritten on an envelope, drifts into view.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS420
In Afghanistan, SOMEONE patrols a bustling street.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS421
He pauses to talk to a young boy.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS422
In a close-up of SOMEONE's letter, we glimpse fragments of sentences.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS424
Just not the same without you. Rises and sets for both of us, is what helps me survive day to day. Love SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS426
In a college classroom SOMEONE writes thoughtfully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS427
A close-up shows her pen gracefully filling a page with elegant cursive.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS428
Back in Afghanistan, a pallet drops from a plane, and a parachute opens above it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS429
Later, two soldiers approach the fallen crate. SOMEONE heads over and receives a mailbag.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS430
At the army camp, he distributes letters to soldiers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS431
With a letter in his hand, SOMEONE sits on a cot.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS432
Now, a close-up shows a smooth cursive signature. Always SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS434
SOMEONE drops some letters on top of others in a metal box. Then closes the lid. He kicks it under his cot as he begins to write a reply on a pad of paper. In Charleston, SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride horses together.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS435
Back in Afghanistan, SOMEONE trains another soldier.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS437
The soldier fires at a target.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS438
SOMEONE pats him on the back.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS439
Close-ups of a pen show him writing the dates on more letters to SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS440
June, September, December.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS441
In Charleston, moonlight shines across SOMEONE's face as she lies awake in bed. Our view of the moon morphs into the blazing sun.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS442
In Afghanistan, SOMEONE riffles through a pile of letters. With a disappointed look, he turns away from the mailbag.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS443
Now he cleans a gun.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS444
Glancing up, he notices a soldier reclined on a cot, and reading a letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS445
In Charleston, SOMEONE sits alone on the beach. She closes her eyes regretfully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS446
In Afghanistan, SOMEONE's dark-haired buddy, passes him with a mailbag.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS447
SOMEONE hangs his head as the soldier walks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS448
Now, SOMEONE cautiously glances around as he steps into a tent.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS449
He finds a cellphone on a desk, and reaches for it. Sitting down, he dials, then lifts the phone to his ear.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS450
Now dust billows as a bundled pallet parachutes to the ground. Later, a soldier opens a mailbag and searches its contents.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS451
Now, SOMEONE's dark-haired buddy carries a letter in one hand, and the mailbag in the other, as he enters the fenced-in base camp.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS452
Passing a group of soldiers playing football, he approaches other lounging on picnic tables outside a tent.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS453
He heads into the tent.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS454
SOMEONE sits at a weight machine.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS455
He hands SOMEONE the thin envelope.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS456
SOMEONE thoughtfully runs his thumb over it. Gauging its weight.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS457
Later, he sits outside and reads the letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS458
SOMEONE trudges into his tent with the letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS459
He sits on his cot.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS460
SOMEONE glances at the other soldiers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS461
He lowers his miserable gaze to the handwritten pages.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS462
SOMEONE lifts his head into the sunlight, and bites his lip resolutely.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS463
Reaching under his cot,
DEAR_JOHN_DVS464
he extracts the metal box and carries it outside. As he pries off its cover, he fumbles it, and it falls to the ground.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS465
As SOMEONE retrieves his spilled letters, a soldier passes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS466
Now, flames dance inside a trash can.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS467
SOMEONE tosses a stack of letters onto the fire. As he adds more from his box, his dark-haired buddy walks up.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS468
Clenching his jaw, SOMEONE shakes his head, as he continues to toss letters into the flames. His friend eyes him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS470
SOMEONE dumps the remainder of the box into the trash can.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS471
He heads off, leaving SOMEONE staring at the fire.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS472
Later, a convoy of military vehicles trundles down a dirt road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS473
Dust churns from their wheels. A Humvee passes a man leading a camel and maneuvers unto a busier road.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS474
SOMEONE rides inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS475
A man runs in front of their Humvee with his arms raised over his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS476
The Humvee stops, and the soldiers climb out with their guns drawn.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS477
SOMEONE heads away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS478
SOMEONE's dark-haired friend joins him. With their guns at the ready, they creep around the parameter of a decrepit factory.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS479
The captain gestures to the rest of the team. Meanwhile, SOMEONE and Noodles round the corner of a deteriorating cement wall. Noodles glances at SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS480
A man on a balcony shoots Noodles. SOMEONE fires back, then talks into his radio.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS481
He grabs Noodles by the vest and drags him out of harm’s way. Then inspects the soldier's chest.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS482
SOMEONE extracts a bullet from Noodles' tactical vest.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS483
As SOMEONE helps Noodles stand, four bullets rip through him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS484
SOMEONE falls back in slow motion.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS485
Soldiers fire at his shooter, who collapses.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS486
Kneeling beside SOMEONE, Noodles props him against a wall.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS487
SOMEONE's vision blurs.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS488
SOMEONE glances drowsily at Noodles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS489
He gently slaps SOMEONE's cheek.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS490
Our view of the soldiers tilts upside down, then drifts to the ground.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS492
Now pale light shines through Venetian blinds, as SOMEONE lies in a bed.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS493
A hand adjusts the slats on the blinds and bright sunlight pours into the room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS494
SOMEONE's head shifts, and his hazy vision finds a nurse at his bedside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS495
She smiles down at the groggy soldier.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS496
As helooks at the nurse's kind expression, SOMEONE's vision gets blurrier, and he closes his eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS497
Fade to black.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS498
Now, SOMEONE sits on the side of his bed, with his arm in a sling. Struggling, he manages to lift the strap over his head. He drops the sling on the floor.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS499
Eyeing his reflection in a mirror, he unsnaps the top of his hospital gown, to reveal his bandaged shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS500
He winces as he tears the tape and gauze from his skin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS502
As SOMEONE slips one arm into a t-shirt, sunlight gleams on the scarred flesh of two bullet wounds on his back.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS503
Later, he straightens the collar of his army fatigues. Standing in front of the mirror in his uniform, he pulls his belt tight around his waist.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS504
Now, he enters a military building, and turns down a hallway.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS505
He finds the captain writing at a desk in his office.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS506
The captain looks up, as SOMEONE walks in.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS507
SOMEONE doesn't budge.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS508
He sullenly lowers himself into a chair, across from the captain.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS509
The captain grins.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS510
SOMEONE holds the captain's gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS511
Now, a helicopter sweeps over a desert.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS512
Inside, SOMEONE shifts his gaze away from the open side door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS513
Now, a smoke grenade billows on an Afghan street, as soldier’s race across it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS514
SOMEONE searches an abandon building, his gun drawn.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS515
Outside of a village, three explosions burst from the ground.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS516
SOMEONE leads a group of soldiers down a rocky hill.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS517
He directs his team as they race away from a hut.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS518
It explodes and flames shoot into the sky.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS519
Now, words appear. Special forces base, Qatar.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS521
SOMEONE strolls into his room, and reclines on his bed.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS522
A soldier stops in the doorway.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS523
SOMEONE sits up with an alarmed look.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS524
He lowers his gaze from the soldier.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS525
Now, he stares out an airplane window. His eyes narrowing as sunlight rises across his face.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS526
Later in a hospital hallway, SOMEONE watches his father through a window.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS527
Tubes trail from Mr. SOMEONE's mouth to a nearby ventilator.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS528
A doctor stops beside SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS529
SOMEONE bows his head slightly and nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS531
Wearing his army uniform, and carrying two bags, SOMEONE mounts the steps to his dad's house.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS532
He sets one bag down, opens the screen door and heads inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS533
Dim light bathes his face as he steps into the kitchen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS534
Dirty dishes, bottles, and jars clutter the counter top and stove.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS535
SOMEONE's haunted stare holds steady on the mess.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS537
He treads down a hall to his father's shadowy study, and lingers in the doorway.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS538
Now, he pulls open a drawer and finds a jumble of dozens of coins in small boxes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS539
He takes out a blue velvet box and opens it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS540
With a sober stare, he turns over the Jefferson Mule in his fingers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS541
Seated at his father's desk.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS542
He lifts his head and gazes out a window.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS543
SOMEONE sets the coin aside, and takes out a blank sheet of paper.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS544
He lays it on the desk, then takes a pen from a holder and writes the word, Dear in the upper left hand corner.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS545
Now in the hospital, SOMEONE strides up to his father's room. But finds his bed empty.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS546
He glances around, uneasily.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS547
Doctors and nurses bustle past.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS548
His brow furrowed, SOMEONE spots a cot in the corridor, and strides toward it to find his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS549
The ailing man wears an oxygen mask. An IV bag hangs above his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS550
A doctor reading a file, continues on her way.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS551
Mr. SOMEONE gives a weary blink.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS552
SOMEONE stares at him uncomfortably.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS553
He takes an envelope from his back pocket.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS555
Glides his finger along its edge, then reluctantly hands it to his father.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS556
Mr. SOMEONE lifts the flap.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS559
With palsied hands, Mr. SOMEONE closes the envelope’s flap, and tucks the letter against the side of his body.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS560
SOMEONE sways awkwardly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS561
He scoots a wheeled stool over, and takes a seat.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS562
As doctors and nurses stride past, he slides the letter out of the envelope.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS563
His father watches through heavy lidded eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS564
His ailing father offers a series of slow nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS565
Mr. SOMEONE gazes at his son tenderly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS566
His right hand trembles against his chest.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS567
SOMEONE's smoothly shaven jaw quivers as his eyes remain locked on his letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS568
He resolutely shakes his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS569
His father limply raises one hand and rests it against SOMEONE's shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS570
As it slides off, SOMEONE catches it, and lovingly touches his chin to his father's frail fingers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS571
Mr. SOMEONE pulls his hand away and places his palm against SOMEONE's cheek.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS572
SOMEONE holds it in place with his own hand.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS573
Sliding his father's hand to cup the back of his neck.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS574
SOMEONE hunches down and hides his face in the crook of the man's frail arm.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS575
Mr. SOMEONE raises his other hand to his son.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS576
The soldier lifts his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS577
And his father strokes his short hair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS578
SOMEONE gently collapses unto the man's chest. And the coin collector cradles him as best he can.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS579
Now, as misty rain pours down on an otherwise empty beach.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS580
SOMEONE sits beside his surfboard with his knees pulled up, and his head bowed.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS582
Later, lying belly down on his surfboard, he paddles out in the steel gray sea.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS583
Cloudy rain sheets down, as the waves buck and toss beneath him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS584
He swings his legs into the water, and drops his unhooked ankle leash onto his board.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS585
Releasing his grip on the board.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS586
He lets himself drift away from it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS587
As he floats on his back,
DEAR_JOHN_DVS588
a foamy wave breaks nearby.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS589
Water laps at his face, and flows over his mouth.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS590
His head sinks beneath the surface and he vanishes. His board gently bobs on the waves.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS591
A few feet under water, SOMEONE hovers vertically. His arms raised limply over his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS592
Bubbles stream out of his mouth, as he tips his head back.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS593
Later, still submerged, the grieving son buries his face in his hands. Then runs his fingers back into his hair, and covers his eyes with his palms.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS595
SOMEONE sits alone in a vacant church. A coffin stands in front of the alter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS596
A pastor creeps in.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS597
The pastor nods, sympathetically.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS598
Then glances at the coffin and paces out.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS599
Wearing his dress uniform, SOMEONE stares off beneath his knitted brow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS600
His gaze shifts and he blinks sadly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS601
The pastor disappears through a doorway, leaving SOMEONE alone once again.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS602
Now, the soldier drives his car with a stoic frown.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS603
The images of passing trees reflect faintly on his windshield.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS604
The car pulls through the gate of SOMEONE's family home. And follows the winding drive around a knarled tree.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS605
Slowing, the car pulls up alongside the corral beside the modest stables.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS606
Inside, SOMEONE's slender long-legged silhouette stands, petting a horse.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS607
SOMEONE stops the car and takes out his keys.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS608
Her features lost in shadows, SOMEONE looks toward him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS609
SOMEONE gets out and faces the stables. Nervously pursing his lips.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS610
SOMEONE quickly locks the horse into its stall.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS611
Her form still silhouetted against the stables rear open doorway. SOMEONE treads towards SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS612
He moves across the corral.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS613
His mouth twitches uneasily above his neatly pressed uniform shirt.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS614
The shadows hiding SOMEONE's face fade, as she steps outside into the gentle sunlight.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS615
It bathes her doe-like eyes and rosy cheeks.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS616
SOMEONE moves faster.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS617
A pain smile fades from his former lover's rosebud lips. She halts.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS618
SOMEONE continues toward her, then stops a few yards away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS619
SOMEONE's corn silk hair lies captured in a tight braid, and she wears slim-fitting breaches and riding boots. She allows a smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS620
A brief grin flickers over the corner of his mouth, as he stares at SOMEONE intensely.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS621
Gazing back at him, she summons a deep breath.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS622
SOMEONE uncomfortably shoves a hand into his pocket. His lips parting sadly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS623
SOMEONE swallows, dropping his gaze, then shakes his head and locks eyes with SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS624
Her jaw drops.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS625
She clutches both hands to her mouth and arches her brow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS626
She studies SOMEONE sympathetically.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS627
He bows his head and shifts awkwardly from foot to foot.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS628
He reads a sign above the barn door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS629
She forces a smile and gives a high shrug.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS630
SOMEONE lowers his stare and swallows. Swaying on his feet. Then looks back up at her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS631
She tearfully meets his gaze before glancing away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS632
SOMEONE offers a faint nod.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS633
Later in SOMEONE's dining room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS634
SOMEONE nods, then sorrowfully shakes her head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS635
SOMEONE stares down at the table.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS636
Smiling, SOMEONE drops his gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS637
SOMEONE offers a candid grin.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS638
SOMEONE nods.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS639
She hurries away, and he idly looks around.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS640
The soldier gets up and ambles towards a mantle.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS641
Where several framed photographs stand.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS642
SOMEONE glances at him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS643
She presses her lips together.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS644
One photograph shows SOMEONE in a wedding dress.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS645
She poses with SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS646
SOMEONE stares at the wedding photo. His brow knit.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS647
SOMEONE summons a breath and eyes him uneasily.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS648
SOMEONE swallows hard.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS649
In the photo, SOMEONE beams beside her bearded groom.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS650
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stroll through a sunny park.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS651
Later in a hospital, they head into an atrium.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS652
They find a beardless SOMEONE sitting in a wheelchair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS653
He musters a smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS654
A teenage SOMEONE jogs up.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS655
SOMEONE faces her husband.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS656
She kisses him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS657
SOMEONE skips off after SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS658
SOMEONE stands awkwardly in front of the cancer patient. Clasping his hands.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS659
SOMEONE takes a seat and the ailing father studies him wryly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS660
Nodding, the two men lock gazes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS661
SOMEONE earnestly lifts his brow.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS662
SOMEONE drops his eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS663
SOMEONE gives a long weary blink.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS664
The soldier's gaze drifts thoughtfully.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS665
SOMEONE stares off. His eyes bleary.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS666
SOMEONE tucks his lips into his mouth and bites them gently.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS667
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE as she stands with SOMEONE at a snack kiosk.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS668
SOMEONE bows his head, avoiding SOMEONE's gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS669
The patient's lips twitch into a wincing smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS670
SOMEONE's eyes remain downcast.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS671
He lifts his head and glances at SOMEONE, blinking pensively.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS672
Later, SOMEONE's SUV parks in front of her plantation style home.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS673
SOMEONE gets out and races away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS674
SOMEONE and SOMEONE linger in the vehicle. Their seat-belts fastened.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS675
SOMEONE unbuckles.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS676
SOMEONE shakes her head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS677
Staring off despondently.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS678
SOMEONE tightens her rosebud lips, then locks eyes with her former lover.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS679
SOMEONE manages a smile and looks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS681
In a dining room, SOMEONE pours herself a glass of wine.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS682
SOMEONE glowers.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS683
She uncomfortably shifts her gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS684
As SOMEONE studies her inscrutably out of the corner of his eye, she rubs her lips together.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS685
Her wounded smile fades, and she looks to the ceiling.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS686
SOMEONE taps his fork against his plate and sets it down.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS687
SOMEONE stares with doe-like eyes, then lowers her dark lashes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS688
SOMEONE glares, shifting his jaw.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS689
His mouth opens as if to speak.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS690
But he shuts it and looks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS691
He shakes his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS692
His intense gaze grows tearful.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS693
SOMEONE hangs her head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS694
Bobbing it equivocatingly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS695
She stares at the table.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS696
She looks up imploringly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS697
SOMEONE gapes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS698
SOMEONE rises and starts out of the room, then whirls around.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS699
SOMEONE pulls her into his arms.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS700
She buries her face against his chest.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS701
Cupping SOMEONE's head in his hand, he gently rocks her back and forth.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS702
Later in the sitting room.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS703
She removes a rubber band from a stack of SOMEONE's letters.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS704
He takes an envelope.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS705
SOMEONE slides out the letter inside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS706
It reads, I love you, SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS707
As she reaches for the stack of letters, she knocks over a glass of wine.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS708
Liquid drips from SOMEONE's sleeve.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS709
SOMEONE unbuttons his wet sleeve as he heads into a bathroom.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS710
Behind him, SOMEONE stands just inside a bedroom with a door half open.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS711
She removes her blouse.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS712
As SOMEONE scrubs his sleeve, he glimpses a reflection of her bare back in the bathroom mirror.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS713
He eyes her longingly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS714
SOMEONE brushes her hair back and turns, catching SOMEONE's gaze in the mirror.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS715
The former lovers lock eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS716
SOMEONE turns away pulls a flannel shirt over her shoulders. SOMEONE bows his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS717
Now they head downstairs.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS718
She heads into the kitchen, but SOMEONE strides past the doorway.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS719
She glances back at him, then leans heavily on a counter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS720
In the hall, SOMEONE shifts his weight uneasily, then treads toward the kitchen.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS721
As SOMEONE turns to face him, he halts in the doorway and stares at her resolutely. One hand shoved in his pocket.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS722
She tearfully locks eyes with him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS723
Clenching his jaw.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS724
He holds SOMEONE's gaze. Then turns from the doorway and strides off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS725
He walks into the dining room, and retrieves his jacket from the back of his chair.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS726
SOMEONE joins him, her dark-lashed eyes blinking forlornly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS727
She looks to SOMEONE, then shyly shifts her gaze.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS728
He grinds his jaw as he watches her.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS729
She beams at him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS730
SOMEONE looks away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS731
His gaze downcast, he backs away.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS732
Then heads to the front door.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS733
He halts.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS734
SOMEONE stares at the floor.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS735
She takes a few steps toward him and raises her tearful eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS736
As SOMEONE turns, she lifts her brow expectantly and offers a faint smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS737
He meets her pleading stare, then bows his head.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS739
He opens the screen door and steps outside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS740
SOMEONE swallows, cringing as tears well in her eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS741
She shakes her head disbelievingly.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS742
Outside, SOMEONE trudges to his car. His jacket slung over his shoulder.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS743
Inside, tears stream down SOMEONE's face.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS745
SOMEONE's car trundles down the driveway.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS746
Inside, SOMEONE rests his head against his hand.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS747
Tears shine on his face.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS748
His face seizes. His chin trembling.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS749
He rubs his brow, then pounds his hand on the steering wheel.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS751
He accidentally turns on his wipers and they glide across the windshield.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS752
He flips them off.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS753
Later at his house, he stands in his father's study with his hands in his pockets.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS754
He thoughtfully eyes the boxes of coins stored under a glass counter. Then pulls them out.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS755
Now at the Honest Coin dealer shop.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS756
Outside, SOMEONE opens his trunk to reveal the collection.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS757
Now in a desert, SOMEONE holds out his Jefferson Mule.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS758
SOMEONE flips the coin into the sand. The soldier inspects it.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS759
As SOMEONE leads the group, a soldier approaches him.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS760
He hands over an envelope.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS761
SOMEONE studies the envelope.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS762
Later, soldiers load cargo into vehicles as SOMEONE reads his letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS763
In a flashback, guests greet SOMEONE at a casual party.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS764
He laughs with SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS765
In another flashback, SOMEONE writes the letter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS766
Nighttime, SOMEONE stands on her porch and gazes into the sky.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS767
Tears glisten in her eyes as she stares at the moon.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS768
Now, SOMEONE wheels a bike down a busy street.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS769
He wears a button down shirt and a neatly trimmed goatee.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS770
A view through a cafe window shows SOMEONE seated at a table by herself.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS771
SOMEONE's reflection appears on an adjoining window, as he bends to lock his bike to a parking meter.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS772
Inside, SOMEONE notices SOMEONE.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS773
Noticing her, he does a double take,
DEAR_JOHN_DVS774
and they share a smile.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS775
SOMEONE rises and heads outside.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS776
Grinning, she wraps her arms around SOMEONE's neck.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS777
And blissfully closes her eyes.
DEAR_JOHN_DVS778
SOMEONE holds her tightly. His face buried against her shoulder.