Mice are posed spinning hula-hoops and riding on a roundabout.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS37
The man uses a gas lighter to light little balls that one of the bespectacled male mice is juggling.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS38
He gives the redheaded female mouse a model fire extinguisher.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS39
Now he airbrushes a sunbathing mouse so that it looks like a topless female mouse has a bikini line.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS40
Two more mice are posed with their hands in each other's back pockets.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS41
The man paints a piece of cheese resting on a table between two mice sitting in a pergola.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS42
All the separate but identical mouse couples are revealed in their places on the diorama.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS43
Three office workers - SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE - watch a man carry a box of things to a car in the car park below.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS44
SOMEONE goes.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS45
Later, he talks to SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS46
Carrying a large plastic box, SOMEONE steps out of an elevator followed by SOMEONE and several other workers.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS47
They enter a plush open-plan area at the end of which is a glass-walled boardroom,
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS48
in which several executives are gathered.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS49
One demonstrates his golf swing.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS50
SOMEONE leads the other workers into the boardroom.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS51
SOMEONE puts his hand up.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS52
SOMEONE produces a bomb.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS53
Another bomb has been converted into a lamp stand.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS54
SOMEONE, the CEO, indicates the meeting is over.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS55
SOMEONE comes over to SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS56
Outside the boardroom
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS57
SOMEONE looks over at SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS58
SOMEONE heads off to an office. SOMEONE glances over at SOMEONE who shrugs.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS59
SOMEONE goes after SOMEONE. He enters the plushly appointed office.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS60
SOMEONE puts his box down and takes a seat at an enormous desk.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS61
SOMEONE regards SOMEONE with a puzzled expression.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS62
The guy masseuse knocked over by a log.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS63
The two execs, SOMEONE and SOMEONE, go.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS64
Slightly bemused, SOMEONE looks around the plush office and smiles to himself.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS65
That evening, he walks up outside an art gallery.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS66
Inside, it's packed with people.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS67
SOMEONE looks through the window and spots a brunette woman, He smiles and waves at her.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS69
then indicates to step outside.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS72
They kiss and hug.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS73
An engagement ring.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS75
he nods.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS76
Another self-portrait. His knob's a snake.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS78
SOMEONE frowns. SOMEONE joins them.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS79
Later, SOMEONE has dinner with SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS80
He's also driving and hits a guy in the road. The guy splats against SOMEONE's Porsche's windscreen and falls in the road.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS81
He stops and gets out.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS83
SOMEONE considers.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS84
SOMEONE looks around and tight-jawed, nods grimly.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS85
He picks up a box.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS86
Leonardo Da Vinci's Last Supper.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS87
But done with stuffed mice.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS88
The Jesus Mouse.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS89
SOMEONE looks unconvinced.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS90
SOMEONE comes in.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS91
A ring bearing the crest.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS93
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE and goes after SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and the Mueller’s.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS94
The Mueller’s step in the elevator. SOMEONE holds up his ring finger as the doors close.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS95
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS96
SOMEONE goes.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS97
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS98
SOMEONE gives him the finger and goes. SOMEONE arrives home and finds SOMEONE already there.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS99
She pulls the Jesus Mouse out of his pocket.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS100
She marches off.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS101
SOMEONE yanks SOMEONE away from the lift.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS102
SOMEONE lays him on the sofa and breathes on him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS103
SOMEONE straddles him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS104
SOMEONE makes a call and SOMEONE's phone rings on the table.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS105
SOMEONE crouches beside SOMEONE and puts a hand on him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS106
He takes out a stuffed mouse wearing a suit.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS107
SOMEONE yanks him upright.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS108
SOMEONE takes a few faltering, stiff-legged steps towards the bedroom. He pauses at the split-level.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS109
SOMEONE waves him away. SOMEONE slaps his hand.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS110
SOMEONE fell over the step.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS111
He pulls himself along.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS112
SOMEONE drags himself into the bedroom.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS113
SOMEONE wanders across the apartment to the desk
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS114
and sits at SOMEONE's computer.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS115
Onscreen, chat with Darla22. "Tim, I found you, are you online?" SOMEONE types "No. ”
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS116
as his answer. SOMEONE responds. How's the girlfriend?
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS119
SOMEONE types Not good.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS121
She just walked out.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS123
Is SOMEONE lonely?
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS124
SOMEONE pulls a comedy sad face and types
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS125
SOMEONE is lonely.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS126
A picture of SOMEONE's shapely pink-panty clad backside appears onscreen.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS127
Delighted, SOMEONE immediately prints it off.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS128
SOMEONE asks
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS129
Are you touching yourself?
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS130
SOMEONE ponders then types
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS133
Where are you?
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS134
SOMEONE types in the address as SOMEONE comes out of the bedroom wearing the back brace.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS135
SOMEONE looks up guiltily.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS136
SOMEONE gets up from the desk.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS137
SOMEONE sits downstairs in SOMEONE's apartment block lobby.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS138
He conceals the photo of SOMEONE's bum behind a newspaper and compares it with the backsides of women waiting for the elevators.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS139
He sees a woman wearing tight-fitting jeans and thinks he has a match.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS140
The owner of the backside is actually SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS141
As she gets in the lift,
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS142
SOMEONE sprints upstairs to intercept her on the landing.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS143
She goes. SOMEONE opens the door.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS144
He looks at a magazine.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS145
He checks the phone's memory.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS146
Night. SOMEONE parks the Porsche and gets out.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS147
He opens SOMEONE's door, bashing it against a post.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS148
He takes SOMEONE's hand.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS149
SOMEONE gets out on his own
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS150
SOMEONE gazes at an upper floor. A fire escape leads up to it.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS151
SOMEONE throws keys through an open window.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS152
SOMEONE purses his lips in annoyance.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS153
SOMEONE heads up the fire escape followed by SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS154
He stops when he reaches a platform outside the large window of the upper floor apartment.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS155
The keys on the floor. SOMEONE spots a cat on the sofa.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS156
SOMEONE has called SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS157
A photo of SOMEONE and Nelson Mandela.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS158
SOMEONE strolls through the apartment past a giant painting of himself.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS159
SOMEONE puts down the framed photo. He sinks to his knees then leans forward so his forehead is on the floor. Wearing a pair of orange boxer shorts, SOMEONE picks up a piece of fruit from the coffee table and bites into it.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS160
He stops and glances around. A chair obscures SOMEONE from his view. SOMEONE scrambles over to the chair and sits with his back to it.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS161
SOMEONE beats a rhythm on some bongos.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS163
SOMEONE looks at himself in the mirror. He bares his teeth and raises an eyebrow.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS164
He stands up and pelvic thrusts.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS165
The cat pads over to SOMEONE and steals the SOMEONE stuffed mouse.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS166
SOMEONE is on all fours, making noises at the cat.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS167
SOMEONE knocks a pot plant off the fire escape. It smashes on the ground below.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS168
SOMEONE looks round abruptly.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS169
He stands and scans the apartment.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS172
He looks toward the windows.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS174
He jogs off.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS175
SOMEONE heads after SOMEONE. He stops when he sees a naked woman.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS176
SOMEONE bends down to climb in through the window.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS177
SOMEONE peeks through a gap in curtains. A woman poses with SOMEONE, who wears a bird mask.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS178
SOMEONE takes photos on his phone.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS179
Another woman joins them. They're on a set of a forest with dry ice, making it seem misty. SOMEONE barges in.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS180
Come on.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS181
He pats SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS182
SOMEONE walks off, a tail stuck to his bum.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS183
At SOMEONE's apartment.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS184
He pulls SOMEONE's shoulders back.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS185
SOMEONE wiggles.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS186
SOMEONE points.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS187
SOMEONE frowns and glances at the photo.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS188
SOMEONE glowers. SOMEONE opens the door.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS189
SOMEONE points. SOMEONE struts in.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS190
She sticks her tongue out and waggles it around. SOMEONE puts his hand up and she slides her tongue between his fingers.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS191
She spanks herself. SOMEONE gets up and copies. He spanks himself.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS192
She chases him. They knock chairs over.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS193
She slides over the table.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS194
He throws a towel over her.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS195
She topples over a handrail. She stands with her curly blonde hair over her shoulders and glares at SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS196
She takes two bottles of wine from a rack. SOMEONE shuffles along like a penguin.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS197
She lobs a bottle. It smashes a glass shelf behind him. She throws another. He catches it and pretends to drink it, then throws it.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS198
SOMEONE wields two more bottles. SOMEONE ducks as she throws one. He backs into a door and slides down to the floor, limp, his eyes closed.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS199
SOMEONE opens the door and peeps through the crack.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS200
SOMEONE's head was resting on the door and it drops,
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS201
a pool of red wine by him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS202
SOMEONE opens his eyes and grins.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS203
SOMEONE jogs over to the table and closes a folder full of slides and finds SOMEONE's phone.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS204
SOMEONE sits.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS205
SOMEONE runs a hand through his hair.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS206
SOMEONE starts for the door then stops.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS207
In a large open-plan office, they peer into a workstation.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS208
SOMEONE scowls.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS209
SOMEONE grins.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS210
SOMEONE wears a polo neck under a blazer.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS211
Under his jacket, the polo neck's a bib.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS212
They glance at each other.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS213
SOMEONE stares blankly.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS214
SOMEONE sags forward.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS215
SOMEONE gawps at SOMEONE whose face is scarlet and contorted in a pained expression.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS216
He fixes his gaze on SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS217
He holds up the number.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS218
They walk away from the IRS building, SOMEONE ignoring SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS219
SOMEONE sees a car pull up.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS220
SOMEONE hides behind the Porsche as Martha gets out of her car and waves to SOMEONE as he comes out of the building.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS221
Hefty Martha goes over to SOMEONE who crouches down in front of her and runs his hands all over her.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS222
SOMEONE watches, distraught.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS223
SOMEONE notes SOMEONE's reaction.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS224
As SOMEONE gets in the car, he shoots a superior look in SOMEONE's direction.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS225
Crushed, SOMEONE hangs his head.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS226
SOMEONE and Martha drive off.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS227
SOMEONE nods.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS228
SOMEONE glares.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS229
Back at SOMEONE's apartment, SOMEONE sits on the sofa, ready for bed,
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS230
and finds the engagement ring that SOMEONE offered to SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS231
He hands the ring and SOMEONE's jacket back to him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS232
SOMEONE goes into his bedroom. SOMEONE settles down on the couch.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS233
Later, as SOMEONE lies asleep in bed, SOMEONE lies beside him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS234
SOMEONE opens his eyes but doesn't see SOMEONE is behind him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS235
SOMEONE puts SOMEONE in front of the TV with snacks and sticks headphones on him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS236
SOMEONE pulls a pillow over his head to block out SOMEONE's laughter.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS237
The alarm clock says it's just after 4:30 in the morning.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS238
SOMEONE lies awake in bed.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS239
He gets up and goes in the living room.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS240
SOMEONE has finally fallen asleep on the sofa.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS241
SOMEONE picks some photographs up off the floor.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS242
He sits down and studies them.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS243
They're all of SOMEONE's stuffed mice.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS244
The first shows two mice getting married.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS245
The next shows the specky boy mouse returning home and finding the girl mouse in bed with a bearded mouse that wears a polo neck bib.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS246
The next shows the boy mouse sitting alone at the kitchen table with a photo of the girl mouse propped up in front of him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS247
Portions of cheese are in front of him and the photo.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS248
SOMEONE looks sympathetically over at the soundly slumbering SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS249
The next morning, SOMEONE gets SOMEONE some cereal.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS250
SOMEONE picks up SOMEONE's mobile by mistake and goes out.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS251
SOMEONE's phone rings and SOMEONE answers it.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS253
SOMEONE looks at the door then at the armchair he's in.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS255
He stands up, still hanging onto the chair, and scuttles crablike over to the door.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS256
Still sitting in the chair, he dials again.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS257
He dials again.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS258
SOMEONE arrives at the salubrious brunch venue.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS259
The Mueller’s.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS260
SOMEONE pulls a face and gets the phone.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS261
He has 45 missed calls.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS262
SOMEONE's on a bus.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS264
He hands the phone to SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS265
SOMEONE arrives with SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS266
She snogs him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS267
SOMEONE seethes and pulls up a chair.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS268
Mrs. SOMEONE shakes hands with SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS269
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a napkin with I'm wet written on it in lipstick.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS270
SOMEONE hands the napkin to SOMEONE, who regards him dubiously.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS271
Forcing a smile, SOMEONE takes the ring box and gets on one knee.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS272
SOMEONE bangs his glass to attract everyone's attention.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS273
He winces.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS274
He puts the ring on her finger and stands up.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS275
SOMEONE comes into the restaurant just as SOMEONE lustily snogs SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS277
she drives away.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS278
As SOMEONE watches her go, SOMEONE pulls up in SOMEONE's Porsche Boxster.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS279
SOMEONE gets in the driver's seat. SOMEONE smashes the rear window.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS280
She smashes off a wing mirror then breaks the passenger's window before breaking the headlights and pounding the bonnet with a barrier pole.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS281
She pummels the boot then steps up on the roof and drives the pole through it into the cabin.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS282
SOMEONE feigns death.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS283
SOMEONE jumps off the roof and leans in the window.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS284
She marches off.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS285
Open-mouthed, SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE who snaps out of his death impersonation.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS286
SOMEONE pummels SOMEONE, who immediately plays dead.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS287
SOMEONE gives up hitting him and SOMEONE sits up again.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS288
SOMEONE turns away, looking fed up.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS289
SOMEONE looks concerned.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS290
SOMEONE makes a call.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS291
The battered Porsche, which still has the barrier pole sticking through its roof and trails a rear light, makes its way towards SOMEONE's ranch.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS292
SOMEONE appears behind her, dressed as a goat-man.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS293
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS294
They all stare at him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS295
SOMEONE steps forward then backs away slowly.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS296
SOMEONE goes.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS298
SOMEONE still wears his goat-man outfit.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS299
He gives SOMEONE a pointed look.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS300
SOMEONE looks at some goats in front of them then turns back to SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS301
SOMEONE is in the doorway and overhears SOMEONE. SOMEONE and SOMEONE see him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS302
He's gone.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS303
SOMEONE looks down sadly.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS304
Hands sunk deep in his pockets, SOMEONE wades ankle deep into a pond next to the ranch house.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS305
SOMEONE watches him for a moment
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS306
then walks down the bank and wades into the pond as well.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS307
They stand side-by-side, staring morosely at the water.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS308
SOMEONE looks down uncomfortably.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS309
SOMEONE takes his hand out of his pocket and rubs his thumb and forefinger together.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS310
SOMEONE frowns and looks contrite.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS311
SOMEONE turns and wades out of the pond.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS312
SOMEONE stays put, staring at the water.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS313
That evening, SOMEONE returns to his modest bungalow.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS314
He lets himself in, puts his bag and keys down in the hall
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS315
then goes into his workshop.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS316
He switches a light on and looks at his workbench, which is cluttered with taxidermy paraphernalia and a picture of him with SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS317
He takes the SOMEONE Mouse from his shirt pocket and stares at it
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS318
then tosses it in the bin.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS319
He begins sweeping everything off his bench into the bin.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS320
He turns around and switches on another light.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS321
It illuminates the huge
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS322
park diorama populated by stuffed mice.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS323
He stares at the pair of mice in the pergola who are posed sucking on a piece of cheese through straws like teenagers sharing a milkshake.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS324
SOMEONE walks back to his workbench and sits down.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS325
He fishes the SOMEONE Mouse out of the bin
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS326
and smooths the fur on its head.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS327
He puts on a magnifying glass headband with small working lights
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS328
then opens a box containing mouse wedding-wear.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS329
He picks up a mouse-sized top hat
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS330
and puts it on SOMEONE Mouse's head.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS331
He gets up and goes over to a wooden chest.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS332
He pulls a cloth cover off it and undoes the catches.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS333
SOMEONE returns home to his apartment.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS334
He stands in the middle of the living room
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS335
and looks around sadly.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS336
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the phone.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS337
SOMEONE hangs up and looks thoughtful. The Porsche pulls up in front of SOMEONE's palatial home. SOMEONE chats with SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS338
He's alone.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS339
SOMEONE's a dummy.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS340
A vulture takes food from a man's mouth.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS341
SOMEONE gestures to SOMEONE to go ahead.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS342
Around a baronial-style banqueting table,
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS343
he brandishes a sword.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS346
Waiters serve lobster.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS347
The animal psychic holds her hands over her grilled lobster and goes into a trance.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS348
Everyone looks up.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS349
SOMEONE and SOMEONE snigger.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS350
Unsettled, everyone pushes their plates away except SOMEONE, who tucks in.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS351
SOMEONE walks over to the chest from his workshop.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS352
He takes out a case containing stuffed mice in Evolution of Man style poses.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS353
The final mouse holds a sheet of paper.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS354
Mice fly in a bike lane.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS355
Now two mice making a massive sandwich.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS356
He grins at SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS357
A painter mouse.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS358
Medical mice tend to a patient.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS359
A block of cheese is suspended above the patient.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS360
SOMEONE stacks the various dioramas into a pyramid and places a mouse flying a kite on the top.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS361
He presses a button and the kite lights up.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS362
An Evel Knievel mouse on a motorbike.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS363
The bike jumps back and forth over campervans.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS364
The SOMEONE Mouse.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS365
The SOMEONE Mouse joins a SOMEONE Mouse on top of a wedding cake.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS366
SOMEONE looks moved.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS367
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange smiles.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS368
Wearing a cape, Orson Welles-like SOMEONE marches in. SOMEONE shrinks.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS371
SOMEONE and SOMEONE snigger.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS372
SOMEONE nods.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS373
SOMEONE mouths "Thank you" then turns back to SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS374
SOMEONE gets to his feet. SOMEONE shakes his head.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS375
SOMEONE looks down ruefully.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS376
SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE are cracking up.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS377
The vulture man and the beard man shake their heads sadly.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS378
Annoyed, SOMEONE gets up from the table.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS379
In a courtyard.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS380
SOMEONE frowns.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS381
SOMEONE's incredulous.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS382
SOMEONE stares at him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS383
SOMEONE's crestfallen.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS384
SOMEONE turns to look in at the others through the French windows.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS385
SOMEONE stares at him, his brow knitted.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS386
SOMEONE turns back to him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS387
SOMEONE smiles.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS388
SOMEONE raises his brows and beams.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS389
SOMEONE smiles back at him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS390
SOMEONE turns back towards the room the others are in.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS391
SOMEONE nods. SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE as he goes back in. SOMEONE glares.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS392
SOMEONE glances away.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS393
SOMEONE mimes throwing a thought out of his head at SOMEONE. SOMEONE zaps him back, making his fingers like a gun.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS394
SOMEONE shoots. SOMEONE uses his tie as a shield. SOMEONE blows a dart at SOMEONE. SOMEONE plucks the imaginary dart from his neck.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS395
SOMEONE saves SOMEONE from an arrow. SOMEONE holds SOMEONE hostage.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS396
SOMEONE holds his cape up. SOMEONE leaps using the back of a chair as support. SOMEONE grabs an imaginary weapon from a woman's cleavage and lobs it at SOMEONE who catches it, throws it back and it gets SOMEONE in the heart.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS398
SOMEONE is bewildered.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS399
SOMEONE laughs and claps his hands.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS400
SOMEONE's jaw drops and he smiles.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS401
He hugs SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS402
The blind fencer storms out, knocking over a tray of drinks.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS403
The guy SOMEONE feels the wall for a light switch.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS404
He paws a painting.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS405
He turns a light illuminating the painting off.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS406
He draws his sword.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS407
He lunges.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS408
SOMEONE slices SOMEONE's finger off. It lands on the table.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS409
The vulture picks the finger up.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS410
SOMEONE slashes candles which set light to spilt booze.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS411
He picks up a bottle of wine.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS412
SOMEONE flings the bottle, smashing a window with a coat of arms on it.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS413
The vulture flies out of the window.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS414
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS415
SOMEONE points through the window.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS416
SOMEONE and SOMEONE drive off.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS417
Fire trucks pull up
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS418
SOMEONE and SOMEONE go into SOMEONE's apartment.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS419
He jogs over to a card on a table, picks it up and reads it.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS421
SOMEONE takes it and reads it.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS422
SOMEONE chucks it down.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS423
SOMEONE's come in.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS424
SOMEONE's spotted her.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS425
SOMEONE grins toothily.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS426
SOMEONE smiles and shrugs serenely
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS427
then turns slowly towards the door where SOMEONE is standing, tears in her eyes.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS428
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE and smiles.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS429
SOMEONE pushes the door open.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS430
SOMEONE steps over to him.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS431
He looks at SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS432
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS433
They lean in and kiss tenderly.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS434
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch them.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS435
SOMEONE blinks sadly.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS436
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pull away and gaze at each other. SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE gravely.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS437
They pat each other on the shoulder. SOMEONE pats SOMEONE again. SOMEONE copies. They move from shoulder to cheek then forehead, then tap each other's chins with their fists.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS438
SOMEONE backs out with his hands up.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS439
SOMEONE shuts the door. SOMEONE and SOMEONE kiss again.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS440
SOMEONE stands close and watches them.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS441
They stop and SOMEONE hugs them both.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS442
SOMEONE frowns good-naturedly. The End. A series of mouse scenes. A breakfast with SOMEONE and SOMEONE in the center, holding trophies.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS443
One of SOMEONE's paintings.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS444
The painting's in a mouse scene. It has SOMEONE and SOMEONE in it.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS445
The sculpture is of SOMEONE's finger with the ring with his family motto on it.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS446
SOMEONE's dressed as Sherlock Holmes. Arrows point to SOMEONE's privates.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS447
In an asylum.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS448
Framed in a window, the Eiffel Tower lit up in the night sky.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS449
He's under the bed.
DINNER_FOR_SCHMUCKS_DVS450
They're in a posh hotel room.