A dusty avenue swarms with aliens.
DISTRICT_9_DVS21
An alien butchers a cow's head.
DISTRICT_9_DVS22
Now a title appears high above the slum, crowded with jerry-built shacks. District 9. Another interview, Dr. Katrina McKenzie - UIO Aid Worker.
DISTRICT_9_DVS24
A young civilian.
DISTRICT_9_DVS25
Signs throughout the city read, For Human Use Only, and, No Non-Human Loitering.
DISTRICT_9_DVS27
He gives a talk show interview with SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS30
In old video footage, a lit circle highlights an arrowhead-shaped module descending.
DISTRICT_9_DVS36
We traveled through the city beneath a hovering ship. Now civilians give interviews.
DISTRICT_9_DVS40
Showing a police officer.
DISTRICT_9_DVS43
Protesting citizens march with clubs.
DISTRICT_9_DVS46
A worker checks a helicopter, and soldiers gear up.
DISTRICT_9_DVS50
We glimpse a fenced-in camp.
DISTRICT_9_DVS71
In the depot, a staffer hands out guns.
DISTRICT_9_DVS84
SOMEONE struggles with his mic.
DISTRICT_9_DVS87
Now from a helicopter we gaze over a soldier's rifle at the convoy of MNU trucks. Words appear - 12 kilometers to District 9. 8:48 AM. In one of the trucks, the mercenaries raise masks over their mouths and prepare their weapons.
DISTRICT_9_DVS93
Aliens clear the road
DISTRICT_9_DVS96
In the slum, an alien clubs an unseen figure on the ground.
DISTRICT_9_DVS97
Looks on, dangling from its mouth. By a shack, a rifle-wielding alien wears a helmet with SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS100
The soldier chews a toothpick.
DISTRICT_9_DVS105
He beats on the door with his folder.
DISTRICT_9_DVS111
Later, SOMEONE walks with SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS113
They spot an alien eating a truck's spare tire.
DISTRICT_9_DVS115
Rips his arm off and kicks him across the yard.
DISTRICT_9_DVS116
Gather around them. In the helicopter, a soldier readies his rifle.
DISTRICT_9_DVS119
SOMEONE throws cans at the alien.
DISTRICT_9_DVS120
Later, soldiers bag their comrade's arm.
DISTRICT_9_DVS121
Later, outside a shack. No, it's not my house. I don't live here. SOMEONE holds out a form.
DISTRICT_9_DVS122
The alien obeys, and SOMEONE sets the can down.
DISTRICT_9_DVS123
The can, the alien crams it in his molar.
DISTRICT_9_DVS124
As SOMEONE addresses another resident, the caption reads - District 9, Zone 4. Shacks cleared: 1,018.
DISTRICT_9_DVS128
Wrangle a mule, while two soldiers hold them in.
DISTRICT_9_DVS136
SOMEONE is Talking to SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS140
Tubes and pods filled with space.
DISTRICT_9_DVS141
He uses a radio.
DISTRICT_9_DVS147
He pulls a tube.
DISTRICT_9_DVS152
SOMEONE stands before the burning shack.
DISTRICT_9_DVS153
He faces SOMEONE, who wears a surgical mask.
DISTRICT_9_DVS155
Alien vomits at their feet. Now they approach another. They find an alien gun under some weeds.
DISTRICT_9_DVS157
An agent inventories the contraband. Now a human boy speaks. Some of the guns are small, but if it shoot you, it make a big mess. Now an armed alien fires an alien rifle.
DISTRICT_9_DVS160
Alien graffiti.
DISTRICT_9_DVS162
Now an alien in a pink bra
DISTRICT_9_DVS165
Helicopter, the sniper fires warning shots in the air.
DISTRICT_9_DVS166
The helicopter flies off.
DISTRICT_9_DVS168
Wearing a vest, searches through a trash pile, tossing aside unwanted items. A child-sized alien scavenges nearby.
DISTRICT_9_DVS169
As the vest-clad alien crosses to another pile, a yellow patterned alien adult holds up a piece of trash.
DISTRICT_9_DVS170
The first alien rises.
DISTRICT_9_DVS174
The little alien approaches him with a canister.
DISTRICT_9_DVS176
The vest-clad alien taps the youngster on the head.
DISTRICT_9_DVS177
Now inside their shack, the two adult aliens mix a concoction over a makeshift laboratory.
DISTRICT_9_DVS181
by tiny alligator clips holds a gelatinous puddle. From a pipette, a droplet falls onto the jelly which ripples and bubbles up. Another black drop falls through the mesh into a metallic canister, which electronically seals itself.
DISTRICT_9_DVS183
A helicopter view outside shows SOMEONE's team approaching their shack.
DISTRICT_9_DVS184
Inside, the vest-clad alien takes out the canister and hands it to his partner. The yellow alien hands it back.
DISTRICT_9_DVS185
Clippings on the shack's wall.
DISTRICT_9_DVS192
Pointing his rifle, SOMEONE kicks open the door and the Yellow alien steps out
DISTRICT_9_DVS199
Sprangs the panel back with his baton.
DISTRICT_9_DVS200
That SOMEONE reveal the alien lab.
DISTRICT_9_DVS202
SOMEONE rifles through cabinets.
DISTRICT_9_DVS204
Now he finds a rusty metal box.
DISTRICT_9_DVS205
The alien slender metallic canister inside.
DISTRICT_9_DVS207
Black fluid sprays him in the face. Gagging, SOMEONE hunches forward. He waves the camera and ran off, and takes out a tissue to wipe his face. He palms the camera.
DISTRICT_9_DVS208
When he appears cleaned-up,
DISTRICT_9_DVS209
he bags the canister.
DISTRICT_9_DVS212
Now SOMEONE leads SOMEONE into a room of weapons.
DISTRICT_9_DVS215
In the shack, SOMEONE studies an alien rifle.
DISTRICT_9_DVS223
An incoming chopper. The alien knocks SOMEONE's gun hits SOMEONE with it.
DISTRICT_9_DVS224
As the hiding alien watches, the helicopter descends.
DISTRICT_9_DVS225
Fires a shot into the alien's back.
DISTRICT_9_DVS226
Lies on the ground, riving.
DISTRICT_9_DVS228
SOMEONE helps SOMEONE sit up. SOMEONE backs the camera away. As the yellow alien crawl.
DISTRICT_9_DVS230
SOMEONE shoots it in the head.
DISTRICT_9_DVS231
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look on. The hiding alien backs around the corner.
DISTRICT_9_DVS232
The surviving alien moves off.
DISTRICT_9_DVS238
Now medics bandage SOMEONE's arm.
DISTRICT_9_DVS239
Inside another shack, the little alien stands at a table where device displays a hologram of the solar system. His father enters.
DISTRICT_9_DVS243
Watch for humans. He opens the door for the little one to go out.
DISTRICT_9_DVS244
The child exits and the father shuts the door.
DISTRICT_9_DVS246
Outside their doorway, the little alien plays with an empty cat food can. The agents approach.
DISTRICT_9_DVS249
He throws the alien child a candy.
DISTRICT_9_DVS250
The child throws it back in his face. SOMEONE aims his shotgun at the kid.
DISTRICT_9_DVS254
Moves out and drops to his knees.
DISTRICT_9_DVS261
SOMEONE confers with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS265
The alien blocks SOMEONE from approaching the shack.
DISTRICT_9_DVS267
He kneels at the door.
DISTRICT_9_DVS268
SOMEONE steps inside and finds the walls covered with computer parts.
DISTRICT_9_DVS270
The little alien hides under a table.
DISTRICT_9_DVS272
Looking queasy, SOMEONE runs out, outside.
DISTRICT_9_DVS273
The alien looks over. SOMEONE waves off SOMEONE, accidentally flinging puke.
DISTRICT_9_DVS274
Again, then braces himself on the shack. He faces his assistant. Embarrassed, SOMEONE backs the camera away. Now they rejoin SOMEONE. The alien, SOMEONE Johnson.
DISTRICT_9_DVS276
Now in the MNU transport, a piqued SOMEONE rubs his brow, seated opposite SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS279
At a restaurant named Gunther's, workers serve up fish and chips. As SOMEONE eats happily, his nose leaks black fluid.
DISTRICT_9_DVS281
A droplet lands on his thumb. Startled, SOMEONE glances at his companions and wipes it with a napkin. Now, the truck enters the MNU facility.
DISTRICT_9_DVS282
In the headquarters, SOMEONE leans back in a cubicle holding his head. He coughs into a napkin, and starts filling out a form.
DISTRICT_9_DVS283
He flips to another page then stares at his fingernail. A security camera captures the moment.
DISTRICT_9_DVS284
As SOMEONE trembles, his fingernail comes off. He sets it down on the desk.
DISTRICT_9_DVS285
Now he crosses the office floor. He passes a co-worker at a water cooler and enters the bathroom. Inside, he scans the room. Then standing in front of a mirror, nips at his other fingernails. The first couple hold, but his thumbnail easily comes off. SOMEONE recoils. He spits out the thumbnail.
DISTRICT_9_DVS287
He and his child brood around.
DISTRICT_9_DVS289
Find it, it contains the fluid.
DISTRICT_9_DVS290
It’s not here. It has to be, keep looking.
DISTRICT_9_DVS293
Two aliens, one armed, stand in front of them.
DISTRICT_9_DVS296
While people watch, robot's chest opens
DISTRICT_9_DVS298
A thug hold up his index finger.
DISTRICT_9_DVS305
Two men unwrap an alien body part. You cut it here, this is the heart. It cures high blood pressure when you boil it.
DISTRICT_9_DVS306
Diabetes, all diseases.
DISTRICT_9_DVS307
The gang leader watches the witch raise an alien arm in a ritual.
DISTRICT_9_DVS310
To the yard. Night time, SOMEONE drives in traffic.
DISTRICT_9_DVS311
Van De Merwe Residence, 8:22 PM. SOMEONE pulls into the driveway and gets out of the car. SOMEONE greets him as he enters the darkened house.
DISTRICT_9_DVS313
The lights go on in the house.
DISTRICT_9_DVS314
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS315
SOMEONE hugs his parents.
DISTRICT_9_DVS317
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS323
SOMEONE goes off. SOMEONE faces SOMEONE's parents.
DISTRICT_9_DVS324
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE's cheek.
DISTRICT_9_DVS327
SOMEONE rises from the sink. Later he blows out candles on a cake. Pale and sickly, he briefly turns away from the surrounding guests, wipes his mouth then grabs a knife.
DISTRICT_9_DVS329
Cuts the cake, his eyes widen.
DISTRICT_9_DVS330
A sweaty SOMEONE cuts a small piece for his mother. He hold his hand to his mouth.
DISTRICT_9_DVS331
Black fluid across the cake and hors d'oeuvres. He grabs a napkin and starts to mop it up, but collapses onto the table and rolls to the floor. Cut to black.
DISTRICT_9_DVS332
Admission to a hospital, 10 PM. SOMEONE sits in the waiting room. In an examination wing, a doctor snips the blood soaked bandage from SOMEONE's left arm.
DISTRICT_9_DVS335
Now in the waiting room.
DISTRICT_9_DVS336
Masked guards storm past SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS338
confused. In the exam area, they seize a struggling SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS339
Noticing the commotion across the room.
DISTRICT_9_DVS340
The guards zip SOMEONE into a body bag.
DISTRICT_9_DVS345
Stares upward under the body bag's clear front panel. Two doctors in coveralls wheel him down a corridor, then unzip the bag.
DISTRICT_9_DVS346
Outside the door, a guard peers through a small eye-level window. Later, doctors work on the ragged bleeding flesh of his mutating arm.
DISTRICT_9_DVS347
Wearing an oxygen mask, SOMEONE glances up. Doctors study x-rays. Another tech finds the confiscated alien canister in SOMEONE's jacket.
DISTRICT_9_DVS350
SOMEONE peers at the canister, watching the doctors study it through the plastic bag. Later, two doctors host on SOMEONE, who's strapped to an exam table. Four security cameras show fast-motion footage of SOMEONE getting worked on.
DISTRICT_9_DVS351
16 hours after exposure.
DISTRICT_9_DVS352
A doctor wheels SOMEONE into a laboratory. They pass a tech stretching an alien
DISTRICT_9_DVS353
membrane over his hands. Rows of stainless steel tables hold various alien body parts.
DISTRICT_9_DVS354
Later in a live recording, a doctor holds a surgical drill.
DISTRICT_9_DVS355
SOMEONE and another man watch on a monitor as he drills into SOMEONE's arm.
DISTRICT_9_DVS358
Now a doctor holds up a slate. He shows a machine gun-like alien weapon.
DISTRICT_9_DVS359
Two techs hurry from the opposite side of the room where a dead pig hangs upside down. The head doctor places SOMEONE's alien hand on the gun.
DISTRICT_9_DVS360
They curl his tentacles through the handle.
DISTRICT_9_DVS361
The head doctor zaps SOMEONE's
DISTRICT_9_DVS362
arm with a cattle prod.
DISTRICT_9_DVS363
Bits of light burst from the gun as it fires into the pig.
DISTRICT_9_DVS368
The gun fires, blowing a hole in the wall.
DISTRICT_9_DVS371
Shoot from the weapon's barrel.
DISTRICT_9_DVS372
Setting off another weapon. The captive trembles and his eyes widen.
DISTRICT_9_DVS374
An alien marked with a red X to the wall.
DISTRICT_9_DVS377
SOMEONE's right hand around the gun.
DISTRICT_9_DVS382
The executive smiles at the monitors.
DISTRICT_9_DVS383
Streaked with the alien's blood, SOMEONE jerks back and forth numbly.
DISTRICT_9_DVS384
Stands over him in an operating room.
DISTRICT_9_DVS385
SOMEONE lies strapped to a table.
DISTRICT_9_DVS386
MNU executive nods.
DISTRICT_9_DVS387
The head doctor hurries off with the executive close behind. SOMEONE glances down at his son-in-law's extended arm, then exits as well. Now at the Van De Merwe House, SOMEONE pours two drinks.
DISTRICT_9_DVS388
SOMEONE looks up tearfully from the couch.
DISTRICT_9_DVS389
He sits beside her.
DISTRICT_9_DVS390
Meanwhile, the head doctor talks into a camera.
DISTRICT_9_DVS398
into a surgical cart.
DISTRICT_9_DVS399
The doctor hits a large button on the wall.
DISTRICT_9_DVS400
Holds a scalpel to the head doctor's neck.
DISTRICT_9_DVS401
A guard rushes over, his gun pointed at SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS404
Lowers his gun, SOMEONE swipes an ID through a card reader.
DISTRICT_9_DVS406
Scampering down a hallway. He hurries up a flight of stairs and burst out
DISTRICT_9_DVS407
in the street. Back at the house,
DISTRICT_9_DVS408
SOMEONE's face crumples. SOMEONE wraps an arm around her shoulders.
DISTRICT_9_DVS409
SOMEONE watches her father rise from the couch and answer his phone.
DISTRICT_9_DVS410
Listens, his face slackens and his eyes widen.
DISTRICT_9_DVS411
He watches attentively. SOMEONE glances back at her.
DISTRICT_9_DVS412
Prawn SOMEONE wears a hospital gown and scrub bottoms as he races over a hill beside the highway, and darts behind the backs of two guards.
DISTRICT_9_DVS413
Some garbage, finds a trash bag and eats a piece of thrown out food.
DISTRICT_9_DVS414
He sneaks up behind a pedestrian and snatches his phone.
DISTRICT_9_DVS416
His neighborhood. He hides behind a car, then cautiously peeks over
DISTRICT_9_DVS417
the guard patrolling his front yard.
DISTRICT_9_DVS418
He makes a call.
DISTRICT_9_DVS422
The tall grass behind him, a German shepherd leads a group of soldiers.
DISTRICT_9_DVS424
SOMEONE steals garments off a clothesline.
DISTRICT_9_DVS426
Later, SOMEONE wears the stolen clothes with a blanket over them like a hooded cloak. A surveillance camera records him at the counter at Gunther's.
DISTRICT_9_DVS430
A Gunther's employee eyes SOMEONE nervously.
DISTRICT_9_DVS433
SOMEONE fights
DISTRICT_9_DVS436
SOMEONE stands on a hill, using the stolen phone.
DISTRICT_9_DVS437
He hangs up with a frustrated look.
DISTRICT_9_DVS438
He turns abruptly and lowers himself into the grass. An MNU vehicle pulls into a nearby clearing. It's blue and white lights flashing. A soldier steps out.
DISTRICT_9_DVS439
He sweeps his gaze over the area, then climbs back into his vehicle.
DISTRICT_9_DVS440
SOMEONE turns his head toward the sky, his eyes tracking the helicopter above, then looks back at the MNU vehicle. He ducks lower into the grass as the truck pulls out of the clearing. He stands, gazes out of the city, then hurries away.
DISTRICT_9_DVS443
Across the bleak grounds of District 9. He reaches a run-downed shack, peers through the window, then removes orange and white caution tape from across the door. With a glance at the dismal slum, he shuffles backward into the shanty. SOMEONE lies on the floor using a thin cushion of foam as a mattress, and pulls a wide sheet of cardboard over himself like a blanket. He settles newspaper around his alien arm, then lets his head fall back onto the foam. Morning.
DISTRICT_9_DVS444
Two aliens pick through the garbage.
DISTRICT_9_DVS445
A white hen and her chicks peck at the ground, while a rooster struts nearby.
DISTRICT_9_DVS446
40 hours after exposure.
DISTRICT_9_DVS447
SOMEONE jerks awake, glancing around with wide fearful eyes. Later, he squints as he snips a plastic container.
DISTRICT_9_DVS448
He finds a can of cat food and turns it upside down over his tilted back head. Milky white mush falls into his open mouth. Now, he exits the shack, his left arm hidden inside his coat. With his human arm, he lifts his collar to shield his face from nearby aliens. He stands in line at a meat seller's stall.
DISTRICT_9_DVS450
Meat seller smiles at his associates.
DISTRICT_9_DVS453
Sitting in the dirt, SOMEONE rips the lid off a can. Using two fingers, he shovels the moist cat food into his mouth.
DISTRICT_9_DVS454
His cheeks bulge as he chews hastily. He rocks forward and raises a shaking hand to his lips.
DISTRICT_9_DVS455
He chucks the can.
DISTRICT_9_DVS456
He spits something into his hand, then stares at it. Reaching into the back of his mouth, he rips out something else.
DISTRICT_9_DVS457
With a horrified look, he examines the two bloody molars in his hand.
DISTRICT_9_DVS458
SOMEONE takes out his phone.
DISTRICT_9_DVS460
Lowers the phone from his ear.
DISTRICT_9_DVS461
Now he races back to the meat seller's stall and steals an ax off a table.
DISTRICT_9_DVS463
SOMEONE races away and ducks behind some shrubbery. He drags a cinder block out of the rubble and sets it on the ground in front of him. Rolling up his sleeve, he places his alien arm on the block and raises the ax.
DISTRICT_9_DVS464
He lowers, adjusts his hand on the block, then determinedly raises the ax above his head.
DISTRICT_9_DVS465
His hand trembles as he grits his teeth and licks his lips.
DISTRICT_9_DVS466
He swings down the ax.
DISTRICT_9_DVS467
SOMEONE sits back and muffles his mouth with his human arm.
DISTRICT_9_DVS468
His attention drifts to the sky.
DISTRICT_9_DVS469
He stands and watches several helicopters approach. SOMEONE scans the area from one chopper.
DISTRICT_9_DVS470
A soldier cocks a machine gun aimed at the camp. On the ground, SOMEONE races through a trash laden area behind a roll of shacks.
DISTRICT_9_DVS471
As an MNU chopper passes overhead, he opens the door to one shanty and enters. Inside, SOMEONE Johnson looks up and sees him.
DISTRICT_9_DVS472
Subtitles. You, what do you want?
DISTRICT_9_DVS473
SOMEONE peers out a window at the retreating helicopters.
DISTRICT_9_DVS474
He leans toward SOMEONE's son.
DISTRICT_9_DVS478
His eyes widen, as data appears on the multitude of computer monitors stacked around the room. His gaze follows their electrical cords through a hole in the floor.
DISTRICT_9_DVS480
He grabs the refugee with his alien hand, then collapses. SOMEONE's antenna twitch as he stares at SOMEONE's left arm. The alien nervously looks around, the tendrils on his mouth swinging back and forth.
DISTRICT_9_DVS482
Now you, get down there.
DISTRICT_9_DVS483
Now SOMEONE lie supine on the ground. He slowly wakes and sits up.
DISTRICT_9_DVS484
He presses his hand to his head. SOMEONE approaches.
DISTRICT_9_DVS486
SOMEONE stomps his foot and turns his back to SOMEONE. As the human stands, he surveys the tangles of wires crisscrossing out of electronics and over the walls.
DISTRICT_9_DVS487
SOMEONE turns. You ruined everything. SOMEONE stares through a hatch in the ceiling, which leads to the hole in the shack's floor.
DISTRICT_9_DVS488
SOMEONE's son points to a hole in a small metal tank.
DISTRICT_9_DVS503
SOMEONE's son stands beside SOMEONE. He looks at the man's alien arm and holds out his own arm next to it.
DISTRICT_9_DVS504
We're the same.
DISTRICT_9_DVS505
His eyes glisten as he glances at SOMEONE's son. He rubs his stubble chin with his thumb.
DISTRICT_9_DVS506
We get the fluid back from MNU.
DISTRICT_9_DVS511
He hangs his head and massages his temple with his thumb.
DISTRICT_9_DVS512
The transformation is accelerating, you do not have much time.
DISTRICT_9_DVS514
his pant leg onto his shoes. He stares at the dark spatters, then stands.
DISTRICT_9_DVS515
The setting sun burns orange beyond the shadowed urban home.
DISTRICT_9_DVS516
The image dissolves to night time, where an alien tosses a blanket onto a bonfire.
DISTRICT_9_DVS517
Inside the shack, SOMEONE packs a garbage bag. 56 hours after exposure. He tears some of the bandages from his arm and stuffs them in the bag.
DISTRICT_9_DVS518
Noticing his reddened chest, SOMEONE grabs a broken mirror. He takes off his shirt and inspects the wound. Twisting around, he seizes back. On the left side, sections of alien exoskeleton protrude from his torn flesh. He touches it.
DISTRICT_9_DVS521
He pulls hard on a bloody flap of human skin on his love handle, then lets it hang loose. SOMEONE sits and hangs his head over his fist.
DISTRICT_9_DVS522
SOMEONE looks around and finds the cellphone on the bag.
DISTRICT_9_DVS525
SOMEONE listens in.
DISTRICT_9_DVS526
SOMEONE stops headphones.
DISTRICT_9_DVS527
Now a helicopter passes in the distance beyond SOMEONE Johnson's shack.
DISTRICT_9_DVS529
Reaches behind an old computer monitor.
DISTRICT_9_DVS530
He grabs a pamphlet.
DISTRICT_9_DVS532
Kneels at the child's side.
DISTRICT_9_DVS538
Arrives in the doorway. He watches SOMEONE show his son the MNU.
DISTRICT_9_DVS542
SOMEONE knocks, startling the aliens.
DISTRICT_9_DVS544
We go up to the mothership.
DISTRICT_9_DVS545
SOMEONE sits across from them.
DISTRICT_9_DVS546
He glances from his alien arm to the open door.
DISTRICT_9_DVS548
Daytime. SOMEONE crosses a dirt road.
DISTRICT_9_DVS549
A group of Nigerians, two of them sit on a couch.
DISTRICT_9_DVS552
He shows SOMEONE with the alien.
DISTRICT_9_DVS553
With a demon. You're one brave white man.
DISTRICT_9_DVS556
The thug forces SOMEONE into a shallow ditch, then steps away.
DISTRICT_9_DVS557
Another thug opens a curtain, and the bald one wheels SOMEONE out. The gangsters keep their guns on SOMEONE, situated low in the ditch before their leader.
DISTRICT_9_DVS559
SOMEONE takes out some cash.
DISTRICT_9_DVS560
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE and studies his face.
DISTRICT_9_DVS561
They pull SOMEONE's jacket off.
DISTRICT_9_DVS562
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's alien arm in his hand. SOMEONE glances around. The gang leader pulls out a knife and pricks the alien flesh.
DISTRICT_9_DVS569
Powers up, as the thug grabs a machete.
DISTRICT_9_DVS573
He aims at SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS574
SOMEONE stares fearlessly into the strange gun's blazing barrel.
DISTRICT_9_DVS575
Get that hand. The bald thug brings out a bag of weapons.
DISTRICT_9_DVS576
SOMEONE grabs the bag.
DISTRICT_9_DVS579
Outside, SOMEONE holds off the others with the alien gun.
DISTRICT_9_DVS580
Now an eight-wheeled armored transport sits parked outside
DISTRICT_9_DVS581
MNU headquarters. Inside, SOMEONE paces in front of SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS588
A ponderous explosion rips into the building's facade. Inside, office workers flee their desks. On the ground, SOMEONE leads the way into the building, armed with an alien blaster.
DISTRICT_9_DVS590
To a stairwell and face panicked office workers fleeing downstairs.
DISTRICT_9_DVS591
They descend.
DISTRICT_9_DVS595
SOMEONE loads his gun. On a lower floor, SOMEONE wearing a gas mask
DISTRICT_9_DVS597
And the guard shoots him in the chest. SOMEONE fires.
DISTRICT_9_DVS601
In a code on a security keypad. Now with their guns aimed, SOMEONE heads down a stairwell with a few other soldiers. They open an elevator. Meanwhile, SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter the bio lab.
DISTRICT_9_DVS602
Group of doctors.
DISTRICT_9_DVS604
They cross the lab.
DISTRICT_9_DVS606
SOMEONE tips over another cart.
DISTRICT_9_DVS607
Now an elevator door opens, and the soldiers enter a bombed out floor.
DISTRICT_9_DVS608
In the bio lab, SOMEONE peers into a windowed case and seize the canister.
DISTRICT_9_DVS609
The glassing grabs the canister.
DISTRICT_9_DVS610
It’s the mutilated body of a fellow alien.
DISTRICT_9_DVS611
Grip on his weapon wearily drop.
DISTRICT_9_DVS612
SOMEONE drops his gun completely.
DISTRICT_9_DVS615
Electronic doors open, and the focused soldiers pass through the chamber.
DISTRICT_9_DVS616
He ducks out of the way.
DISTRICT_9_DVS617
Position themselves.
DISTRICT_9_DVS622
As SOMEONE re-positions himself, SOMEONE peers at SOMEONE through the dust and smoke. SOMEONE snaps out of his trance and joins SOMEONE, who fires again at the humans.
DISTRICT_9_DVS624
Fires again.
DISTRICT_9_DVS627
Making a bomb. SOMEONE pieces together various weapons parts at a table, then leads SOMEONE through another chamber.
DISTRICT_9_DVS628
The breach opens onto a motor pool containing dozens of armored MNU pickups. SOMEONE climbs the car.
DISTRICT_9_DVS629
and SOMEONE gets in next to him. Go, drive. SOMEONE pulls out and speeds through the garage.
DISTRICT_9_DVS631
A guard fires at their vehicle.
DISTRICT_9_DVS632
city reads - Terrorist bombing in downtown JHB.
DISTRICT_9_DVS633
A helicopter flies over District 9. SOMEONE rides on board.
DISTRICT_9_DVS634
SOMEONE fires at the renegade truck.
DISTRICT_9_DVS636
He hurries down a hill.
DISTRICT_9_DVS638
Outside, the helicopter flies over
DISTRICT_9_DVS644
SOMEONE glares at him.
DISTRICT_9_DVS650
The plank, and SOMEONE hits the floor unconscious. SOMEONE wipes his mouth, then picks up the canister. He climbs down through the trap door. Now, the helicopter lands and SOMEONE hops off with a masked soldier. Under the shack, SOMEONE shuts a hatch below the open trapdoor and climbs down. SOMEONE enters the upper level and finds SOMEONE at the opened trapdoor.
DISTRICT_9_DVS651
SOMEONE cowers under SOMEONE's aimed gun.
DISTRICT_9_DVS652
He throws SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS653
The alien child points, Father.
DISTRICT_9_DVS658
In the ship, SOMEONE approaches a chamber where a pilot seat pops out.
DISTRICT_9_DVS659
He takes off his jacket. SOMEONE sits in the chair and pulls down a harness, which engages the seat to move forward to a control station. SOMEONE studies the equipment.
DISTRICT_9_DVS662
up at the hatch.
DISTRICT_9_DVS663
As SOMEONE struggles on his back, SOMEONE loads his gun and steps on the alien's throat.
DISTRICT_9_DVS666
A confused SOMEONE fidgets.
DISTRICT_9_DVS667
Next to each of his knees, he finds two angled cylinders filled with greenish jelly. He inserts his alien hand into one, and a holographic screen appears before his eyes. Behind him, the little alien eyes the hatch.
DISTRICT_9_DVS669
The structure wrecks.
DISTRICT_9_DVS675
Fire at the ship, the first misses.
DISTRICT_9_DVS677
Now with SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS678
Watching the spinning ship on television.
DISTRICT_9_DVS679
Drops to his knees, devastated. SOMEONE gazes toward the crash site. My son. SOMEONE stands. My son's in there.
DISTRICT_9_DVS681
Crew films the downed ship.
DISTRICT_9_DVS682
On the ground, the crashed ship smokes and sparks. The MNU transport arrives, followed by an armored pickup.
DISTRICT_9_DVS683
A soldier hops out and shuts the door.
DISTRICT_9_DVS684
SOMEONE, aiming a rifle, cautiously approaches an open hatchway to the ship.
DISTRICT_9_DVS685
On board, SOMEONE crawls on the floor. SOMEONE stands in the doorway where sunlight floods into the vessel.
DISTRICT_9_DVS686
Off to the side, the little alien hides behind bundled wiring. SOMEONE enters the ship and turns to find SOMEONE crawling away from him.
DISTRICT_9_DVS687
The commander lowers his rifle. Grabbing SOMEONE's shirt, SOMEONE lifts his captive to his feet.
DISTRICT_9_DVS688
He turns SOMEONE around and marches him outside.
DISTRICT_9_DVS689
Still unnoticed, the little alien watches them pass. Outside, SOMEONE brings SOMEONE to the pickup and forces him into the backseat.
DISTRICT_9_DVS693
As SOMEONE watches from the transport, a rear door shuts, blocking his view. In the pickup, SOMEONE rides with a blank stare. 72 hours after exposure. In the passenger's seat, SOMEONE reloads his handgun. In the transport, a soldier aims a pistol at SOMEONE. In the pickup, SOMEONE remains entranced.
DISTRICT_9_DVS695
A gangster aims an RPG.
DISTRICT_9_DVS696
The pickup's tail gate trapping them.
DISTRICT_9_DVS700
And SOMEONE from the transport.
DISTRICT_9_DVS701
As SOMEONE's men fall back, SOMEONE watches from the truck.
DISTRICT_9_DVS702
SOMEONE ducks behind a corner.
DISTRICT_9_DVS703
Men advance on the overturned pickup. A man crawls in.
DISTRICT_9_DVS704
A light shines on SOMEONE's SOMEONE, as the gangsters haul him out.
DISTRICT_9_DVS708
As SOMEONE trenches, his captors maintain their grip on his limbs. In the transport, SOMEONE stands with his arms bound behind him, and peers out a cracked window at the abduction.
DISTRICT_9_DVS709
To another window, watching the gangsters dragging SOMEONE away.
DISTRICT_9_DVS710
Now aboard the crashed command module, the little alien types and manipulates schematics on the screen. A metal stripe projects a paper-thin panel made of light. The energy panel expands and displays the mothership.
DISTRICT_9_DVS711
Now SOMEONE is brought before SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS714
A new chopper lands in District 9 and drops off a handful of reinforcements.
DISTRICT_9_DVS716
Affords an MNU gunman a wide aerial view. As his peers on the ground take up positions, SOMEONE's men hustle. Above, gangster barks, Kill them, kill all of them.
DISTRICT_9_DVS719
SOMEONE continues. Once I have that power, no one SOMEONE stop me. It was your turn, now it's mine. As SOMEONE shoots a gangster.
DISTRICT_9_DVS722
The gunfight outside continues.
DISTRICT_9_DVS723
The gangster missing several teeth accepts a machete.
DISTRICT_9_DVS724
Now, the little alien manipulates projected diagrams and activates sections of the mothership. Outside, the real mothership still hovers.
DISTRICT_9_DVS725
As the sonic wave sweeps over Johannesburg, hundreds of windows shatter, block after block.
DISTRICT_9_DVS727
Up a cut with the machete.
DISTRICT_9_DVS731
The robot unleashes the collected bullets in a single blast, and
DISTRICT_9_DVS732
it shoots SOMEONE. A projectile the size of a soda can launches.
DISTRICT_9_DVS733
Cranium swells and explodes.
DISTRICT_9_DVS734
Blood and cerebral spinal fluid. Now on the command module, the little alien manipulates more diagrams.
DISTRICT_9_DVS737
The robot's arms lower, and its chest cavity opens before him.
DISTRICT_9_DVS739
Outside, choppers fly toward the mothership. Aboard one, a mercenary peers at the elaborate technology covering the sunny hall. The choppers appear puny, like hornets before an elephant. On the ground, one of SOMEONE's scorpion-like fighting creatures nibbles on a dead thug lying slumped over the penned fence.
DISTRICT_9_DVS741
An alien opens its shaft door and joins a group of five others outside. They gaze into the sky at the drifting mother ship. SOMEONE crouches with his men between two shacks. In the MNU transport, SOMEONE moves to the window and peers out. He watches as the mother ship makes its way across the sky.
DISTRICT_9_DVS742
Back with SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS743
SOMEONE signals, then heads towards the transport. SOMEONE peeks out of the hideout's window and spots the advancing mercenaries.
DISTRICT_9_DVS744
On a news report.
DISTRICT_9_DVS745
SOMEONE sidesteps into the open area.
DISTRICT_9_DVS747
SOMEONE watches from the window as SOMEONE beats SOMEONE with a baton.
DISTRICT_9_DVS748
A mercenary pulls the pin from a smoke grenade and tosses it. SOMEONE signals.
DISTRICT_9_DVS749
Mercenaries close-in on the hideout. Inside, the smoke grenade lands on the floor, a few feet from SOMEONE. As it releases a burst of smoke, SOMEONE crouches and covers his mouth. He flinches as another grenade lands in the shack and deploys. With a hard stare, SOMEONE eyes the robot. Outside.
DISTRICT_9_DVS750
SOMEONE points.
DISTRICT_9_DVS751
Now, SOMEONE sits inside the robot. A helmet lowers. It secures itself to his head.
DISTRICT_9_DVS752
Robot's chest closes.
DISTRICT_9_DVS754
In the control seat, data forms a sphere around SOMEONE's head. SOMEONE steps back.
DISTRICT_9_DVS758
SOMEONE moves closer.
DISTRICT_9_DVS759
The robot turns to face him. It shifts its shoulders, then tilts its head to look at SOMEONE, who kneels in front of him held at gunpoint by a mercenary. From the control seat, SOMEONE stares sadly. The robot takes a step back.
DISTRICT_9_DVS760
As SOMEONE retreats in the robot, SOMEONE talks into his radio.
DISTRICT_9_DVS762
SOMEONE leans toward SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS763
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, then heads off. The alien turn
DISTRICT_9_DVS764
to the gun-wielding mercenary. Meanwhile, the robot stops across the dry ground.
DISTRICT_9_DVS765
Turns its face to the mother ship. In the control seat, SOMEONE cringes.
DISTRICT_9_DVS768
The robot turns. Back by the transport, the mercenary aims his gun at SOMEONE's head. A volt of electricity hits the gun-wielding mercenary dead-on, exploding him and takes off
DISTRICT_9_DVS769
SOMEONE's arm. SOMEONE looks up to see the robot shooting as it charges over. SOMEONE returns fire, then runs away.
DISTRICT_9_DVS773
200 yards away, a cloud of dust and smoke billows from the crashed command module. The little alien steps out. Meanwhile, the robot jumps over a car.
DISTRICT_9_DVS775
As the mercenaries fire, SOMEONE uses a piece of metal as a shield.
DISTRICT_9_DVS777
Mercenaries' bodies go limp,
DISTRICT_9_DVS778
SOMEONE and his men hustle to new positions. A sniper sets up beyond a low concrete barrier.
DISTRICT_9_DVS779
The sniper cocks his rifle and steers fixedly into its sight. As SOMEONE and SOMEONE pass, he fires.
DISTRICT_9_DVS780
Hits SOMEONE. The sniper aims again. As the robot stands, the sniper fires.
DISTRICT_9_DVS781
The robot races away.
DISTRICT_9_DVS784
it knocks it off balance.
DISTRICT_9_DVS787
Revealing new space.
DISTRICT_9_DVS790
Limps away, shielding himself against an onslaught of bullets. Abandoning the metal hatch, he races up a narrow path. Gunfire blast the dirt surrounding him.
DISTRICT_9_DVS792
Continuing their assault.
DISTRICT_9_DVS793
Mercenaries. Elsewhere, SOMEONE runs at a full sprint after another.
DISTRICT_9_DVS795
A machine gunner kicks a sheet metal barrier from a guard top.
DISTRICT_9_DVS796
Meanwhile, SOMEONE arrives at the command module's door.
DISTRICT_9_DVS797
They fly through a sheet metal wall. SOMEONE turns on the others. Meanwhile, SOMEONE enters the command module, his son in his arms.
DISTRICT_9_DVS798
Puts the little alien down. The mother ship hovers directly above their craft, rotating slowly.
DISTRICT_9_DVS800
A rifle as he advances on SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS803
Thunder side flare. On the news.
DISTRICT_9_DVS805
Leaning against the command module's wall, SOMEONE sinks to the floor and draws his son.
DISTRICT_9_DVS808
It's deflect off the robot's shell.
DISTRICT_9_DVS809
Fire rockets launch.
DISTRICT_9_DVS811
From inside, our point of view rolls chaotically. Yards away, the command module lifts off the ground.
DISTRICT_9_DVS812
Inside, SOMEONE look wearily. The robot glances toward the rising craft, then fires.
DISTRICT_9_DVS813
Outside, the dust clears.
DISTRICT_9_DVS814
Several fallen men. Scrambling to his feet, SOMEONE faces a soldier.
DISTRICT_9_DVS817
Kneeling, SOMEONE fires a rocket
DISTRICT_9_DVS820
He looks its remaining arm, knocking it over.
DISTRICT_9_DVS822
Lying back in the control seat, SOMEONE convulses. The machine spurts clear fluid past his face, while the screen flickers behind him.
DISTRICT_9_DVS823
He watches the module approach the mother ship.
DISTRICT_9_DVS824
He bites his lower lip, SOMEONE coolly steps away. The truck door opens. Its driver climbs out and fires at SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS826
Hundreds of feet above, the command module continues its steady ascent. Inside, SOMEONE's son clings to him, gazing upward. On the ground, the robot takes a few faltering steps, then falls. As it gets to its feet again,
DISTRICT_9_DVS827
SOMEONE arrives behind it, his rifle raised.
DISTRICT_9_DVS829
The machine sinks down, and black fluid pours
DISTRICT_9_DVS830
SOMEONE stares dully as the main components around him part.
DISTRICT_9_DVS831
The facial frame lifts, and he slams forward landing face down in the dirt. The robot topples backward and lies motionless. SOMEONE unsteadily pushes himself up on his elbows, then crawls with strained effort over the littered ground.
DISTRICT_9_DVS832
Yards behind him, SOMEONE swaggers through drifting watts of smoke.
DISTRICT_9_DVS833
On his belly, SOMEONE continues doggedly through a patch of yellow weeds.
DISTRICT_9_DVS834
Above, the command module reaches the mothership.
DISTRICT_9_DVS835
Inside, the little alien glances about excitedly, as a shadow sweeps over the cabin. The module locks into place, locking out the radiant blue light. The levitating rocks and SOMEONE plummet downward. In the module, SOMEONE's son watches lights blink on throughout the interior.
DISTRICT_9_DVS837
On the ground, a trembling SOMEONE wills his arms forward, one after the other as he drags himself along the ground. As we watch from behind the blasted brick wall, a caption reads - 74 hours after exposure.
DISTRICT_9_DVS838
Strides over, draws a pistol and takes aim. Spotting the colonel, SOMEONE rolls over to face him and raises his trembling human hand. His scalp bears swollen bald patches.
DISTRICT_9_DVS839
SOMEONE stares through one blue eye and one yellow eye, double its previous size.
DISTRICT_9_DVS840
A red splotched alien spies them.
DISTRICT_9_DVS841
He trails his arm down SOMEONE's body. Looking up, he springs to his feet and points his gun at the red alien, who now stands before him. Two more arrive behind SOMEONE.
DISTRICT_9_DVS842
The colonel turns.
DISTRICT_9_DVS843
A fourth alien leaps over a mount of rubble.
DISTRICT_9_DVS844
As the aliens advance on SOMEONE, SOMEONE stares wide-eyed. The colonel shoots two of them.
DISTRICT_9_DVS845
One rips his head off. SOMEONE recoils. From a bird's eye view, we watch the aliens dismember SOMEONE and devour his flesh. SOMEONE's overwhelmed gaze shifts below small dark green plates, peeking out from his hairline.
DISTRICT_9_DVS846
He gradually manages to collect himself.
DISTRICT_9_DVS847
He casts his earnest gaze upward. In the command module, SOMEONE lumbers to the pilot's chair and flops down. It carries him to the holographic navigation frame.
DISTRICT_9_DVS848
His son hops up on his knee as the screen blinks to life. Within a circular blue graphic, a three-dimensional intergalactic map appears. SOMEONE makes selections from the blue graph, and the map hones in on a galaxy. The alien zooms in on a pair of twin stars and selects one.
DISTRICT_9_DVS849
He brings up a blue planet.
DISTRICT_9_DVS850
It shows a saucer-like jet at its perimeter.
DISTRICT_9_DVS851
A second jet activates. SOMEONE watches with a heaving chest. He swallows, allowing a faint smile. As we watch from a distant field, a wave of dust blast toward us. The mothership rises. In the slum, aliens freeze in their tracks, staring upward.
DISTRICT_9_DVS852
Now, we follow a news helicopter's point of view. A caption reads - Historic moment, as alien mothership leaves earth.
DISTRICT_9_DVS860
SOMEONE gazes pensively.
DISTRICT_9_DVS861
On-board the command module, SOMEONE leans back on his seat, blinking heavily. The soft tendrils over his mouth sway lazily, the jointed maxillary palps flicking out on either side. He gazes down at the child in his lap, then eyes the navigation screen. From the ground, SOMEONE stares upward, his mismatched eyes glistening. Bowing his head, he shields his face. We watch him from above.
DISTRICT_9_DVS862
SOMEONE wears an orange jumpsuit.
DISTRICT_9_DVS863
Words appear - SOMEONE is currently awaiting trial for exposing MNU's illegal genetic research program.
DISTRICT_9_DVS864
District 9 was demolished after the alien resettlement operation was completed. District 10 now houses 2. 5 million aliens and continues to grow. At SOMEONE's desk interview,
DISTRICT_9_DVS865
there's a wedding photo.
DISTRICT_9_DVS867
Now, SOMEONE gingerly unwraps a bundle of pink tissue, revealing a delicate metal sculpture of a flower.
DISTRICT_9_DVS868
She stares tenderly at it.
DISTRICT_9_DVS869
A framed wedding photo stands nearby.
DISTRICT_9_DVS870
In a meadow field of rubbish, an alien in blood-stained rags crafts another flower. With a caring gaze, he gingerly adjust the petals.
DISTRICT_9_DVS871
Glances up at us, then finishes the flower. Turning to profile, he holds up the imitation