The teacher catches a boy with a joint.
EASY_A_DVS14
He offers a bong.
EASY_A_DVS15
She reaches for it, letting her breasts hang out.
EASY_A_DVS16
Friday afternoon, SOMEONE opens a greeting card that reads, "To my granddaughter, you're my pocket full of sunshine. " She finds a $5 SOMEONE inside.
EASY_A_DVS17
Saturday morning, SOMEONE opens the card again.
EASY_A_DVS18
Painting her toenails, she sings to a dog on her bed, then paints the dog's nails.
EASY_A_DVS19
Saturday afternoon.
EASY_A_DVS20
Saturday night, SOMEONE kneels before her dog, shaking her hips. Sunday morning, SOMEONE repeatedly opens and shuts the card.
EASY_A_DVS21
Sunday afternoon, in the shower.
EASY_A_DVS23
She glances about, then shuts the card and joins the dog on her bed.
EASY_A_DVS24
In the ladies room.
EASY_A_DVS25
Another girl steps out of a stall and glares at SOMEONE, while washing her hands.
EASY_A_DVS26
She flicks water at SOMEONE, and leaves.
EASY_A_DVS27
SOMEONE passes out flyers.
EASY_A_DVS28
Last year.
EASY_A_DVS29
A guy in a devil costume tears through a banner, his face and bare chest painted blue. Launching off a trampoline, he flips and dunks a basketball then hangs from the hoop. He throws his toy pitchfork into the crowd.
EASY_A_DVS31
This year.
EASY_A_DVS32
A plush Woodchuck mascot rips through a banner with a wheelbarrow of logs. He pretends to gnaw on one.
EASY_A_DVS33
He launches off the trampoline for a dunk, but falls on his face.
EASY_A_DVS34
He shows a title.
EASY_A_DVS35
Our view dashes across the school grounds to a guy on a cellphone. We zip into a classroom where a few students read a text message. In a theater class, a guy checks his phone while lying on stage mid rehearsal.
EASY_A_DVS36
We zoom out the window, then zip around the building into another class. Where a girl turns to show a text to a friend at a desk behind her.
EASY_A_DVS37
The friend turns to a guy behind her, then we shoot outside past a row of lockers to find SOMEONE. The red-haired teen stands alone. Listening to the chatter.
EASY_A_DVS38
Turning to go, she runs into SOMEONE with a snooty friend.
EASY_A_DVS39
They pat their hearts and raise their hands to the sky.
EASY_A_DVS40
She rejoins SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS41
Now at home.
EASY_A_DVS42
A black boy sits beside her.
EASY_A_DVS43
At school her peers stare.
EASY_A_DVS44
SOMEONE's hand shoots up.
EASY_A_DVS45
She faces SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS46
Now SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE, from behind an administrative counter, while aggressively stapling a document.
EASY_A_DVS47
SOMEONE pounds on the stapler.
EASY_A_DVS48
An athletic team steps into view, followed by a smaller guy holding a rag to his bloody nose.
EASY_A_DVS49
Now in the principal's office.
EASY_A_DVS50
He scribbles on a slip.
EASY_A_DVS51
He points at the door.
EASY_A_DVS52
Outside Woodchuck SOMEONE carries the head of his costume as he falls into step with SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS53
He high fives a guy.
EASY_A_DVS54
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS55
SOMEONE mimics a boxer.
EASY_A_DVS56
She musses her friend's hair and saunters off. Now at home, SOMEONE's mother serves her peas.
EASY_A_DVS57
SOMEONE eyes her younger brother.
EASY_A_DVS59
Her brother eyes her plate.
EASY_A_DVS60
She kisses her mom.
EASY_A_DVS61
Her husband sits with their son.
EASY_A_DVS62
Now SOMEONE mops the gym.
EASY_A_DVS63
She grins at him. Now they clean a tennis court.
EASY_A_DVS64
Later, SOMEONE wipes graffiti from a bathroom stall.
EASY_A_DVS65
SOMEONE adds graffiti.
EASY_A_DVS66
Now on a ridge overlooking the town.
EASY_A_DVS67
Lounging on the hood of an old VW bug, SOMEONE reaches through the window and takes out her cellphone.
EASY_A_DVS68
SOMEONE nods.
EASY_A_DVS69
We peer through an arched hedge.
EASY_A_DVS70
SOMEONE rides into view on a scooter, lurches to a halt and dismounts awkwardly. He arrives at the Penderghast front door and knocks. SOMEONE's mother answers with a warm delighted smile.
EASY_A_DVS71
She pulls him inside.
EASY_A_DVS72
She faces a stairway.
EASY_A_DVS73
She leads SOMEONE upstairs.
EASY_A_DVS74
Under her puzzled stare, SOMEONE screws up his mouth and nods coolly.
EASY_A_DVS75
His eyes well with tears.
EASY_A_DVS76
SOMEONE shakes her head.
EASY_A_DVS77
SOMEONE stares imploringly at her.
EASY_A_DVS78
At the party, two teens water slide into a pool.
EASY_A_DVS79
She leans close to Melody.
EASY_A_DVS80
She pretends to munch on his ear.
EASY_A_DVS81
She shuts the door.
EASY_A_DVS82
She slips off a pair of red SOMEONE panties from under her skirt.
EASY_A_DVS83
She hangs them on the doorknob, blocking the keyhole.
EASY_A_DVS84
The bully tries to peer through, as a crowd gathers. SOMEONE eyes the drapes.
EASY_A_DVS85
He goes to the bed.
EASY_A_DVS86
The eavesdropping team swap looks.
EASY_A_DVS87
She slaps him, then cups a hand over his mouth.
EASY_A_DVS88
She spanks him with a book.
EASY_A_DVS89
He yanks him to his feet.
EASY_A_DVS90
SOMEONE and SOMEONE jump on the bed and smack the wall.
EASY_A_DVS91
He slaps her rear end and she smacks him.
EASY_A_DVS92
She punches him in the gut.
EASY_A_DVS93
SOMEONE hops down off the bed as SOMEONE recovers.
EASY_A_DVS94
As he stands, she musses his hair and rumbles his shirt.
EASY_A_DVS95
Pausing, SOMEONE grabs her arm.
EASY_A_DVS96
Olives meets his earnest gaze.
EASY_A_DVS97
As she smiles and nods, he leans his forehead against hers.
EASY_A_DVS98
SOMEONE beams kindly, and gives another nod. Facing the door, SOMEONE halts.
EASY_A_DVS99
He hands her the panties. SOMEONE salutes him, then stuffs them in his pocket.
EASY_A_DVS100
The eavesdroppers scatter as SOMEONE opens the door.
EASY_A_DVS101
He heads into the hallway.
EASY_A_DVS102
His bully accosts him.
EASY_A_DVS103
The bully gives him a friendly shove into a crowd of congratulatory males. As SOMEONE makes her way through the hallway, other teens clear a path and stare at her. She nearly bumps into SOMEONE at a doorway.
EASY_A_DVS104
Behind her back, several guys crudely thrust their pelvises.
EASY_A_DVS105
As she turns around, they sheepishly stop.
EASY_A_DVS106
Now SOMEONE plays an acoustic guitar in her room.
EASY_A_DVS107
Her mother enters, bearing a green box wrapped with a blue ribbon.
EASY_A_DVS108
Her mother bumps and grinds her hips on her way out.
EASY_A_DVS109
SOMEONE bonds unto her bed and opens the box. Inside she finds a greeting card with a gift card.
EASY_A_DVS110
She pulls out a phallic object wrapped in tissue.
EASY_A_DVS111
SOMEONE sets it back in the box, and answers her cell.
EASY_A_DVS112
The box vibrates.
EASY_A_DVS113
She ends the call.
EASY_A_DVS114
She flings all the clothes out of her closet and storms out.
EASY_A_DVS115
Later, she returns toting a half dozen shopping bags. Now SOMEONE tears red fabric into scraps then meticulously cuts them up with scissors as her dog looks on.
EASY_A_DVS116
Pulling bustiers from the shopping bags, she sits to work with a needle and thread.
EASY_A_DVS117
She pricks herself.
EASY_A_DVS118
She sucks her thumb, but keeps working, cutting the thread with her teeth.
EASY_A_DVS119
Her father steps in.
EASY_A_DVS121
They share a grin, and he heads out. Later SOMEONE sews with a smile. She bites off the thread then studies her handiwork.
EASY_A_DVS123
In an outdoor breezeway, SOMEONE struts into a crowd of students wearing a black bustier with a red letter A sewn to the bust. A double strand of pearls rings her neck, and her auburn hair falls in soft curls around her face. Dark sunglasses hide her eyes above her coy smile. As she sashays onward, the students stare at her.
EASY_A_DVS124
She makes a kissy face.
EASY_A_DVS125
A girl and guy watched slack-jawed. SOMEONE smirks to herself.
EASY_A_DVS126
With a bustier showing off her narrow waist, she halts facing SOMEONE and SOMEONE. The blonde eyes her friend scandalous outfit, and shakes her head.
EASY_A_DVS127
SOMEONE frowns.
EASY_A_DVS128
SOMEONE smacks SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS129
Now at the lunch counter, SOMEONE serves herself mashed potatoes. Two guys ogle her. She eats some of her potatoes, and sucks the spoon.
EASY_A_DVS130
One guy drops his tray. As they scramble away, SOMEONE finds herself facing SOMEONE, who snares and heads off.
EASY_A_DVS131
Seeing Mr. SOMEONE behind her, SOMEONE yanks the spoon from her mouth.
EASY_A_DVS132
Now in a gazebo.
EASY_A_DVS133
She points at everyone.
EASY_A_DVS134
A hunky guy with a cross necklace accompanies a boy on guitar.
EASY_A_DVS135
SOMEONE climbs out of a lap pool.
EASY_A_DVS136
He gives her a playful shove. A chubby guy drives off behind her.
EASY_A_DVS137
She stutters and stalks off.
EASY_A_DVS138
She gives him an angry gape. SOMEONE blinks shamefully.
EASY_A_DVS139
He gestures at his chunky build.
EASY_A_DVS140
He plods away.
EASY_A_DVS141
SOMEONE lingers, brushing her hair back.
EASY_A_DVS142
She watches as SOMEONE plops down on a bench.
EASY_A_DVS143
He glumly eats a snack. SOMEONE bombs her head equivocatingly.
EASY_A_DVS144
His hopeful expression fades as she saunters off.
EASY_A_DVS145
Our view zooms from guys texting at the pool, to more guys huddle around a cellphone on the soccer field.
EASY_A_DVS146
Nearby, a girl talks to a football player. She heads to the track, where four other girls race, then stop and huddle around a phone.
EASY_A_DVS147
Our view whizzes to the bleachers, where another girl chats with a couple.
EASY_A_DVS148
We zoom through tennis courts, through a locker room, and into the gym. A dance team reads a text, as they rehearse a can-can. We whiz back through the locker room, to the lap pool, where SOMEONE stands uncomfortably. A guy points at her.
EASY_A_DVS149
A Christian boy play guitar.
EASY_A_DVS150
Paris Bueller sings.
EASY_A_DVS151
SOMEONE shows another page to her webcam.
EASY_A_DVS152
Now she knocks on Mr. SOMEONE's open door.
EASY_A_DVS153
She takes a seat facing his desk.
EASY_A_DVS154
He nods, then waggles a finger at a scarlet A on her pink bustier.
EASY_A_DVS155
A tall blonde enters.
EASY_A_DVS156
SOMEONE leaves.
EASY_A_DVS157
As they kiss, he gropes her rear.
EASY_A_DVS158
He pinches her butt.
EASY_A_DVS159
He stares longingly after his wife, then frowns and shifts his gaze. Now in the administrative office, SOMEONE sharpens pencils and blows off the shavings.
EASY_A_DVS160
SOMEONE scowls at SOMEONE, who winks back at her.
EASY_A_DVS162
She shows a plaque.
EASY_A_DVS163
SOMEONE nods blankly.
EASY_A_DVS164
She offers a handful of condoms.
EASY_A_DVS165
Mrs. SOMEONE nods and smiles as SOMEONE collects her things.
EASY_A_DVS166
In the main office, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE comforting Micah.
EASY_A_DVS167
SOMEONE squeezes his arm and murmurs. He tearfully heads toward the counselor's office.
EASY_A_DVS168
She kisses her fingers, pats her hand over her heart, then raises it skyward. Micah does the same.
EASY_A_DVS169
SOMEONE takes a seat beside SOMEONE, and awkwardly pats the sobbing girl's head.
EASY_A_DVS170
SOMEONE grabs her.
EASY_A_DVS171
She yanks her into a hug.
EASY_A_DVS172
SOMEONE seizes her in another hug.
EASY_A_DVS173
SOMEONE shakes her head.
EASY_A_DVS174
As they hug again, SOMEONE sniffs her hair.
EASY_A_DVS175
The next day they hug again.
EASY_A_DVS176
SOMEONE points at her phone. SOMEONE reads her text. "Hey girlie, hang after SKL today, xoxox. WWJD. "
EASY_A_DVS177
SOMEONE points at her ceramics partner and mimes gagging. SOMEONE gives a sarcastic thumbs up.
EASY_A_DVS178
As they hug, SOMEONE rests her hand near a spinning table saw.
EASY_A_DVS179
SOMEONE uses a wooden cross to edge it away. Now in a hospital room.
EASY_A_DVS180
His mother swats him.
EASY_A_DVS181
She smacks him again. Later she uses her cellphone.
EASY_A_DVS182
Now in the school office, SOMEONE holds a phone to her ear.
EASY_A_DVS183
Mrs. SOMEONE steps in and overhears.
EASY_A_DVS184
Now SOMEONE storms into the locker room.
EASY_A_DVS185
She slaps SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS186
SOMEONE smirks. Now Micah uses his cell.
EASY_A_DVS187
Mrs. SOMEONE hangs up.
EASY_A_DVS188
She paces in her office, a hand cupped over her mouth.
EASY_A_DVS189
SOMEONE walks in.
EASY_A_DVS190
She throws a photo of herself with her husband into a box, breaking the frame.
EASY_A_DVS191
SOMEONE stares sympathetically at the tearful guidance counselor.
EASY_A_DVS192
Mrs. SOMEONE looks up at her.
EASY_A_DVS193
She nods emphatically. SOMEONE lays a hand on her shoulder.
EASY_A_DVS194
SOMEONE winces, then lowers her hand.
EASY_A_DVS195
Mrs. SOMEONE pulls her into a hug. Her hair pokes into SOMEONE's mouth.
EASY_A_DVS196
Later SOMEONE steps outside, to find the fundamentalists holding signs reading variations of, "Olive is a slut. "
EASY_A_DVS197
SOMEONE pickets.
EASY_A_DVS198
She rejoins the group. As SOMEONE starts to leave, she bumps into SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS199
He glimpses at the protesters.
EASY_A_DVS200
SOMEONE turns away.
EASY_A_DVS201
With her back to SOMEONE and the protesters, she wears a wounded stare as she walks away.
EASY_A_DVS202
At a bookstore.
EASY_A_DVS203
Later she flips through a Bible.
EASY_A_DVS204
Now at a church.
EASY_A_DVS205
SOMEONE steps into a confessional booth.
EASY_A_DVS206
SOMEONE's large green eyes glisten.
EASY_A_DVS207
The young outcast gives a slow nod, then shrugs tearfully.
EASY_A_DVS208
Light from the confessional's grated screen cast an ornate shadow pattern against her cheek.
EASY_A_DVS209
Looking in, she finds the priest's booth empty.
EASY_A_DVS210
She leaves the confessional and rushes past a pew, knocking a Bible from the seat. She puts it back and hurries out.
EASY_A_DVS211
Now in the pastor's office.
EASY_A_DVS212
His placid smile briefly vanishes.
EASY_A_DVS213
She knocks over a family photo. Righting it, she finds SOMEONE in the picture.
EASY_A_DVS214
She topples another photo of him and SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS215
Now at home, SOMEONE sits on a sectional with her mom and brother.
EASY_A_DVS216
In the cafeteria.
EASY_A_DVS217
SOMEONE smiles as he stands.
EASY_A_DVS218
She beams softly to herself.
EASY_A_DVS219
Nighttime at the Lobster Shack, SOMEONE shares a booth with SOMEONE who wears a demure black dress.
EASY_A_DVS220
He smiles boyishly.
EASY_A_DVS221
Under SOMEONE's unwavering gaze, SOMEONE gives a nervous nod, then looks down at the table.
EASY_A_DVS222
Wearing a plush lobster on his head, SOMEONE leads fellow servers to a table.
EASY_A_DVS223
Watching fondly, SOMEONE spies SOMEONE on the other side of a fish tank.
EASY_A_DVS224
SOMEONE spots them.
EASY_A_DVS225
Sneaking out, SOMEONE glances over and finds her staring.
EASY_A_DVS226
SOMEONE turns away.
EASY_A_DVS227
Later, SOMEONE walks her to a car.
EASY_A_DVS228
She starts to open the passenger door, but he shuts it.
EASY_A_DVS229
He presents a gift card.
EASY_A_DVS230
Staring at it, SOMEONE tears up and bites her lip.
EASY_A_DVS231
SOMEONE looks up at him with a wounded glare.
EASY_A_DVS232
He kisses her. She pulls back.
EASY_A_DVS233
He tries again. She pushes him away.
EASY_A_DVS234
He grabs her.
EASY_A_DVS235
She shoves him.
EASY_A_DVS236
He leans in again.
EASY_A_DVS237
SOMEONE wrestles him off her. Then marches toward the restaurant.
EASY_A_DVS238
She chucks the gift card at him.
EASY_A_DVS239
She turns her back to him and cries.
EASY_A_DVS240
She bites her lip hard. SOMEONE gets in his car.
EASY_A_DVS241
SOMEONE picks at the stitching of her A.
EASY_A_DVS242
SOMEONE comes out from the back of the building.
EASY_A_DVS243
SOMEONE's car peals through the parking lot as the off-duty waiter approaches the tearful girl.
EASY_A_DVS244
She gives a grateful nod.
EASY_A_DVS245
Now SOMEONE drives, as SOMEONE cries in the passenger seat.
EASY_A_DVS246
She shakes her head, wincing tearfully.
EASY_A_DVS247
They smile and lock eyes. SOMEONE bashfully drops her gaze.
EASY_A_DVS248
Knitting her brow, she shakes her head. SOMEONE blinks.
EASY_A_DVS249
She unbuckles her seat belt and they share a tight embrace.
EASY_A_DVS250
SOMEONE buries his face in her shoulder.
EASY_A_DVS251
As she pulls away, he holds on to her hand.
EASY_A_DVS252
She pulls it away, and opens the door. Then swings her long slender legs outside.
EASY_A_DVS253
She stands and shuts the door behind her, strolling off.
EASY_A_DVS254
Facing the car once again, she leans down to peak at SOMEONE through the window.
EASY_A_DVS255
He rolls it down. And turns off the ignition.
EASY_A_DVS256
She cringes, rolling her eyes, then heads off.
EASY_A_DVS257
She grins at him over her shoulder.
EASY_A_DVS258
The gossipy girl dashes off.
EASY_A_DVS259
She crumbles ice-cream cones at the chubby server.
EASY_A_DVS260
Micah scratches himself as he reads a Bible.
EASY_A_DVS262
SOMEONE stares wide-eyed. Mrs. SOMEONE smiles, and shifts in her seat.
EASY_A_DVS263
SOMEONE hurries out and runs across the quad into Mr. SOMEONE's classroom.
EASY_A_DVS264
SOMEONE's jaw drops and she shakes her head.
EASY_A_DVS265
She shifts her horrified gaze.
EASY_A_DVS266
Now at her webcam.
EASY_A_DVS267
Mr. SOMEONE trudges though campus.
EASY_A_DVS268
Nighttime on the ridge.
EASY_A_DVS269
SOMEONE shows her scarf.
EASY_A_DVS270
The mother kisses her daughter's head.
EASY_A_DVS271
She cradles SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS272
SOMEONE shows a glittery sign to her webcam.
EASY_A_DVS273
Now in a packed gym, SOMEONE rolls out the wheelbarrow. SOMEONE climbs out of the wood in a feather boa.
EASY_A_DVS274
She rips off SOMEONE's Woodchuck costume, revealing his blue devil costume.
EASY_A_DVS275
They share a grin.
EASY_A_DVS276
In the stands, the fundamentalists stare as other students smile and clap.
EASY_A_DVS277
SOMEONE pumps his fist.
EASY_A_DVS278
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE's cheek and gives her the feather boa.
EASY_A_DVS279
In a black corset with red stripes, SOMEONE bumps her hip at a gawking basketball player. Then smacks a dancer's rear.
EASY_A_DVS280
SOMEONE's jaw drops. SOMEONE pulls the slide of a band member's trombone, and poses with SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS281
SOMEONE narrows her eyes.
EASY_A_DVS283
Principal Gibbons storms over.
EASY_A_DVS284
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap disgusted looks.
EASY_A_DVS285
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's arm and scampers out with him.
EASY_A_DVS286
Later she faces her webcam as her classmates, teachers, and family watch her webcast.
EASY_A_DVS287
SOMEONE peeks outside, and finds SOMEONE standing on a lawnmower holding a pair of speakers.
EASY_A_DVS288
She faces her webcam once again.
EASY_A_DVS289
Her brother stares, listening in.
EASY_A_DVS290
The webcast shows her grin and trod out the door.
EASY_A_DVS291
The pastor frowns at his laptop.
EASY_A_DVS292
SOMEONE watches on a cellphone and a truck almost hits him.
EASY_A_DVS293
He hurls ice cream at it.
EASY_A_DVS294
Now, Mr. SOMEONE stares steadily at his laptop.
EASY_A_DVS295
His wife smiles at him, but he ignores her.
EASY_A_DVS296
She sheepishly sucks her lips and heads off.
EASY_A_DVS297
Mr. , SOMEONE watches her go.
EASY_A_DVS298
In the gazebo, SOMEONE soberly touches her cross necklace.
EASY_A_DVS299
SOMEONE sits at a fountain, staring at a text that reads, "Ri, sorry I lied to you. "
EASY_A_DVS300
The busty blonde gazes off tearfully.
EASY_A_DVS301
Now in a hotel room, SOMEONE lies in bed.
EASY_A_DVS302
His beefy mocha skin boyfriend snuggles up behind him and they watch Huckleberry Finn on a laptop.
EASY_A_DVS303
SOMEONE smiles. Now outside, SOMEONE leaps into SOMEONE's arms.
EASY_A_DVS304
He whirls her around, then sets her down. They share a sweet passionate kiss.
EASY_A_DVS305
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's hand, then leads her to the lawnmower.
EASY_A_DVS306
She climbs onto the rear grass-bagger as SOMEONE takes a seat at the wheel.
EASY_A_DVS307
She wraps her arm around his chest and they ride off.
EASY_A_DVS308
They wheel slowly across the lawn.
EASY_A_DVS309
SOMEONE raises an arm victoriously, and so does SOMEONE.
EASY_A_DVS310
Their image freezes.
EASY_A_DVS311
They drive onward, keeping their fists in the air.
EASY_A_DVS312
The mower carries them up a tree-lined road on a hill.