The woman climbs on the bed.
FLIGHT_DVS22
She straddles the man.
FLIGHT_DVS23
She puts the joint to his lips.
FLIGHT_DVS24
She gets off the bed.
FLIGHT_DVS25
He smokes his cigarette.
FLIGHT_DVS26
He sits up and snorts a line of cocaine.
FLIGHT_DVS27
The man walks out of the room, dressed in a black suit and sporting dark glasses under a pilot's cap.
FLIGHT_DVS28
An airplane pin is on his lapel.
FLIGHT_DVS29
People run across the tarmac, as rain lashes the airport.
FLIGHT_DVS30
Lightning flashes in the distance.
FLIGHT_DVS32
The man, now in a raincoat, walks under a parked South Jet airplane.
FLIGHT_DVS34
He pauses near one of the wheels, opens his mouth, and sprays some mouth freshener.
FLIGHT_DVS36
He trots to the mobile stairway leading to the passenger walkway, and slips on the first step.
FLIGHT_DVS37
He joins the passengers through a side door.
FLIGHT_DVS38
Whitaker sits next to his copilot.
FLIGHT_DVS39
SOMEONE inhales the oxygen.
FLIGHT_DVS40
SOMEONE fidgets on his side of the cockpit.
FLIGHT_DVS41
Ken watches as SOMEONE brushes his hair.
FLIGHT_DVS42
A woman steps out of a room at Hotel Atlanta, carrying a folded up massage table.
FLIGHT_DVS43
She wears a dress, and has a small tattoo on her shoulder.
FLIGHT_DVS44
She pulls some bills from a bundle of cash.
FLIGHT_DVS45
She walks to a car and places the massage table in the trunk.
FLIGHT_DVS46
She smokes as she makes a call from the driver’s seat.
FLIGHT_DVS47
She leans on the steering wheel, and lowers the phone to the passenger seat.
FLIGHT_DVS48
A man snorts coke.
FLIGHT_DVS49
He looks SOMEONE over.
FLIGHT_DVS50
SOMEONE drops his towel.
FLIGHT_DVS51
He holds a small square.
FLIGHT_DVS52
SOMEONE sits facing SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS53
Pushes the side stick forward.
FLIGHT_DVS54
The cockpit shakes.
FLIGHT_DVS55
SOMEONE takes the yoke and pulls back.
FLIGHT_DVS56
They ascend.
FLIGHT_DVS57
The plane shakes, and items fall from the overhead bins.
FLIGHT_DVS58
Ken casts an uneasy sideways glance at SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS59
SOMEONE eyes the horizon as he steers the plane through rough air.
FLIGHT_DVS60
He moves the side stick forward.
FLIGHT_DVS61
The altimeter slides quickly to the right as the plane rises.
FLIGHT_DVS62
They reach a clearing, through clouds and bright sunlight, as SOMEONE levels out.
FLIGHT_DVS63
SOMEONE smiles, and looks at the passengers from her jump seat.
FLIGHT_DVS64
SOMEONE takes the phone.
FLIGHT_DVS65
A car speeds past a sign that reads Georgian Gardens, and stops.
FLIGHT_DVS66
SOMEONE gets out of the car, and runs up to the second floor of a small, run-down apartment complex.
FLIGHT_DVS67
She pulls out a key as she reaches the door, only to discover it is slightly open.
FLIGHT_DVS68
She smiles at him.
FLIGHT_DVS69
He stands in the doorway.
FLIGHT_DVS70
She kicks the door closed.
FLIGHT_DVS71
She flings her bag on a table and it hits a box, which falls and scatters its contents.
FLIGHT_DVS72
She spots a syringe.
FLIGHT_DVS73
SOMEONE speaks into the intercom.
FLIGHT_DVS74
He pours the contents of a small vodka bottle into a juice container, hidden from the passenger's view.
FLIGHT_DVS75
He tosses three miniature bottles as he grabs the spiked orange juice.
FLIGHT_DVS77
He takes a long drink as SOMEONE exits the toilet, and he goes in.
FLIGHT_DVS79
In SOMEONE's apartment, framed photographs on the table show a younger, smiling SOMEONE with her mother.
FLIGHT_DVS80
SOMEONE lightly taps the syringe,
FLIGHT_DVS81
then pushes out a small drop that slides down the needle.
FLIGHT_DVS82
She tightens a tourniquet around her arm, and holds the end securely in her mouth.
FLIGHT_DVS83
She positions the needle and injects.
FLIGHT_DVS86
Her arms relax and she lets go of the syringe.
FLIGHT_DVS88
She leans back, eyes closed.
FLIGHT_DVS89
The strap falls from her mouth.
FLIGHT_DVS90
Her head lolls to her shoulder.
FLIGHT_DVS91
Her dilated pupils shrink to tiny dots.
FLIGHT_DVS92
She grabs the packet of cocaine that Kip gave her, and falls on her side.
FLIGHT_DVS93
The packet falls, inches from her hand.
FLIGHT_DVS94
Her fingers reach out, but only push it away.
FLIGHT_DVS96
Her hand goes still, as feet appear under the door.
FLIGHT_DVS99
In the cockpit, SOMEONE sleeps with paper covering his eyes, and his sunglasses over the paper.
FLIGHT_DVS100
Ken's yoke jerks away.
FLIGHT_DVS101
The yoke slips out of Ken's hands as SOMEONE struggles to gain control, and the plane begins to dive.
FLIGHT_DVS102
The wheels of the aircraft unfold. In the galley, SOMEONE grabs the phone.
FLIGHT_DVS103
SOMEONE unbuckles her seatbelt.
FLIGHT_DVS104
Alarmed passengers grasp the seat in front of them, as a flight attendant tries to assist someone.
FLIGHT_DVS105
SOMEONE falls, and hits her head.
FLIGHT_DVS106
SOMEONE lies still.
FLIGHT_DVS107
SOMEONE banks to the left.
FLIGHT_DVS109
The planes turns upside down.
FLIGHT_DVS111
She slides the side stick forward.
FLIGHT_DVS112
One wheel gets stuck while retracting.
FLIGHT_DVS113
Inside the cabin, SOMEONE comes to a rest on the ceiling, and SOMEONE sees a young boy slip out of his seat.
FLIGHT_DVS114
Outside Georgian Gardens, a medical aide wheels SOMEONE beside Fran, as the upside down plane flies past.
FLIGHT_DVS115
SOMEONE crawls to the boy, and straps him back in his seat.
FLIGHT_DVS116
A light flashes on the control panel in the cockpit.
FLIGHT_DVS117
The plane turns upright, and a still unconscious SOMEONE falls on some passengers.
FLIGHT_DVS118
SOMEONE loses her hold, and falls against the bulkhead.
FLIGHT_DVS119
Fire and smoke billow from the left engine.
FLIGHT_DVS120
SOMEONE tumbles across the galley, as the plane straightens out.
FLIGHT_DVS121
Gauges drop.
FLIGHT_DVS122
They head towards a church, sitting on an expanse of open land.
FLIGHT_DVS123
SOMEONE steers the plane away from the church's steeple,
FLIGHT_DVS124
but the wing grazes the top.
FLIGHT_DVS125
The plane hits the ground. SOMEONE flies past the cockpit, as SOMEONE bangs his head and passes out.
FLIGHT_DVS127
Through blurred vision, SOMEONE sees Ken leaning to the side in his seat, as he is dragged out.
FLIGHT_DVS128
SOMEONE is slumped next to SOMEONE's still body, her head crushed by a collapsed bulkhead.
FLIGHT_DVS130
Smoke blocks SOMEONE's vision, as he is pulled away from the plane.
FLIGHT_DVS131
As people in white robes help the passengers, a fire engine arrives.
FLIGHT_DVS133
SOMEONE looks up at a female EMT leaning over him,
FLIGHT_DVS134
then turns towards the black smoke rising from the crash site.
FLIGHT_DVS135
The broken off spire from the church lies some distance away from an ambulance, as rescue workers help survivors.
FLIGHT_DVS137
In a hospital ward, SOMEONE slowly opens his right eye.
FLIGHT_DVS138
The other eye is covered by a bandage.
FLIGHT_DVS139
He sees a seated man on the TV gesturing, as rescue workers push a stretcher behind him.
FLIGHT_DVS140
The tagline reads, Breaking news. SOMEONE Hogg, South Jet 227 passenger.
FLIGHT_DVS141
A field reporter for Channel 12 News comments live from the site, as lights flicker in the background.
FLIGHT_DVS142
On TV, cell phone footage shows the descent of the plane, as it swerves and slices off the church steeple.
FLIGHT_DVS145
It glides overhead, both engines on fire, and slams down on its side, as people in white robes run for cover.
FLIGHT_DVS146
SOMEONE, his head wrapped in gauze,
FLIGHT_DVS147
watches in a daze, as the church folk stand and take in the scene from a distance,
FLIGHT_DVS148
then slowly approach.
FLIGHT_DVS149
SOMEONE averts his gaze from the screen, and notices a man in the room.
FLIGHT_DVS150
The man wears a suit with a collar open, and is staring intently at his cell phone.
FLIGHT_DVS151
SOMEONE turns, and SOMEONE smiles.
FLIGHT_DVS152
A man walks in wearing an NTSB jacket, followed by a few law officers, a nurse, and a doctor.
FLIGHT_DVS153
The NTSB officer places a recorder on SOMEONE's bed.
FLIGHT_DVS154
SOMEONE nods weakly.
FLIGHT_DVS155
The doctor leaves.
FLIGHT_DVS156
Craig takes his recorder, and leaves with the others,
FLIGHT_DVS157
but SOMEONE stays back.
FLIGHT_DVS158
SOMEONE smiles.
FLIGHT_DVS159
He reaches for a plastic bag.
FLIGHT_DVS160
SOMEONE leaves.
FLIGHT_DVS161
SOMEONE puts his bandaged hand to his mouth, as tears flow down his face,
FLIGHT_DVS162
then shakes his head, and takes his cell phone from the plastic bag.
FLIGHT_DVS164
He drops the phone on his stomach.
FLIGHT_DVS165
A heavy man with a goatee walks into the hospital, wearing Bermuda shorts and dark glasses, with earphone wires hanging on each side of his head.
FLIGHT_DVS166
He strides through the corridors, carrying a bag in his hand, and another slung over his shoulder.
FLIGHT_DVS167
He removes his earphones, and leans over the reception desk.
FLIGHT_DVS168
He enters SOMEONE's room with a video camera, as a nurse helps SOMEONE from the bed, exposing his buttocks.
FLIGHT_DVS169
The nurse leaves the room.
FLIGHT_DVS170
SOMEONE places his hand on SOMEONE's head, and leaves.
FLIGHT_DVS171
SOMEONE closes his eyes.
FLIGHT_DVS172
SOMEONE is startled awake.
FLIGHT_DVS173
He looks around the dark room, then clicks on the light.
FLIGHT_DVS174
He peeks into the corridor, as a nurse walks by the reception desk.
FLIGHT_DVS175
He quickly limps down the hall, using a cane.
FLIGHT_DVS176
He stops at a door marked Stairwell, third floor, and opens it.
FLIGHT_DVS177
He sees SOMEONE sitting on the stairs, smoking a cigarette.
FLIGHT_DVS178
She rises, to leave.
FLIGHT_DVS179
She sits.
FLIGHT_DVS180
SOMEONE leans against the wall, facing her.
FLIGHT_DVS181
He lights a cigarette.
FLIGHT_DVS182
She shakes her head.
FLIGHT_DVS183
A patient climbs the stairs.
FLIGHT_DVS184
SOMEONE tosses her pack.
FLIGHT_DVS185
The gaunt man stands by his IV pole.
FLIGHT_DVS186
She shakes her head.
FLIGHT_DVS187
She glances at SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS188
The bald man turns to SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS189
Cigarette hanging out of his mouth, the man picks up the IV pole and walks downstairs.
FLIGHT_DVS192
She wipes a tear from her eye, offers a smile, then stands, and climbs up the stairs.
FLIGHT_DVS193
A black Cadillac lurches out of the hospital parking structure, and passes the news crews parked outside.
FLIGHT_DVS194
SOMEONE opens a beer, and takes a swig.
FLIGHT_DVS196
He hands SOMEONE a package, a bundle of cash.
FLIGHT_DVS197
A car turns onto a dirt driveway and passes a sign that reads, Whitaker Crop Dusting Company.
FLIGHT_DVS199
There's a For Sale sign next to it.
FLIGHT_DVS200
The car passes a dilapidated shed on the right, and pulls up to a large, older farmhouse.
FLIGHT_DVS201
SOMEONE stops the car.
FLIGHT_DVS202
SOMEONE places a bag beside the door, and reaches above one of the wooden posts supporting the veranda roof.
FLIGHT_DVS203
He grabs a hidden key.
FLIGHT_DVS204
He enters a cozy, fully furnished living room, and looks around.
FLIGHT_DVS205
A retro stereo sits on a cabinet, against a wall with framed photos.
FLIGHT_DVS207
His eye still covered by a bandage, looks around.
FLIGHT_DVS209
SOMEONE carries a plastic bag into the kitchen, and places it on a dining table.
FLIGHT_DVS210
He plugs in a charger, and checks his iPhone.
FLIGHT_DVS211
It shows 127 voice messages.
FLIGHT_DVS212
He leans on a bureau, and pulls out a prescription bottle from his pocket.
FLIGHT_DVS213
He glances at the pills, then, at a decanter of whiskey, and other liquor bottles near the stereo.
FLIGHT_DVS216
He licks his lips, and clenches his jaw.
FLIGHT_DVS218
Using a cane for support, he strides into the bathroom, and dumps the pills down the toilet.
FLIGHT_DVS219
He collects the bottles of liquor and the decanter, and turns on the stereo.
FLIGHT_DVS220
He empties the bottles in the sink, then dumps the empties in the garbage.
FLIGHT_DVS222
He takes a case of Corona and some other beer cans from the fridge, and also drains them.
FLIGHT_DVS223
He dumps the cans in a bin.
FLIGHT_DVS224
He takes a bag of marijuana from a wooden box in a drawer, and flushes it.
FLIGHT_DVS226
He continues his chore with determination, as he moves from cabinet to cabinet, removing and tossing bottles and cans.
FLIGHT_DVS228
He opens a freezer, and finds a bottle of vodka.
FLIGHT_DVS229
He places his packet of money, wrapped in white paper labeled Veal, and removes the bottle. He pours it down the sink.
FLIGHT_DVS232
He lifts the balding plastic trash bag out of the trash can, and carries it outside.
FLIGHT_DVS233
He slides the doors of the shed open,
FLIGHT_DVS234
revealing a two seat Cessna plane in the small hangar.
FLIGHT_DVS235
SOMEONE removes a blanket covering the windshield, and switches on the lights.
FLIGHT_DVS236
He looks at a group of photos hanging above a workstation off to one side of the hanger,
FLIGHT_DVS237
then takes a picture of a young African American boy, wedged in a frame.
FLIGHT_DVS238
He kisses the photograph.
FLIGHT_DVS239
He pulls out a bottle of liquor from a bowling bag, and tosses it aside.
FLIGHT_DVS241
He holds a framed wedding photo of himself and his wife.
FLIGHT_DVS243
Later that evening he sits, watching the news.
FLIGHT_DVS244
SOMEONE stands at a table strewn with the pictures of the crash, as men in suits look on.
FLIGHT_DVS245
The next morning, SOMEONE walks through the lobby of a hotel, cane in hand,
FLIGHT_DVS246
the large eye patch gone, and now stitches remain above his eye.
FLIGHT_DVS247
He enters a dining area with a buffet to one side, and approaches SOMEONE, seated with a man wearing glasses.
FLIGHT_DVS310
SOMEONE looks through a file.
FLIGHT_DVS339
SOMEONE looks at the piece of paper before him, narrows his eyes.
FLIGHT_DVS341
SOMEONE rises to leave.
FLIGHT_DVS342
He stops in the bar area.
FLIGHT_DVS343
A photo of SOMEONE appears on the TV behind the bar.
FLIGHT_DVS344
SOMEONE sits at the bar and moves a cocktail napkin back and forth, As he studies the glass of vodka.
FLIGHT_DVS346
He picks it up, and takes a drink.
FLIGHT_DVS350
He smacks his lips, picks up the glass again, and drains the contents.
FLIGHT_DVS351
Later, he sets a case of Budweiser in the passenger seat. He gets in the car and unscrews a gallon bottle of vodka.
FLIGHT_DVS353
He Looks around and drinks from the bottle.
FLIGHT_DVS355
He drives with groggy eyed.
FLIGHT_DVS357
SOMEONE drives down a street, beer can in hand.
FLIGHT_DVS358
He passes a dead-end street, and stops.
FLIGHT_DVS361
SOMEONE looks away, then back at SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS362
He watches, as SOMEONE loads items in the back of a car.
FLIGHT_DVS363
As she runs back through a worn fence,
FLIGHT_DVS365
SOMEONE pulls up to the apartment entrance, behind SOMEONE's car.
FLIGHT_DVS367
He passes the car with SOMEONE's things, and glances through a few enlarged photographs in a basket.
FLIGHT_DVS368
He takes a sip from his beer and looks up.
FLIGHT_DVS370
SOMEONE walks toward the apartment.
FLIGHT_DVS371
SOMEONE pushes Fran to the floor.
FLIGHT_DVS372
SOMEONE nods.
FLIGHT_DVS373
SOMEONE takes out some money.
FLIGHT_DVS374
SOMEONE looks at her for a moment.
FLIGHT_DVS376
SOMEONE sits in the passenger seat of SOMEONE's car, as he drives and drinks his beer.
FLIGHT_DVS377
She bites her thumb.
FLIGHT_DVS378
He offers SOMEONE a beer, and she refuses.
FLIGHT_DVS379
He lights a cigarette.
FLIGHT_DVS380
She fidgets as she smiles to herself, and observes SOMEONE as he drives.
FLIGHT_DVS382
A cassette labeled Soul Funk No. 2 plays on the stereo.
FLIGHT_DVS383
As SOMEONE lies back with a pack of ice on his knee, he picks up a glass of whisky.
FLIGHT_DVS384
SOMEONE fresh from taking a shower, exits the bathroom.
FLIGHT_DVS385
She picks up a cushion.
FLIGHT_DVS386
Carrying the pillow, she walks to SOMEONE, kneels down beside him, and removes the ice pack from his knee.
FLIGHT_DVS388
She lifts his leg, and places the cushion under it.
FLIGHT_DVS389
She massages his knee.
FLIGHT_DVS391
SOMEONE is laid back in the armchair, watching as SOMEONE's hands move up to cover his hand. He raises the glass, as if to take a drink, but stops midway.
FLIGHT_DVS392
SOMEONE hesitates, her gaze steady on him.
FLIGHT_DVS396
She takes the glass from his hand, and sets it carefully on the nearby table.
FLIGHT_DVS398
She pushes herself towards him.
FLIGHT_DVS399
They kiss. They look into each other's eyes, and their lips meet again.
FLIGHT_DVS401
The next morning, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE as she briefly stirs in her sleep.
FLIGHT_DVS402
SOMEONE looks up, and rises off the bed.
FLIGHT_DVS404
SOMEONE gets out of a car.
FLIGHT_DVS405
SOMEONE steps onto the veranda, holding his cane and a gun.
FLIGHT_DVS406
SOMEONE partially raises his hands.
FLIGHT_DVS407
SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb a platform near the church.
FLIGHT_DVS408
A small congregation listens to a sermon in a cordoned off area.
FLIGHT_DVS409
SOMEONE takes a pair of binoculars, and watches a woman step out of a black SUV.
FLIGHT_DVS410
SOMEONE watches, as reporters and officials wander around the wreckage.
FLIGHT_DVS411
SOMEONE clenches his jaw.
FLIGHT_DVS446
SOMEONE stands at the far end of the large conference table, opposite SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS488
SOMEONE pushes through the double glass doors and walks towards SOMEONE, who stands.
FLIGHT_DVS489
SOMEONE forces a smile.
FLIGHT_DVS490
SOMEONE drinks straight from a whisky bottle.
FLIGHT_DVS491
He watches a home video of his father and son playing football.
FLIGHT_DVS492
SOMEONE walks in the door.
FLIGHT_DVS493
SOMEONE watches him.
FLIGHT_DVS494
He increases the volume on the TV.
FLIGHT_DVS495
SOMEONE has not moved since she walked in.
FLIGHT_DVS496
She watches SOMEONE try to stand, and then fall.
FLIGHT_DVS497
He lies prone on the carpet.
FLIGHT_DVS498
SOMEONE covers her mouth with her hand.
FLIGHT_DVS499
SOMEONE has passed out.
FLIGHT_DVS500
SOMEONE removes the cigarette from his fingers and adjusts his head, so he can breathe easily.
FLIGHT_DVS501
SOMEONE covers SOMEONE with a blanket, then turns off the video and switches off the light.
FLIGHT_DVS504
SOMEONE sits in a chair on the veranda, taking pictures.
FLIGHT_DVS505
SOMEONE steps out in a bathrobe.
FLIGHT_DVS506
He ambles toward her.
FLIGHT_DVS507
He sits in a rocking chair.
FLIGHT_DVS508
He smiles at her.
FLIGHT_DVS509
He places a cigarette in his mouth, and picks up her camera.
FLIGHT_DVS510
He picks up a book from the coffee table between them.
FLIGHT_DVS511
He points to some open land.
FLIGHT_DVS512
SOMEONE puffs on her cigarette.
FLIGHT_DVS522
Points the camera at her.
FLIGHT_DVS523
At a church, a large, framed picture of SOMEONE stands surrounded by flowers, as a coffin is carried out.
FLIGHT_DVS524
SOMEONE stands in a dark suit, and watches the procession pass.
FLIGHT_DVS525
A young boy touches SOMEONE's arm.
FLIGHT_DVS526
SOMEONE turns around, and sees SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS527
He goes to her, and they hug.
FLIGHT_DVS528
SOMEONE reaches for her son, and pulls him close.
FLIGHT_DVS529
Both watch, as Trevor goes off to find his dad.
FLIGHT_DVS530
They hug again.
FLIGHT_DVS546
She looks at him, with tears in her eyes.
FLIGHT_DVS572
They stare at each other, unmoving.
FLIGHT_DVS573
He wipes her tears with his thumb.
FLIGHT_DVS581
SOMEONE watches him, her brow creased and her eyes soft with sympathy.
FLIGHT_DVS582
He kisses her, and leaves.
FLIGHT_DVS583
SOMEONE leans against his car in a parking lot, and watches an airplane overhead.
FLIGHT_DVS584
SOMEONE approaches in quick strides.
FLIGHT_DVS586
She hands him a Zippo.
FLIGHT_DVS587
He sticks a cigarette in his mouth.
FLIGHT_DVS588
A man stands at a podium.
FLIGHT_DVS589
SOMEONE sits, semi-slumped in a char.
FLIGHT_DVS590
The majority in the room lift their hands, including SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS591
SOMEONE does not raise his hand, crosses his arms.
FLIGHT_DVS593
SOMEONE leaves.
FLIGHT_DVS594
SOMEONE parks outside a bar, and walks in as his copilot, SOMEONE, appears on the news.
FLIGHT_DVS595
SOMEONE exits the bar.
FLIGHT_DVS597
At the hospital, SOMEONE walks over to a private room, and peeps in.
FLIGHT_DVS598
He taps his cane on the door frame.
FLIGHT_DVS599
A nurse dresses SOMEONE's wounds.
FLIGHT_DVS600
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look toward SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS601
SOMEONE turns to the nurse.
FLIGHT_DVS602
SOMEONE's left leg lies in a brace.
FLIGHT_DVS603
He closes the door.
FLIGHT_DVS605
SOMEONE rises to leave.
FLIGHT_DVS606
SOMEONE reaches for SOMEONE's hand.
FLIGHT_DVS607
SOMEONE's eyes dart up and down.
FLIGHT_DVS609
He takes SOMEONE's hand.
FLIGHT_DVS610
Later, at SOMEONE's family farm, SOMEONE sees the lights on in the hangar.
FLIGHT_DVS611
SOMEONE leans over the Cessna, still wearing his tie, his shirtsleeves rolled up.
FLIGHT_DVS613
He jumps off the ladder and hustles over to SOMEONE, kissing her.
FLIGHT_DVS626
He sips his beer.
FLIGHT_DVS627
She notices cocaine on a table.
FLIGHT_DVS659
SOMEONE sits on the bed.
FLIGHT_DVS660
She ends a call, and continues packing her things in the bedroom.
FLIGHT_DVS661
She ignores SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS662
SOMEONE takes a large swig before setting the bottle on a table, and entering the bedroom.
FLIGHT_DVS670
SOMEONE walks past SOMEONE, raising a hand to her head before she sits on the bed.
FLIGHT_DVS672
He sits next to her on the bed.
FLIGHT_DVS674
She leans in and their foreheads touch.
FLIGHT_DVS675
He kisses her, and she allows him to pull her into an embrace.
FLIGHT_DVS677
In the morning, SOMEONE lies sleeping on the bed, fully dressed.
FLIGHT_DVS678
SOMEONE stands at the bedroom entrance.
FLIGHT_DVS680
She leaves an envelope with SOMEONE's name on it, between his lighter and a bottle of whiskey.
FLIGHT_DVS681
She carries a suitcase and a basket, and walks away from the house.
FLIGHT_DVS682
SOMEONE's van is parked behind some trees, and SOMEONE puts her things in.
FLIGHT_DVS683
The van drives off.
FLIGHT_DVS684
He stops as he sees the envelope.
FLIGHT_DVS685
He trods over to the table and picks up the envelope.
FLIGHT_DVS687
He picks it up and opens it.
FLIGHT_DVS688
He reads the letter, using the light from a nearby window.
FLIGHT_DVS689
He picks up the bottle, and throws it hard across the room. It explodes against a hanging photo of his son.
FLIGHT_DVS690
SOMEONE stares at it, motionless.
FLIGHT_DVS691
Rain falls steadily as SOMEONE sits in the car and pours alcohol into a bottle of juice, and takes a drink.
FLIGHT_DVS692
He exits the car, and enters a large hangar.
FLIGHT_DVS693
The crashed South Jet aircraft stands almost completely assembled, with parts strewn around beside it.
FLIGHT_DVS694
Cabinets and shelves line one side of the building.
FLIGHT_DVS695
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE out of the plane.
FLIGHT_DVS738
SOMEONE Cocks his head.
FLIGHT_DVS768
SOMEONE turns and walks away.
FLIGHT_DVS770
SOMEONE speeds down the mud road, splashing slush to the side.
FLIGHT_DVS771
He brakes when he sees news crews outside the farm house.
FLIGHT_DVS772
Some reporters spot him, so he reverses and drives back onto the main road.
FLIGHT_DVS773
He stops opposite a house in a quiet neighborhood, pulling up on the curb, barely missing a fire hydrant.
FLIGHT_DVS774
He chugs on the bottle of juice.
FLIGHT_DVS775
He steps out of the car, and walks up a foot path to a house.
FLIGHT_DVS776
A man watches SOMEONE from a parked car, and speaks into his cell phone.
FLIGHT_DVS777
SOMEONE's ex-wife opens the door.
FLIGHT_DVS778
Her smile fades.
FLIGHT_DVS807
SOMEONE hugs a struggling SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS825
SOMEONE turns off the news.
FLIGHT_DVS850
SOMEONE lifts his arm.
FLIGHT_DVS851
SOMEONE walks down a hotel corridor, with SOMEONE holding a can of Coca Cola.
FLIGHT_DVS852
They approach a burly man.
FLIGHT_DVS853
SOMEONE emerges from a room.
FLIGHT_DVS854
SOMEONE enters the room.
FLIGHT_DVS880
They shake hands.
FLIGHT_DVS882
SOMEONE looks around the spacious room.
FLIGHT_DVS883
He picks up a can of coke, and goes over to the fridge.
FLIGHT_DVS884
He finds it stocked with juices and non-alcoholic beverages.
FLIGHT_DVS886
He eats a meal alone, in his room.
FLIGHT_DVS887
He lies in bed, surfing channels on the TV.
FLIGHT_DVS888
He shaves.
FLIGHT_DVS889
He tries to open the thick file SOMEONE left for him, and it spreads like an accordion.
FLIGHT_DVS890
He abandons it.
FLIGHT_DVS891
He sits over the toilet, smoking as the bath fills.
FLIGHT_DVS892
The clock shows 2:08 a. m. as he hangs a suit in a wardrobe.
FLIGHT_DVS893
He looks around for the source of the knocking.
FLIGHT_DVS894
Lying in bed, he's awakened by the same sound.
FLIGHT_DVS895
He gets out of bed, and goes to a side door.
FLIGHT_DVS896
He holds his ear to it,
FLIGHT_DVS897
then pulls it open.
FLIGHT_DVS898
The extended lock on a door leading to an adjoining room, bumps repeatedly against a door jam.
FLIGHT_DVS899
SOMEONE enters the room.
FLIGHT_DVS900
A gentle breeze blows through the balcony doors, ruffling drawn curtains.
FLIGHT_DVS901
SOMEONE walks over and gazes at the skyline.
FLIGHT_DVS902
A plane's beacon lights flash in the night sky.
FLIGHT_DVS903
SOMEONE turns around,
FLIGHT_DVS904
and his eyes fall on a fridge.
FLIGHT_DVS905
He opens the door to reveal rows of miniature bottles of alcohol on the shelves.
FLIGHT_DVS906
SOMEONE squats and looks over the array of spirits.
FLIGHT_DVS907
He settles for vodka.
FLIGHT_DVS909
Still kneeling, he unscrews the top from the bottle, and runs his fingers over the cold surface of the glass.
FLIGHT_DVS910
He brings the bottle to his nose.
FLIGHT_DVS912
He replaces the cap, then slowly stands up and sets the bottle on top of the fridge.
FLIGHT_DVS913
He closes the fridge door, and walks away.
FLIGHT_DVS914
SOMEONE swoops up the bottle.
FLIGHT_DVS915
SOMEONE exits an elevator, carrying three coffees.
FLIGHT_DVS916
SOMEONE follows.
FLIGHT_DVS918
The men look at each other.
FLIGHT_DVS919
SOMEONE checks the time.
FLIGHT_DVS920
Bottles lie everywhere.
FLIGHT_DVS921
SOMEONE lies face down in the bathroom, a large blood stain on the toilet.
FLIGHT_DVS934
SOMEONE arrives, a bag slung over his shoulder.
FLIGHT_DVS935
SOMEONE jumps back, and SOMEONE raises his hands.
FLIGHT_DVS936
SOMEONE gestures to SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS937
SOMEONE clears the table.
FLIGHT_DVS938
SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS939
He cuts the coke.
FLIGHT_DVS940
SOMEONE smiles up at SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS941
A torn piece of toilet paper, with a spot of blood, hangs over his eye.
FLIGHT_DVS942
SOMEONE fetches the water.
FLIGHT_DVS943
SOMEONE prepares the cigarette.
FLIGHT_DVS944
SOMEONE drinks.
FLIGHT_DVS945
SOMEONE sucks on the cigarette, and hands it to SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS946
SOMEONE cuts more lines of coke.
FLIGHT_DVS947
SOMEONE snorts a line,
FLIGHT_DVS948
and offers a hit to SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS949
SOMEONE nods.
FLIGHT_DVS950
SOMEONE enters the bathroom.
FLIGHT_DVS963
SOMEONE puts on his shades.
FLIGHT_DVS964
SOMEONE strides out the room wearing sunglasses,
FLIGHT_DVS965
a band aid on his forehead, and dressed in a suit.
FLIGHT_DVS966
SOMEONE and SOMEONE follow behind him.
FLIGHT_DVS967
They enter an elevator with a woman and a little girl.
FLIGHT_DVS968
The girl stares at SOMEONE as SOMEONE hands him a handkerchief,
FLIGHT_DVS969
He tilts his head back, and presses the cloth to his nostril. He removes his glasses, and looks at his reflection on the elevator ceiling.
FLIGHT_DVS971
He lowers his gaze to the little girl.
FLIGHT_DVS973
In the hearing room, cell phone footage of the plane crash is played on a large screen.
FLIGHT_DVS974
The cell phone footage ends.
FLIGHT_DVS1034
SOMEONE shifts in his seat.
FLIGHT_DVS1053
SOMEONE Sips some water.
FLIGHT_DVS1054
SOMEONE presses a remote.
FLIGHT_DVS1055
She rises and walks around the table at the head of the room.
FLIGHT_DVS1056
She projects an image on two giant screens.
FLIGHT_DVS1084
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE in the middle of the room.
FLIGHT_DVS1106
SOMEONE slips on her glasses and checks her notes, as SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS1115
The evidence appears onscreen.
FLIGHT_DVS1133
SOMEONE nods, and leafs through a file.
FLIGHT_DVS1146
SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a glance.
FLIGHT_DVS1147
SOMEONE gazes at an enlarged photograph of SOMEONE on the screen.
FLIGHT_DVS1148
SOMEONE rolls his tongue, and looks briefly at SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
FLIGHT_DVS1149
SOMEONE studies SOMEONE's smiling face with pressed lips.
FLIGHT_DVS1150
He takes a sip of water.
FLIGHT_DVS1169
SOMEONE looks firmly at SOMEONE, his face shiny with perspiration.
FLIGHT_DVS1170
SOMEONE looks down, his eyes heavy.
FLIGHT_DVS1179
SOMEONE closes her file, and slowly walks to her seat.
FLIGHT_DVS1181
A year later, SOMEONE sits facing a group of inmates in an Alcoholics Anonymous meeting.
FLIGHT_DVS1195
Some inmates smile.
FLIGHT_DVS1218
He shuts his eyes.
FLIGHT_DVS1223
A smile plays on his lips.
FLIGHT_DVS1225
SOMEONE sits, writing at his desk in his cell.
FLIGHT_DVS1226
A board hangs above the desk, covered in photographs and cards.
FLIGHT_DVS1228
SOMEONE closes a bound book, and tosses his glasses on it.
FLIGHT_DVS1230
Photos of SOMEONE and SOMEONE, standing next to a Christmas tree.
FLIGHT_DVS1237
In between the photos, hangs a copy of the serenity prayer.
FLIGHT_DVS1241
a guard punches in a code and a wire gate opens, letting SOMEONE through.
FLIGHT_DVS1242
SOMEONE smiles as he walks towards SOMEONE, seated at a desk.
FLIGHT_DVS1244
They hug.
FLIGHT_DVS1245
They're seated at a table.
FLIGHT_DVS1246
SOMEONE opens a writing pad.
FLIGHT_DVS1247
SOMEONE shifts, his hands resting on the table.
FLIGHT_DVS1249
he lowers his eyes.
FLIGHT_DVS1250
SOMEONE turns on his cell phone recorder.
FLIGHT_DVS1251
SOMEONE's brow furrows, then he smiles.