Four and then plummeting to number 93 and beyond.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS8
Uneasily. A caption reads
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS9
Turns the clock radio off.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS10
Wearing scrubs his girlfriend climbs into bed.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS11
She makes a spurting motion.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS12
She dawns a sleep mask.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS14
A sleazy man with a horseshoe mustache innocently shifts his gaze. The hefty guy eyes him and smirks. The sleazy man glances at him uncomfortably.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS15
The sleazy man opens his cell.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS16
The sleazy man shakes his head.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS17
Hurls his cell out of the door then nods at the executive.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS18
A fat bodyguard chuckles.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS19
SOMEONE points to the hefty guy.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS20
The hefty guy gives a faltering smile.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS21
Here at home, SOMEONE steps
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS22
His chubby cheeked smile falters.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS23
He forces a jolly grin. SOMEONE glowers.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS25
The hefty SOMEONE nods blankly.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS26
SOMEONE gives a dopey smile.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS27
SOMEONE's stares slack-jawed, then drops his gaze.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS28
And walks away. SOMEONE blinks dumbfoundedly.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS29
Slender man opens the door.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS30
He Kisses his cheeks.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS31
Now on a terrace overlooking the Thames.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS32
SOMEONE steps out behind SOMEONE and squints at him. The lanky rock-star drops a hand on SOMEONE's shoulder.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS33
The scruffy wavy-haired rocker heads inside.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS34
Now in the den, SOMEONE sips a beer. SOMEONE's mom holds a teacup.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS35
Now in a restaurant, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and Duffy sit with other pals.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS36
Actor SOMEONE Felton sporting Draco Malfoy's bleached locks.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS37
Gives a puzzled smile.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS38
The young actor stares blankly.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS39
SOMEONE stalks off as SOMEONE continues to grin.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS40
A grin slowly spreads across SOMEONE's face.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS41
He flops onto a bed.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS42
His TV shows a hoop-rolling match.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS43
SOMEONE groggily wakes up and finds his suite trashed. A clock reads 6 o’clock.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS44
He wakes up.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS45
SOMEONE swigs from his own glass. SOMEONE woozily sets his aside.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS46
SOMEONE blinks then arches his brow and shakes his head. Licking his lips he raises both hands in a shrug. SOMEONE nods.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS47
SOMEONE locks eyes with the rock-star. His broad grin fades sheepishly.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS48
He spots a TV.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS49
It shows a petite blonde surgeon. SOMEONE lifts
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS50
The rocker's cell shows SOMEONE vomiting.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS51
Other photos show Naples.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS52
SOMEONE answers his cell. It's SOMEONE in a red leather jacket on a music video set.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS53
SOMEONE faces Farrell SOMEONE who wears red jacket.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS54
SOMEONE dances like the old sitcom character.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS55
SOMEONE ends the call. SOMEONE sips from a flask.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS56
He hands it over.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS57
SOMEONE frowns at the flask, then takes a drink. A male stylist primps SOMEONE.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS58
And gags. SOMEONE lights a joint.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS59
SOMEONE exhales and passes it to him. SOMEONE cringes and gulps down more whiskey, then frowns and puffs on the joint. SOMEONE studies him quizzically licking
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS60
Takes another drag and reels.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS61
SOMEONE clutches his chest.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS62
SOMEONE glances at the half burnt down joint, then guzzles from a crystal decanter. Later
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS63
Meredith backs away.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS64
He gives a showy wink.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS65
In a greenroom.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS66
Musician grins broadly and mimes playing bongos.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS67
Stumbles down a hallway where a photo of SOMEONE.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS69
He takes SOMEONE's cell.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS70
SOMEONE gapes. Later, back in the bar.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS71
SOMEONE glances at his watch.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS72
Meanwhile, SOMEONE sleeps. Her cell shows a photo of SOMEONE. She puts it to her ear.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS73
SOMEONE slams her phone down. Now SOMEONE
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS74
Later, portraits show SOMEONE and SOMEONE. SOMEONE sleeps on a couch.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS75
He convulses.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS76
SOMEONE and SOMEONE
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS77
SOMEONE watches the video drinking.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS78
Where SOMEONE lies asleep.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS79
In a luxurious bed by a glimmering pool she picks up her cellphone.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS80
He takes the phone.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS81
Lars surrenders the phone.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS82
New York's morning skyline fills the penthouse windows behind SOMEONE who throws a pillow.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS83
He stalks off. SOMEONE woozily shifts his gaze.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS84
The SUV limo pulls over to a curb. A man with a frizzy hairdo stands waiting near the corner. SOMEONE climbs out and ambles over to him. Back in the SUV, the chauffeur glances.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS85
SOMEONE lets others in line pass.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS86
SOMEONE eats a string cheese.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS87
Back in the airport SOMEONE trudges back to SOMEONE and holds out a hand.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS88
SOMEONE sneaks the balloon into his palm. SOMEONE strides out of the line.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS89
Nonchalant air and strolls up to the handrail overlooking the terminal’s ground floor.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS90
His back to the railing, SOMEONE shoves the balloon into the back of his jeans and digs around. His stunned lips part as he gives a pained
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS91
Deepens his reach.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS92
He wipes his hand on a potted plant’s wide leaf, then waddles back toward the line, keeping his legs together.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS93
Later in the Admiral's Club, SOMEONE lounges in an armchair beside a window. He sips a beer. SOMEONE sits stiffly facing him.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS94
SOMEONE winces, his eyes shut.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS96
His pants are around his ankles.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS97
SOMEONE nervously rubs his face.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS98
SOMEONE yanks his sunglasses off and squats, then wipes the corner of his mouth and massages his upper lip.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS99
SOMEONE studies him and shifts from foot to foot.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS100
SOMEONE heads out. Later he hurries up to the concierge.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS101
Concierge knits his brow and frowns.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS102
The rock star pauses the video.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS103
SOMEONE turns the video back on.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS104
A McClain impersonator have drinks
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS105
A waitress brings a fresh round.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS106
Walks up behind him. Turning, SOMEONE stares wide-eyed at his glaring boss then puts on a smile.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS107
A party in a garish house.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS108
He intercepts a hottie.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS109
She spots SOMEONE and gives a drunken wave.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS110
She gives an acquiescent shrug.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS111
Destiny waves at SOMEONE again. Now she and SOMEONE face each other on a bed.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS112
SOMEONE nods drowsily.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS113
Destiny climbs on top of SOMEONE.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS114
Sitting at a nurse’s desk.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS115
Jonathan leans back and lights a fat joint.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS116
Jonathan glares, then gives
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS117
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS118
Finds SOMEONE gone. Now SOMEONE returns to SOMEONE at the furry wall.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS119
He SOMEONE's chest.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS120
He lights the rug.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS121
SOMEONE gets to his feet and faces them.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS122
Now as the limo travels through the desert.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS123
SOMEONE faces the driver.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS124
Later, SOMEONE faces him and shifts on his feet.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS125
Now SOMEONE knocks on a rusty door.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS126
SOMEONE opens it.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS127
They share a kiss and SOMEONE pulls him into the modern industrial home.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS128
SOMEONE lies back as a blanket covering her midriff rides.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS129
Lifting his brow he nods earnestly.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS130
SOMEONE looks him in the eye and takes a deep breath.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS131
With a wounded glare, the rock star steps away in his burgundy briefs. Later, SOMEONE and Naples sit on a couch playing with toys. The musician gazes at the cheerful bespectacled boy
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS132
SOMEONE holds his arms out and the boy gives him a hug. The rock-star holds him close then stands and steps away.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS133
Lars joins then.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS134
A countdown shows four hours until the concert. Now in SOMEONE's apartment.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS135
SOMEONE spreads rose petals, lights a candle, dips strawberries in chocolate and waits. SOMEONE comes home.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS136
The stunned woman takes in the romantic setting.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS137
A nervous grin flickers on SOMEONE's lips. SOMEONE briefly smiles.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS138
SOMEONE stands at the door.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS139
SOMEONE flops onto the couch and take his sunglasses off. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS140
SOMEONE levels a scolding finger at SOMEONE and glances between the lovers, then nods. SOMEONE shakes his head.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS141
SOMEONE shrugs encouragingly.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS142
SOMEONE gives a confused blink of his eyes.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS143
SOMEONE sits primly. SOMEONE arches his brow.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS144
Later in the bedroom, SOMEONE turns on an iPod.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS145
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lean close to kiss.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS146
Munching chocolate covered strawberries SOMEONE watches.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS147
Later SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie facing each other, kissing tenderly.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS148
SOMEONE crawls up behind SOMEONE and she pulls away from SOMEONE.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS149
She rolls toward the rocker. As they make out, her arm lies on SOMEONE's face. He frowns. Later he and SOMEONE lie under the covers kissing.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS150
SOMEONE' head bobs under the quilt.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS151
Later, SOMEONE stares as SOMEONE lies on top of SOMEONE.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS152
SOMEONE angrily seizes SOMEONE and kisses him.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS153
SOMEONE backs off.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS154
As SOMEONE heads off, a stunned SOMEONE covers her mouth.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS155
She checks her cell.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS156
She hurries off.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS157
SOMEONE trudges out numbly. SOMEONE exits the bathroom wearing her scrubs.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS158
As she leaves, SOMEONE glances below his Beastie Boys t-shirt.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS159
A view from behind SOMEONE shows his bare chubby rear.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS160
In the Pacific, SOMEONE talks on
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS161
Swaggers off. The pale
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS162
Now SOMEONE watches TV in his apartment.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS163
SOMEONE reads a text.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS164
To the roof and looks a few stories down.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS165
Gazes at the street, many stories below.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS166
His vision wavers as he sticks one foot over the edge.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS167
SOMEONE arrives at the pool.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS168
Crouches as the rocker surfaces treading water.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS169
Blood stains the water.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS170
The watery cloud of blood grows.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS171
SOMEONE gazes down at him sympathetically, then shakes his head.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS172
Blood tints the water all around SOMEONE.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS173
Pool lights illuminate the bloody water.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS174
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE some pills.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS175
Their fists. Spotlights sweep over them and fog rolls onto the dark stage. Blue lights come on revealing
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS176
Above the stage as the drummer plays enthusiastically. As SOMEONE offers his mic to some fans, SOMEONE watches peacefully.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS178
Now sunlight bathes SOMEONE and SOMEONE's apartment building.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS179
In their bedroom, SOMEONE and SOMEONE wake up. SOMEONE checks a bedside clock.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS180
SOMEONE beams at him, then gives him a gentle kiss on the cheek. They lie face to face gazing at each other lovingly and share a smile.
GET_HIM_TO_THE_GREEK_DVS181
They carry out the mattress.