In his father's work area, SOMEONE thumbs through diagrams and plans.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS23
He uncovers a blueprint and studies it.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS25
Later wearing welding goggles, SOMEONE welds pieces of metal together.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS28
SOMEONE stops welding and lifts the goggles above his forehead. Newspaper and magazine clippings with photos of SOMEONE Stark hang on the surrounding walls. On one magazine cover, SOMEONE is Iron Man. Starring Robert Downey Jr. as SOMEONE Stark and Iron Man. Gwyneth Paltrow as Pepper Potts. SOMEONE Cheadle as Colonel James 'Rhodey' Rhodes and War Machine. Scarlett Johansson as SOMEONE Romanoff and Black Widow. SOMEONE Rockwell as SOMEONE Hammer.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS35
A white cockatoo watches as SOMEONE welds, sews, and solders. Smiling, SOMEONE holds a full wine glass up to the drinking bird.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS37
SOMEONE drips liquid into a round dish-like device, then turns a knob attached to a long thin tube.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS38
The tube glows.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS39
Flying sparks illuminate the cockatoo perched near a computer screen nearby. The bird flies off. The dish-like device glows with bright light.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS40
SOMEONE smiles as he stares down at the glowing device, which emits a bright beam of light as he picks it up.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS41
Iron Man 2
IRON_MAN_2_DVS42
Six months later.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS43
At night, SOMEONE wearing a red and gold armor-like suit and helmet, stands in the bay of an airplane. As the bay door opens, SOMEONE runs down a ramp and leaps out of the plane. He free-falls toward the city below, then as two small thrusters on his feet flare up, he zooms and spins through the sky.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS44
He speeds downward, past exploding fireworks, toward an arena, and lands on a circular platform at the front of the stage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS45
Behind him on the stage, young long-haired women wearing matching bikini tops and short shorts form a line and kick their legs out in unison, while pyrotechnics explode around the gigantic video image of a fluttering American flag. Stark Expo, Flushing, New York.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS46
Outstretched arms, SOMEONE poses for the crowd as the circular platform revolves.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS47
Portions of the platform floor open. Giant robotic arms rise from the platform and remove SOMEONE's helmet, revealing his smiling face. Other arms remove his Iron Man suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS48
The robotic arms descend into the floor which closes up. The platform stops revolving.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS49
Wearing a crisp black tuxedo, SOMEONE surveys the cheering crowd.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS50
The women dancing onstage pause to strike various poses, then rush over and form a semicircle around SOMEONE, who faces them as they each punch out one hand.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS51
The dancers rush off clapping. SOMEONE turns toward the crowd.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS52
A thin-mustached man appears on the giant screen.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS54
Backstage, SOMEONE pricks his finger and uses a scanner.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS55
On the scanner, "Blood Toxicity 19%. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS56
A brunette woman speaks into a microphone. "WHIH World News 21. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS57
Brown-haired bodyguard, Happy Hogan, leads SOMEONE outside.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS58
SOMEONE greets fans.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS59
A blond woman hands SOMEONE a note.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS60
SOMEONE autographs Iron Man photos.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS61
Happy and SOMEONE approach a young brunette woman leaning against a white convertible.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS62
SOMEONE climbs behind the wheel and Happy sits in the passenger seat.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS63
Happy takes a subpoena from the woman.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS64
The woman holds up a federal SOMEONE's badge.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS65
Smiling, she steps away from the car. SOMEONE turns to Happy.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS66
SOMEONE drives off. Daytime, Washington, D. C.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS67
A Senate hearing room.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS68
Brown-haired Senator SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS69
Senate Armed Services Committee.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS70
SOMEONE glances back at Pepper Potts's blond assistant, who shakes her head.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS71
CEO, Hammer Industries.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS72
Sitting nearby, brown-haired SOMEONE raises a water glass toward SOMEONE and takes a sip.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS73
SOMEONE stands.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS74
SOMEONE sits.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS75
A man with short-cropped black hair and wearing a dark-blue military uniform steps in. SOMEONE stands, approaches SOMEONE, and shakes his hand.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS76
SOMEONE sits between SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS77
Satellite images of a facility appear on the large screen.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS78
SOMEONE presses a small hand-held computer's touch screen.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS79
As SOMEONE lifts his computer, images on its touch screen appear on the large screen.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS80
In a video on the large screen, a person in a huge armored suit topples over. The suit's machine guns discharge.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS81
In another video, a pilot wearing an armored suit crashes into the ground.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS82
In the hearing room, SOMEONE tries to unplug the video screen as a video of him and the pilot wearing an armored suit plays.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS83
SOMEONE and the smirking SOMEONE exchange glances. On-screen, the pilot's suit sparks.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS84
SOMEONE unplugs the video screen and sits.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS85
SOMEONE stands and faces the rows of people behind him. They stand and applaud.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS86
SOMEONE dons dark sunglasses, gives a thumbs up, and blows kisses to SOMEONE. At home, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE leave the hearing room on TV.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS88
In his dim work area, SOMEONE attaches a whip to one of the arms for his armored suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS89
He activates the arc reactor, which sends an electrical charge along the frame of the arm and into the whip.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS90
SOMEONE puts on both of the suit arms, activates the arc reactor and spins around.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS91
Electrified whips slice through objects in the room.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS92
Malibu, California. In the huge basement workroom below his mansion, SOMEONE claps. J. A. R. V. I. S. , a computer system including robots, lights up.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS93
Video of the hearing appears on a screen.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS94
At a nearby sink, a robotic arm with legs knocks over a blender filled with dark-green chlorophyll.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS95
The robot arm's mechanical hand droops.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS96
SOMEONE drinks chlorophyll from a glass.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS97
SOMEONE presses his right thumb onto a small device.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS98
SOMEONE reaches under his own t-shirt and removes a glowing, cylindrical, repulsory technology, arc reactor - or RT unit - from his chest.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS99
He replaces a smoking ingot of palladium and reinserts the RT unit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS100
SOMEONE grimaces as he locks the RT unit into place inside his chest.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS101
Pepper steps into the workroom as SOMEONE gulps down the remaining chlorophyll.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS102
She follows him as he walks away.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS103
SOMEONE taps a long-armed robot.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS104
SOMEONE picks up a framed drawing of Iron Man.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS105
SOMEONE hops onto a counter, removes a painting from a wall, and hangs the Iron Man poster.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS106
Pepper stares at SOMEONE, who walks across the room, as a long-armed robot brings him a champagne bottle and flutes on a tray.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS108
SOMEONE uncorks the bottle. Champagne foams out.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS109
SOMEONE pours champagne. Wide-eyed, Pepper sits.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS110
He hands Pepper a glass of champagne.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS111
Shaking her head, she smiles.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS112
SOMEONE sits beside Pepper. They tap their glasses together and drink.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS113
In Moscow, snowfall blankets a city street. A dark-haired man steps through an archway and into a dark passageway, where he hands SOMEONE an envelope.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS114
SOMEONE tucks the envelope in his jacket and pays the man, who leaves.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS115
SOMEONE glances out toward a sidewalk, then steps back into the passageway.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS116
He takes out the envelope and opens it.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS117
He pulls out a passport and a ticket. "Grand Prix de Monaco Historique. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS118
Elsewhere, Pepper enters SOMEONE's home gym, where SOMEONE and SOMEONE box in a ring.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS119
SOMEONE, wearing protective headgear, swings at SOMEONE and misses. SOMEONE jabs at SOMEONE, then elbows him in the face.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS120
The men turn and gaze at a young woman with long dark-brown hair, who walks into the gym carrying paperwork.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS121
The woman hands Pepper a pen.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS122
SOMEONE taps SOMEONE's head.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS123
SOMEONE kicks SOMEONE, who sails backward into a corner post. Pepper signs a paper.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS125
SOMEONE sashays over to the ring, ducks through the ropes, and steps onto the platform.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS126
Watching her, SOMEONE drinks chlorophyll from a sports bottle.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS127
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE, who lowers the bottle.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS128
SOMEONE glances down, then turns to SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS129
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE. SOMEONE steps out of the ring and sits beside Pepper.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS130
SOMEONE taps on a glass table top. Web pages appear.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS131
In a photo, SOMEONE, wearing a dark bikini, lies on her side.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS132
From the ring, SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS133
SOMEONE jabs at SOMEONE, who grabs his glove and pulls his arm, flipping him onto his back.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS134
SOMEONE stands and walks slightly bent over.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS135
SOMEONE climbs down from the ring and faces SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS136
SOMEONE presses his thumb onto an ink pad, then puts his fingerprint on a form.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS137
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE stares after her, then turns to Pepper.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS138
Pepper smiles at SOMEONE, who turns away. Elsewhere, a city on a rocky sloping coastline near tall mountains.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS139
Monaco, Gran Prix de Monaco Historique.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS140
Two officers on motorcycles escort a black luxury car along a city street. The car stops outside a building's ornate facade. Hotel de Paris.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS141
SOMEONE steps out of the car and waves to onlookers. Pepper and SOMEONE step out and join SOMEONE as he enters the hotel. Inside, SOMEONE walks off while SOMEONE and Pepper step into a restaurant.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS142
SOMEONE approaches.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS143
A man snaps photos of SOMEONE and Pepper.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS144
SOMEONE walks with SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS145
Pepper follows.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS148
SOMEONE and Pepper walk to the bar.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS149
The tall blond, Christine.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS150
A photographer snaps photos as SOMEONE puts his arm around SOMEONE, who squirms.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS151
SOMEONE walks to a table and sits.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS152
Christine holds out a recorder.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS153
SOMEONE stands and follows SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS154
In the restaurant bathroom, SOMEONE takes a blood-level reading with a scanner, then sticks his pricked finger in his mouth.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS155
He takes out his finger, leans against the sink counter with his head lowered, pauses, then stares at his reflection in the mirror.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS156
Later wearing a blue car-racing uniform, SOMEONE walks through a crowd of smiling people. He hops over a low wall and onto a roadway. Meanwhile, SOMEONE and Christine sit in the restaurant.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS157
SOMEONE turns to face SOMEONE on TV.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS158
Sitting alone at a table, Pepper watches the TV as another uniformed man throws down his helmet and stomps off as SOMEONE approaches a blue and white racecar.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS159
SOMEONE again turns toward the TV. SOMEONE, wearing a helmet, sits in the racecar driver's seat and points toward the camera. SOMEONE frowns.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS160
On the roadway, SOMEONE gives a thumbs up to a crew member. The car's tail light glows red.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS161
Above the track, a series of colored lights flash, signaling the start of the race. As two rows of racecars speed off, smoke rises from their wheels.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS162
SOMEONE and the other driver steer their racecars along the course's winding road.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS163
SOMEONE and other men wearing helmets and orange coveralls walk alongside a chain-link fence by the roadway.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS164
In the restaurant, Pepper watches the cars race on TV. She turns and glances out a window behind her as the cars speed past. Outside, SOMEONE chews on a toothpick as he strolls. The racecars speed through the city, passing through a tunnel and by tall buildings. As the cars approach, SOMEONE steps through the fence and onto the road.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS165
Watching from bleachers above the road, race fans lean over the fence and gawk as SOMEONE throws his helmet off and walks down the center of the road toward the approaching cars.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS166
Inside the restaurant, Pepper, SOMEONE, and other patrons stand and watch SOMEONE on television. On the road, a car zooms past SOMEONE as he rips open his orange shirt, revealing the arc reactor attached to his body frame. As the whips drop from SOMEONE's sleeves, he grips their handles. Streams of electricity flow along coils on the body frame and along the whips. SOMEONE's orange shirt ignites and falls in tatters around his hips. A red racecar speeds up to SOMEONE, who raises his right arm and slices off the front of the car with a whip. The car explodes into sparks and gray smoke as it spins in the air. The car crashes, flips several times, and breaks apart on the roadway behind SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS167
In the restaurant, SOMEONE watches with a furrowed brow.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS168
Pepper stares open-mouthed. She turns to face the entrance where SOMEONE stands holding a red case containing SOMEONE's Iron Man suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS169
Pepper and SOMEONE rush outside. Pepper climbs into the back seat of a dark blue limousine. SOMEONE jumps into the driver's seat and speeds off.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS170
SOMEONE maneuvers the car down the street and toward a tall barricade.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS171
The car crashes through the barricade, skids sideways, and turns right onto the racing course. Approaching racecars zoom around the limousine as SOMEONE drives faster.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS173
SOMEONE speeds around a curve and faces SOMEONE, who swings the whips. As SOMEONE drives past, SOMEONE swings the whip in his left hand and slices off the front of SOMEONE's car. The car flips into the air, lands upright, and slides into the red car, then flips over and crashes into the fence.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS174
Upside down, with his right shoulder touching the ground, SOMEONE places his left hand on the road as he tries to wiggle free.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS175
Gasoline pools around SOMEONE's car. SOMEONE pulls off his helmet and glances through a smoky haze at SOMEONE, who snaps the whips out to each side.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS176
Two other racecars speed around the curve and crash by SOMEONE. The cars explode, bounce along the road, then crash into walls on both sides of the course.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS177
While restaurant patrons stare open-mouthed at the towering flames, in the limousine's back seat, Pepper leans forward.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS178
SOMEONE dodges two cars. Up ahead, a helmeted man in orange coveralls sprays wreckage with a fire extinguisher. SOMEONE strolls over to SOMEONE's upside-down car and slices it in half with a whip.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS179
As SOMEONE peers into the SOMEONE, SOMEONE sneaks up behind him and hits the back of his head with a piece of metal from the red car.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS180
SOMEONE turns and knocks the metal from SOMEONE's hand with a whip. SOMEONE falls back onto the ground. SOMEONE strikes the ground with his whips, as SOMEONE rolls out of the way, then spreads his legs as a whip lashes the asphalt inches from his groin. SOMEONE stands and runs. SOMEONE whirls a whip which strikes the ground behind SOMEONE, who leaps onto an overturned race car, then falls onto the road. SOMEONE, with a bloody gash under his left eye, shakes his head.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS181
Glancing into the racecar's side mirror, he watches SOMEONE approach from behind.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS182
Nearing SOMEONE, SOMEONE slings his whips in circles, and criss-crosses them faster and faster. SOMEONE leaps out of the way as SOMEONE's whips strike gasoline pooling around the car. The car explodes.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS183
With his jacket's left sleeve on fire, SOMEONE stands and pats the flames, extinguishing them. Smiling, SOMEONE steps through the fiery car SOMEONE and creeps toward SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS184
SOMEONE leaps against the chain-link fence as the limousine hits SOMEONE and pins him against the guardrail below the fence. SOMEONE slumps onto the limo's hood.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS185
SOMEONE jumps off the fence.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS186
SOMEONE opens the right-rear door.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS187
SOMEONE stands and slices the car door in half with a whip.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS188
SOMEONE puts the car in reverse and backs up. He changes gears and drives forward, slamming SOMEONE against the guardrail.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS189
As SOMEONE drives forward and back, crushing SOMEONE, SOMEONE reaches for the red case in the back seat.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS191
The driver airbag deploys, hitting SOMEONE's face. SOMEONE smashes the windshield, then slices the car's roof with a whip. He slices the left side of the car away.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS192
Pepper tosses the red case onto the ground. SOMEONE taps the case with his foot. The case opens, converting into a condensed Iron Man suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS193
SOMEONE bends over and puts his hands into two gloves inside the suit. As he stands, the suit expands, covering SOMEONE's entire body. Small armored plates pop vertically out of the suit, then fold down to form a layer of protective metal. Other metal plates pop up from behind SOMEONE's neck, and cover his head, to form a red helmet and a silver mask with glowing eyes. With his foot, SOMEONE - or Iron Man - pushes the limousine yards away with one foot. Iron Man turns and raises his left hand toward SOMEONE. A glowing circle appears in Iron Man's hand. With his whip, SOMEONE slaps Iron Man's hand downward, then strikes Iron Man's suit. Iron Man lifts his right hand and fires two blasts at SOMEONE, who ducks.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS194
SOMEONE flings one whip at Iron Man, who catches it. SOMEONE flings a second whip, which wraps around Iron Man and jerks him through the air. SOMEONE slings Iron Man onto the hood of the limousine, then pulls him down onto his knees with one whip.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS195
Waves of electricity pulse through the whip and around Iron Man's suit. Iron Man stands and wraps the whip around his right arm. Approaching SOMEONE, Iron Man wraps the whip around his own suit several times, and punches SOMEONE's stomach and face.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS196
Lengthening the whips, Iron Man hurls SOMEONE through the air. SOMEONE lands face-up on the asphalt.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS197
Reaching down toward SOMEONE's chest, Iron Man pulls the arc reactor out of SOMEONE's body frame.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS198
The electricity ceases to flow through the frame and whips.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS199
Officers in black uniforms and helmets rush over and grab SOMEONE by the shoulders. As they lift him and drag him away, SOMEONE spits blood at Iron Man.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS200
Through a computer screen in his mask, Iron Man studies the arc reactor,
IRON_MAN_2_DVS201
then crushes it in his hand.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS202
Inside the restaurant, SOMEONE smiles as he watches TV with the other customers. Later, a balding mustached man and several police officers follow SOMEONE through a dark corridor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS204
SOMEONE stares straight ahead. The man points. SOMEONE nods to the man.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS206
An officer opens a door and SOMEONE enters a dim room.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS207
The officer closes the door behind SOMEONE who walks into the room where a handcuffed SOMEONE, wearing only underwear, sits on a bench.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS208
SOMEONE sits on the opposite end of the bench.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS209
SOMEONE stands, walks to the door, and knocks.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS210
The officer opens the door. SOMEONE leaves.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS211
The officer closes the door. SOMEONE laughs.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS212
In a private jet, Pepper watches Senator SOMEONE on a television screen.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS213
Holding a covered tray, SOMEONE stands behind her.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS214
He places the tray and silverware on a counter by the jet's windows.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS215
He uncovers the tray, revealing an omelet.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS216
They exchange half smiles.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS217
The jet flies over orange-tinged clouds. Elsewhere in his cell, SOMEONE sits leaning against a sink.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS218
Outside the cell, a dark-haired guard approaches with a tray of food.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS219
Staring at SOMEONE, the guard places the tray on a shelf attached to the cell door and leaves.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS220
SOMEONE stands, picks up the tray, and grabs a note lying on it.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS221
Sitting on the bed, SOMEONE reads the note, which is written in a foreign language.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS224
SOMEONE picks up a white potato-like ball of putty from the tray and turns it over.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS225
On the bottom, a digital readout: "35. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS226
SOMEONE glances around himself. The guard returns and opens the cell door. Wearing a prison uniform, a long-haired man resembling SOMEONE steps into the cell.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS227
The guard closes the door, locks it, and leaves.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS228
SOMEONE and the man study each other. The man glances down at a number printed on his own shirt.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS230
SOMEONE glances down at the number on his own shirt. 6219. Smiling, SOMEONE stands, punches the man's face, then slams the man's forehead into the sink.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS231
The man falls to the floor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS232
The guard passes and places a key on the shelf.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS233
SOMEONE sticks the putty on the wall and presses a button.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS234
The readout counts down. SOMEONE grabs the key, reaches through the cell bars, and unlocks the door. As SOMEONE walks down a hallway, he passes another guard who turns toward him.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS235
SOMEONE pauses.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS236
The guard places one hand on SOMEONE's shoulder. SOMEONE turns, punches the guard, then snaps his neck. As SOMEONE walks off, his cell explodes.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS237
SOMEONE enters a stairwell and runs down the stairs. At the bottom, guards open a gate. SOMEONE turns and runs back up the stairs.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS238
The dark-haired guard and another man rush down the stairs, grab SOMEONE, and place a white bag over his head.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS239
They lead him outdoors, then throw him into the back of a van, and closes its doors.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS240
Later, inside a pristine airplane hangar, two men in gray coveralls open the van's back doors. The dark-haired guard pulls the bag from SOMEONE's head and leads him out of the van.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS241
Handcuffed, he walks toward SOMEONE, who sits eating at a table beside a large white jet.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS242
SOMEONE stands.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS243
The guard removes SOMEONE's handcuffs.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS244
The guard turns to SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS245
The guard and the others leave. SOMEONE and SOMEONE shake hands.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS246
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit at the table.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS247
A short-haired waiter.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS248
Several waiters serve SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS249
SOMEONE grins.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS250
SOMEONE raises his wine glass. SOMEONE picks up a bottle of vodka and taps it against SOMEONE's glass.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS251
At SOMEONE's mansion.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS252
Pepper and SOMEONE both speak into telephones.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS253
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS254
A dark-haired CNN reporter appears on TV.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS255
In SOMEONE's basement, holographic web pages appear.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS256
SOMEONE presses buttons on a security system, opens a glass door, and steps into the basement.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS257
SOMEONE looks down. SOMEONE touches SOMEONE's shoulder.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS258
SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS259
SOMEONE steps out of a convertible car and falls.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS260
SOMEONE helps his friend stand.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS261
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE to his desk.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS262
SOMEONE opens a box containing palladium ingots.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS263
SOMEONE picks up his arc reactor from the desk and ejects a half-melted ingot.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS264
SOMEONE takes the reactor and removes the smoking ingot.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS265
SOMEONE turns away from SOMEONE and rolls in his chair toward his desk.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS266
SOMEONE inserts palladium into the reactor and hands it to SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS267
SOMEONE inserts the reactor into his own chest.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS268
The reactor glows through SOMEONE's shirt. SOMEONE sits up straight, then turns to glance at SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS269
Stroking his own chin, SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE. Queens, New York. A black stretch limousine pulls up to a factory building. Inside, SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk with SOMEONE past large cylindrical machines.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS270
They approach two rows of white armored suits standing atop platforms. SOMEONE dons eyeglasses, walks to a computer keyboard, and types.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS271
On a screen, "Access Granted. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS272
SOMEONE climbs metal steps and studies one of the suits.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS273
SOMEONE yanks off a helmet.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS274
SOMEONE sets the helmet atop the suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS275
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS276
Nighttime in his bedroom, SOMEONE stares at his reflection in a mirror and studies the damaged skin on his neck and chest.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS277
SOMEONE enters. SOMEONE buttons his shirt.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS278
SOMEONE places a black box on a counter, then pours a martini.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS279
She hands the martini to SOMEONE. He takes a sip.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS280
SOMEONE sits. SOMEONE carries the box holding watches to SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS281
SOMEONE sits on the arm of SOMEONE's chair. She opens a compact and dabs makeup on the scars on SOMEONE's face.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS282
SOMEONE stands and walks out.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS283
SOMEONE gulps down the martini.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS284
Later, SOMEONE, wearing an Iron Man suit, dances in front of a deejay station on a stage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS285
People, including many young women, crowd in front of the stage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS286
Pepper steps in from the back of the room.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS287
Frowning, she watches as SOMEONE bumps fists with the dark-haired deejay.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS288
Outside, a line of cars pulls into SOMEONE's circular driveway. In one car, SOMEONE talks on a cell phone.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS289
Moments later, SOMEONE walks into SOMEONE's house and approaches Pepper.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS290
Pepper leads SOMEONE toward the stage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS291
SOMEONE stumbles and falls onstage. He stands, then points one arm upward.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS292
SOMEONE speaks into a microphone.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS293
SOMEONE closes his eyes, then opens them.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS294
Smiling, Pepper steps onstage and takes the microphone from SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS295
SOMEONE leans toward the microphone.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS296
SOMEONE steps down from the stage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS297
As SOMEONE points toward the door, a fireball blasts from his palm and shatters a glass wall surrounding a fountain.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS298
People in the crowd smile and jump up and down.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS299
SOMEONE crouches and pretends to flex his arm muscles.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS300
At the front of the crowd, a busty blond woman holds a champagne bottle by its neck. She throws the bottle upward. SOMEONE blasts it with his palm weapon.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS301
Pepper ducks. Watching from the back of the room, SOMEONE, his nostrils flared, storms out.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS302
The blond woman throws another bottle in the air and SOMEONE blasts it. Downstairs, SOMEONE punches buttons on the security system, enters the basement workroom, and eyes the Iron man suits.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS303
Upstairs, SOMEONE blasts another flying bottle. Downstairs, SOMEONE puts on a silver Iron Man suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS304
At the party, another blond woman lifts a watermelon overhead.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS305
She tosses the watermelon into the air. SOMEONE uses his chest weapon to blast the watermelon to bits.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS307
SOMEONE dances around onstage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS308
Everyone turns to face SOMEONE, who wears the suit with the mask flipped up.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS309
SOMEONE's mask flips down and the party-goers scurry from the room. SOMEONE faces SOMEONE as he approaches.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS310
SOMEONE turns to the deejay.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS311
The deejay punches keys on his laptop. SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE from behind.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS312
SOMEONE's mask flips down. He grabs SOMEONE's arm. SOMEONE's thrusters fire up. He and SOMEONE fly backward through a wall, then through a window. They land on the gym floor. SOMEONE walks away from SOMEONE, who lies on the floor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS313
A weight plate hits the back of SOMEONE's helmet. SOMEONE turns. His helmet's eyes glow bright white. Standing, SOMEONE slings another weight past SOMEONE, shattering a glass door.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS314
SOMEONE picks up a barbell, shakes off the weights and hits SOMEONE with the metal bar. SOMEONE sails backward into the boxing ring and slams into a wall. Using his thrusters, SOMEONE hovers overhead.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS315
SOMEONE grabs a post.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS316
SOMEONE hits SOMEONE in the chest and head with the post, which SOMEONE then grabs. Lifting the post, SOMEONE throws SOMEONE through the ceiling and into his bedroom. Using his thrusters, SOMEONE rises through the hole in the floor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS317
In a circular room, Pepper approaches SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS318
SOMEONE and SOMEONE drop through the ceiling. SOMEONE runs to Pepper.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS319
SOMEONE and SOMEONE fight nearby.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS320
SOMEONE ushers Pepper out one way while SOMEONE hurries out another. Outside, the party-goers watch through a huge wall of glass surrounding the room.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS321
SOMEONE throws SOMEONE to the floor. SOMEONE stands. SOMEONE punches SOMEONE's helmet, then swings and misses. The two men exchange punches.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS322
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE and slams his head through a table. SOMEONE falls to the floor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS323
With his eyes glowing, SOMEONE turns to the window and stares at the party-goers, who stand motionless.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS324
SOMEONE lunges toward them.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS325
The people run off. SOMEONE stands, rips off a countertop, and smashes it against SOMEONE's back.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS326
SOMEONE flies head-first into a fireplace. He lies staring through the flames, then pulls his head out of the fire.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS327
Balanced on one knee, he turns and raises his palm weapon toward SOMEONE. SOMEONE raises his own hand.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS328
They fire their palm weapons at each other. The two blasts meet, forming a huge fireball, which explodes and destroys much of the room.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS329
Later, smoke rises throughout the room. With his eyes no longer glowing, SOMEONE lies near a wall with his back against charred furniture.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS330
The eyes of SOMEONE's helmet light up as he raises his head and surveys the destruction.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS331
Glancing around himself, SOMEONE focuses on SOMEONE, who stands across the room.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS332
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange stares.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS333
SOMEONE turns, fires his thrusters, and zooms through an opening in the roof.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS334
SOMEONE watches as his friend disappears into the night sky.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS335
Daytime, Edwards Air Force Base, Mojave, California.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS336
Men in camouflage fatigues work in an air traffic control tower. A dark-haired man, Major Allen, turns to his left and gazes into the distant sky.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS337
Another short-haired man peers through binoculars. The men move their heads from left to right as SOMEONE speeds past the tower.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS338
On the ground below, an armed soldier guarding a stealth bomber stares into the sky. Uniformed men across the base watch as SOMEONE zooms down and lands in front of a giant hangar.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS339
Major Allen steps out of the passenger side of a slowing truck and hustles toward SOMEONE as dozens of men gather around the silver-suited colonel.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS340
Major Allen and SOMEONE shake hands.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS341
The onlookers disperse as SOMEONE, Major Allen, and a small group of men walk toward the hangar.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS342
Morning. Wearing his suit without the helmet, SOMEONE eats a donut.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS344
as he sits inside a giant donut perched atop a building's roof. SOMEONE's Donuts. Wearing a long black leather coat, goateed SOMEONE Fury, a tall bald man with an eye patch over his left eye, gazes up at SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS345
Lowering his sunglasses, SOMEONE peers down at SOMEONE. Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in a booth inside SOMEONE's shop.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS346
SOMEONE studies SOMEONE's neck. SOMEONE, wearing a tight black leather outfit, approaches the booth.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS347
SOMEONE studies SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS348
SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS349
SOMEONE leaves.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS350
SOMEONE returns with a needle and injects a liquid into SOMEONE's neck.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS351
SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS352
At Hammer Industries, SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach SOMEONE, who works atop a small scaffold. He climbs down.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS353
SOMEONE places a covered cage on a table. He and SOMEONE remove the cover, revealing a white cockatoo.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS354
SOMEONE glances up at a white armored suit on the scaffold.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS355
SOMEONE climbs the steps to the scaffold and pulls a control unit off the top of the suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS357
SOMEONE climbs down.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS358
SOMEONE takes the control unit from SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS359
In the hangar, SOMEONE opens a storage room door. Standing beside SOMEONE, short-haired General SOMEONE studies the silver SOMEONE II suit hanging inside.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS360
General SOMEONE walks off. SOMEONE follows.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS361
The men exchange salutes and SOMEONE walks away. Elsewhere, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on a patio overlooking the ocean.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS362
SOMEONE shakes his head.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS363
Agents arrive with a crate.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS364
With his right eye, SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE, then turns and leaves. SOMEONE stands nearby.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS365
SOMEONE shakes his head at Agent SOMEONE, a brown-haired man wearing a black suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS366
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE turns and glances down at the crate. Stamped on the top,
IRON_MAN_2_DVS367
"Property of H. Stark. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS368
In the hanger, the SOMEONE II suit lies on a table. Standing beside SOMEONE, Major Allen and another man watch as SOMEONE removes the chest plate from the suit, then takes out the glowing arc reactor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS369
SOMEONE places the reactor in a pouch.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS370
SOMEONE approaches.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS371
SOMEONE bites into a lollipop. Later, he demos weapons.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS378
Expressionless, SOMEONE and Allen stare at SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS379
SOMEONE puts down a gun and picks up a small black box.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS380
He pulls a small cigar-shaped missile from the box.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS381
SOMEONE nods. SOMEONE sniffs the missile.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS382
SOMEONE places the missile back in the box.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS383
SOMEONE walks off.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS384
At his house, SOMEONE opens the crate.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS385
He picks up a rolled-up blueprint from inside the crate. "Arc Reactor, Anton Vanko, SOMEONE Stark. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS386
He unrolls the blueprint and places it behind himself. He picks up an old newspaper's front page. A headline: "Soviet Scientist, Vanko, Defects. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS387
SOMEONE opens a round canister's lid and takes out a reel of film.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS388
Later, he watches the film on a projection screen.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS389
In the film, SOMEONE Stark sits on the front of a large desk.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS390
A large cylindrical reactor sits in front of him.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS391
While the film plays, SOMEONE pages through a notebook filled with handwritten notes, formulas, and diagrams.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS392
SOMEONE walks to one side of a scale city model on a table and steps to his right.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS393
A young dark-haired boy holding a piece of the model stands behind the table.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS394
Young SOMEONE places the piece on the table.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS395
A young man picks up young SOMEONE and carries him off.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS396
The screen goes black. In a second outtake, SOMEONE drinks from a glass.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS397
While drinking, SOMEONE lifts one index finger. Another outtake.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS398
SOMEONE watches the film, then thumbs through the notebook.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS399
SOMEONE flips through dozens of blank pages filling the remainder of the notebook. He tosses the notebook aside, leans forward, and rubs his eyes. As SOMEONE drinks from a glass on the screen, SOMEONE leans against the table, holding the model.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS400
SOMEONE turns.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS401
Close-ups of the Unisphere, a metal globe sculpture, and the arc reactor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS402
SOMEONE stares at his mustached father, who nods and smiles.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS403
The film clip ends.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS405
Driving the white convertible, SOMEONE speeds along a highway above the ocean.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS406
He pulls to the side of the road, where a goateed vendor sells strawberries.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS407
SOMEONE hands him a watch.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS408
The man places a basket of strawberries on SOMEONE's passenger seat.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS409
SOMEONE drives off.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS410
A woman steps in.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS411
SOMEONE walks in holding the strawberries. Pepper talks on the phone.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS412
A TV commentator, SOMEONE O'Reilly.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS413
SOMEONE sits.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS414
Pepper glances at her watch.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS415
A toy with a rotating pole. SOMEONE wheels his chair over to Pepper.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS418
Pepper and SOMEONE exchange stares. SOMEONE and SOMEONE, as SOMEONE, step in.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS419
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE, who mouths the word, "No. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS420
SOMEONE turns back to Pepper and SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS421
SOMEONE watches Pepper as she walks out of the office.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS422
SOMEONE also leaves.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS424
SOMEONE closes the door as she leaves.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS425
SOMEONE leans back in his chair, then leans forward and grabs the toy's rotating arm.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS426
With his free hand, he places items from atop the desk on the toy's tripod-like base. As he lets go of the toy, the arm rotates again.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS427
He stands and grabs the basket of strawberries.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS428
Walking across the room, he pops one strawberry into his mouth and dumps the rest into a wastebasket.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS429
Turning toward a large object covered with a sheet,
IRON_MAN_2_DVS430
SOMEONE spits out the strawberry.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS431
He approaches the object and reads a plaque on its side.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS432
"The key to the future is here. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS433
SOMEONE pulls off the sheet,
IRON_MAN_2_DVS434
revealing the scale city model propped on its side with the roofs of miniature buildings pointing toward him.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS435
SOMEONE forms an O with his right hand, and peers through the makeshift scope
IRON_MAN_2_DVS436
at the Unisphere in the center of the model.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS437
He smiles slightly, then furrows his brow.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS438
Later, the disassembled model, stacked in four panels, rises out of the passenger seat of SOMEONE's convertible, as he drives down a highway. In his basement laboratory, SOMEONE blows dust off the assembled model.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS439
A holographic image of the scale model appears, overlapping the actual model.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS440
SOMEONE lifts the holograph with both hands and turns.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS441
SOMEONE lowers the holograph and pushes it out in front of himself.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS442
He snaps his fingers, then spins the holograph and sits. As the holograph slows to a stop, it turns sideways. The holograph of Unisphere hovers at eye level.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS443
The center of the Unisphere.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS444
The Unisphere glows bright white. SOMEONE draws a circle in the air with his finger. As he moves his hands apart, the Unisphere expands.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS445
He studies the sphere and the surrounding architecture on the holographic model.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS447
As SOMEONE touches and flicks images on the holograph, they disappear.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS448
Moving his hands, SOMEONE expands the Unisphere again.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS449
Dozens of holographic dots appear and enter the Unisphere. SOMEONE pats his thighs, then throws his arms overhead.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS450
The sphere expands so that SOMEONE is sitting inside it.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS451
Glowing golf ball sized holographic dots radiating pulsing rings float around him.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS452
SOMEONE smiles. As he claps his hands together, the giant element condenses into a single golf ball sized holograph.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS453
Facing SOMEONE, the robotic arm taps its three fingers together. SOMEONE smiles, then stands and walks across the room.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS454
SOMEONE swings a sledgehammer and knocks holes in a concrete wall.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS456
He jackhammers a hole in the floor, exposing an electrical junction box. He connects cables to the box, then breaks a hole through the living room floor above into the ceiling of his laboratory. He drops the cables through the ceiling, down to the lab floor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS458
In the lab, he opens a wooden crate containing massive tubes. He takes out the tubes and assembles them.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS459
Later, he completes the construction of a particle accelerator which incorporates the long tubes. The accelerator extends across the entire house.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS460
SOMEONE walks downstairs into the basement, punches in the security code, and enters SOMEONE's lab.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS464
SOMEONE lifts a red, white, and blue shield from a crate.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS465
As SOMEONE lifts a section of the tubing, SOMEONE slides the shield underneath.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS466
SOMEONE places a level atop the section of tubing propped up by the shield.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS467
They shake hands. SOMEONE leaves.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS468
Later wearing goggles, SOMEONE inserts a prism into the accelerator and activates it.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS469
Across the room, a circular metal casing houses a triangular core.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS472
The accelerator shoots beams of light through the prism.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS473
Using a pipe wrench, SOMEONE turns a wheel which rotates the prism, directing the beam outside the tubing.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS474
Firing from left to right toward the triangular core, the beam burns a line in the wall which drips with flames.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS476
The beam cuts off the top half of a huge file cabinet as SOMEONE points the beam at the center of the core.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS480
The triangular core glows brighter and brighter inside its casing.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS481
SOMEONE shuts off the accelerator.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS482
He gazes at the triangle, which contains the glowing element.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS483
SOMEONE approaches the triangle.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS485
With a pair of tongs, he retrieves the glowing triangle and studies it.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS486
SOMEONE places the triangle inside an arc reactor. The reactor pulses with light.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS487
At Hammer Industries, SOMEONE works on an arc reactor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS488
Elsewhere, SOMEONE plays golf with Senator SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS489
SOMEONE activates the reactor, which electrifies a long coil.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS490
Later, SOMEONE and two men arrive at the lab. SOMEONE presses buttons on a panel, unlocking a door. He and the men enter a room where SOMEONE lounges on a cot.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS491
SOMEONE strokes the cockatoo which is perched on his knee.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS493
One man grabs the bird
IRON_MAN_2_DVS495
and stuffs it in a sack.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS496
The other man grabs SOMEONE's pillows.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS497
The man yanks off SOMEONE's shoes, revealing letters written on SOMEONE's bare feet.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS498
Stern-faced, SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS499
The two guards stare at SOMEONE. SOMEONE glances up at them and smiles.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS502
SOMEONE's lab.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS503
In his room, SOMEONE talks on the phone while the two dead guards hang from the ceiling behind him.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS504
SOMEONE mutes then unmutes, a speaker phone.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS506
SOMEONE studies a web page on a computer monitor. Above a photo of SOMEONE, a headline: "In Defense of Peace, with SOMEONE Hammer. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS507
SOMEONE grabs the reactor containing the new element and pops it into his chest.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS508
SOMEONE grits his teeth. The arc reactor glows brighter and brighter.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS510
Nighttime. A crowd gathers inside the Expo's glass-ribbed arena. Outside, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and Pepper step out of a silver car.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS511
Pepper and SOMEONE ascend a flight of steps into the arena.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS512
On the huge screen behind the stage, "Hammer Advanced Weapons Systems. " Spotlights shine on SOMEONE as he dances onto the stage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS513
He dances to the front of the stage and stands behind a clear Plexiglas podium.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS514
A man and a woman run onstage and carry the podium away.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS515
Lights illuminate the stage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS517
As footage of military aircraft and ships appear on the screen, eight drones rise from the floor on a platform at the back of stage left. SOMEONE and Pepper exchange glances.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS519
More drones with wing-like panels atop their shoulders rise from the back of the stage left.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS520
Eight drones with glowing faces rise at the front of stage left.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS521
Stage right, eight more drones rise from the floor. All the drones are equipped with different weapons.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS522
In a dark room, SOMEONE controls a drone by a computer.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS523
SOMEONE, wearing the war machine suit, the SOMEONE II heavily modified with weapons, rises from the floor of the circular main stage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS524
SOMEONE surveys the audience, then salutes.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS525
Behind him, the drones and SOMEONE also salute.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS527
SOMEONE gazes off into the night sky. SOMEONE, in his Iron Man suit, zooms down and hovers above the stage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS528
The suit's thrusters shut off. With his back to the audience, SOMEONE lands in front of SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS530
SOMEONE approaches the colonel.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS532
SOMEONE walks over to SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS533
Elsewhere, SOMEONE types a command: "Engage. " A Gatling gun on SOMEONE's back pops up and points at SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS535
The drones each raise one arm.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS536
SOMEONE runs offstage.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS537
SOMEONE flies out through the opening in the glass roof. SOMEONE and the drones fire their guns at SOMEONE. The glass panels in the roof shatter, showering down on the audience as people run off. SOMEONE types on his computer. Commands pop up on his computer screen: "Deploy, deploy, deploy. " Onstage, SOMEONE's thrusters fire up.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS539
SOMEONE rockets straight upward and out of the arena. The Air Force drones fly through the roof, breaking more glass.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS541
The Air Force drones follow SOMEONE as he speeds up after SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS543
SOMEONE's suit fires the Gatling gun at SOMEONE, who maneuvers through the sky.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS545
Firing their weapons, the Air Force drones zip through the sky after SOMEONE. They follow him toward an Expo building while firing bullets through the windows. Inside the building, people duck for cover. The Army and Navy drones march through the still crowded arena.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS546
Backstage, SOMEONE runs up to SOMEONE, who holds a telephone. A bespectacled IT man works at a computer.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS547
Pepper and SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS549
SOMEONE turns to the tech.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS550
SOMEONE twists SOMEONE's arm behind his back and slams him against a desk.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS552
SOMEONE lets go of SOMEONE and leaves. Pepper makes a phone call.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS553
Pepper approaches the tech.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS555
Firing their guns, the Air Force drones trail SOMEONE around Expo buildings as they zip through the sky.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS557
The drones on the Expo grounds stand on steps and fire missiles at people as they run away. In his control room at Hammer Industries, the smiling SOMEONE watches the mayhem on two large computer monitors.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS558
People hurry past SOMEONE as she strides out of the Expo's main entrance and approaches SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS559
SOMEONE sits in the driver's seat while SOMEONE climbs behind him in the back seat. The Army drones march double-time behind the fleeing crowd, then stop.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS560
Metal anchors fall down from their feet, securing them to the ground. The drones raise their guns toward the sky and fire at SOMEONE as he flies toward them.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS561
One of the bullets strikes an Air Force drone, which crashes and bounces across the ground in flames.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS568
On SOMEONE's computer, "Air 0303 Offline. " SOMEONE types on his keyboard. At the Expo, a Navy drone marches and fires its guns.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS569
The bullets hit a building.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS570
Concrete showers down on running people. An Army drone stomps up to a young child wearing an Iron Man mask. The drone's camera focuses on the mask.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS571
The child raises his left arm, revealing a glowing light in his hand. As the drone's shoulder-mounted gun lowers and aims at the child, SOMEONE lands and blasts the drone to pieces.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS575
SOMEONE flies off.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS577
Air Force drones follow SOMEONE as he zooms high into the sky. Below, SOMEONE makes a sharp turn onto a city street.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS578
SOMEONE stares into the rear-view mirror as SOMEONE changes clothes. Glancing forward, SOMEONE swerves.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS579
SOMEONE stares straight ahead. In the sky, SOMEONE and the drones follow SOMEONE as he flies along a freeway. SOMEONE zips into a huge parking garage and around tall concrete columns. As SOMEONE and the drones zoom over parked vehicles, car alarms set off flashing tail lights.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS580
One drone crashes into a column and explodes in a ball of fire.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS583
Another message flashes on SOMEONE's computer screen: "Air 0305 Offline. " SOMEONE types on his keyboard. On the screen, three triangles representing Air Force drones move off together.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS584
Trailing closer, SOMEONE fires at SOMEONE and misses.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS587
SOMEONE fires at SOMEONE again and sets dozens of parked vehicles on fire. The vehicles explode and flip into the air behind SOMEONE, who darts toward the Expo. Meanwhile, the silver car pulls up outside Hammer Industries and parks.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS588
SOMEONE and SOMEONE, wearing a form-fitting black leather outfit, step out.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS590
SOMEONE stands watch while SOMEONE swipes a card through a security system.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS592
SOMEONE opens the building's door and sprints inside. SOMEONE follows. On SOMEONE's computer monitor, "Security Breach. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS593
SOMEONE punches a muscular guard. As the two men fight, SOMEONE enters a second set of doors and runs past another guard. Turning as she slides across the floor, she throws Taser darts at the second guard, who collapses.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS594
SOMEONE runs down a hallway while SOMEONE exchanges punches with the first guard near the entrance. A third guard steps into the hallway. SOMEONE leaps over a cart and kicks him in the face, knocking him unconscious. She slides between the legs of a fourth approaching guard and punches him in the groin. He falls as a fifth guard appears. SOMEONE jumps over the downed fourth guard and kicks the fifth guard in the head. He also falls and lies motionless. SOMEONE watches on a monitor as SOMEONE runs out of view. At the Expo, Air Force drones follow SOMEONE as he zooms overhead. One drone crashes into a huge video screen mounted on a tower. A drone on the ground fires at SOMEONE, then rockets skyward. SOMEONE types. On his computer screen, the Marine drone status changes from "Engage" to "Deploy. " On the arena stage, the Marine drones' thrusters fire as the drones fly straight up. Backstage, the tech types at his computer.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS595
At Hammer Industries, the first guard knees SOMEONE in the stomach, punches him, and slams his face onto a counter. In the hallway, SOMEONE tosses two gas pellets at a sixth and seventh guard. As dark smoke rises from the pellets, the guards cover their eyes.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS596
SOMEONE kicks the guards and knocks them out. An eighth guard with a nightstick appears. SOMEONE deflects the nightstick with a steel cord. She punches the guard and wraps the cord around his neck. Two more guards charge SOMEONE. Still holding the cord, SOMEONE knocks one guard out and releases the cord. The eighth guard falls to the floor. SOMEONE slams the remaining guard onto the floor. An eleventh guard rounds a corner. SOMEONE breaks his right arm and knocks him out with a kick. SOMEONE strides down the corridor. She lifts a can of mace and sprays a twelfth guard in the eyes as he steps out of a doorway. In the lobby, SOMEONE bites the first guard's ear, then punches the guard's stomach. SOMEONE punches the guard's face, sending him sailing backward onto the floor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS599
SOMEONE gazes down the hallway at the many guards lying on the floor. With a cord around his neck, one guard flails as he dangles from the ceiling. SOMEONE watches security camera videos. He types on the keyboard. A rolling list of data and the graphic outline of an arc reactor suit displays on a monitor. At the Expo, SOMEONE and the drones chase SOMEONE as he speeds over a long line of reflecting pools.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS603
SOMEONE flies faster and faster toward the Unisphere. He enters the Unisphere, bounces off the Eurasian continent, then shoots back out. The drones follow SOMEONE inside, crash into continents, and explode. At Hammer Industries, SOMEONE kicks open the door to SOMEONE's control room. Inside, the two guards hang by their necks from the ceiling. SOMEONE follows SOMEONE, who holds two cocked pistols, into the room.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS604
SOMEONE hurries across the room toward SOMEONE's computer station.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS605
Above the Expo grounds, SOMEONE flies alone.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS606
SOMEONE zooms down and tackles SOMEONE in the sky. The men crash through an exhibit's geodesic dome, bounce across rocks at the base of a small waterfall, and land in a shallow stream. SOMEONE types on SOMEONE's keyboard. SOMEONE approaches as data and the outline of a suit pop up on the screen.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS607
Inside the dome, SOMEONE hurls SOMEONE onto a rocky stream bed. SOMEONE aims and fires the Gatling gun at SOMEONE. Bullets ricochet off SOMEONE's suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS608
SOMEONE works at the computer. A message appears onscreen: "System Access. " In the dome, the war machine's glowing eyes dim.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS609
SOMEONE falls off a small cliff and lands on his back in the stream below.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS611
SOMEONE's face appears on the monitor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS613
Pepper appears on another monitor.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS616
Inside the dome, SOMEONE taps SOMEONE's helmet.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS619
The face plate on SOMEONE's helmet flips up. SOMEONE opens his eyes.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS620
SOMEONE helps SOMEONE to his feet.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS621
They walk shoulder to shoulder.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS622
They turn as a Navy drone lands on the ledge above them. Other military drones drop down and surround them.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS624
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand back to back as they glance around at the drones.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS625
The face plates on SOMEONE's and SOMEONE's suits flip back down.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS626
The drones fire their guns as they charge toward the two men. SOMEONE and SOMEONE fire back, destroying several drones. SOMEONE and SOMEONE shoot and punch more drones as they approach. One drone fires a missile at SOMEONE, who dodges it. SOMEONE fires a blast at the drone, which explodes, also destroying two other drones flanking it.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS632
SOMEONE and SOMEONE shoot and destroy more drones.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS634
SOMEONE sweeps both arms out around himself as he fires.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS635
SOMEONE ducks. SOMEONE crosses his wrists and fires a repulsor beam which swivels, hits the remaining drones, and slices a tree in half.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS637
Uniformed police officers arrive backstage at the arena.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS638
Pepper glances at the officers, then at SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS639
One officer handcuffs SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS642
Two officers escort SOMEONE out. Outside the arena, four police officers walk with Pepper.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS643
At SOMEONE's computer, SOMEONE studies the drone tracker.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS644
A person wearing a bulky, black armored suit drops inside the dome and lands in front of SOMEONE and SOMEONE. The suit's face plate flips up, revealing SOMEONE's smiling face.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS648
Pulse whips shoot out from the arms of SOMEONE's suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS652
A small missile launcher pops out of SOMEONE's left shoulder. It loads the Ex-Wife Missile. A thruster ignites on the back of the missile and launches it toward SOMEONE. The missile strikes SOMEONE's chest plate and bounces off. It falls into a puddle at SOMEONE's feet and extinguishes.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS653
The launcher retracts.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS654
Grinning, SOMEONE takes one step forward.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS655
Using the computer screen in his helmet, SOMEONE targets SOMEONE. Guns pop out of SOMEONE's shoulders and fire as SOMEONE's face plate flips down. Swinging the pulse whips, SOMEONE lashes the ground in front of SOMEONE and SOMEONE. SOMEONE fires his Gatling gun at SOMEONE, who slices the gun off SOMEONE's shoulder with a pulse whip. SOMEONE rockets upward. SOMEONE lassos SOMEONE and slings him against a rock.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS656
SOMEONE runs sideways and fires at SOMEONE. SOMEONE leaps out of the way as a drone fires a missile then explodes near SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS657
SOMEONE swings a pulse whip which wraps around SOMEONE's suit.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS658
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE close and punches his helmet. SOMEONE soars over and hits the back of SOMEONE's helmet, freeing SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS659
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE, who head butts SOMEONE, then lassos him again with a pulse whip.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS662
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE along as he marches over and stomps on SOMEONE's chest.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS666
SOMEONE's face plate flips up. On SOMEONE's right, SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE toward him. SOMEONE throws his other pulse whip around SOMEONE, who stands to SOMEONE's left.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS670
SOMEONE and SOMEONE each lift a hand toward each other.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS671
They fire repulsor blasts, which meet where SOMEONE stands and form a fiery ball that explodes. Lying on the charred ground, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand. They walk over to SOMEONE, also on the ground. SOMEONE opens his eyes.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS673
SOMEONE and SOMEONE glance down as SOMEONE's arc reactor blinks.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS674
The arc reactors on the defeated drones also blink.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS675
SOMEONE and SOMEONE rocket up through the dome's roof. SOMEONE zooms toward the front steps of the arena, where Pepper stands near a wrecked drone. The drone's arc reactor blinks faster and faster.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS676
Pepper tilts her head and, frowning, stares at the drone's flashing reactor. SOMEONE speeds down, picks up Pepper, and zooms off as the nearby drone, as well as the other drones, explode.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS678
SOMEONE flies away from the fiery Expo park and lands atop a tall building.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS680
Pulling away from Pepper, SOMEONE yanks off his sparking helmet and throws it down.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS683
They step closer together.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS684
SOMEONE kisses Pepper.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS685
Pepper places her left hand on SOMEONE's chest. They stop kissing and gaze at each other.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS686
They kiss.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS687
SOMEONE sits nearby.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS688
SOMEONE stands.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS689
SOMEONE fires his thrusters and rockets upward. SOMEONE turns to Pepper.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS691
Daytime at S. H. I. E. L. D. Headquarters, a remote warehouse, SOMEONE sits at a desk.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS692
He slides one of two folders atop the desk toward himself and studies the cover.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS693
"Avenger's Initiative Preliminary Report. "
IRON_MAN_2_DVS694
SOMEONE picks up the folder. SOMEONE Fury steps up and presses the folder to the desktop.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS695
SOMEONE sits facing SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS696
The second folder.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS697
SOMEONE hands the folder to SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS698
SOMEONE stands, then sits on the desk by SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS699
SOMEONE stands and shakes SOMEONE's hand.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS700
SOMEONE walks off, then turns around.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS701
SOMEONE nods.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS702
Later, Senator SOMEONE stands at a podium outdoors.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS703
SOMEONE pins a medal on SOMEONE's military uniform.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS704
SOMEONE picks up another medal and approaches SOMEONE.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS705
SOMEONE pins the medal on SOMEONE's suit jacket.
IRON_MAN_2_DVS706
SOMEONE stands between the two men and places his hands on their shoulders. They all smile. As a photographer approaches and snaps a photo, SOMEONE lifts his right arm and forms a V with his index and middle fingers.