She swaps a look with her copper-haired friend.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS6
SOMEONE's friend joins her.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS7
As they hug, SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS8
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder and watches as SOMEONE
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS9
Now, a young woman carries a box across the well-kept lawn of the Spanish-style home and drops it in the trunk of a hatchback.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS10
A guy lugs over a suitcase.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS11
An SUV approaches.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS12
Purses her lips as SOMEONE pulls.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS13
SOMEONE hugs her mother.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS14
The older daughter swaps a look with her boyfriend.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS15
Hug. The oldest
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS16
good-naturedly, then hugs SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS17
Her daughters wait anxiously.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS18
SOMEONE climbs into her car.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS19
She reads a text. She mimes texting.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS21
As SOMEONE disappears down the long driveway her sister's boyfriend wraps his arm around SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS22
As she starts toward the house,
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS23
pauses and waves at the departing couple.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS24
A black SUV heads down the tree-lined graveled driveway.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS25
Left alone, SOMEONE gazes at her picturesque house. Now, she enters through the front door and sets her purse on a chair beside it. She unwraps a white shawl from her shoulders, tosses it on to a dining room chair, and removes an earring. To her left, a wide archway opens into the kitchen. As she takes out the other earring she notices uncleared plates on the kitchen island. Shaking her head she strolls over. She nibbles a piece of food from a plate as she carries it to the sink. Her eyes shift thoughtfully as she rinses the plate and looks out a window.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS26
She averts her dejected gaze, then shakes her head dismissively, wipes the tears from her eyes, and resumes clearing the plates.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS27
She notices the line of customers.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS28
She refills a water glass.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS29
Moving down the counter she pauses at a server.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS30
She stops in front of a white-haired man.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS31
They shake hands.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS32
SOMEONE and SOMEONE shake hands.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS33
In an office, they roll out the blueprint.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS34
SOMEONE dons her reading glasses.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS35
Peter trade an eyebrow raise.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS36
She glances at SOMEONE. He smiles.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS37
She takes off her glasses.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS38
She eyes SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS39
Shakes his hand again.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS40
SOMEONE shifts his eyes.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS41
In a doctor's examining room, SOMEONE crosses her jittery legs. She begins to fiddle with a piece of equipment.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS42
The doctor sits across from her.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS43
He holds a measuring tool to her brow.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS45
SOMEONE and his lover step on.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS46
eyelid up with her ring finger SOMEONE notices a fertility
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS47
hand, they share an awkward look.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS48
SOMEONE averts his embarrassed gaze.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS49
climbs on his head.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS50
Nighttime, SOMEONE and three friends
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS51
One girl friend rubs her back.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS52
SOMEONE thoughtfully lifts her wineglass.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS55
Later, they cross the hotel lobby.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS56
SOMEONE shakes her head.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS57
SOMEONE nods meekly. SOMEONE gives her a squeeze.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS58
SOMEONE glances at the counter.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS59
Alone in an elevator, a smiling couple hurries in as the doors close. SOMEONE watches out of the corner of her eye as the older man whispers in the younger woman's ear. The woman laughs and her lover runs a hand down her back.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS60
SOMEONE uncomfortably arches her brows, then gives a sad blink and gazes at the ceiling.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS61
Hotel room, she lies on a bed then resolutely sits up.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS64
The bartender sets down a cocktail
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS66
over and takes a seat
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS67
She gives an amused smirk.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS68
SOMEONE purses her lips.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS70
SOMEONE flops on to a bed his shirt hanging open. SOMEONE lies ravished next to him
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS71
as the rumbled sheets covering her crotch.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS72
She jogs into the bathroom holding a pillow over her rear and kicks the door shut.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS73
SOMEONE follows finding her crouched by the toilet.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS76
It shows assembled guests. SOMEONE wipes tears from her eyes then leans toward SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS78
SOMEONE whistles.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS80
SOMEONE glances at her ex-husband who cocks his head and offers a tender smile. SOMEONE's own smile falters.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS81
Now, in a chic restaurant, SOMEONE's oldest daughter returns to her family's table.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS82
her oldest notices.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS83
He tears up. SOMEONE bulks dubiously.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS84
He lifts his glass.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS85
SOMEONE's face softens.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS86
SOMEONE rumples his lips into a grin. SOMEONE's pensive gaze drifts. SOMEONE glances tearfully at her sister who looks to her fiance.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS87
SOMEONE lifts his glass,
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS88
his family sips their champagne. Now, at the hotel's front desk the clerk gives SOMEONE and SOMEONE their bills.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS89
SOMEONE eyeballs him, then faces their children.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS90
SOMEONE answers his cell.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS91
SOMEONE ends his call.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS92
waits at the end of the line. SOMEONE frowns and swallows. He kisses her cheek.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS93
Now, SOMEONE drives his car.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS94
SOMEONE stops the car and rolls down his window.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS95
Wearing earbuds she halts quizzically.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS96
She gets in.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS97
He and SOMEONE share an awkward smile. She faces forward and chuckles.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS98
In her graveled courtyard they stand.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS99
He muses slack-jawed.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS100
He narrows his eyes.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS101
SOMEONE heads off, SOMEONE shakes her head.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS102
SOMEONE looks over his shoulder. He sees SOMEONE rub SOMEONE's back, the SOMEONE side steps away.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS103
She swaps up the water cooler jug.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS104
She eyeballs him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS105
He goes to kiss her then picks her up instead.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS106
when the lawn sprinklers springs to
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS107
Later in bed, SOMEONE lies curled up covering her eyes, beside her SOMEONE beams.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS108
He leans in and kisses her.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS109
They share a mischievous grin.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS110
SOMEONE holds up her hands.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS111
blanket and rolls on top of her.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS112
With their feet sticking out from under the blanket he rolls to her other side.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS113
He kisses her shoulder.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS114
Smiling at each other they press their foreheads together.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS115
She watches as he gets out of bed. Wearing only boxers SOMEONE grabs his shirt then faces her and slaps his ample belly.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS116
He hands her a robe.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS117
She twirls her finger.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS118
He eyes her quizzically.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS119
She pleadingly gestures him around.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS120
He tucks in his shirt.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS121
She sits on the edge of the bed.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS122
He fixes his tie.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS123
She glares at him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS125
She bashfully rumples her lips.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS126
Her stunned friends stare.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS127
SOMEONE waits in her yard where two ladders
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS128
She looks over his work.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS129
He unhooks a strand of blue tape.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS130
She wanders into the middle of the taped off area, glances around then faces him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS131
Now they climb the two ladders, SOMEONE gently guides her with a protective hand on her back.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS132
look out over her Spanish-tiled roof to the tree-filled horizon.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS133
SOMEONE takes out her cell.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS134
reads SOMEONE, she glances at SOMEONE, shuts off the phone, then stumbles.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS135
They smile out at the view. Now in a bathroom,
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS136
Fully clothed SOMEONE puts his phone in his pocket, steps out of the shower, and shuts its glass door. He turns off the running sink faucet, then glances at the mirror, and checks his watch.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS137
Grimacing, he opens the door. SOMEONE waits outside.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS138
SOMEONE storms up.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS139
Nighttime, SOMEONE removes a tray of two thick cheese-topped slices of bread from the oven.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS140
They sit side-by-side at the kitchen island.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS141
By the hedge and spies
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS142
Inside, SOMEONE gathers his blueprints.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS143
They share an uncomfortable smile and shift awkwardly.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS145
She waves back and SOMEONE continues to his car. SOMEONE smiles and shuts the door.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS146
She strolls back into the kitchen brushing her hair with her fingers.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS147
She hurries back and opens the door but finds SOMEONE on the porch.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS148
He slides in and grabs her waist.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS149
She eyes him skeptically,
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS150
smiles and shakes her head. Later, SOMEONE reclines in a bubble bath while SOMEONE sits on the floor leaning on the tub eating ice cream.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS151
She squeezes water out of a washcloth.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS152
She flicks water at him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS153
He sets his dish on the floor.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS154
He points his spoon at the dish.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS155
She drapes the cloth over her chest.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS156
He mimes smoking.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS157
drops it in a drawer.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS158
Now, SOMEONE changes a high light bulb.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS160
He nuzzles her neck then stares lustfully at her. SOMEONE gives in her lips meeting his in a sensual mood.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS161
SOMEONE pulls away from him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS162
Entering a bedroom she answers a phone.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS163
She nods at SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS164
As he leans to nuzzle her she scoots away.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS165
She walks SOMEONE to the door.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS166
She ends the call.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS167
SOMEONE eyes his cell, shows it to SOMEONE, and answers.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS168
his ex and leaves.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS169
SOMEONE smiles after him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS170
SOMEONE smirks back at SOMEONE. She gapes at him and he shrugs. With a careless wave
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS171
her smile fades. Shaking her head she lifts her hands.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS172
They head inside.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS173
reach his office.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS174
He lets her in.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS175
She reaches for her bag then hesitates.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS176
She digs out her cell phone.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS177
Screwing her mouth to one side she lowers the phone and looks away. She manages a brief tearful smile and continues.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS178
Lifting her brow SOMEONE gives a wide-eyed nod.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS179
Smiling she opens her hands in his direction.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS180
Now at the fertility center, a middle-aged man sits on a waiting room couch texting while a younger woman at his side reads a magazine. Next to them a silver-haired man fills out paperwork beside a gum-smacking blonde. At the end of the row SOMEONE sits hunched over a hand to his brow.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS181
A separate female client smiles. The nurse takes SOMEONE to a private room,
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS182
SOMEONE node wryly. As the nurse leaves he sets down his specimen cup.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS183
He removes his jacket then his trousers.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS184
As he digs out his cell phone SOMEONE tours a farmer's market.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS185
While SOMEONE lifts his brow and smiles.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS186
his arms. Now at a hotel restaurant SOMEONE shares a table with SOMEONE, her back's to the lobby.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS187
SOMEONE enters the lobby.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS188
Boarding an elevator SOMEONE and SOMEONE make out.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS189
Now in a suite, a bathrobe-clad SOMEONE puts a CD in a player.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS190
then shakes her head, takes a breath, and steps out from behind the bed. He fidgety hands move to untie her bathrobe
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS191
lower to her side. SOMEONE clasps the belt again
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS192
then changes her mind. As she gazes at a door it open the door.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS193
with a matching robe. They
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS194
SOMEONE nervously bites her lip and her ex-
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS195
husband holds her in a fond gaze.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS196
She lifts a hand to her chest.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS197
as she exposes one shoulder.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS198
As she pulls the robe off her other shoulder she looks up and
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS199
faces SOMEONE and sensually cycles her shoulders. The bathrobe drops around her ankles.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS200
SOMEONE stares admiring and shakes his head.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS201
Taking a breath SOMEONE beams at him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS202
with her. He pauses, his smile vanishing. He staggers
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS203
Downstairs, SOMEONE tensely gazes past SOMEONE and the wedding consultant.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS204
He dashes away, hiding his face with his hand he crosses toward the reception desk.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS205
SOMEONE gawks. Now, the doctor checks SOMEONE's blood pressure.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS206
SOMEONE cocks an eyebrow.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS207
Wide-eyed, SOMEONE shifts her confounded gaze.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS208
In the lobby, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE seated on a bench. Hunched over his hands wrung through his hair he bounces one knee rapidly.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS209
He sees the doctor signal the clerk thumbs up.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS210
He hugs her and shakes her.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS211
SOMEONE and SOMEONE eats soup served on trays as they watch Oprah. SOMEONE starts to salt his, but SOMEONE takes the shaker away.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS212
SOMEONE smiles at him then sobers.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS213
She aims the remote at the TV.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS214
Leaning back against the headboard she faces him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS215
SOMEONE gazes off pensively and SOMEONE looks away.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS216
Smiling, SOMEONE shakes his head.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS217
SOMEONE bites her lip. Resting on the upholstered headboard she thoughtfully scratches her arm.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS218
Jake’s smile fades and he stares at her. SOMEONE looks askance at him then fully meets his gaze.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS219
She starts to push her tray away then leans back.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS220
She moves her tray. As she starts to get up SOMEONE takes her hand and she waits. Leaning her head back SOMEONE wistfully watches his thumb stroke her fingers. The ex’s share a vulnerable gaze
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS221
then yields a smile.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS222
Biting her lip she turns away and answers her cell. SOMEONE beams fondly as he watches.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS223
He gives SOMEONE a pleading look.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS224
She grips the phone thoughtfully then raises it to her ear.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS225
SOMEONE ends the call. In the suite, SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE from behind and kisses her neck. At the firm, SOMEONE pulls two tickets from his pocket then faces a young coworker.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS226
She thoughtfully folds her arms.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS227
SOMEONE kisses her and leaves.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS228
She admires the spread silky crimson dress.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS230
In SOMEONE’s room a bedside alarm clock reads 8:46. Jakes cell phone rest beside it. Lying tensely on the bed SOMEONE eyes his phone and exhales nervously. He surreptitiously takes the phone, creeps toward the door leaving SOMEONE typing on her laptop by a sleeping SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS231
SOMEONE freezes then faces her.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS232
She points at SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS233
As SOMEONE stretches SOMEONE scoops her son off the bed. She shuts her laptop.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS234
SOMEONE's stunned gaze darts.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS235
She pulls off her t-shirt and smiles at him in her amply filled black bra. SOMEONE manages a nod and hurries out. In SOMEONE's room he lays the curly-haired boy in bed and tucks him in.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS236
The child lays it on his chest over his heart and hugs it tightly.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS237
SOMEONE gives a tender smile which fades to a serene look. Sitting on the edge of the boy's bed he leans over his
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS239
She sits on her kitchen wearing the silky crimson dress. Her legs crossed, she idly bounces her foot, and stares off. She faces the chocolate cake on the island then stands and sets a glass cover over it.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS240
Adjusting the black belt at her narrow waist she strides out and turns off the kitchen light. On the patio the table remains set with the flowers, dinnerware, and a bottle of wine. Picture windows show SOMEONE trudging past and turning off lights in the house.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS241
As she takes off her earrings she plods down a hall and shuts off its light as well. Daytime, SOMEONE's, and SOMEONE and SOMEONE’s SUVs sit parked in front of SOMEONE's house.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS242
SOMEONE frowns.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS243
car arrives.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS244
SOMEONE fills his wine glass.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS245
SOMEONE carries in SOMEONE's bag as SOMEONE
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS246
notes the five settings on the table.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS247
As SOMEONE blows him off SOMEONE gulps his wine.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS248
She set the roast chicken.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS250
SOMEONE answers his cell.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS251
SOMEONE fans herself. SOMEONE ends his call and faces his family.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS252
SOMEONE brings his dad some SOMEONE oil.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS253
SOMEONE stops carving the chicken and turns in SOMEONE's direction still holding her knife.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS254
SOMEONE takes the knife as she leaves.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS255
Outside, SOMEONE follows her ex onto the patio.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS256
She tightens her lips.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS257
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE who pleadingly puts his hands up.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS258
At the front door, SOMEONE hugs and kisses her father goodbye. As SOMEONE lingers in the doorway she takes her place at the table.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS259
SOMEONE stares at his family glumly then gives a regretful look.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS260
She watches SOMEONE through a window.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS261
He watches her smile. SOMEONE's car speed off.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS263
Later, SOMEONE saunters to her front door carrying a gift. He gives a little hop.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS264
He rings the bell.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS265
SOMEONE opens the door and peeks out then grins.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS266
She shows a big slice of chocolate cake.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS267
He hands her the gift. She digs into her cake then glances at the present.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS268
She shoves the cake at him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS269
She unwraps the slender book with the bright cover.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS270
She clumsily kisses him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS271
He smacks his lips.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS272
She lose the joint.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS273
She glances at them and drops it.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS274
He look over and she waves.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS275
they nod then drive off.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS276
Up later outside, guests hurry up.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS277
SOMEONE and SOMEONE
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS278
Hide with the joint behind the seven-foot hedge.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS279
SOMEONE puts it to his lips.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS280
SOMEONE's jaw drops. He waves the joint in front of his nose and mouth, and inhales more smoke.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS281
He addresses the joint.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS282
He takes another hit. On the other side of the hedge a guy walks by.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS283
She stifles her laughter in the crook of her arm.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS284
SOMEONE mouths wow.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS285
SOMEONE jerks his head and stalks off.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS286
She lights the joint.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS287
She puffs out a cloud of smoke.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS288
SOMEONE stares at her reflection in a mirror.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS289
She widens her eyes. SOMEONE blows smoke out of the joint and into SOMEONE's mouth.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS292
He is pretending to cast a fishing line at her then reels
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS293
Later in SOMEONE's car,
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS294
SOMEONE disbelievingly shakes her head.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS295
SOMEONE's lips stutter.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS296
She hesitates thoughtfully.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS297
They share a smile.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS298
SOMEONE bashfully hides her face with her hand then grows serious.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS299
He solemnly locks eyes with her and she beams, cocking her head.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS301
Lights reveals the well-stocked artfully arranged on a central island.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS302
He squints at the chalkboard menus.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS304
back in the restaurant dining room.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS305
SOMEONE plucks a crumb from her croissant and eats it.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS306
SOMEONE skeptically quirks his brow.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS307
She faces him and they lock gazes.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS308
SOMEONE strokes her hand then lifts it and examines her palm. He knits his brow.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS309
He tenderly slides up her sleeve.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS310
He kisses the inside of her wrist and wraps his hand around hers.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS311
She nods and leans toward him. They share a steady kiss.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS312
They start to kiss again.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS314
She presses her forehead to his and shakes her head.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS317
She strolls in with a bouquet of purple bellflowers then snips the ends off the stalks and puts them in a vase. SOMEONE staggers out drowsily.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS318
wears girl's pajamas.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS319
SOMEONE arrives.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS320
Frowning, SOMEONE peeks out the window and finds SOMEONE's sports car parked in the driveway. SOMEONE's arm rests along the open window, SOMEONE jogs outside, and he gets out. She casts a nervous glance back at the house then faces her ex-husband.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS321
Their kids file outside.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS322
SOMEONE summons a breath, SOMEONE glances at her.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS323
SOMEONE winces tearfully.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS324
He turns away and covers his face with one hand. SOMEONE squints at him doubtfully.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS325
stifles tears and rubs her chest.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS326
SOMEONE eats breakfast with the rest of his family. Forking up a morsel of food he pours syrup right onto it then shovels it to his mouth, SOMEONE gapes.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS327
She forces a smile.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS328
Later, wearing a wide-brimmed hat she stands in one of the plots of her spacious garden. She hunts around a five-foot plant then locates a tomato and sniffs it.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS329
As she places it in her shallow vegetable basket SOMEONE strolls into the garden. She nods irritably to herself.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS330
widens his arms in a helpless gesture.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS331
She hugs him and pats his back.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS332
She fans herself with her hat.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS333
She answers her cell.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS334
She frowns and turns her back to him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS335
He smile and drops his gaze.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS336
He heads off.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS337
Later, SOMEONE serves popcorn to his family as they snuggle under blankets in front of the television. He hands the bowl to SOMEONE then one to SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS338
He sits between SOMEONE and SOMEONE with the third bowl and they smile at the TV.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS339
SOMEONE catches SOMEONE's eye and mouths, I'm so happy.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS340
Nighttime, SOMEONE and SOMEONE raid the fridge SOMEONE joins them.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS341
SOMEONE hands him a plastic tub.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS342
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS343
He sheepishly looks up from his bite.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS344
He shows SOMEONE in a patterned sweater.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS345
A dog pops out.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS346
his shirt has three-quarter sleeves.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS347
He runs out.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS348
Now, SOMEONE peeks into SOMEONE's bedroom. Her shadow passes over the curtains covering the window in the bathroom door.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS349
went into the bedroom and gives a mischievous grin.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS350
robe wearing only a t-shirt and boxers underneath.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS351
then pulls the laptop closer. Now, SOMEONE steps
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS352
SOMEONE bends for his boxer.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS353
SOMEONE falls out of his chair. SOMEONE aims the laptop at SOMEONE, then grabs his robe. SOMEONE climbs back into his seat and locks eyes with SOMEONE through the webcam. Her lips flutter helplessly.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS354
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run in.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS355
The shocked siblings gape.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS356
SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS357
At his desk, SOMEONE reaches for a button. His image vanishes from SOMEONE's screen. A tearful SOMEONE shifts her gaze.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS358
SOMEONE and SOMEONE each look to SOMEONE who shakes her head.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS359
SOMEONE stares.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS360
SOMEONE leans heavily against an arched doorway. As SOMEONE's chest heaves she nods and lowers her tearful gaze. SOMEONE swallows, scratches the back of his head, then hurries out.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS361
SOMEONE follows and SOMEONE trails after them. SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze off in different directions avoiding eye contact.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS362
Later, a duffle bag gets tossed on the backseat of a car. As her brother sits in the front passenger seat SOMEONE climbs behind the wheel. They swap shell-shocked looks and put on their seat belts.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS363
In her SUV, SOMEONE gazes back at her mother's house as she and SOMEONE drive away. SOMEONE's car follows down the driveway. SOMEONE jogs outside clutching a shawl around her shoulders and halts in the middle of the yard with a desperate shrug. The two vehicles speed off. Beyond her SOMEONE trudges to his sport car with a leather travel bag. The grief-stricken man pauses and looks at his ex-wife. SOMEONE eyes him resignedly. SOMEONE gazes back at her then looks away and opens the driver side door.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS364
Blinking back tears SOMEONE sympathetically cocks her head. She watches as SOMEONE's sports car drives away passing a three-rail horse fence that lines the road. His car turns the corner.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS365
The image dissolves to the surface of the pool. Beside it SOMEONE lies on the lounge chair wrapped tightly in a blue shawl curled into a fetal position.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS366
She stares up at the night sky with her hands crossed protectively over her chest. A three-quarter moon gleams high above the treetops. Clutching a rumpled tissue in her hands she closes her eyes and falls asleep.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS367
Daytime, brilliant sunlight reflects off the surface of the pool and brightens SOMEONE's face as she sleeps on the lounge chair.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS368
A butterfly flits over the pool, sprinklers come on nearby, and SOMEONE wakes.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS369
She looks up at the sunny sky then swings her legs down and glances around thoughtfully.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS370
The lovelorn woman shakes her and bravely purses her lips.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS371
At SOMEONE and SOMEONE's house SOMEONE's trots past the garage and up the winding steps to the front door above it.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS372
SOMEONE opens the door and smiles.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS373
SOMEONE steps inside and he shuts the door behind her. In a hallway,
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS374
she opens a door and finds SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE lying in bed together under a blanket. SOMEONE taps her brother and they sit up. From the hallway, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE tread into the room then peeks in after her. SOMEONE sets her purse on a chair then takes a seat on the edge of the bed. The siblings hug their knees to their chests.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS375
She drops her gaze and gives a pensive nod.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS376
SOMEONE nods and rests her hand on SOMEONE's knee.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS377
SOMEONE covers her mother's hand with her own and SOMEONE touches his sister's forearm. SOMEONE shares a look with SOMEONE and draws them all into a hug.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS378
He puts her arms around them.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS379
Now at SOMEONE's architecture firm, SOMEONE enters and crosses the bustling floor to SOMEONE's office. Large windows show him talking on a phone.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS380
He glances over his shoulder and sees her waiting in the doorway.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS381
He hangs up and musters a faint smile.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS382
She slides the door close behind her then faces him clutching the strap of her purse with both hands. SOMEONE rests his hands on his chair back.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS383
They exchange nods.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS384
SOMEONE locks eyes with him and he regretfully tightens his lips.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS385
She drops her eyes and shifts uncomfortably.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS386
He paces away from her as she gives a fleeting smile.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS387
He gives a gentle grin and she gazes at him earnestly.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS388
Past the horse fence near her house, at the wheel she
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS389
parked from across the front yard. She studies him through the window.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS390
SOMEONE climbs out of the SUV and shuts the door keeping her eyes fixed.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS392
SOMEONE treads closer, SOMEONE scoots over inviting her to sit beside him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS393
SOMEONE crosses the walkway, sets down her purse,
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS394
they share a lingering look and SOMEONE glances away.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS395
SOMEONE shifts her stare then fixes it on him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS396
She moves to lean on one arm.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS397
She smiles and shakes her head.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS398
She bites her bottom lip and blinks at him sheepishly as the wind tousles her honey blonde hair.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS399
She playfully points at him.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS400
SOMEONE gestures at him once again. SOMEONE gives a broad shrug then drops his hands into his lap.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS401
She reaches across the space between them and rubs his shoulder.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS402
She looks away from him then leans one elbow on the armrest and gazes off thoughtfully. SOMEONE watches her. Her fingertips drop from his shoulder and her arm rests on the back of the bench. As our view slowly orbits the ex-lovers SOMEONE's distanced stare drifts.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS403
Now, a hard rain pounds down on the vacant bench swing.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS404
the leafy plants in SOMEONE's garden and streams
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS405
A view from the front door shows a flatbed truck carry timber past an excavator. SOMEONE steps outside and opens an umbrella.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS406
SOMEONE halts, gives a long nod.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS407
She trudges toward a construction crew huddled around a table collapsible canopy.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS409
The worker smiles. SOMEONE steps up beside.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS410
SOMEONE's eyes widened and her jaw drops open.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS411
SOMEONE smiles and she looks to the other men.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS412
Workers gather their things and hurry.
ITS_COMPLICATED_DVS413
He nods at her beaming. SOMEONE smiles and looks away.