The car halts in front of an ivy-covered building.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS27
SOMEONE steps out of the driver's seat and views the residence. A concierge opens double doors to a courtyard.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS28
Now a woman packs an original copy of Mastering the Art of French Cooking into a box with more cookbooks, then thrusts it into a packed jeep.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS29
Queens, New York, 2002. She rides in the jeep next to a dark-haired man.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS30
The young woman glances at her companion, and with a grin, shakes her head of short red hair.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS31
The jeep drives past a tall decrepit warehouse and a water tower covered in graffiti.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS33
The jeep pulls up to a small two-story brick building. A red and white checkered awning on the first floor's pizzeria shades the storefront. Music by Alexandre Desplat. The redhead trudges up the stairs to the vacant second floor apartment, toting a cat-carrier. She sets it down and opens its door. A ginger tabby steps out.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS35
As the woman roams the empty apartment, the dark-haired man climbs the stairs with a box.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS36
Later, the redhead unpacks items from boxes, while the dark-haired man goofs around in the half-settled bedroom.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS37
He finds the redhead squatting in the kitchen.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS38
The redhead gives a resigned nod.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS39
She looks at her beau.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS40
They sit side by side on the kitchen floor.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS41
The redhead faces SOMEONE somberly.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS42
SOMEONE presses his lips to her cheek.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS43
Back in Paris, SOMEONE roams their elegant apartment, fanning herself.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS44
SOMEONE enters, carrying a large wicker basket.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS45
SOMEONE opens French doors to a faux balcony, closing her eyes, as a breeze wafts through her curly hair. She smiles, takes in a savoring breath, then inspects the rest of the apartment.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS51
SOMEONE lies on the bed. Her feet hang off the end.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS52
She glances at them, dangling over the mattress.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS53
Now, in Queens, a burly man opens the storefront of the pizzeria.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS54
The redhead with the short shaggy haircut exits from a door beside the pizza parlor. She smacks a plastic bag as it blows by.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS55
Later, Manhattan skyscrapers rise into the sky beyond an old cursive Pepsi Cola sign. The former Brooklyn-er walks past it.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS59
Later, she emerges from a subway station.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS60
As she passes ground zero, she glances at people gathered by a fence adorned with flowers and flags.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS61
Now, she sits in a cluttered cubicle surrounded by other workers wearing headsets.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS62
SOMEONE closes her eyes.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS63
SOMEONE answers numerous calls.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS64
Instructions on a cubicle wall read, "Do not become emotionally involved. "
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS65
Now, SOMEONE listens carefully.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS66
Later, SOMEONE talks to her boss.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS67
SOMEONE smiles gratefully and leaves.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS68
Now, amid the flow of pedestrians on the sidewalk, she strides along with a down-hearted look.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS69
She stops at a shop window displaying a chocolate fountain.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS70
Later at the apartment, she stirs a bowl of chocolate filling.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS71
SOMEONE tastes the filling.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS72
As SOMEONE tastes more, SOMEONE sips a cocktail.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS74
SOMEONE rushes into a SOMEONE Bistro and greets a table of three smartly dressed women, one of whom talks on her cellphone.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS75
The high-nose brunette hangs up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS76
The women gawk.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS77
The snooty brunette answers her cellphone.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS78
Cassie smiles knowingly.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS79
The women clink their water glasses.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS80
As two of the women take calls, the redhaired friend faces SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS81
Annabelle talks into a recorder.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS82
As Annabelle talks into her handheld recorder, SOMEONE nibbles a pencil-thin breadstick. Cassie takes it away.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS83
SOMEONE turns back to Annabelle, who checks her datebook.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS84
Now, a poster shows SOMEONE, three others, and the title - Portrait of a Lost Generation.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS85
Her mousy bohemian friend grimaces.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS86
SOMEONE's friend looks away.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS87
SOMEONE gives an amused smirk. Later at home, she flips bread in a skillet, then slices tomatoes.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS88
She points her knife at SOMEONE, who reads on the couch.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS89
SOMEONE raises her brow and smiles.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS90
They eat Parmesan-sprinkled bruschetta.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS91
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a forlorn look.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS92
They sip red wine.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS93
SOMEONE shifts her eyes thoughtfully as she forks up a piece of sausage.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS94
SOMEONE grins, his mouth full of food.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS95
SOMEONE gazes at SOMEONE's delighted face. Now they watch SOMEONE on TV.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS96
SOMEONE Child holds a pan.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS97
Her flip misses.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS98
SOMEONE returns fallen bits to the pan.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS99
SOMEONE grins, and SOMEONE kisses her on the cheek.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS100
As credits cycle on the black-and-white show, SOMEONE and SOMEONE smooch. SOMEONE reclines on the couch, and SOMEONE lovingly climbs on top of her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS101
Later, SOMEONE sits in bed reading SOMEONE's cookbook.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS102
She flips the page, and sets the book down.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS103
SOMEONE shakes a tums into his hand.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS104
He climbs into bed.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS105
Morning. SOMEONE and SOMEONE face a laptop.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS106
Her blog is titled - The SOMEONE, SOMEONE Project.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS107
A new window appears.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS108
Later, SOMEONE types.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS109
In a countdown field, SOMEONE enters 365 days to go, and 524 recipes to go.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS110
In Paris, SOMEONE visits an outdoor market.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS111
Baguettes jut from her shopping basket. As SOMEONE passes two butchers, one holds up a hare, still with its fur. The aspiring cook grimaces, then meets a green grocer.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS112
Now she buys nuts.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS113
SOMEONE snaps her photo. Now with an oyster man.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS114
Now the Child stroll through a park.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS116
They pass a baby carriage, and SOMEONE's smile fades.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS117
Now at a photography exhibit.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS118
Now at a restaurant.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS119
A waiter brings food.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS120
As SOMEONE puts out a cigarette, SOMEONE steals a bite from her plate.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS121
SOMEONE refrains from digging in and faces SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS122
She shifts her restless gaze.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS123
SOMEONE stares wide-eyed at her. He shifts his gaze then nods.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS124
Her husband eyes her with an affectionate smirk.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS125
Now in a millinery workshop, SOMEONE sits before an unadorned hat on a stand. Her expression listless. She picks up a ribbon and pulls one end through the other with a dissatisfied pout.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS126
Later on a park bench.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS127
In a bridge class, SOMEONE stares out a window.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS128
Now at a bookstore.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS129
Now with a tutor.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS130
Now at a restaurant, SOMEONE sits at the head of a long crowded table. SOMEONE presents her with a gift.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS131
She unwraps it, revealing a thick book.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS132
She turns it, showing the title.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS133
Larousse Gastronomique.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS134
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS135
A waiter brings a pastry with a candle.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS136
She blows out the flame. Later in bed, she leafs through the book.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS137
Photos show poultry being prepared.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS138
Setting the book aside, SOMEONE kisses her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS139
SOMEONE nibbles her neck, then pulls her in for another passionate kiss.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS140
SOMEONE strokes his stomach, then eyes him adoringly as he removes his glasses.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS141
Their embrace grows more intense, and they lie back together.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS142
SOMEONE switches off his bedside lamp.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS143
SOMEONE switches off her lamp,
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS144
and SOMEONE tenderly rolls on top of her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS145
Now an alarm clock reads 5:30. SOMEONE rises then types at her laptop.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS146
Now she chops off an artichoke stem.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS147
She whips the sauce.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS148
She and SOMEONE eat.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS149
Five pounds of it sit in her fridge.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS150
She melts a chunk in her pan.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS151
She adds two more. Now she sautés mushrooms.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS152
Her words type out.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS153
Now she buys cheese.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS154
She descends subway stairs.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS155
SOMEONE cooks while on the phone.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS156
She returns to the kitchen. Now she types.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS157
SOMEONE stares.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS158
A pot steams.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS159
She cracks an egg into the water.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS160
With a wooden spoon, SOMEONE prods the egg. It disintegrates into filmy stands.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS161
SOMEONE tries a bite.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS162
She raises her glass.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS163
She eats another bite of egg.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS164
SOMEONE points upward.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS166
SOMEONE blogs at work.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS167
A comment window appears.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS168
Her co-worker grins. The comment reads, "Julie, it's your mother. I still don't understand why you're doing this. I seem to be your only reader. "
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS169
At Le Cordon Bleu in Paris, SOMEONE and two other women face a teacher.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS170
Now in an office.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS171
Madame SOMEONE shakes her head.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS172
Now a classroom door opens. Wandering in, SOMEONE beams excitedly. A chef with a snowy mustache looks up, and his male students turn.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS173
Later, we move down a long table, watching masculine hands rapidly chop onions. SOMEONE's hands tentatively saw with her knife into an onion. Her classmates stare, and the chef approaches.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS174
SOMEONE notices the others watching.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS175
Later at home, SOMEONE practices chopping. A mound of chopped onions two feet across sits on the wooden tabletop. SOMEONE appears in the doorway, recoils and rubs his eyes.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS176
With an amused smile, SOMEONE shakes his head and leaves.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS177
She resumes practicing.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS178
Now in class, she finishes chopping first.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS179
Later, she and her classmates each melt butter in a pan. SOMEONE adds beaten eggs and shakes her pan back and forth over a gas flame. Her fellow students add their eggs too.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS180
Madame SOMEONE enters, folds her arms and watches SOMEONE with a sour glare. Straightening, the aspiring chef lifts her pan.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS181
She gives it a small upward jerk, and flips the omelet.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS182
Madame SOMEONE leaves with an indignant huff.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS183
She bisects a lobster's head.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS184
SOMEONE pulls her unto his lap, and kisses her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS185
He takes her into the bedroom.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS186
As they embrace, she yanks down his suspenders.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS187
In class, the master chef paces.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS188
Now at a fish mongers.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS189
She browses pastries then tastes a pair.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS190
At home, she types.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS191
SOMEONE brings a mortar and pestle. Now at a dinner party.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS192
Everyone wears a paper heart badge.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS193
SOMEONE sits at the head of the table.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS194
SOMEONE's merry smile fades.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS195
SOMEONE holds her in a loving gaze. Her chest heaves, and she beams radiantly.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS196
SOMEONE slips a hand beneath her paper heart.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS197
She flutters it.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS198
Now SOMEONE watches her cooking. She towers over their French kitchen.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS199
She whacks hanging pots.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS200
Now in Queens.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS201
They open mail.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS202
SOMEONE opens a padded envelope, which contains a small bottle and a note.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS203
Now SOMEONE receives more food items.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS204
She types.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS205
SOMEONE blows her nose.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS206
She takes out a soufflé.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS207
At a fish market,
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS208
an employee takes a live lobster from a tank and bags it, SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap a look. Now in the jeep.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS209
Behind them, the plastic bag ruffles as a lobster crawls around. SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS210
SOMEONE unbuckles her seat-belt, and checks the bag. The lobster looks at her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS211
She sits down. Now at home.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS212
She snaps tongs at him.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS213
She dons a rubber glove, removes the lid from a pot of boiling water, and takes a lobster out of the bag.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS214
She faces the pot.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS215
She stuffs the lobster in, then grabs another.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS216
She stuffs a second lobster in the pot, and returns to the bag for a third.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS217
She sticks the third in the pot, flips a stray antenna off the brim, and puts the lid back on.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS218
Standing over the closed pot with all the lobsters inside, SOMEONE smiles proudly.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS219
The lid pops into the air, and SOMEONE runs out of the kitchen. SOMEONE hops up as SOMEONE flails her arms and clutches her head. SOMEONE grabs the hot lid from the floor, and covers the pot.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS220
SOMEONE lets go of her head and looks over.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS221
As she cautiously approaches the kitchen, SOMEONE grabs an apple and takes a bite.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS222
She kisses him.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS223
He kisses her hungrily.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS224
She shoves him out of the kitchen.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS225
SOMEONE jumps.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS226
Later, SOMEONE greets arriving guests. One guy hands off a cake. He and SOMEONE hug.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS227
Dressed like SOMEONE Child, SOMEONE puts her hands on her hips and faces her guests.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS228
SOMEONE models her '50s era look, then hugs her friends.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS229
Later, over dinner.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS230
SOMEONE holds up her fork.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS231
Later, SOMEONE blows out candles.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS232
They serve the birthday cake. Now SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a gift.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS233
SOMEONE takes the present and looks SOMEONE in the eyes.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS234
She tears off the wrapping paper to find a thin box.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS235
Opening it, SOMEONE grins at SOMEONE,
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS236
then reveals a pearl necklace.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS237
SOMEONE sets down his cup of coffee, and goes behind her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS238
As he wraps the necklace around her neck, SOMEONE snaps off the fake plasticky pearls she's wearing.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS239
She feels her new pearls and smiles. SOMEONE sits by her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS240
Misty-eyed, SOMEONE grins then waves her hands.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS241
Later, still in her SOMEONE getup, SOMEONE sleeps on the couch.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS242
SOMEONE enters and leans over her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS243
He turns off a lamp and leaves her sleeping peacefully.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS244
Now at work, SOMEONE glances over her cubicle to a co-worker.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS245
They playfully slap hands, then sit back down.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS246
Later with SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS247
In bed.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS248
As SOMEONE falls asleep,
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS249
SOMEONE grabs a bedside container of antacid tablets and pops one in his mouth. He shuts off a lamp, and stares up at the ceiling.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS250
Now at a ballroom party.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS251
Two French women head for the ladies room.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS252
Inside, SOMEONE sits at a vanity, smoking a cigarette.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS253
Another American woman stands at a mirror.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS254
The third woman primps.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS255
Another woman enters.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS256
SOMEONE stands.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS257
SOMEONE and SOMEONE eye her stature. Now all three exit the ladies room.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS258
SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE alone at a desk.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS259
Now SOMEONE shops with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS260
A surprised SOMEONE regards her new friends.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS261
At Le Cordon Bleu.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS262
SOMEONE steps out, leaving SOMEONE to retake her test.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS263
Now in Queens, a hardback of SOMEONE Child's biography strikes the alarm clock.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS264
SOMEONE drops the aspic in the sink.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS265
SOMEONE peeks in.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS266
She faces the sink.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS267
SOMEONE glances over as food and liquid spit up from the drain.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS268
SOMEONE pursues him to the couch. SOMEONE shields his head with a pillow.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS269
SOMEONE returns to the kitchen and kicks a trash can.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS270
At her laptop.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS272
She stuffs it back in.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS273
She sits on the floor, SOMEONE notices.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS274
She hunches forward.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS275
On the kitchen floor, SOMEONE lies flat on her back. SOMEONE approaches.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS276
SOMEONE sits up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS277
She gets up, goes into the living room, and grabs a tissue.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS278
SOMEONE mouths, "Who?" And SOMEONE waves him off with a tissue.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS279
Now SOMEONE holds up a glass of wine.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS280
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand across from her in the Child's kitchen.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS281
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lift a table.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS282
SOMEONE stands.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS283
They teach.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS284
SOMEONE steps out.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS285
SOMEONE tweaks knobs of dough baked together.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS286
In a train station.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS287
SOMEONE listens intently.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS288
On a platform, SOMEONE waits next to SOMEONE, holding yellow flowers.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS289
A tall curly-haired woman with big hips gawks, smiling as she charges. The sisters embrace.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS290
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's handbag.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS291
In a restaurant.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS292
A waiter serves cheese.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS293
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS294
The sisters hook pinkies, tap their thumbs together, then wiggle their hands away. SOMEONE playfully taps SOMEONE on the nose.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS295
SOMEONE tries a dollop.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS296
SOMEONE sucks a bit of cheese off her thumb.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS298
SOMEONE gives a proud smile, and shrugs.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS299
Now SOMEONE faces a wardrobe's full-length mirror. SOMEONE enter, putting in an earring, and fastens a string of pearls around SOMEONE's neck.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS300
Both wear a collared knee-length dress of shiny fabric.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS301
SOMEONE's is coppery orange, and SOMEONE's is midnight blue.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS302
They smile and cock their heads. SOMEONE slips her hands into her pockets.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS303
SOMEONE offers a merry shrug.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS305
Outside, upstairs windows show a crowded cocktail party within. Inside, SOMEONE mingles with a tray of hors d'oeuvres.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS306
Two guest sample the fair.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS307
A tall man faces SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS308
She kisses his cheek.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS309
SOMEONE flirts with a shorter man.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS310
As SOMEONE leans alluringly on an archway before an enchanted SOMEONE, SOMEONE frowns. SOMEONE coyly brushes SOMEONE's belt with his finger.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS311
SOMEONE winces, and SOMEONE eyes the pair curiously.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS312
Now at an outdoor wedding, a young flower girl scatters handfuls of petals. She overshoots the aisle, then backtracks and heads down it toward a waiting priest.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS313
SOMEONE files down the grassy aisle in her heels.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS314
SOMEONE follows, wearing a simple wedding dress, and holding her father's arm.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS315
She kisses his cheek, then faces the priest with SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS316
Later, an elegant pavilion with a roof shaped like a pith helmet houses dining tables and a dance floor. SOMEONE and SOMEONE prance toward each other and clasps hands. SOMEONE blows SOMEONE a kiss, then lifts her arm and pivots beneath it. They wave at SOMEONE, who sits with SOMEONE and her parents.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS317
Her father lights her cigarette.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS318
He glares at SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS319
SOMEONE kicks SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS320
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hurry to the dance floor.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS321
Joining the other slow dancers, they clasp hands.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS322
SOMEONE wraps his arm around SOMEONE's waist, and they share a soft smile.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS323
Nearby, SOMEONE bends and nuzzles SOMEONE, then kisses his forehead.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS324
SOMEONE lovingly cups SOMEONE's face in both hands, and he playfully dodges away.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS325
Later, he kisses her neck as they dance toward the newlyweds.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS326
SOMEONE and SOMEONE squeeze each other's arms, and SOMEONE and SOMEONE shake hands.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS327
Now, the Childs' wood paneled station wagon drives over a bridge.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS328
Later, outside their villa, SOMEONE picks up mail from their concierge.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS329
Now in the kitchen, SOMEONE whisks a creamy sauce.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS330
SOMEONE scoops some up with his pinkie and samples it.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS331
SOMEONE opens a letter.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS332
She reads.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS333
As SOMEONE snacks obliviously, she takes a seat.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS334
He glances at her. She flips to a second page.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS335
She buries her face in his shoulder.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS336
He squeezes her close.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS337
He tenderly kisses her forehead.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS338
She pats his chest.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS339
He presses his lips to her forehead once again.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS340
In a cafe.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS343
SOMEONE pulls out documents.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS345
She hands the sheets to Simone and SOMEONE, then studies their expressions. Her smile fades.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS346
SOMEONE beams and closes her eyes.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS347
Now in Queens, SOMEONE types.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS348
In a market.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS350
SOMEONE cooks.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS351
She puts it in the oven.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS352
She sets a timer.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS353
Later, a TV reads - the French chef.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS354
Dressed like SOMEONE Child, Dan Aykroyd faces the camera.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS355
The actor waivers.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS356
Fake blood spews, dousing the chicken.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS357
Fake blood pours from his hand.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS358
It spurts toward the camera.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS359
SOMEONE and SOMEONE quake with laughter. Blood covers the actor's white blouse.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS360
He passes out.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS361
Later, SOMEONE's timer ticks down from 57 minutes to 56. As SOMEONE sleeps in bed, a clock on the nightstand reads 1:30.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS362
In the living room, SOMEONE snoozes on the couch. Later, the timer shows one minute remaining.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS363
It ticks down to zero.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS364
SOMEONE shifts in her sleep, snuggling a blanket.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS365
Outside, the pizzeria's lights go dark.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS366
In the living room, SOMEONE still sleeps. The tabby jumps off the couch and ambles away.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS367
It strolls into the kitchen and takes a seat, staring at the oven.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS368
Later, in the living room.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS369
SOMEONE jolts awake, and gives a horrified gape.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS370
She scrambles into the kitchen.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS371
She yanks out the pot and takes off the lid, revealing her ruined stew.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS372
Back in Paris, SOMEONE sits at a typewriter and lays carbon paper between two clean white pages.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS373
She rolls the paper into the device.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS374
SOMEONE blinks.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS375
She drags on a cigarette.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS376
Seated at his own desk, SOMEONE shifts.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS377
Standing reluctantly, SOMEONE paces toward her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS378
He briefly creases his lips.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS379
He narrows his eyes.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS380
Later in a restaurant.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS381
SOMEONE raises his glass.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS382
Now SOMEONE types.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS383
In a subway station.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS384
A train arrives.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS385
The women board.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS386
Now a maid leads them into a sitting room.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS388
Irma shooting herself.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS390
SOMEONE hands his wife a letter.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS391
SOMEONE slips the letter from the envelope as she follows SOMEONE into the apartment. She sits at the small entryway table, where SOMEONE turns on a lamp, and sets down his hat.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS392
SOMEONE smiles.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS393
She glares at the ceiling.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS394
SOMEONE steps frantically about.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS395
SOMEONE reads more.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS396
Now in Queens, SOMEONE writes in her blog, as SOMEONE pulls on his jacket.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS397
SOMEONE grabs his bike.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS398
At the meat market.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS399
SOMEONE breathes in the stew's steam.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS400
She stirs thick pink cream.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS401
She sets out crudités.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS402
SOMEONE stows a stack of newspapers in a bin.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS403
She briskly strides to the phone and picks up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS404
She smiles broadly and nods.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS405
Her face falls.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS406
She sits on the couch.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS407
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE poutily hangs up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS408
SOMEONE shakes her head, her lips pursed in a frown.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS409
SOMEONE struts away.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS410
SOMEONE salts his food.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS411
SOMEONE watches, her mouth agape.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS412
SOMEONE bites a carrot stick.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS413
SOMEONE glares from the bathroom doorway.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS414
SOMEONE grabs his jacket.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS415
He puts it on as he strides toward the stairs.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS416
He grabs his coat from a hook, picks up his bag, and hurries downstairs.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS417
Back in Paris, SOMEONE carefully wraps a pot lid in newspaper and packs it into a box.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS418
Facing him, SOMEONE fidgets with her cardigan as she gazes forlornly around the half-packed kitchen.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS419
SOMEONE looks at her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS420
SOMEONE forces a smile.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS421
The Childs’ pose for a photo.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS422
They hold a paper heart.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS423
SOMEONE addresses a postcard version of the Valentine. Now they pose in a tub.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS424
In a postcard version, they share a doting gaze amid the soapy suds. SOMEONE ink stamps the postcard, “Wish you were here,” and addresses it.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS425
Now SOMEONE snaps photos of SOMEONE stuffing a duck.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS426
SOMEONE sews the duck, binding it around the stuffing.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS427
SOMEONE gives a reserved nod.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS428
SOMEONE poses, pulling the sewn flaps of the duck together.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS429
In Paris.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS430
Now at a cafe with SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS431
SOMEONE's eyes filled with tears, and she blows her nose on a folded handkerchief.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS432
SOMEONE glares. SOMEONE faces her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS433
SOMEONE resumes eating. Later she returns with SOMEONE to her apartment.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS434
SOMEONE's concierge opens the front door as they approach.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS435
SOMEONE uses the phone.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS436
With SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS437
SOMEONE smiles faintly.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS438
An investigator leans closer.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS439
SOMEONE sits on the edge of the bed.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS440
He climbs in next to SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS441
As he settles under the covers, SOMEONE watches with tender thoughtful eyes.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS442
SOMEONE turns questioningly to his wife.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS443
He shifts his down-hearted gaze, and SOMEONE looks away.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS444
She gets comfy under the covers.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS445
They share a glance.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS446
They look at each other, and SOMEONE worriedly presses her lips together.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS447
SOMEONE touches her forehead reassuringly, then turns off the light.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS449
In Queens, SOMEONE shifts restlessly in bed.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS450
With a frown, she glances at SOMEONE's empty pillow.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS451
Later she sits at her laptop.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS452
SOMEONE's wide blue eyes filled with tears as she types.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS453
She rests her chin on her hand and re-reads the passage.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS454
Her lips tighten sorrowfully.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS455
She highlights the last sentence, deletes it, and determinedly resumes typing.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS456
Now, as SOMEONE carries a paper bag to work, the bottom breaks, and the dessert crashes to the ground.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS457
At the office.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS458
SOMEONE greets Ernestine.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS459
As SOMEONE appears in the doorway, her boss turns from his computer and gives her a stern look.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS460
SOMEONE nods and sits down.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS461
SOMEONE nods.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS462
She nods again, her face solemn.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS463
She purses her lips and rises.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS464
Hands in her skirt pockets, SOMEONE heads off.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS465
Later she sits at a bar with SOMEONE, holding a half-drunk Martini.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS466
SOMEONE shakes her head.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS467
SOMEONE gives a sympathetic look.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS468
SOMEONE sips her Martini.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS469
SOMEONE knits her brow.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS470
SOMEONE gives a thoughtful look.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS471
Later SOMEONE rides the train home, then writes in her blog.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS472
She moves the cursor to the publish button on screen and clicks it, then turns off the desk lamp.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS473
SOMEONE picks up the cordless phone and dials. She sits on the bed with the handset to her ear.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS474
Meanwhile in his office, SOMEONE lies on the couch reading.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS475
He glances at the phone.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS476
In the apartment, SOMEONE hangs up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS477
In his office, SOMEONE leans his head back on a pillow.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS478
SOMEONE falls backward onto the bed, the phone clutched to her chest.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS479
She turns it on again and listens.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS480
She hangs up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS481
Now, SOMEONE sits at his work computer, eyes trained on SOMEONE's blog. As he reads her latest entry, he swallows hard.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS482
In the apartment, SOMEONE lays face-down on the bed with a pillow over her head, and the phone clutched in her hand.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS483
SOMEONE hangs up and glares at the phone.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS484
With a resolute look, she sits up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS485
She flops back again.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS486
She sits up, swings her legs off the bed, and marches into the kitchen. The phone still in her hand.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS487
Later, SOMEONE strides out of the apartment. Her face set firmly. Inside a market, she closes her eyes as she smells a bunch of fresh basil. Now she walks down the sidewalk toting a grocery bag.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS488
She slows down as she approaches the apartment, and notices SOMEONE crossing the street toward her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS489
He puts his hands in his pockets, and greets her with a faint smile.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS490
She flashes a hopeful wide-eyed smile.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS491
She tears up. SOMEONE takes a deep breath.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS492
He smiles warmly, and SOMEONE reciprocates.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS493
SOMEONE's lips spread in a wide grin, and he reaches for SOMEONE's groceries.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS494
He takes the bag, then slings an arm around her shoulders as they head inside.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS495
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE cross a train station.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS496
They set down their luggage and sit on a bench. SOMEONE shows her a letter.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS497
They peer across the terminal to an entrance, where a bespectacled woman in a plaid jacket hurries in and stops.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS498
She spots their bench, and SOMEONE stands. The newcomer touches her chest.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS499
With open arms, the two cross the floor and embrace.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS500
They hug.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS501
Now in a conference room, the three of them sit with three male executives and a female editor.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS502
A book entitled, Real Home-cooking, shows a chubby American woman.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS503
Now at her home, Avis mixes cocktails. SOMEONE reads the cookbook.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS504
Avis regards SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS505
Now, SOMEONE sharpens a knife.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS506
In her own kitchen, SOMEONE sharpens a knife and slices the air. Now we see SOMEONE turning a crank on a manual sieve strainer, then SOMEONE turning on a food processor. SOMEONE punches keys on a typewriter, floating island. SOMEONE's laptop screen shows her write, "So last night I made floating. "
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS507
SOMEONE taste gooey cheese topping. SOMEONE pinches cheese stretching to her lips. SOMEONE rubs creamy paste on an uncooked chicken. SOMEONE removes a cooked chicken from the oven.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS508
Now SOMEONE, then SOMEONE, then SOMEONE, then SOMEONE, each raid the medicine chests in their bathrooms. As SOMEONE spreads icing over a cake,
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS509
SOMEONE enters and dabs his finger in the bowl.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS510
She smacks his hand, as he steals a taste. SOMEONE lays out a chocolate frosted cake, rimmed with chipped almonds. Before she can slice it, SOMEONE digs in.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS511
He playfully smushes a piece into her mouth, then rubs it over his own face. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE box up a copy of the manuscript.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS512
Now SOMEONE sprays a mirror with glass cleaner and wipes it down.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS513
SOMEONE goes to the intercom.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS514
Later, a photographer documents the pork chops and side dishes.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS515
As they eat, the reporter jots notes.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS516
The chewing reporter's eyes widen.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS517
Now a man reads a newspaper article entitled, A Race to Master the Art of French Cooking, with SOMEONE's picture.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS518
SOMEONE sits next to the reader on the subway.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS519
At a food shop, SOMEONE peeks over a man's shoulder, who glances at the same article. She turns to Ernestine and they high five.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS520
At work, SOMEONE sets down a cup of coffee and puts on her headset.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS521
At home, SOMEONE carries a stack of newspapers upstairs.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS522
SOMEONE lies on the couch.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS523
She puts the stack of papers down. Puts down her purse and goes to the machine.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS524
SOMEONE bounces excitedly and beams at her husband.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS525
She dives on top of him, and kisses him repeatedly.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS526
Now a shirtless SOMEONE carries SOMEONE over to the bed, and they flop onto it.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS527
Their cat looks up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS528
In bed, SOMEONE rolls on his back.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS529
SOMEONE carries in two full martini glasses and sits with him on the bed.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS530
SOMEONE rushes to the phone.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS531
SOMEONE looks on from the bed. Listening, SOMEONE's expression goes blank.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS532
SOMEONE hangs up and looks at SOMEONE sitting up attentively.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS533
She frowns.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS534
Back in the 50s, SOMEONE sits on a couch with her feet up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS535
SOMEONE arrives.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS536
SOMEONE sets down his briefcase, and SOMEONE hands him a letter.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS537
He shifts her feet a smidge on the coffee table and sits facing her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS538
He adjusts his glasses and reads.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS539
SOMEONE folds up the letter and lays it aside.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS540
SOMEONE takes a seat beside her on the couch, and rests a hand on her thigh.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS541
She eyes him.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS542
She takes his hand.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS543
He kisses her hand.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS544
He wraps his arm around her and kisses her forehead.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS545
Now, a sign outside an office reads, Alfred A. Knopf, New York.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS546
A preppy editor reads the title page.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS547
SOMEONE exhales wearily through pursed lips, then picks up the box containing the manuscript and leans back in her chair. As she reads, a smile spreads across her face.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS548
Later, at home, SOMEONE dries cubed red meat with a paper towel.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS549
Now she pours red wine into a stock pot on the stove. Steam surges upward.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS550
A recipe at her side reads - Boeuf Bourguignon.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS551
Later, the editor faces the pot, skeptically tensing her lips.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS552
She slurps a sample from a wooden spoon, smacks her lips, and smiles.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS553
She scoops up a chunk and eats it.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS554
Her eyelids flutter as she reels ecstatically.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS555
She shakes her head.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS556
Now, words label a two-story colonial house - Cambridge, Massachusetts. In a kitchen, SOMEONE and SOMEONE organize and unpack cookware.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS557
Outside, a postman waits at the front door. SOMEONE opens up and shivers.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS558
SOMEONE signs on a clipboard.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS559
She shoves her arms into the sleeves of a sweater draped over her shoulders. The postman hands her an envelope and leaves.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS560
The envelope reads -
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS561
Alfred A. Knopf, incorporated, special delivery.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS562
SOMEONE clutches the letter to her chest and glances nervously inside the house.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS563
Creeping across the porch, the chef summons a breath and paces. She takes a seat on a cushion wicker bench, opens the envelope, and reads.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS564
They hug.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS565
In her office, SOMEONE posts note cards.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS566
SOMEONE rearranges some of the cards on the bulletin board and reads the result.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS567
SOMEONE perks up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS568
SOMEONE gapes.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS569
Now in SOMEONE's Queens apartment.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS573
They sit face to face.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS574
SOMEONE slouches, wincing tearfully.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS575
She flops onto the bed.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS576
She sits back up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS577
Now SOMEONE types.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS578
She turns to a duck recipe now on TV.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS579
SOMEONE aims her knife.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS580
SOMEONE slides the blade down the back of a raw duck on a cutting board.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS581
Later on TV, SOMEONE sews the stuffed duck shut. SOMEONE does the same.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS582
On TV, SOMEONE wraps the duck in pastry dough.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS583
SOMEONE swaddles her's in dough too. Later she pulls a golden dough wrapped loaf from the even.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS584
On a roof, SOMEONE passes SOMEONE flowers and plates through a window.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS585
SOMEONE climbs out and jogs around to help her.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS586
Nighttime at a rooftop dinner party.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS587
SOMEONE brings out the duck and bows.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS588
SOMEONE raises his glass.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS589
The guests toast.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS590
Later they dine.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS591
SOMEONE takes a bite.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS592
She taps her glass, stands, and swallows facing her husband.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS593
SOMEONE raises his glass.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS594
She blogs.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS595
Our view drifts away from SOMEONE's window.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS596
Now in a Smithsonian, a wall display reads - SOMEONE Child's Kitchen.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS597
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive at a roped off exhibit as a wistful young woman snaps a photo of it.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS598
SOMEONE takes a photo of the counters. SOMEONE points.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS599
SOMEONE snaps another photo.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS600
SOMEONE poses, smiling by a portrait of SOMEONE.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS601
SOMEONE takes a picture.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS602
SOMEONE poses as if chatting.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS603
She leans close.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS604
SOMEONE heads off.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS605
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE's portrait with a faint smile, then glances around wearily.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS606
Opening her purse, she pulls out a pound of butter, and shows to the portrait.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS607
and shows to the portrait.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS608
She sets it down on a ledge beneath the framed photograph, and gazes at the renowned chef's coy grin.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS609
SOMEONE smiles and strolls off around a corner.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS610
Beside the portrait, SOMEONE's Cambridge kitchen stands by, quaint and vacant.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS611
Celery green paint covers the door and a set of drawers, and seafoam blue covers the cupboards.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS612
In the center of the homey well-organized space, the table rests, set for two.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS613
We glide inside, over the rope cordoning off the room, and past cookbooks crammed unto a narrow bookshelf.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS614
Cookware hangs from pegboard on the walls.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS615
The overhead lighting fades and shadows appear, as sunshine washes in from one side. A shadow passes over the door.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS616
Then SOMEONE bustles in.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS617
She lifts the lid of a Dutch oven on the stove, and steam billows out. Bending over, she sniffs the contents.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS618
She picks up a wooden spoon and stirs the stew.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS619
As SOMEONE enters, SOMEONE glances up.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS620
They share a kiss.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS621
SOMEONE plops a package down on the table and takes a seat.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS622
SOMEONE adjusts the stove, and joins him.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS623
He hands her the package, the chef takes it quizzically.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS624
Turning it over, she slides her fingers under the manila envelope’s flap,
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS625
then struggles to rip it open.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS626
She pulls out a hardcover copy of her book.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS627
Her jaw drops.
JULIE_AND_JULIA_DVS628
She claps a hand to her mouth, and the image freezes.