The frowning beauty arrives beside SOMEONE and accidentally drops her purse.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS14
As he sets it on the bar, she spies his wedding ring.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS15
The pair leaves.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS17
She puts his hand on her breast.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS18
He keeps his hand on her chest. Beverly Hills 2011.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS19
He leaves a note on a young woman's pillow, Cindy I had a great night.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS20
P. S, thanks for not beating me like my wife does.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS21
Now at a medical practice, a woman takes a stiff dark liquid filled sack from a box.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS22
A deliveryman eyes the product.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS23
She grabs her own breast. The man reaches for it.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS24
With a woman who has one eyebrow much higher than the other.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS25
SOMEONE’s botched eyebrow rises even higher.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS26
SOMEONE dryly lowers her chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS27
Her eyebrow remains cocked.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS28
She nods.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS29
Her brow shoots to her hairline.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS30
As he hugs her, she waggles her brows.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS31
SOMEONE's cousin arrives.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS32
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS33
Now stylish guests attend a hip party at a mansion overlooking the ocean.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS34
SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach a man with an unnaturally stiff, smooth face.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS35
As they down drinks, wine spills down his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS36
Now in a bathroom.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS37
SOMEONE pockets his ring.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS38
He gives Ariel a shot, then smacks him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS39
Later, they leave the bathroom.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS40
Clad in a filmy cerulean dress, a young statuesque beauty with sun-kissed skin and long blonde hair approaches SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS41
The longtime bachelor stops in his tracks and stares.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS42
As the pair steps outside, Adon struggles to close his lips around his straw.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS43
A taut-faced woman.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS44
Later on the beach.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS45
SOMEONE leans in and kisses him. Their arms twine around each other and they sway on their feet.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS47
In a nock encased by tall rock formations, SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie between two blankets.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS48
Digging through his pockets, SOMEONE finds the wedding ring. Her smile vanishes as she holds it up.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS49
She chucks the ring at him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS50
She marches down the beach. Now at SOMEONE's medical practice.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS51
SOMEONE tosses her hair and smiles vapidly.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS52
Two kids enter with a stout SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS53
The SOMEONE plays a hand-held video game.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS54
SOMEONE faces him with a wide-eyed smirk.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS55
Now at a private school, SOMEONE leads a student through a crowded hallway. SOMEONE enters with flowers. Seeing him, the young teacher turns away.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS56
She dumps the extravagant bouquet in a trash bin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS57
SOMEONE takes him to a classroom.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS59
SOMEONE faces a window. From the other side, Silas glares and points menacingly.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS60
On Rodeo Drive.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS61
Now in a high-end store, she wobbles in a pair of four-inch heels.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS62
SOMEONE gives her a gentle shove, and she falls over.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS63
Now SOMEONE eyes a vast display of designer handbags.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS64
Later, SOMEONE carries a few shopping bags in each hand, as he follows her.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS65
In a store, SOMEONE tries on one stylish curve-hugging dress after another.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS66
SOMEONE gives her a playful shove, and she swats at him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS67
She shakes her hips, and they laugh.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS68
Later, SOMEONE follows her out of Tiffany's, loaded down with shopping bags. Now a hairdresser eyes SOMEONE appraisingly.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS69
She frowns as he coldly approaches.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS70
Bending down, he takes up handfuls of her long honey-brown hair and peers closely at it.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS71
Now at an upscale sunlit lounge.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS72
From a stairway, SOMEONE ascends into view in a white sheet dress that shows off her long tan legs and graceful curves.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS73
Her hair tousled in sexy waves, she smirks through glamorous sunglasses. A distinguished man in a suit trails her dutifully.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS74
SOMEONE turns and her jaw drops at the site of the other woman.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS75
Moving in slow motion, SOMEONE blows a kiss to a stranger.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS76
She slaps the waiter's rear.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS77
SOMEONE nearly chokes on her red wine.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS78
SOMEONE jolts.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS79
She kicks SOMEONE hard in the shin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS80
Later, they leave.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS81
Facing SOMEONE, she finds him staring pointedly at her.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS82
She abruptly gets in the limo.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS83
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE, who stares agog at him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS84
At Pizza Hut.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS85
The SOMEONE salsa dances around a janitor.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS86
They shake hands on it.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS87
SOMEONE faces her younger brother.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS88
SOMEONE pours soda into his glass, then takes a sip through a straw. All the while, keeping a cold glare fixed on SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS89
SOMEONE sucks on his straw as if it's a cigarette.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS90
The girl picks up her slice and winces at it.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS92
A woman with mismatched breasts.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS93
They go to the exam room.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS94
SOMEONE meets his gaze, sheepishly. SOMEONE grins.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS95
He wags his finger in his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS96
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS97
He reaches for her phone. She swats him away, then answers.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS98
She ends the call. Returning to Mrs. Harrington, she finds SOMEONE staring at her.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS99
A lopsided bra.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS100
He wiggles his finger from his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS101
Outside, JD McFunnigans.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS102
SOMEONE steps out of her car in a tight dress.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS103
In slow motion, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and the kids try to cross the parking lot.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS104
A boy holding a soda cup runs out in front of them. He stops and turns. As his pregnant mother catches up, he chucks the full cup at her and runs off.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS105
Soaked with soda, the pregnant woman raises her hands overhand and yells after him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS106
Everyone still moving in slow motion, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the kids watch the furious woman chase after her
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS108
Inside, children run wildly through an elaborate play structure with tunnels, slides, and climbing ropes. SOMEONE enters with SOMEONE and the kids.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS109
A chubby boy trips and head-butts SOMEONE in the crotch.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS110
SOMEONE approaches.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS111
SOMEONE stares at him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS112
SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a look.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS113
She runs away.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS114
SOMEONE leaves and SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS115
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE through the play structure.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS116
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look up from the floor.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS117
A little boy sneezes on SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS119
SOMEONE eyes him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS120
She beams and takes a bite.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS121
SOMEONE mouths, Thank you.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS122
SOMEONE returns.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS123
SOMEONE grins at him, then hangs his head and cries.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS124
Now at LAX, SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE and the kids in a busy airport terminal.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS125
A bespectacled SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE on the lips until she pushes him off.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS126
He wags his tongue, and SOMEONE catches it.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS127
She drags him aside and wipes her hand on his vest.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS128
He points to his round glasses.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS129
SOMEONE backhands him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS130
Now a Hawaiian airliner soars over turquoise water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS131
On the island, a luxurious beachside resort boasts several swimming pools on its manicured grounds.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS132
Beyond a large reflecting pool in the lobby, the family arrives. SOMEONE approaches the registration desk.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS133
SOMEONE takes out his credit card then returns to the others.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS134
SOMEONE and SOMEONE raise their hands. Now on a palm tree lined beach, SOMEONE steps out of the water in a yellow string bikini. SOMEONE and SOMEONE check her out as they cross the sand. The voluptuous young woman brushes back her long blonde hair. Ogling her, SOMEONE lifts his round glasses.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS135
SOMEONE walks his fingers up SOMEONE's arm. Later outside a jewelry store.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS136
Nighttime at a luau, fire dancers perform while the group eats dinner.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS137
SOMEONE takes a pitcher from the waiter.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS138
The kids swap a look.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS139
The petite redhead flounces over.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS140
He kisses SOMEONE's cheek.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS141
SOMEONE squints at them.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS142
The guys pound fists.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS143
Dawn in the lobby.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS144
Now in a lush tropical forest, the group hikes a trail.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS145
The black-haired pig charges them and they run. SOMEONE knocks SOMEONE down, and the pig steps on his back.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS146
Later, the group hikes a narrow trail beside a canyon.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS147
SOMEONE scales a steep hill, while the others lag behind. Hiking through bamboo stalks, she leads the group up another incline.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS148
On a river, they paddle two-person canoes. Sitting behind SOMEONE, SOMEONE gawks at the exposed crack of her rear.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS149
SOMEONE whacks him with her paddle.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS150
Now as all six of them cross a rope bridge, a family of four spots them from below.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS151
SOMEONE stands at the tail end.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS152
A board breaks, and he lands on a crossbeam, crotch first.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS154
SOMEONE chucks SOMEONE into a mud puddle.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS155
She lifts her face from the sticky muck.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS156
Now at a lagoon with a waterfall.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS157
SOMEONE strips down to a skimpy string bikini.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS158
She goes to the water's edge.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS159
SOMEONE dives gracefully into the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS161
SOMEONE approaches the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS162
SOMEONE shyly whispers to his mother.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS163
On the far side of the lagoon, SOMEONE emerges from the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS164
She picks her way over some jagged rocks, and stands beneath the waterfall.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS165
He tries to high five SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS166
SOMEONE strips down to a pink string bikini, revealing her tan slender body.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS167
In slow motion, she saunters to the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS168
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare slack-jawed at SOMEONE's well-toned figure.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS169
SOMEONE steps away. SOMEONE picks her way out to a rocky point.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS170
SOMEONE dives into the water. Cladding briefs with frogs printed on them, SOMEONE climbs rocks by the waterfall.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS171
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lounge near-by.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS172
He drops to the water, landing on his back.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS173
Now back at the hotel, the group disembarks from a shuttle.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS174
Evening in SOMEONE's suite.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS175
He wags his finger from his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS176
As she leaves, SOMEONE approaches her in the hallway.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS177
SOMEONE punches him in the gut and keeps walking.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS178
Later in SOMEONE's suite.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS179
SOMEONE draws a card and reads.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS180
SOMEONE draws a card.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS181
SOMEONE shrugs.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS182
As he cries, SOMEONE goes to comfort him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS183
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS184
SOMEONE storms off.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS185
SOMEONE holds her crying brother in her arms. Turning, SOMEONE smacks his shoulder.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS186
Now he tucks them in.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS187
SOMEONE looks in on them.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS188
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE shoves the kids back down on the bed.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS189
Now on a putting green overlooking the ocean.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS190
He gives her the putting flag.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS191
The flag juts up from his butt cheeks. Now by the hotel pool, he wears water wings.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS192
SOMEONE tosses him into the pool. SOMEONE surfaces and scoops him up in his arms.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS193
Later, SOMEONE holds SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS194
SOMEONE puppets a dolphin shaped cookie.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS195
SOMEONE flails his arms and kicks his legs. Slowly making his way towards the pool's edge. As he arrives, SOMEONE feeds him the cookie and tousles his wet hair.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS196
At a spa.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS197
The women get massages.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS198
SOMEONE's brow furrows. At the pool.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS199
SOMEONE takes off his water wings.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS200
SOMEONE tosses SOMEONE from his arms, and the little boy flails and kicks his way across the pool. SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS201
SOMEONE's head dips below the water, and he lifts it back out.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS202
SOMEONE reaches the pool's edge, high fives his mother and grins broadly. SOMEONE happily picks up SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS203
SOMEONE removes her sunglasses, and smiles lovingly at SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS204
Beside her, SOMEONE takes off her shades and regards him with a fond gaze.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS205
SOMEONE drops SOMEONE in the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS206
SOMEONE urges SOMEONE to intervene.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS207
SOMEONE shoves SOMEONE into the pool.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS208
He jumps in the water, dunks her and holds her under.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS209
He lets SOMEONE up, and she splashes him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS210
In SOMEONE's suite, he talks on the phone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS211
SOMEONE emerges from the bathroom, wrapped in a towel. Reclining on a sofa, SOMEONE struggles to sit up.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS212
SOMEONE drops her towel. SOMEONE tosses an apple between his hands.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS213
He resumes his call.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS214
SOMEONE enters the bathroom. In the shower, SOMEONE dances and lip-syncs.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS215
He switches off the music.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS216
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE, eating a mango she thrusts the phone at him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS217
She smacks him.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS218
He ends the call.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS219
She gestures to the bathroom, where a pillow and a blanket sit in the tub.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS220
Now at an upscale restaurant, a woman gracefully hula dances to music by a live band. At a table, SOMEONE scrutinizes a wine list.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS221
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pout and rub noses.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS222
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE staring at his lap. She receives a text from him reading, I think they took one of your yellow bombers.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS223
Glancing at the couple, she suppresses a grin. SOMEONE receives her reply. I just hope their noses are clean.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS224
Now a hybrid car pulls up to a dilapidated outdoor barbecue restaurant.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS225
At dinner, SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap a look.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS226
The waitress pours wine.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS227
SOMEONE gapes.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS228
He faces SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS229
They rub their noses together.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS230
SOMEONE leaves.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS231
With SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS232
The local girl leads them around back.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS233
A crowd gathers. SOMEONE nervously approaches the white sheep, which lies on its side. He pokes it a few times.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS234
With SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS235
SOMEONE mockingly mimes an overbite.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS236
Gazing into his eyes, SOMEONE softly nods.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS237
SOMEONE meets her gaze, and nods as well.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS238
SOMEONE and SOMEONE shift in their seats. Meanwhile, SOMEONE waves the limp sheep's legs.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS239
He shoves hay in its mouth and grabs her udder.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS240
He does CPR.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS241
He drops his elbow into its belly.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS242
He tries the Heimlich maneuver.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS243
A plastic fish pops out, and the sheep walks away.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS244
The girl hugs SOMEONE, then he gives her the Heimlich maneuver.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS245
SOMEONE downs a shot.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS246
She downs another.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS248
SOMEONE leads a group of ladies in bra tops and grass skirts.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS249
SOMEONE re-positions herself center-stage in front of her rival. The ladies start to dance.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS250
He holds his hand over an elderly woman.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS251
As he guides her off stage, SOMEONE gives her a hug.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS252
Tanner highlights SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS253
He moves on to SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS254
A heavy-set woman shimmies in a coconut top.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS255
She storms off. Only SOMEONE and SOMEONE remain.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS256
SOMEONE raises her arms overhead and shakes her hips.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS257
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE, then matches her hip action. SOMEONE glares.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS258
The tall redhead shakes her head and circles her bent arms, then points to SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS259
SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE, who gestures forward to show off her own moves. She shrugs her shoulders, then does a break dancing arm wave, and stops facing SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS260
SOMEONE opens his arms. SOMEONE glances at her opponent, then breaks into a lively Charleston, kicking up her heels. She twirls like a ballerina, then points back to SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS261
SOMEONE lowers her center of gravity, then mimes as though she were juggling. She juggles pretend balls behind her back, catches them in her bosom and throws one to SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS262
SOMEONE watches her rival. With her back to the crowd, SOMEONE gyrates her rear. Slow at first, then faster, and faster.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS263
SOMEONE does the same, until SOMEONE does an aerial cartwheel, twirls and drops into a split.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS264
She raises her arm in a final pose.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS265
SOMEONE hulas in front of SOMEONE, then shakes her hips while raising her arms overhead.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS266
SOMEONE pushes SOMEONE out of the way and poses again. She gets up and blows SOMEONE kisses.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS268
SOMEONE flashes her rear, and all of the men stand up.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS269
SOMEONE grabs the mic.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS270
Later, each couple holds a coconut between them.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS271
Both couples struggle to raise their coconuts above their bellies.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS272
SOMEONE kneels, resting the coconut at SOMEONE's waist on her cleavage.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS273
SOMEONE's chin holds the coconut at SOMEONE's crotch.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS274
SOMEONE and SOMEONE bring their coconut up to their chests.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS275
SOMEONE and SOMEONE drop their coconut on the floor.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS276
SOMEONE lowers his butt over the coconut.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS277
He lifts the coconut off of the floor.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS278
He waddles around, then lifts his backside to SOMEONE's waist.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS279
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold their coconut between their necks.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS280
With their mouth under their coconut, SOMEONE pushes it up to SOMEONE's lips.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS281
SOMEONE drops hers. With their eyes locked, SOMEONE and SOMEONE let their coconut fall.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS282
SOMEONE storms off.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS283
SOMEONE follows.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS285
At SOMEONE's door.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS286
He wags his finger at his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS287
SOMEONE jolts, then hugs her kids.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS288
An obese woman sleeps on a couch.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS289
They shake hands.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS290
As SOMEONE walks away, SOMEONE slowly shuts the door to her suite.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS291
Now SOMEONE steps off of an elevator and crosses a hallway, with his hand shoved in his pockets.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS292
At the end of another hall, he reaches the door to his own suite and stops.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS293
Rounding a corner, he breaks into a run. SOMEONE jogs back to the elevators and presses the call button.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS294
SOMEONE and SOMEONE step out.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS295
SOMEONE points to his ring finger.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS296
The elevator opens and SOMEONE freezes.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS297
She shares a gaze with SOMEONE as the elevator doors close.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS298
Later, we drift over a bed, to find SOMEONE lying alone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS299
Staring thoughtfully, he fondles his wedding ring between his fingertips.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS300
In the next room, SOMEONE tries on short white dresses while chatting on the phone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS301
Elsewhere, SOMEONE lies awake in bed. She restlessly wipes her nose, and flips on her other side.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS302
In the bathroom, SOMEONE sleeps in the cramped tub.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS303
As he turns on his side, his left hand lands in the toilet.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS304
Later, SOMEONE lies sound asleep, resting her head on SOMEONE's shoulder.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS305
He remains awake, staring blankly across the room.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS306
SOMEONE lies awake in bed. SOMEONE rests beside her.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS307
The brown-haired girl takes her mother's hand and rests her head on SOMEONE's pillow.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS308
Half asleep, SOMEONE ambles into the bathroom, where SOMEONE still sleeps with his hand in the toilet.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS309
The bed-headed boy drops his shorts, then sits on the bowl hunched forward with his arms dangling between his knees.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS310
SOMEONE wakes, noticing his hand, and yanks it out of the bowl.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS311
He grabs a towel and wraps his arm.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS312
He storms out past the boy.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS313
Later, SOMEONE steps outside. Surrounded by tropical plants and lit candles, he makes a call on a portable phone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS314
SOMEONE answers a bedside phone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS315
SOMEONE shakes his head.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS316
SOMEONE pensively rubs his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS317
Perched on the edge of a hot tub, SOMEONE stares ahead and lowers the phone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS318
Now silhouetted against the moonlit ocean, a pod of dolphins leap from the water.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS320
In the lobby, SOMEONE faces the concierge.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS321
SOMEONE arrives nearby.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS322
The blonde approaches wearing a white dress and a magnolia in her hair.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS323
As SOMEONE hugs her, SOMEONE spies SOMEONE helping her kids pick out clothes in a gift shop.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS324
She watches him with wistful lovelorn gaze.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS325
Now in an outdoor beachfront bar, SOMEONE finishes off a tropical cocktail, as the bartender brings her another.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS326
SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS327
SOMEONE sips a cocktail.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS328
SOMEONE regards her with a sober frown.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS329
SOMEONE shrugs her hand.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS330
SOMEONE checks up sailors.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS331
Across the bar, SOMEONE clownishly hula dances for the sailors.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS332
The two women hug.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS333
SOMEONE sits next to them.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS334
SOMEONE doubles over laughing with the sailors.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS335
He cocks his head patiently.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS336
SOMEONE tilts his head and grins. Beaming, SOMEONE shakes her head fondly.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS337
Her old friend gives a small nod. Leaning in, she gives him a passionate kiss.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS338
The sailors and SOMEONE watch.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS339
Now in a life-vest, SOMEONE faces a dolphin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS340
Two push him through the water with their noses.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS341
On an airplane.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS342
Now at a wedding reception.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS343
SOMEONE sits alone.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS344
SOMEONE leads him to the dance floor. Nearby, SOMEONE clownishly poses for photos with a gaggle of attractive young women.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS345
Slow dancing with his wife, SOMEONE eyes the stage.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS346
SOMEONE sports a long soul patch. SOMEONE wags his finger from his chin.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS347
SOMEONE grimaces as he plays. His inches long pillar of facial hair waving in a breeze. He makes the gesture again.
JUST_GO_WITH_IT_DVS348
Grinning, SOMEONE pulls him close. The couple sways happily in unison as their friends and loved ones celebrate around them.