SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a bemused frown.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS14
Muffled click.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS15
In the ward, a male nurse tends to a burly patient on his side.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS16
SOMEONE's gloved hand twist the tube.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS17
SOMEONE frowns.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS18
Where SOMEONE and SOMEONE sanitize their hands.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS19
They bump fists.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS20
Now at the SOMEONE' two-story colonial, a red family crest hangs in SOMEONE's basement layer. It reads, Certavi et Vici Byrnes. A framed photo shows SOMEONE with a Bedouin, dressed as a Bedouin. In another, he shoulder-to-shoulder with President SOMEONE W. Bush. Sepia-toned photo shows dates, men, and officers resembling SOMEONE. A shelf holds books on genealogy. On a bulletin board, headshots form a smartly right-angled family tree. SOMEONE frowns at photos of Deborah Banks and Dr. Robert Banks.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS21
He takes down Robert's photo. Now in their bedroom, SOMEONE packs a suitcase.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS22
Holds his chest but quickly smiles.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS23
Now as SOMEONE drives, his cell reads incoming call. Mom Focker.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS24
On a studio. The Bohemian mother talks on the phone.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS25
SOMEONE tosses earpiece aside. In his layer, SOMEONE honkers at his desk.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS26
Using an X-ACTO knife, he neatly cuts a wedding picture of Dr. SOMEONE and SOMEONE down the middle. He folds Dr. SOMEONE's half, tears it in two, and shoves it in a wastebasket. Eyeing SOMEONE's photo, the ex-CIA agent rubs his chest.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS27
He places two fingers alongside his carotid.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS28
As his Siamese cat eyes him from a footstool, SOMEONE dials his cellphone.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS29
SOMEONE turns on his polygraph machine then tears open his button down.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS31
The cat observes.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS32
SOMEONE Skypes them from a yacht.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS33
Bikini clog beauty approaches SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS34
Nuzzling and kissing him.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS35
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE give the departing hottie a playful smack on the rear.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS36
SOMEONE's lasagna.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS37
SOMEONE glances at his family.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS38
He enters a bedroom.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS39
SOMEONE swivels in his chair.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS40
SOMEONE lifts his brow.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS41
He points to a photo of SOMEONE on the family tree.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS42
SOMEONE shifts his thoughtful gaze.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS43
We view him through window blinds.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS44
He stares unflinchingly.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS45
Gazing out the window, SOMEONE lowers his phone. With a strange smile, he strolls back into the kitchen where SOMEONE looks over.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS46
He lifts her brow.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS47
SOMEONE eyes his daughter.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS48
Chewing her food, she turns away. SOMEONE shifts his gaze to his son, SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS49
He looks up.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS50
With a calm look, SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE, his hands folded.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS51
SOMEONE holds up quieting fingers.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS52
SOMEONE closes her mouth.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS53
He eyes him firmly.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS54
SOMEONE takes a small bite.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS55
As SOMEONE gives a satisfied look, SOMEONE vomits.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS56
Daytime, puffy clouds.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS59
Its window, he opens it then jogs across the street to the SOMEONE' car.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS60
With one hand on SOMEONE's waist and the other on his neck, SOMEONE kisses both of the older man's cheeks.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS61
He slaps his hands to SOMEONE's face and kisses him again.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS62
Later at the dinner table.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS63
SOMEONE picks up his glass.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS64
He winks at SOMEONE then leaves.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS65
He takes it out.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS66
SOMEONE's smile disappears.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS67
As he carves, SOMEONE peeks over the table.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS68
SOMEONE winces as SOMEONE mangles the bird.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS70
SOMEONE takes his hand. SOMEONE places his other one over it.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS71
SOMEONE gazes at her.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS72
SOMEONE and SOMEONE turn to SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS73
He squeezes the back of SOMEONE's neck and the boy goes limp, his eyes closed.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS74
He sets him on the couch.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS75
SOMEONE sets a hand on SOMEONE's other shoulder.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS76
They both pat his face.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS77
Morning, SOMEONE feels SOMEONE's flushed brow as she lies in bed.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS78
He and SOMEONE drive into the city.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS79
SOMEONE rumples his lips into a frown.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS80
SOMEONE's face hardens.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS81
Now, a handful of children play in the courtyard of a glass-paneled building. Inside an auditorium, a blonde woman grins at the audience as she strolls on stage.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS82
A slide show starts.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS83
A photo shows surgeons.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS84
Children sketch a shirtless model.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS85
In the courtyard, young children in cheerleading uniforms do backflip.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS86
They give confused looks.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS87
Their smiles fade.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS88
Later, they pull up to the new house where some construction workers take a break in the yard. A dump truck of sand sits in the driveway.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS89
An orange sports car zooms past
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS90
Then swings into a U-turn and parks behind SOMEONE's car. SOMEONE climbs out.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS91
He hops at the bottom of the drive.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS92
He hits door, sand cascades onto SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS93
SOMEONE race over.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS94
He supports SOMEONE's head.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS95
SOMEONE glares.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS96
Later, SOMEONE swabs his ears.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS97
SOMEONE touches his cheek.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS98
SOMEONE returns to the phone.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS99
SOMEONE listens from under the bed.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS100
Later, SOMEONE sits with her as she pretends to shoot green toy soldiers with tan ones.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS101
SOMEONE nods.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS102
SOMEONE's eyes shift.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS103
Later, SOMEONE arrives at home.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS104
Sees SOMEONE stow a bag in a closet.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS105
As SOMEONE hurries down the hall, SOMEONE glares after him. On a table, SOMEONE's phone vibrates. Turning to it, SOMEONE reads a text from SOMEONE, Can't wait to see you at the hotel tonight. Later SOMEONE walks outside, his briefcase clutched in one hand. SOMEONE sneaks after him, disguised in a windbreaker and bucket hat. As SOMEONE glances back, his father-in-law steps into some shadows.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS107
SOMEONE peers back around the corner.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS112
Frowning, SOMEONE sticks his head outside and glances up and down the platform.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS115
Door to SOMEONE's train car, SOMEONE steps inside.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS116
SOMEONE appears behind him.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS117
Turns around.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS118
He stares at SOMEONE, who gives a halfhearted smile.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS121
They enter a convention room.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS122
Narrowing his eyes, SOMEONE shifts them mischievously.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS123
At the apartment, SOMEONE turns on a light in the coat closet. He crouches then inspects SOMEONE's hidden bag. With a furrowed brow, he finds pamphlets for Sustengo then removes a sample box.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS124
As he reads it, SOMEONE creeps up behind him wearing a trench coat over a negligee.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS125
She kisses his cheek.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS126
She unzips his jacket and he frowns.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS127
She kisses her finger then blows him the kiss. As she leaves, SOMEONE eyes the sample box of Sustengo. Now at a bar, three doctors approach SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS128
He strolls over.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS129
He wanders over to the bar.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS130
SOMEONE lifts his gaze to SOMEONE's face.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS131
SOMEONE gives a nod and SOMEONE looks away. Later, SOMEONE opens the apartment door and steps into the dark living room.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS132
As he slides off his coat, a lamp shines its light on him. SOMEONE sits in an armchair beside it.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS133
SOMEONE shields his eyes.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS134
SOMEONE holds up the box of Sustengo.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS135
SOMEONE brightens the light.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS136
SOMEONE hangs up his coat.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS137
As SOMEONE rises, SOMEONE stops and turns to him. He points to SOMEONE's crotch.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS138
SOMEONE steps closer.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS139
In the bathroom, SOMEONE pulls on Latex gloves then opens the needle and syringe.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS140
He gestures at the bulge in SOMEONE's pants.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS141
His shoulders heave as he reaches toward SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS142
As he readies the needle, two slippered feet walk down the hall.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS143
SOMEONE heads to the bathroom. He holds the knob.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS145
He congests himself as he walks down the hall toward SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS146
He gives two thumbs up then heads away. SOMEONE looks at her mother and winces.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS147
Now, SOMEONE tucks SOMEONE in.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS148
SOMEONE lets SOMEONE shut the door then enters anyway.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS149
SOMEONE stands by.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS150
SOMEONE glowers.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS151
Later in the hallway, SOMEONE gently shuts SOMEONE's door.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS152
Without breaking eye contact, the two men circle. SOMEONE gives a mock scowl. He and SOMEONE back away from each other.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS153
SOMEONE tauntingly shrugs his hands apart. SOMEONE does the same. SOMEONE repeats the gesture. Then they go their separate ways.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS154
Daytime, SOMEONE peers out the cracked open door of the guest bedroom while on his cell.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS155
He glances back.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS156
Later at a computer, SOMEONE types A-N-D-I-G-A-R-C-I-A into the Google search field and gets back image results and links for the handsome dark-haired actor. He adds the keyword, Chicago and finds a link to a Myspace profile. Leaning in, SOMEONE opens the zebra print page then scrolls down to find the photo of SOMEONE kissing SOMEONE on the cheek. The retired CIA man reads the caption, "Crazy night at the Hilton. " He minimizes the page as SOMEONE enters.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS158
SOMEONE joins the rest of the family. SOMEONE checks his watch.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS159
SOMEONE gives them a kiss.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS161
The vehicles park and they step out.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS162
SOMEONE lifts his shirt to reveal his lower back. The other study a large tattoo of SOMEONE's smiling face above the banner, forever.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS163
It's only half of SOMEONE's face.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS164
Later in SOMEONE's office.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS165
They swap an icy look.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS166
Now, SOMEONE sits in an easel.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS167
The family watches behind a mirrored window.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS168
She shows SOMEONE a phony eye chart.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS169
SOMEONE starts the timer.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS170
Back at the easel.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS171
SOMEONE recoils.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS172
A stick figure holds a syringe to another's penis.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS173
SOMEONE frowns.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS174
SOMEONE smiles proudly toward the mirrored window. SOMEONE gapes.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS176
On the playground. They spot a surveillance camera. The boy glares at his dad.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS179
SOMEONE beams.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS180
Now, SOMEONE approaches the nurses' station.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS181
SOMEONE pulls him aside.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS183
Back in the hall. SOMEONE emerges.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS184
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE, who holds an arm around SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS185
SOMEONE presses the elevator button.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS188
He park at the new house's driveway.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS190
She leaves and SOMEONE stares ahead.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS191
Now in the new house, SOMEONE stands alone in the middle of an unfinished room. SOMEONE turns away from a three-foot hole in the wall and crosses to the front door, where he finds SOMEONE with a bottle of wine.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS198
Meanwhile, SOMEONE's car arrives out front.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS199
The retired CIA agent gets out and marches gravely toward the house.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS200
Glancing aside, he pauses and stares. His flashlight beam hits the license plate of SOMEONE's convertible. It reads, "RX GRRRL. "
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS201
Killing his light, SOMEONE creeps around toward the side of the house.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS203
As SOMEONE moves through the shadows outside, SOMEONE takes off her blouse.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS204
SOMEONE pounces on him. Outside, SOMEONE pauses and turns. Finding a bay window, he steps close and peeks in. He sees SOMEONE in her bra and skirt.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS206
Her arms and legs wrapped around SOMEONE as she smothers him with kisses. His hands clenching her waist. He spins around the room erratically. SOMEONE looks away. His gaze heartbroken. He backs away from the window. He licks his lips, presses them tight, and leaves. Inside, lands - they knock heads - cut to black.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS207
His legs clad in white pants.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS208
In the pit, SOMEONE snores under SOMEONE. His eyes blink open and he gets his bearings. As SOMEONE arrives out back, SOMEONE's hand slaps down on the pit's rim.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS209
Straining with effort, he pulls himself up.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS210
SOMEONE stares and points at her.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS211
At the birthday party.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS213
SOMEONE nods.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS214
SOMEONE frowns.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS216
SOMEONE leaves his car with the valet. A monk greets him.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS217
Approach chauffeured carts. Passing a valet stand, SOMEONE pauses to dance.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS218
He's off in a cart. SOMEONE stretches his quadriceps.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS219
Clinging by his legs, he opens his arms.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS220
SOMEONE turns and sees SOMEONE approaching.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS221
SOMEONE grins.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS223
SOMEONE opens a shoebox.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS224
Kissing as the twins hug them.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS225
He starts to cry. His tears landing on the stage below.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS226
He gets dizzily to his feet.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS227
As he hobbles off, a boy offers him his cotton candy. SOMEONE takes it and goes to a tent.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS228
Roz peeks inside and finds him sitting pensively.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS229
Now, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE, who sits.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS230
SOMEONE lifts his chin.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS231
SOMEONE eyes the drawing.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS232
SOMEONE scowls, holding a balloon.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS233
With a smile, he holds out a plate of cake. SOMEONE punches him in the nose.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS234
He punches him again.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS235
SOMEONE blocks a strike then hits SOMEONE in the face.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS236
SOMEONE slides off his jacket.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS237
Pump his fists.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS238
He punches him then beckons.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS239
Removes his sweatshirt.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS240
SOMEONE raises his fists and the two men face off. As SOMEONE throws a punch, SOMEONE blocks him.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS241
To push him away. The older man flings him into a giant ball pit. SOMEONE disappears below the balls.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS243
He glances around but sees only the playing
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS244
Behind him move then stop as he whip
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS245
They shift in another part of the pit.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS246
SOMEONE notices and stares with intense eyes.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS249
Other balls shift and SOMEONE turns to them.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS250
Behind him, SOMEONE burst through the surface.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS251
Punches him. He grabs his son-in-law.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS253
Pulled over, SOMEONE kicks his leg back and hits again to a bouncy castle.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS255
Meanwhile, SOMEONE looks in the shoebox.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS256
In the grass, SOMEONE faces Jinx, who stares at him. The cat licks its lips then advances.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS257
He sniffs the lizard. Now, SOMEONE throws himself
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS259
Dangling for Jinx's mouth.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS260
As SOMEONE races past him after the cat, SOMEONE stops. His chest heaving.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS261
He stretches his shoulders back.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS262
Meanwhile, SOMEONE kisses her.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS264
SOMEONE lowers his arms.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS265
Outside, SOMEONE races after Jinx. He stops. SOMEONE lies on the ground clutching his chest. She sprints over.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS267
His cat approaching.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS268
Pushing the cat's stomach like the Heimlich maneuver, he forces the lizard out.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS269
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE and SOMEONE returns his gaze to SOMEONE.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS270
He rubs SOMEONE's shoulder.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS271
Later, Medics wheel SOMEONE to an ambulance.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS272
He gives SOMEONE a look.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS273
SOMEONE winks.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS274
In the ambulance.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS275
Again looks at SOMEONE. SOMEONE replaces the mask.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS278
He smiles as he holds SOMEONE's gaze.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS279
He pats SOMEONE's cheek. His smile growing wider.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS280
SOMEONE gives him a tender look.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS281
SOMEONE winks at him.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS282
They lift the stretcher into their ridge.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS284
Now, snowfalls onto a group of SOMEONEers. Words appear, "Four Months Later. "
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS286
SOMEONE frowns.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS287
He lifts his leg.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS288
Now in his basement lair, SOMEONE types on a computer.
LITTLE_FOCKERS_DVS289
As Jinx looks on, SOMEONE types his name into a Google search window. He trails his cursor over the search results then selects a YouTube video. It's title, Nurse Rags on Psycho Father-in-Law. The image loads up showing SOMEONE speaking at the medical convention. SOMEONE scowls. The video plays.