SOMEONE drives through dark streets and pulls into a car park.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS19
Morning Glory.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS20
SOMEONE hurries into a building. She walks down a corridor.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS21
She talks manically in a meeting.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS22
The meeting room is behind a studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS23
A guy in the meeting has fallen asleep in front of his computer.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS24
SOMEONE chuckles with one of her colleagues. A female presenter, SOMEONE, yawns and sits at a desk in the studio. A male presenter, Ralph Pollard, sits next to her and a make-up artist brushes him with powder.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS25
SOMEONE has headphones around her neck. She listens to one of them.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS26
Staff listen to headphones and watch screens.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS31
In the studio, SOMEONE has fallen asleep.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS32
SOMEONE holds a headphone to her ear.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS33
SOMEONE wakes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS34
A floor manager threw Post-It notes at her to wake her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS35
In the staff kitchen, SOMEONE gulps. In an office,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS36
her friend that told her the news, SOMEONE leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS37
The female presenter, SOMEONE, is onscreen.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS38
A guy in the gallery directs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS39
The studio, now empty, SOMEONE stands in it with a pile of papers in one hand and two mugs in the other.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS40
She smiles and turns to leave.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS41
SOMEONE takes a t-shirt from a gift bag.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS42
It's a red t-shirt with the words, Yes, I accept in white. SOMEONE puts it on under a denim jacket.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS43
In her boss's office,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS44
tears well in her eyes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS45
SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE. Her and other ex-colleagues are wearing Way to go, SOMEONE t-shirts. At her mum's.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS46
SOMEONE lowers her gaze. She nods miserably.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS47
SOMEONE's sitting in bed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS48
Her alarm goes off at 1:30.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS49
She hugs her knees, then folds her arms across her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS50
She fidgets and stares into space.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS51
She switches on the TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS52
She switches on another TV. On the phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS53
In a diner.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS54
In the park.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS55
Now dressed in a suit, SOMEONE runs off a bus towards a ferry.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS56
On the other side of the river lies New York City.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS57
She walks through the smart IBS high rise with a tall, lean guy,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS58
SOMEONE SOMEONE
MORNING_GLORY_DVS59
She balls her fists.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS60
He eyes her wryly. She balls her fists tighter.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS61
SOMEONE looks down,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS62
then smiles sadly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS63
She gets up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS64
She opens the door and leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS65
Wearing a mournful expression, she trudges down a hallway and into a lift.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS67
A fair-haired guy of about 30 walks in behind her, glances at her,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS68
then turns to the lift buttons and push it.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS69
He presses the button.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS70
As the lift doors are closing, a man jams his arms in the doors and pushes them open.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS71
SOMEONE watches the guy get into the lift.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS72
He's in his 60s and wears black-rimmed specs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS73
SOMEONE gawps at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS74
She puts her hand on her heart.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS75
The two guys get out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS76
SOMEONE jams her arm in the doors to stop them from closing.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS77
She strolls along the street outside, her shoulders hunched.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS78
She throws a bit of paper into a bin.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS79
She takes a call on her mobile.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS80
She hangs up the phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS81
She jumps in the air. Pigeons fly off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS82
Sped-up footage. She packs up her apartment until it's completely empty.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS83
She carries the last things into the removal truck and closes the door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS84
She jogs out of a subway in New York.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS85
She runs across a busy road towards IBS.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS86
The skyscraper is white with large, dark windows.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS87
Inside, SOMEONE waits on a bench in the wood-paneled reception area. There's a smart, gold desk.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS88
The attendant is watching a small TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS89
He smirks.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS90
Then he takes SOMEONE's mug and goes. SOMEONE straightens up her fridge and knocks on a door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS91
The door handle comes off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS92
They smile.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS93
SOMEONE smiles uncertainly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS94
She raises her brows.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS95
SOMEONE glances around at everyone talking at once.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS96
SOMEONE licks her lips and turns to SOMEONE with interest. SOMEONE grins. SOMEONE frowns and pauses. She looks up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS97
SOMEONE heads off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS98
He steps back into the room.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS99
She hits the table. SOMEONE loses his smirk and stares sourly at her. She holds his gaze.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS100
A member of staff takes a photo on his phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS101
SOMEONE leaves. The others gape at her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS102
SOMEONE giggles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS104
SOMEONE walks off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS105
SOMEONE hurries along the street. She dials on her mobile, then holds it to her ear.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS106
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch a horse-faced news anchor on TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS107
She glances at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS108
SOMEONE's heading out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS109
She has a box of tapes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS110
SOMEONE rolls his eyes sardonically as he turns to camera.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS111
A woman is waiting for SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS112
SOMEONE stares at her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS113
SOMEONE sits at a bench outside. She's eating a salad and going through the contract with a marker pen.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS114
Her brow is furrowed with intense concentration.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS115
She lifts the contract and highlights a line.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS116
She strides across long grass.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS117
A man stands on the crest of the hill she's climbing with a shotgun in his hands.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS118
She stops just short of him,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS120
throws her arms out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS121
He turns to her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS122
SOMEONE shoots two pheasants flying above the trees. SOMEONE claps her hands over her ears
MORNING_GLORY_DVS123
then follows SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS124
SOMEONE beams. Frowning, SOMEONE stares, lines showing on his forehead.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS125
SOMEONE smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS126
He walks off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS128
they stare.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS129
SOMEONE steps slowly across the studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS130
SOMEONE stands at the other side of it, his hand in his pockets, gazing down at the floor.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS131
SOMEONE raises his brows.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS132
She nods.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS133
She smiles and turns back to the rest of the studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS134
They change the name on SOMEONE's dressing room and paint over the huge poster of him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS135
They walk through the office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS136
A fruit plate
MORNING_GLORY_DVS137
He hands her an orchid.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS138
He picks up a newspaper and sits down.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS139
SOMEONE takes the orchid to SOMEONE's dressing room and knocks.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS140
SOMEONE sets down the flower.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS141
SOMEONE tosses a card aside.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS142
SOMEONE goes from one dressing room to the other.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS143
SOMEONE marches from one end of the corridor to the other, then finds the central point.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS144
SOMEONE and SOMEONE meet
MORNING_GLORY_DVS145
in the middle.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS146
SOMEONE stares at her blankly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS147
SOMEONE goes into his room and slams the door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS148
SOMEONE marches off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS149
SOMEONE and SOMEONE on a photo shoot.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS150
SOMEONE hands his specs to an assistant.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS151
They smile and pose. SOMEONE links her arm through his.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS152
She takes off her jacket.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS153
They stand close.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS154
SOMEONE walks through the office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS156
She stares at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS157
SOMEONE tries to suppress giggles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS158
Everyone turns to look at SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS159
SOMEONE smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS160
SOMEONE smiles anxiously.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS161
SOMEONE plays with her fringe nervously. SOMEONE chucks an apple core past her into a bin.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS162
SOMEONE saunters off casually.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS163
SOMEONE runs up steps.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS164
He glares.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS165
He screams silently. She heads a meeting outside.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS166
It's SOMEONE. He points at SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS167
SOMEONE grins and waves,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS168
then heads off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS169
SOMEONE covers her face.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS170
SOMEONE drinks a glass of beer at a bar and chats to a friend.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS171
SOMEONE enters the bar.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS172
She poses and looks over at SOMEONE who turns.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS174
and notices her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS175
She waves
MORNING_GLORY_DVS176
and accidentally throws her phone up in the air.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS177
In a booth
MORNING_GLORY_DVS178
a tall, slender blonde kisses him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS179
SOMEONE sinks back into his seat and the woman leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS180
SOMEONE frowns with confusion as SOMEONE hurries off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS181
He comes out of the bar
MORNING_GLORY_DVS182
and presses herself against the wall in shame.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS184
At the studio
MORNING_GLORY_DVS185
he gets up and walks off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS186
SOMEONE watches TV in his dressing room.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS187
SOMEONE has a notebook.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS188
He's drinking whisky.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS189
He stands up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS190
On TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS191
SOMEONE backs out of SOMEONE's dressing room.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS192
In the toilet, she bangs her head against the dryer.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS193
She stops and turns to regard herself in the mirror.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS194
She tidies up her fringe.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS195
She makes her way through a large, open-plan office. The sign reads, IBS News.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS196
She sidles along, peering into a private office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS197
In the office, SOMEONE sits at a desk.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS198
She pulls the door closed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS199
She's sitting on a sofa. She bangs her head on a lamp above her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS200
She puts down two heavy bags.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS201
She mimes rowing.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS202
Her goofy smile fades.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS203
In a large, plush apartment, SOMEONE and SOMEONE make out. He leans her over a worktop.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS204
She checks her watch.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS205
SOMEONE's taken her skirt off. They roll over the back of the couch onto it. Suddenly, SOMEONE pulls back.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS206
SOMEONE eyes her dubiously. She looks at him sharply.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS207
She grabs her bags and runs out without her skirt on.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS208
She grabs her bags and runs out without her skirt on. without her skirt on.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS209
SOMEONE picks up her skirt
MORNING_GLORY_DVS210
and waits for her to run back.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS211
She kisses him and leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS212
SOMEONE asks a tubby, middle-aged woman sitting at the bar in her lines.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS213
She comes out onto the dark streets where several musicians are basking.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS214
Next she visits the Algonquin.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS215
As she runs out, a model is being photographed at the entrance.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS216
She runs out of another cocktail lounge, then another bar just as two guys are thrown out into the street.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS217
She pulls open the doors of the 21 Club in Manhattan.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS218
She walks into the wood-paneled bar and spots SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS219
She takes a deep breath and heads towards him with a look of grim determination.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS220
She raises her brows.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS221
She shoves him into a taxi.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS222
The taxi drives off without her. It pulls up outside an apartment building.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS223
They walk slowly into SOMEONE's dark apartment.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS224
SOMEONE walks through different rooms in the huge apartment.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS225
SOMEONE walks through a dark room towards another lamp lit room.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS226
He eats a nut.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS227
He wanders off through the dark apartment as she sets up her laptop.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS228
He stops and turns back to wish her goodnight.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS230
SOMEONE sits on the sofa in front of her laptop.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS231
Later she dozes in front of it.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS232
She nods off, but awakens as her head drops.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS233
She sits upright again.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS234
She nods off again.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS235
She opens her eyes and blinks. Her vision is blurred.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS236
She falls asleep once more.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS237
She collapses over onto the sofa.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS238
SOMEONE stands over her with a rain stick which makes the sound reminiscent of rain.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS239
SOMEONE wakes with a start.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS240
SOMEONE's wearing a cream dressing gown.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS241
He plods off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS242
SOMEONE buries her head in a cushion then sits upright.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS243
She races into the kitchen.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS245
He's whisking eggs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS246
They head into the Daybreak offices.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS247
The cast and crew all gawp at her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS248
SOMEONE grins sheepishly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS249
The crew sits in the gallery with their headphones on.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS250
SOMEONE grins irritated.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS251
SOMEONE and SOMEONE in the studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS252
SOMEONE shrugs on air.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS254
The caption, Sexual Offender, remained under the photo of SOMEONE SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS255
SOMEONE stares into the distance wearily.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS256
SOMEONE watches Daybreak in his office. The attendant at the reception desk has it on his small TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS257
They both gaze into the camera.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS258
SOMEONE's smile vanishes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS259
SOMEONE gets up and heads off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS261
He's getting his shoes shined.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS262
SOMEONE storms off, throwing her arms out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS263
Dusk falls over New York.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS264
SOMEONE opens his front door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS265
She grabs him and kisses him hard.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS266
She wraps her arms around his neck and they make out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS267
She reaches into her pocket for her phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS268
He grabs it.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS269
He won't let her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS270
He puts it in the fridge.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS271
He carries her into his bedroom.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS272
SOMEONE wakes. SOMEONE isn't there.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS273
He sits up and eyes the empty space in his bed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS274
He goes into the living room where SOMEONE is watching the news and typing on her laptop.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS275
He smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS276
She shifts and looks at him uncertainly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS277
SOMEONE smiles gleefully. She picks up her laptop and jogs off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS278
She stops
MORNING_GLORY_DVS279
and goes back to SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS280
She kisses him tenderly on the lips and heads off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS281
It's dark with the first wisps of pink morning light as SOMEONE strides over a bridge.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS282
The moon still shines in the sky.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS283
SOMEONE sits in the Daybreak office and smiles to herself,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS284
fiddling with a strand of hair.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS285
SOMEONE glances up at her as she gazes ahead,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS286
a wistful smile on her face.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS287
He grins to himself.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS288
She shrugs at him and he mocks her gesture.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS290
She slams her hands on the table.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS291
SOMEONE's on the phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS292
They walk along the street.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS294
She took a photo.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS295
SOMEONE scowls, then turns away.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS296
On air,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS297
SOMEONE points upwards.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS298
A guy delivers a note to SOMEONE. She glances disapprovingly at SOMEONE, then reads the note, raises her hand, and points upwards.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS299
She gets up, taking a flask with her. In SOMEONE's office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS300
She cocks her head.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS301
SOMEONE frowns.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS302
Horrified, SOMEONE sits down.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS303
SOMEONE takes off his glasses and throws them down. SOMEONE gazes down miserably.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS304
Her shoulders sag.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS305
He makes a call.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS306
SOMEONE sits alone on a sofa, going through papers.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS307
On the verge of tears, she rubs her nose.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS308
She puts her hand over her eyes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS309
Onset, a stage manager reads out words to SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS310
She seethes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS312
She storms onto the set.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS313
They watch in the news office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS314
SOMEONE drops down out of the camera shot.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS315
A producer watches in the gallery.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS316
SOMEONE struggles with the door that leads to SOMEONE's office.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS317
She heads out.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS318
SOMEONE's slack-jawed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS319
SOMEONE heads back into the gallery.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS320
SOMEONE looks nervous.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS321
In his office, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE on TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS322
In the studio, SOMEONE cringes. SOMEONE and SOMEONE are glued to the screens.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS323
Watching the TV, the attendant is cracking up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS324
After the show
MORNING_GLORY_DVS325
she stares at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS326
He raises his brows and shoves a pastry into his mouth.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS327
SOMEONE beams.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS328
Live on Daybreak, SOMEONE is dressed in a sumo suit.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS329
Out on the plaza, she wrestles with a real sumo who bashes her repeatedly with his flabby belly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS330
On set
MORNING_GLORY_DVS335
she handles a sugar glider, a raven, and a skunk.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS336
SOMEONE's in a plane.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS337
He jumps out strapped to another guy.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS338
With his mouth stretched open, his cheeks jiggle.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS339
In the studio, SOMEONE slinks down towards the desk with an agonized expression.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS341
She gives the frog a sloppy kiss.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS342
SOMEONE lands, skidding along grass. SOMEONE plays the bagpipes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS343
50 Cent in the Daybreak studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS344
SOMEONE performs with him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS345
SOMEONE and SOMEONE dance in the gallery.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS346
SOMEONE's in an aircraft.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS347
He faints.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS348
His head lolls backwards as he spirals upwards.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS349
She talks to the producer in the corridor. In the studio, SOMEONE is getting a tattoo on his ass.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS350
SOMEONE gawps. SOMEONE's stony faced.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS351
Some papers.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS352
SOMEONE glances down awkwardly.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS353
SOMEONE watches a man screwing on a door handle.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS354
SOMEONE smiles, impressed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS355
SOMEONE's fallen asleep on a couch. SOMEONE throws a pencil at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS356
SOMEONE is jogging. SOMEONE races after him with the ratings.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS357
In a SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS358
To SOMEONE
MORNING_GLORY_DVS359
SOMEONE jogs off. SOMEONE stands there holding the bag, figures and sags.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS360
In SOMEONE's apartment they have dinner together.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS361
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS362
He shakes his head. Then pulls a face.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS363
She switches off the TV.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS364
She looks at graphs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS365
He eyes her gravely.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS366
She carries her plate away.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS367
She leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS369
It's dark. She sits in the back of a taxi and presses her hand to her forehead.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS370
Morning - a golden sky over the silhouetted skyscrapers of Manhattan.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS371
SOMEONE's in his dressing room on the phone.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS372
SOMEONE overhears. SOMEONE shuts his door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS373
Everyone sits back down. SOMEONE removes his spectacles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS374
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE in surprise.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS375
SOMEONE smiles at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS377
She stands by a monument.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS378
An IBS van pulls up and she runs to it.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS379
SOMEONE's in the front.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS380
She gets in the back.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS381
They pull up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS382
SOMEONE, who's striding toward the Colonial-style clapboard country mansion, stops in his tracks.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS383
SOMEONE nods gravely and beckons SOMEONE, the cameraman.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS384
He marches towards the mansion. SOMEONE follows with his camera.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS385
On the phone,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS386
SOMEONE knocks on the Governor's door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS387
The Governor answers the door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS388
He points.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS389
SOMEONE grabs a weather vane.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS390
He trips.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS392
Squad cars pull up outside the mansion.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS393
On air, SOMEONE glances at the squad cars.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS394
Watching, SOMEONE beams.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS395
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on a bench. SOMEONE smokes a cigar.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS396
He frowns thoughtfully.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS397
SOMEONE looks down and shakes her head.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS398
She smiles at him warmly. He nods pensively and gazes ahead.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS399
She meets his gaze directly and he turns in towards her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS400
Her brow pinched, SOMEONE glances down at the ground.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS401
SOMEONE looks down and pinches the material of his trousers nervously.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS402
He gives her a gentle smile, then looks down.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS403
SOMEONE and SOMEONE head back into the Daybreak offices to find the team gathered around a table.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS404
They all stand and clap as the pair enter.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS405
SOMEONE leans over and kisses SOMEONE on the cheek, then wipes off her lipstick SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS406
She sits opposite SOMEONE in his office, as he leafs through graphs and charts.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS407
She eyes him with anticipation wearing a slight smile and raising her brows.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS408
SOMEONE smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS409
She stares in surprise.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS410
Her eyes widen and dart about.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS411
He smiles at her. Her jaw slackens. She looks down. Her eyes flit from side to side.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS412
Their eyes meet.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS413
SOMEONE lowers her gaze again and frowns.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS414
Deep in thought.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS415
SOMEONE drinks in a bar at a table with a group of friends.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS416
They all laugh and joke with one another.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS417
SOMEONE turns to the window with his brow furrowed.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS418
SOMEONE stands gazing in from outside. She smiles at him nervously.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS419
SOMEONE stands on the street outside with SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS420
They sit inside the local bar where they first went for a drink.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS421
She smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS422
SOMEONE nods.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS423
Coming out of IBS.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS424
He glowers at her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS425
SOMEONE fights back tears.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS427
SOMEONE looks down.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS428
He hangs his head, glances up briefly, then walks away, putting on his sunglasses.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS429
SOMEONE stands on the plaza, her chest heaving, her eyes wet with tears.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS430
She turns and heads back towards the entrance of the building.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS431
In the Daybreak offices, she stands in a doorway staring down, and puts her hand on her hip.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS432
A woman approaches carrying a note.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS433
The woman leaves the note with SOMEONE and heads off.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS434
Later, SOMEONE sits on the couch with the note still in her hands.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS435
SOMEONE remembers.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS436
SOMEONE laughs and jokes with a couple of other members of staff.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS437
SOMEONE chats animatedly with colleagues.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS438
One of them throws a screwed up piece of paper at him.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS439
They all smile.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS440
Two members of staff chat and study a piece of paper. SOMEONE walks through the corridor behind them.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS441
He gazes in through the window, his craggy face set in its usual curmudgeonly expression.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS442
SOMEONE shakes her head and looks down at the note in her hands.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS444
SOMEONE stands outside the NBC building and examines the note in her hands.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS445
She looks up at the enormous skyscraper
MORNING_GLORY_DVS446
then heads in.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS447
She heads through the spacious lobby with classical style paintings on the walls
MORNING_GLORY_DVS448
and goes up to the reception desk.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS449
At Daybreak, SOMEONE sighs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS450
SOMEONE stares ahead.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS451
Daybreak plays on the screen in the interview.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS452
He comes into the gallery,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS453
SOMEONE leaves. SOMEONE's bewildered.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS454
He stops at a table of food.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS455
He steals food from a guy's takeaway container.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS456
The interview.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS457
SOMEONE hurries back onto the set with the food.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS458
She eyes the screen.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS459
The interviewers all turn to see SOMEONE breaking eggs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS460
SOMEONE gawps.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS461
He pours in whisked eggs.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS462
He looks into the camera.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS463
On the phone,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS464
SOMEONE nods.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS465
SOMEONE runs through the lobby.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS466
She leaves.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS467
She runs past a huge golden statue by a fountain.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS468
SOMEONE sprinkles salt into the frittata.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS469
SOMEONE grinds pepper onto the frittata.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS470
SOMEONE races up steps and across a plaza filled with trees and plants.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS471
In the gallery,
MORNING_GLORY_DVS472
SOMEONE bends down to pick something up.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS473
SOMEONE races across a road.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS474
SOMEONE opens a large oven on the set.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS475
SOMEONE runs past the IBS building. Pigeons scatter in her wake.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS476
SOMEONE runs a spatula around the edge of the saucepan in which he has cooked the frittata.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS477
SOMEONE steps, light-footed, through the studio.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS478
She wears a pretty, floaty dress.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS479
She stops just off the set and watches SOMEONE
MORNING_GLORY_DVS480
who eventually looks up and spots her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS481
He looks down again
MORNING_GLORY_DVS482
then glances up and smiles.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS483
SOMEONE smiles back. Tears glisten in her eyes.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS484
SOMEONE grins. Her eyes sparkle.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS485
SOMEONE sneaks up behind SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS486
SOMEONE touches his chest gently.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS487
SOMEONE tries his frittata.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS488
SOMEONE beams and nods.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS489
MORNING_GLORY_DVS490
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE who grins cheekily. SOMEONE waves to her from across the studio and she waves back.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS491
SOMEONE presents a gift bag to her friend, SOMEONE.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS492
It's a t-shirt that reads, Welcome to Daybreak.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS493
SOMEONE smiles and hugs her.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS494
SOMEONE ambles along with SOMEONE, chatting.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS495
SOMEONE's mum pins up a newspaper clipping on a notice board that reads Daybreak revitalized.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS496
She smiles proudly, tears in her eyes, and puts her hand over her mouth.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS497
SOMEONE reads a huge dictionary.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS498
A magician with an assistant saws SOMEONE in half.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS499
In SOMEONE's apartment, SOMEONE runs to the fridge
MORNING_GLORY_DVS500
and puts her phone in it.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS501
SOMEONE goes into SOMEONE's dressing room.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS502
He has a hand on her butt
MORNING_GLORY_DVS503
and her hand is over his.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS504
SOMEONE gazes down the corridor
MORNING_GLORY_DVS505
then shuts the door.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS506
A pink sky over New York.
MORNING_GLORY_DVS507
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stroll along together.