The oldest listens intently.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS8
A blonde boy vomits.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS10
They pass a pristine white, estate house.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS11
SOMEONE takes a deep breath.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS12
In a muddy yard a fallen sign reads - Deep Valley.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS13
Fresh plops of manure splat between the cows.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS14
Dirty water gets launched from a barn doorway. Then the farm girl emerges visibly mucking a stall. Her older brother totes buckets
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS16
and the bellows. Flywheels and belts turn an axle.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS17
A horizontal assembly of pipes is shaped like a castle
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS19
The elevator drops down to one and the piglets stand. Now, the children's mother hurries down a narrow road, buttoning a cardigan beneath her inside-out overcoat. On a nearby wall, a coal black jackdaw squawks at her.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS20
It waddles alongside her a few paces then opens its beak.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS21
The bird flies toward her.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS22
She enters a store.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS23
An old woman peeks from behinda counter.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS24
SOMEONE joins her behind the counter.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS25
It's piled waist high.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS26
She appears stuck in a snowdrift of flour.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS27
Now, SOMEONE passes a hedged in path.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS28
He doubles back. A hand seizes him. He faces two platinum blondes - one large, one small.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS29
He tries to climb over the wall, but fails.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS30
Now, a vast field of golden barley wavers gently in a breeze. Standing among the healthy crops, SOMEONE plucks a grain from one of the wispy stalks. He bites a seed, examines it and casts a hopeful gaze toward the sunny sky.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS31
He strolls happily through the barley. Reaching a light blue tractor, he climbs into
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS32
He goes to prop an elbow on his knee, but slips.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS33
SOMEONE rests an arm on the tractor hood.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS34
SOMEONE reaches for the ignition.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS35
SOMEONE jumps, then waves the boy onward.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS36
As his nephew drives the trucktor down the path.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS37
SOMEONE turns away with a calculating gaze.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS38
He marches into the barley field.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS39
His limousine passes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS40
SOMEONE hauls a bucket through the muddy work yard.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS41
The limousine drives past the yard. The three siblings stare.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS42
In unison, the three dash toward the arriving car, short-cutting through the barn.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS43
Now, one of the chauffeur's polished leather shoes steps from the limousine, but halts mid-stride above the mud. He gives in and steps down.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS44
SOMEONE lowers a newspaper.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS45
SOMEONE opens his door.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS46
SOMEONE makes a wild face at her.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS47
In yellow checked knickerbockers, SOMEONE leans foppishly on the car.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS48
He produces a candy bar.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS49
SOMEONE eats the last bite and tosses the wrapper at him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS50
It's boutique boxes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS51
SOMEONE chases him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS52
SOMEONE halts at one of the muddy boxes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS53
He runs after the others. Now at the shop.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS54
The old woman licks her fingers.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS55
She walks away from an apothecary cabinet.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS56
Mrs. SOMEONE enters an adjoining room and shuts the door behind her. Stepping behind the counter, SOMEONE finds syrup dripping from the cabinet drawers, pooling on the floor. Her handbag and green overcoat drop from her grip, landing in the mess. A higher drawer slides open, leaking more syrup.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS57
SOMEONE lifts a foot. Gooey syrup trails stringily from her shoe.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS58
She checks the drawers.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS59
sloshes on her hands.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS60
She slams it shut. From the counter, the SOMEONE watches her as she wearily peeks in another. A third opens high above her.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS61
her way to a shelf where a teapot's lid opens like a mouth.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS62
Tin canisters tip their lids.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS64
The phone lunges on an accordion wall bracket.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS65
Now, SOMEONE enters the farmhouse.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS66
He enters a pantry.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS67
He exits with a jar marked Dad's Jam.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS68
SOMEONE glares. With a sneer, SOMEONE strolls to the table.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS69
He opens it.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS70
The jar falls over the edge.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS71
The Greens watch with wide eyes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS72
SOMEONE gawks at SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS73
SOMEONE faces him and SOMEONE bolts.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS74
Nighttime.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS75
swirl leaves around SOMEONE as she heads home.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS77
makes a mechanical wood carved man pump up and down.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS78
SOMEONE picks a leaf from her
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS80
Spinning SOMEONE as they run by.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS81
SOMEONE headlocks SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS82
SOMEONE extends a hand.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS83
above the house lightening flashes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS86
turning his head with the contract papers.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS87
She shuts the door.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS88
She has one beauty-spot on her chin and one on her upper lip.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS89
She shuts the parlor door.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS90
SOMEONE SOMEONE steps inside.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS91
The SOMEONE slips in just as the door shuts. The SOMEONE regards SOMEONE frankly.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS93
The SOMEONE retreats under SOMEONE's skirt as the
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS95
Golden sparks burst from it. Outside. More radiate outward from the house and dissipate. In the parlor, the kids freeze. SOMEONE smirks.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS98
with her stick. Everything freezes. The bundled letters hovers safely over the flames.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS99
The SOMEONE emerges.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS100
fireplace and grabs the letters.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS101
With the bundle in his talons, Mr. Edelweiss swoops
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS102
the kids who remain frozen in time.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS103
past SOMEONE pinching her own nose and SOMEONE yanking his own tie. With her head tilted, SOMEONE SOMEONE watches as the bird hovers over an end table.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS104
taps the letters. The bird lights on her shoulder.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS105
The bird moves to the floor in front of her.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS106
Hanging his head, the bird trudges away. SOMEONE SOMEONE squints and
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS107
taps her stick. Sparks spray from it and the kids unfreeze. They stare at SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS108
As she eyes them firmly, the parlor door opens behind her.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS109
She steps aside. As SOMEONE and his sister rise from the floor, SOMEONE straightens his tie. The kids file out of the parlor past SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS110
SOMEONE blinks disbelievingly at the well-behaved group.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS111
She watches as they head upstairs.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS112
In the parlor.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS113
She hands him the letters. Glancing at her, he smiles faintly, then turns back to face the room. He finds the elegant dishware unbroken on the table.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS114
The candy dish sits by, perfectly intact. The unharmed tractor drawing rests on a shelf.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS115
SOMEONE shifts his gaze to a bench seat against a wall. Toting the cricket bat, he heads over and places the letters on the sill above the seat back. His eyes take in SOMEONE as he walks back to her. He hands her the bat.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS116
As SOMEONE leaves the parlor, the mole above SOMEONE's upper lip disappears.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS117
She eyes Mr. Edelweiss.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS118
She looks at a window which opened.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS119
As she strides out of the room, Mr. Edelweiss obeys. Now, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE in the kitchen.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS120
SOMEONE tilts her head.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS121
She leans the bat on the stair rail.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS122
In a disheveled attic bedroom, a miniature carousel spins.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS123
SOMEONE and SOMEONE cower as SOMEONE enters. SOMEONE and his sister scoot back on their beds.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS124
SOMEONE stares stoically, her snaggletooth pressing into her lower lip. She produces her walking stick from inside her frock and raises it. In the kitchen, SOMEONE sets a teakettle on the stove.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS126
SOMEONE rubs her eyes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS127
At a second look, she finds the staircase as plain as ever. She collects a teapot from the kitchen table and turns her attention to the sink. The front door behind her opens and a goat steps inside. With her back to the animal, SOMEONE washes dishes. As the goat creeps to the stairs, SOMEONE sniffs the air. So does the goat.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS128
SOMEONE resumes her work. The goat hurries upstairs. It disappears around the corner just as SOMEONE turns. She sets the now clean teapot on the table, then turns her back to the door again and smooths a clock at a sideboard. As she arranges a setting on a tray, a cow enters the house. Geraldine glances at the oblivious woman, then hooves her way upstairs.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS129
to the sink, a baby elephant enters the house.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS130
She shields the elephant from SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS131
SOMEONE turns.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS132
The elephant nudges SOMEONE with its trunk.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS133
As SOMEONE turns away, SOMEONE directs the elephant up the stairs with a friendly pat on its rear.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS134
SOMEONE starts for the door. SOMEONE emerges from the pantry.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS135
SOMEONE beams. SOMEONE produces a lantern.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS136
The door shuts.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS138
The SOMEONE gazes at the children's window.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS139
The dark hairy mole on SOMEONE's chin vanishes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS140
SOMEONE skulks past a gatepost and nearly bumps into her.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS141
She brushes past him and strolls off with her lantern.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS142
SOMEONE's gaze darts. He hunches low and sneaks onto the farm proper toting a shovel. The saboteur freezes warily then trots on. Now curtains drawn over the children's bedroom window flutter. We glide through them and inside. At the foot of the nearest bed, a carousel night light glows softly. A lamp at the head of the bed illuminates the girls sleeping toe-to-toe under the covers next to Geraldine who snores.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS143
In the next bed over, the goat sleeps with his head on a pillow next to
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS144
SOMEONE's slumbering face and SOMEONE sleeps with his head at the foot of the bed. Like the girls and cow, all three share a single blanket. Across the room, SOMEONE sleeps by the baby elephant.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS145
SOMEONE's trunk steals SOMEONE's half of the covers. The chilly boy curls up. Now framed photos show SOMEONE and Rory on their wedding day and Rory playing cricket. In bed, SOMEONE reads a worn letter, then sniffs a dried flower folded inside. She presses the letter to her lips.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS146
Outside, by the side of the barn he digs a hole.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS147
leans against the barn, then glances back at the house.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS148
and sticks his head into the hole. He braces himself with both arms as he walks his legs up the side of the barn and eases deeper inside.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS149
Outside, SOMEONE gets stuck up to his chest.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS150
His feet flail in the air, they flop over and he pulls himself out.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS151
As he stands to walk away, one of his feet slips into the hole and he falls flat.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS152
He scrambles up.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS153
He glances at the house as another pig follows.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS154
Another piglet trots off. Daytime. A rooster perches on the hood of the tractor. Now in the children's room, SOMEONE's shadow passes over their sleeping forms. The animals are gone.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS155
As she leaves, SOMEONE peeks under his covers.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS157
The children join them. SOMEONE marches downstairs in purple pajamas and a full-face gas mask with a single snout-like filter. He eyes SOMEONE suspiciously as she cooks, then strides to a seat at the head of the table. SOMEONE stares at his headgear and cocks her head.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS158
SOMEONE serves breakfast.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS159
SOMEONE hurries into SOMEONE's room and opens the wardrobe. She rifles through floral sundresses hanging inside.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS161
Back in the kitchen.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS162
SOMEONE rushes out.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS163
The pane falls inward and shatters.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS164
Later, he flies to a fence and burps.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS165
He soars into the barn. SOMEONE knits her brow and follows him inside.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS166
She peeks into the hole.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS167
Now inside, SOMEONE repairs the window.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS168
She smooths putty at the seam.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS169
SOMEONE mouths Ew, affecting a mock fearful expression.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS170
SOMEONE descends the stairs in a flowing white gown of layered tulle. She wears a silky veil.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS171
She studies the dress. Outside, SOMEONE carries a bucket into the barn.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS172
He finds the pigpen empty. In the kitchen.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS173
She lifts her brow and raises her stick, then leans it gently against the table.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS174
SOMEONE blinks thoughtfully, then doffs his mask.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS175
He storms out after his cousins. SOMEONE lingers on the staircase landing. SOMEONE summons a breath, picks up her gnarled walking stick, and faces the girl. The SOMEONE looks from the open door to SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS176
SOMEONE steps closer.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS178
pair of rubber boots.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS179
Now SOMEONE stands on a hilltop. SOMEONE hobbles toward him, panting.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS180
A piglet flees.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS181
find some pigs. She dives for them.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS182
nearby piglet races for a tree. SOMEONE chases him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS183
at the base of a tree.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS184
Back at the farm.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS185
She bangs her walking stick on the ground, creating sparks. At the tree, the piglet runs up the trunk.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS186
Boys gape. It bounced to a branch high over their heads.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS187
The piglet performs a flip, somersaults through midair, then lands easily back on the branch.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS188
It smiles at them. The boys swap looks. One hoof slips off, bouncing the branch.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS190
and lands on another tree branch.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS191
The boys give chase.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS192
SOMEONE bangs her stick again.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS194
and dives gracefully into the water.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS195
Blinks quizzically. The pig surfaces and swims
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS196
then faces them. It pinches its snout with a hoof and takes a breath.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS197
pokes its rear into view and playfully flexes its legs to the sky.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS198
poking their heads up they circle
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS199
They lie on their sides and then roll and place making a turning shapes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS203
The six pig hold it in his hooves. The five others fling the flower, the pig into the air.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS204
Splashing the water,
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS205
by the children, the pigs swims in circle,
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS206
then glide away in a queue.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS207
The first pig does a backstroke.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS208
Now on a road, SOMEONE haps upon a man driving a horse drawn cart.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS209
He hustles along as the farmer halts.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS210
The saboteur thoughtfully slows to a stop.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS211
SOMEONE shifts his gaze and hustles off down the road.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS212
hops to the cart. Now all five children meet on a hilltop. The pigs race away through a meadow.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS213
SOMEONE draws in the dirt. Later, apples lie on a wooded road. SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit astride a branch above, holding SOMEONE's veil.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS214
The girls perch high on the road shoulder. SOMEONE cups his hands.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS215
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hold the veil between them. Under the branch, the piglets barrel down the road toward them. SOMEONE runs after them, driving them along, holding his safari hat in place with one hand.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS216
The steep embankments on either side of the road help
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS217
the animals gallop by.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS219
Together Mouth three, two, one and drop the veil like a net. Now, in the barn.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS220
SOMEONE gives a smarmy wave good-bye. SOMEONE sinks down.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS221
Outside, the five children return with the piglets. SOMEONE dashes through the barn, SOMEONE trailing closely behind.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS222
He stares wide-eyed. SOMEONE and SOMEONE carry a few
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS223
Smiling, Farmer SOMEONE opens the cart.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS224
SOMEONE joins the children at the cart.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS225
SOMEONE glances at the contract.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS227
He jerks his feet lose from the deep doubles through the barn and dashes out of sight. SOMEONE scowls at the money.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS228
SOMEONE joyfully kisses his cheek.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS229
notices SOMEONE looking on.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS230
The others turn. The mysterious woman tilts her head.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS231
Farmer SOMEONE shuts the cart and eyes a piglet.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS232
gathers the children in her arms.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS233
Noticing SOMEONE, she straightens and frowns.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS234
SOMEONE stares at the girl with a furrowed brow.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS235
SOMEONE returns the torn filthy veil wadded up in a ball.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS236
As SOMEONE stares at it, SOMEONE remorsefully hangs her head.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS237
SOMEONE observes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS238
Her unibrow vanishes. She catches a piglet watching her. SOMEONE winks and the animal winks back. She puts a shushing finger to her lips and the piglet joins its siblings. Farmer SOMEONE watches with a puzzled frown.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS239
As the cart leaves, two piglets peer over the back gate.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS240
SOMEONE tilts her head.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS241
SOMEONE turns. The limousine approaches.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS242
Running to the car, she opens the passenger door and finds the backseat empty. SOMEONE shuts the door with a wounded gaze. SOMEONE looks on sympathetically as his sister faces SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS243
Her brother glances toward their cousins.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS244
The chauffeur meets her gaze.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS245
SOMEONE holds out a shoebox of SOMEONE's egg blue marked with a scallop-shell logo. SOMEONE slowly takes it from him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS246
Under SOMEONE's compassionate gaze, SOMEONE hangs her head then steps away.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS247
The chauffeur sadly faces forward.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS248
The city girl marches out through the farm gate, biting her rosy lips in a suppressed sob.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS249
SOMEONE follows his sister. Heading into a lush green field, SOMEONE chucks the shoebox to the ground. SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare after their unhappy cousins, then turn away and head toward the barn. SOMEONE observes the children, then shifts her thoughtful gaze.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS250
Above, clouds drift across a violet sky. Later, SOMEONE sits dejectedly on the edge of SOMEONE's bed. The farm girl enters with the shoebox and sets it down beside her cousin.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS251
SOMEONE shrugs. Sitting by her, SOMEONE puts the box on her own lap. She admiringly sets the lid aside, reaches into the rosy tissue paper, and pulls out a graceful pale pink slipper. It bears an ankle strap at the back and a pale pink bow and rhinestone buckle on the closed toe.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS252
The farm girl faces her cousin and finds her expression sincere. She puts the shoe back in the box, sets it aside, and goes to a trunk at the foot of her bed. SOMEONE cranes her neck to watch. SOMEONE pulls out some brown velveteen pants and a crisp white blouse, both neatly folded.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS253
She lays them beside SOMEONE, then sits and returns the shoebox to her lap. With a faint smile, the city girl picks up the dainty blouse which bears small blue toned polka dots. She holds it to her chest and smiles. SOMEONE lays it aside and regards the velveteen. Our view dips to a pair of hands scrubbing filthy fabric. At a bathtub, SOMEONE massages lather into her wedding veil, bites her lips, then checks the rinsed cloth. It bears a one-inch hole. In a gold-tinged flashback, a modest carriage stands adorned with sunflowers, roses, and a Just Married sign. In the driver's seat, a handsome man in a black jacket and a boutonniere made of barley sprigs beams at his bride, SOMEONE. A wreath of flowers holds her snowy veil upon her head. As we glimpse SOMEONE eyeing the ruined veil, she remembers laughing merrily with her groom. They stand in the mud. He in his boots and she, luxuriantly, dipping in her bare foot. Rory scoops SOMEONE into his arms. They share a loving kiss and he carries her toward the house. She clings to him, holding her shoes and wedding bouquet. Back in the present, SOMEONE hangs the tattered veil on a clothesline. As it flutters in a breeze, our view of its SOMEONE trim blurs.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS255
She eyes the large manure patty
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS256
SOMEONE wears seven colorful medals.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS257
He perches on her shoulder.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS258
The bird covers his beak with his wing.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS259
SOMEONE shows an illustration.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS260
He move his hands like wings and pretends to fly.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS261
He outlines a bomb with his hands.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS262
with a hat over her face.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS264
Mrs. SOMEONE gazes sadly as SOMEONE hikes toward them.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS265
SOMEONE glances at the old woman, who swallows hard.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS266
SOMEONE's joyful smile fades slightly. Standing apart, SOMEONE steps forward. SOMEONE faces SOMEONE and the children.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS267
He holds the envelope out to his sister-in-law. She accepts it bravely, turns it over in her graceful hands, and musters a smile.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS268
SOMEONE looks away. SOMEONE faces Mrs. SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS269
The old woman nods. As SOMEONE turns away, Mrs. SOMEONE's brow furrows compassionately. Her lips pressed into a brisk smile, SOMEONE opens the envelope. SOMEONE's chest heaves. As his mother reads the telegram, her smile vanishes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS270
She sinks to the ground. SOMEONE takes the message.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS271
SOMEONE sits close to SOMEONE as his older siblings read.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS272
SOMEONE drops his full glass of ginger beer and SOMEONE collapses behind their mother. SOMEONE bows her head. As SOMEONE listlessly steps away, SOMEONE crouches before SOMEONE and the Docherty's draw near.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS273
The husband reaches for SOMEONE, but his wife tactfully restrains him. SOMEONE continues through the field, leaving the others behind. As SOMEONE stares off with heartbroken gaze, SOMEONE clutches her hand in both of his.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS274
Now the sun shines cheerily on the barn. Inside, SOMEONE sits slumped on the Scratch-o-matic seat. He takes a ragged breath. Watching him from the doorway, SOMEONE meekly shifts on his feet.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS275
SOMEONE turns to face him. His gaze solemn, SOMEONE steps up alongside him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS276
He looks up, admiring the Scratch-o-matic.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS277
SOMEONE faces his cousin.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS278
SOMEONE climbs down from the Scratch-o-matic seat.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS279
SOMEONE gives a respectful nod.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS280
Taking a seat, he smiles up at him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS281
SOMEONE bites his lip and shifts his thoughtful gaze.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS282
In the barn.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS283
Grins. They pass a row of red-coated guards who salute SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS284
The children stare.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS285
An statue coming to life.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS286
statue bows his head. A lion statue rests at the base
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS287
Lion statue is coming to life as SOMEONE and the boys smile.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS290
SOMEONE turns a red knob in the sidecar.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS291
The SOMEONE patiently taps her handle bar.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS292
front tire as the motorcycle levitates. It carries them
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS293
Now, the motorcycle lands safely
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS294
Now, Topsey and Turvey join SOMEONE on the country road.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS295
They each grab a shoulder.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS297
SOMEONE dismounts and waits as SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb out of the sidecar.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS298
Both boys wear suits. SOMEONE's is blue gray and SOMEONE's is checked with a purple necktie. They eye the towering building, then stride toward it.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS299
Black boots block their way. The boys sweep their eyes up the red coat of a barrel chested guard in a tall bearskin hat.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS300
SOMEONE mouths, Tell him, to SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS301
SOMEONE's lips stutter.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS302
SOMEONE wears a military uniform and
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS303
Jeffreys spins his rifle, then shoulders it and stands at attention.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS304
The boys exchange a look.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS305
She salutes, then heads over.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS306
Sergeant Jeffreys uneasily shifts his gaze.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS307
She gives a nod. Sergeant Jeffreys smiles.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS308
Grinning, the boys follow the sergeant as he marches past sand bag barricades through a doorway. The boys glance back at SOMEONE, garbed once again in her black dress. She knowingly touches the side of her nose. Sergeant Jeffreys leads SOMEONE and SOMEONE down a corridor to an elevator where they ride to the 100th floor. On the top floor, they pass military strategists who position model planes, ships, and tanks on a table map as big as eight king size beds.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS309
Back on the farm. The girls find SOMEONE and SOMEONE in the kitchen.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS310
Leafs through the contract.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS311
Back at the War Office, SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk side by side down a narrow red carpet.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS312
At the end of a long room, the carpet spreads into a square underneath a wide desk. A mustached man in a military uniform stands behind it. As the boys stop in front of his desk, he stares down at them with stern eyes.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS313
Lord SOMEONE's eyes widen at SOMEONE. He sets his glasses down on his desk, then steps out from behind it. With his arms crossed at his back, he regards the boys frankly.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS314
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a nod.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS315
Lord SOMEONE listens.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS316
SOMEONE presses his lips tightly.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS317
Licking his lips, SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS318
Lord SOMEONE closes the distance between them and glares at SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS319
SOMEONE glances at his cousin's anguished face.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS320
Lord SOMEONE stares, his reddened face almost queasy.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS321
SOMEONE shifts his gaze from SOMEONE to Lord SOMEONE. The man looks into his nephew's unwavering eyes, then opens his mouth to speak. His lips stutter.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS322
With an embarrassed look, he turns away.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS323
The boys watch as he walks back behind his desk and straightens his tie. Lord SOMEONE stares downward, picks up his glasses, then lifts his gaze thoughtfully to the boys before him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS324
As he trudges out of the room, SOMEONE rests a hand on SOMEONE's shoulder. At the farmhouse, SOMEONE clutches a pen in his hands as he hovers over SOMEONE, watching her review the contract.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS325
As he leans over her shoulder, the fountain pen poised, SOMEONE gives him a look.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS326
SOMEONE yanks the pen from SOMEONE, then continues reading. SOMEONE steps up onto a chair.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS327
Glancing at him, SOMEONE stomps to the chair. She kneels and peeks underneath.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS328
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a puzzled look, but
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS329
SOMEONE grabs it and stows it in her tool belt.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS330
SOMEONE leans against a wall.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS331
SOMEONE nods sadly. He swallows hard.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS332
SOMEONE hangs his head.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS333
The boys look to the door where an officer enters with Lord SOMEONE. The officer gathers a long strip of ticker tape as it trails behind him. Lord SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS334
SOMEONE averts his heartbroken gaze, then furrows his brow.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS335
It's Lord SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS336
SOMEONE releases him, then turns to SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS337
They start to run.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS338
The boys stop by the door. With a tender look, Lord SOMEONE strides down the narrow red carpet, his eyes on his son. He faces SOMEONE and takes a breath. The boy holds his father's gaze.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS339
Cyril's lips purse into an uncertain smirk. His father flashes a hint of a smile, then nods.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS340
Lord SOMEONE allows his smile through.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS341
He shakes SOMEONE's hand.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS342
With a nod, SOMEONE releases his father's hand and turns away. Lord SOMEONE watches the boy shoot him a final glance, then exit the room.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS343
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE hurry through the War Office building.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS344
is the SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS345
the sidecar. SOMEONE
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS346
hits the ground under the chair with the small
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS347
comes off the counter
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS348
SOMEONE climbs down from the chair. SOMEONE glances around.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS349
He frowns as he notices the table and the contracts, but no pen. Lifting the papers, he searches underneath, then pats his pockets.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS350
He scratches behind his ears, then tilts his head as if shaking out water.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS351
just through a drawer, tossing items
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS352
onto the next one.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS353
He knocks a piece to the floor. The girls share a glance as SOMEONE tears apart
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS354
inside a box, then turns to them with three pens.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS355
He smiles triumphantly. SOMEONE storms onto the stairs and peers upward.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS356
Peel lifts from SOMEONE's face
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS357
at the sky as she drives SOMEONE and SOMEONE
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS358
SOMEONE lifts the walking stick from the sidecar.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS359
SOMEONE looks nervously at SOMEONE. He eyes the road.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS360
SOMEONE bangs the stick.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS361
SOMEONE looks over.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS362
SOMEONE rolls her eyes. Back at the farm, SOMEONE sits alone in the barn and watches some chickens. The baby elephant appears behind him and taps him with its trunk.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS363
The elephant curls its trunk, then extends it.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS364
SOMEONE sets two pens beside SOMEONE who holds her head as she reads the papers.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS365
There's a third pen on the contract for SOMEONE. The elephant's trunk sneaks up from under the table and steals it.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS366
SOMEONE reaches for his pen, but it's gone. He pats the table.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS367
search under the table, the elephant steals the other two pens.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS369
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stifle their grins as SOMEONE searches under the table. They see the elephant leaving.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS370
SOMEONE sees him off.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS371
SOMEONE's head rises from behind the tabletop as he straightens and eyes SOMEONE. With a dry look, he brushes his bangs out of his face. Now SOMEONE's motorcycle speeds down the road.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS372
In the sidecar, SOMEONE glances at his wristwatch.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS373
grins at SOMEONE, then leans forward. As the motorcycle
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS374
on the road, disappearing in a trail of smoke. Back at the house, SOMEONE and SOMEONE nervously watch SOMEONE as he shuffles over on his knees. He stares eye level to SOMEONE, gawking first at her, then at her tool belt. SOMEONE squeezes her eyes shut. SOMEONE plucks out the pen.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS375
SOMEONE sadly eyes her daughter as SOMEONE stands and uncaps the pen.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS376
SOMEONE holds her gaze.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS377
He puts the pen in her hand and she pushes him away.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS378
SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE aside.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS379
They watch with terrified looks.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS380
Outside, an enemy plane soars in the sky.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS381
Below, in the house, SOMEONE starts to sign the deed.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS382
As he sneezes, the pilot's head bobs, dropping dangerously close to a red control button. SOMEONE finishes writing her first name.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS383
The nose hits the button and it lights up.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS384
SOMEONE's pen bumps the paper too hard and spills ink on the deed. She and the kids rush to the window.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS385
bomb in the middle of the barley field.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS386
Mr. SOMEONE arrives.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS387
Staring with dazed eyes, SOMEONE sinks into a chair.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS388
SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS389
SOMEONE strides over to her.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS390
He holds his mother's gaze. She nods tearfully.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS391
She smiles at SOMEONE, then rises and embraces him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS392
The boys hurry to the window.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS393
He reads a manual.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS394
Reading, Mr. SOMEONE
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS395
SOMEONE and the kids turn from the window and glare at SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS396
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE, who wears one cuff on his wrist.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS397
the unused cuff and locks it around a pot rack bar over
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS398
She leaves him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS399
Now in the barley field, the bomb stands lodged, nose first in the ground. Mr. SOMEONE stands on a ladder over its steaming tail vent. As he refers to his manual, he spots the others on the field's edge.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS400
Mr. Edelweiss lands atop a quaint Vardo styled wagon. As Mr. SOMEONE peers into the bomb's tail, his eyes widen. He swings backward and the ladder tips.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS401
SOMEONE races towards the bomb.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS402
SOMEONE chases the kids.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS403
In the house without a chair, SOMEONE balances on one foot, crosses the other over as if sitting, and props an elbow on his crooked knee.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS404
He releases the pose.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS405
He grimaces.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS406
Outside, SOMEONE stands on the ladder and peers through a circular opening in the bomb that has louvers like a window shutter.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS407
SOMEONE removes the circular vent. She tosses it.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS408
SOMEONE removes a pair of scissors from her tool belt. Peering into the vent, she tries to work the scissor blades past the protective metal spiral coiled around the wire. They won't fit. The others watch nervously.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS409
As everyone searches their pockets, SOMEONE's face lights up.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS410
She takes out a manicure case and removes a pair of nail scissors.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS411
She hands them to SOMEONE, who grins, then passes them up the ladder to SOMEONE. SOMEONE receives the scissors and inspects them.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS412
SOMEONE gives a relieved nod. SOMEONE reaches through the bomb's vent and works the scissors between two of the coils. She snips the wire.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS413
He frees up a hand and grabs a shaker off the table to season his eggs. He dips a finger in for a taste, then moves a pan onto a burner and pours the eggs in.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS414
Miss SOMEONE and Miss SOMEONE stand behind him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS415
They wear candy striper uniforms. Outside by the bomb.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS416
SOMEONE leans into the bomb, her arms stretching toward the wire. The tip of her scissors stop a few inches away.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS417
She keeps trying. As SOMEONE bites a knuckle, SOMEONE waits anxiously. Mrs. SOMEONE startles them.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS418
She glances at SOMEONE. The kids return their attention to SOMEONE, who leans down into the vent and stretches her arms toward the red wire. Her scissor blades close around it and she snips through. She straightens and looks at the others.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS419
A large blonde woman shows a stuffed and mounted owl.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS420
She has a doll sized replica of SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS422
around the wire revealing a green loop.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS423
She hits the wire. The countdown stops.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS424
The red bulbs close up.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS426
SOMEONE lifts her brow and nods proudly.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS427
And SOMEONE turns to him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS429
who descends the ladder. As SOMEONE reaches the bottom,
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS430
they share a big group hug.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS431
She smiles at the loving group. SOMEONE points to the sky
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS432
at the body expanding like a balloon.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS433
SOMEONE eyes him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS434
She lifts her chin.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS435
The others flee.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS436
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pull an IV bottle of pink fluid from their medical bag. SOMEONE jerks against his handcuffs.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS437
Inside, the boys and SOMEONE peek out from behind the wagon, as Mr. Edelweiss, now enormously round like a balloon, descend to SOMEONE. The girls take cover behind a trough with Mr. SOMEONE. SOMEONE catches the bird, points him in a new direction, and releases him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS438
He floats high, flapping his wings which appear puny compared to his inflated body. SOMEONE watches with an awestruck gaze.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS439
SOMEONE raises her walking stick.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS440
In the kitchen. The windows burst open.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS441
She seizes a banister.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS443
The door swings shut.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS444
As the wind dies down, SOMEONE descends safely to the floor.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS445
He sits on the stove.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS446
Magical wind mows a curving path through the barley.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS448
sparkling golden light. Next, the whirlwind transforms into a cloud of green above SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS449
The baby elephant with the bird perched on its back.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS450
Next, a fish, then a dolphin undulating through an unseen current.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS452
in a circle, moving up and down like carousel horses.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS454
Snowflakes. The children hold up their hands and Mrs. SOMEONE tried
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS455
catching some in her open handbag.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS456
Turning on the spot, SOMEONE stops, facing the field and stares.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS457
The SOMEONE's follow his gaze. Their mouths agape.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS458
Our view sweeps out to the field where SOMEONE stands among a vast and tidy arrangement of the baled and bundled crops.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS459
SOMEONE returns.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS460
The slide leans on a hay bale.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS461
Smiling, SOMEONE follows the others out to the slide. Mrs. SOMEONE lags behind with a bittersweet gaze.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS462
SOMEONE slides down the tin chute.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS463
SOMEONE takes the next turn, followed by Mr. SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS464
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS465
SOMEONE blinks wistfully.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS466
She tenderly faces Mrs. SOMEONE with her snaggletooth smile.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS467
The two share a warm smile and hug. SOMEONE peers toward the children, then steps away. Mrs. SOMEONE gazes after her tearfully, then faces the children with a sobbing breath. Now atop the hay bale, SOMEONE discovers the Medal for Resolve pinned to her overalls. SOMEONE wears the Medal for Kindness.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS468
SOMEONE has one too. As SOMEONE cherishes the Leaps of Faith Medal, SOMEONE admires yet another.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS469
SOMEONE points.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS470
Shading his eyes, SOMEONE spots her halfway across the field.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS471
Mr. Edelweiss takes flight.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS472
SOMEONE's got a medal too.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS473
SOMEONE and the kids run off.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS474
Mr. SOMEONE steps up beside his wife.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS476
up the wooded road, SOMEONE leads the chase after her.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS477
Leaving the woods, SOMEONE rounds a turn, stops running and stares. She steps forward. Her eyes wide.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS478
The children catch up to her.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS479
Taking in her emotional smile, they follow her gaze. Atop a distant ridge, SOMEONE swaps cordial bows with Rory.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS480
He drops a duffle bag. With one arm in a sling, he raises the other in a wave and runs forward.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS481
The kids dash out to meet him.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS482
SOMEONE beams as her husband races to their children, his face illuminated by his warm toothy grin. Leading the others, SOMEONE flings his arms around his father who scoops him up and spins him around.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS483
him down. He lifts SOMEONE up in a big hug.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS484
He kisses the boy's neck. SOMEONE joyfully strolls up to join them. Setting SOMEONE down, Rory straightens and meets her
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS485
in a passionate kiss.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS486
The two cling to each other in a fast embrace, then draw SOMEONE, SOMEONE
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS487
SOMEONE and SOMEONE
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS488
Facing them, Rory warmly extends a hand to his nephew.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS489
Her snaggletooth gone from her lovely face,
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS490
a warm smile brightens her pleasing features.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS491
As the reunited family heads down hill, SOMEONE finds Mr. Edelweiss perched by her side.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS492
She pets her shoulder.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS493
He jumps up and down happily, then alights upon her shoulder. SOMEONE beams at the bird, then turns her back to us and strolls toward a gentle valley.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS494
Back on the other side of the grassy ridge, wild flowers blanket the field between us and the distant SOMEONE. Silhouetted against the sunny sky, the magical woman slowly descends out of view. Cut to black. Words appear. The end. SOMEONE's silhouette appears in profile above them.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS495
The figure taps her walking stick. We drift into the silhouette and find a cartoon where SOMEONE pedals the Scratch-o- matic
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS496
The meters needle jumps to
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS497
Our gaze flies along the contraption to three brushes, each scratching a piglet.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS499
Five children peek out from her skirt, then tumble out and frolic away.
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS501
The elephant gulps down the jam with his trunk. He sneezes some
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS503
SOMEONE struggles to balance on a teeter-totter as she juggles the children. SOMEONE Gyllenhaal. Two piglets fly through the air using their floppy ears
NANNY_MCPHEE_RETURNS_DVS506
He lands in a puddle as the children mirthfully look on. Mr. SOMEONE takes him away in handcuffs. Now the shop drawer open and close by themselves. Mr. Edelweiss peeks out from one.