The both stared straight ahead.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS27
No String Attached
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS28
Five years ago, a large white fraternity house with columns on the ground, white pediment at the front
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS40
Standing beside his buddy, SOMEONE, SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS42
SOMEONE points a massive foam hand.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS44
SOMEONE slinks up behind the girl and dances in time with her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS49
It's her father's funeral.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS50
Standing by the coffin everyone's in black. Apart from SOMEONE who's wearing a bright yellow Michigan top and beige chinos
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS51
the men wear skullcaps.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS52
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE's attractive mom a big hug.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS54
Mourners gather at SOMEONE's family home, a colonial-style mansion with white walls, shuttered windows, and a red-tiled roof.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS55
Two boys run down the stairs.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS56
SOMEONE's mother, SOMEONE, is standing outside by a pretty rose garden.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS59
SOMEONE walks SOMEONE to his car, a blue BMW.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS60
He gets in the driving seat and SOMEONE leans by the door.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS61
Looking slightly lost he drives away.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS62
Pretty, dark-haired SOMEONE watches him with her arms folded.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS65
One year ago, a bright sunny day, the steel and glass skyscraper of Los Angeles gleam.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS66
People mill about at a farmer's market by an artificial lake.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS69
SOMEONE's friend SOMEONE is nearby. He's stocky guy with a friendly face he sees SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS70
SOMEONE's with a girl.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS71
SOMEONE walks over, SOMEONE's nearby watching.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS76
SOMEONE and SOMEONE smiled approvingly.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS86
A guy shows a picture to the girls.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS93
SOMEONE walks down to see him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS95
SOMEONE lights the joint.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS96
He takes a script from his back.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS97
SOMEONE proudly points to the name on the cover page.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS98
SOMEONE takes a drag on the joint.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS100
SOMEONE raises his brows and Vanessa runs off.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS102
SOMEONE has a drag.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS106
In a bar SOMEONE makes some calls.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS111
sunlight washes over SOMEONE's face.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS112
He frowns as he slowly wakes up on a couch.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS113
He opens his eyes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS114
He holds up his hand to block out the bright sunlight.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS117
She sits in the kitchen counter eating cereal.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS118
SOMEONE squints at her blearily.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS119
SOMEONE's naked apart from the towel he's clutching over his groin.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS121
He sits up and looks around.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS122
He hugs the cup and drinks.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS123
SOMEONE stands watching.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS124
SOMEONE looks up at her with his eye narrowed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS128
She smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS129
He goes to stand but stops himself.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS130
He clutches the towel over his penis.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS132
SOMEONE turns away SOMEONE sits on her bed and pulls on his jeans.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS133
She wiggles her hips and waves her hand around provocatively.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS134
She sits beside him and puts her arm around his shoulder.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS135
He clutches her knee.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS137
He undoes the belt in her blue robe.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS138
They gaze at each other for a moment,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS139
SOMEONE leans closer.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS140
and kisses SOMEONE passionately.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS141
He lays her on her back, gets on top of her, and pulls off her robe.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS145
Her chest heaves as he struggles with the packet.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS147
They make love.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS150
Outside the room, SOMEONE smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS153
He puts his hand over her mouth.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS154
SOMEONE's mouth gapes. She gazes into Adams eyes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS155
Later they get dressed and SOMEONE hand SOMEONE his top.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS156
He puts it on.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS157
She smiles and pats his arm.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS158
At an outside restaurant SOMEONE checks messages on his iPhone, SOMEONE gets up.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS160
He frowns heavily.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS162
SOMEONE stands up.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS163
SOMEONE stops SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS164
With an awkward look she walks off.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS166
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE go into to the restaurant SOMEONE wearily shakes his head.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS168
They high five.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS169
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walked past with their lunch.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS170
SOMEONE watches them go and get in SOMEONE's red Prius.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS171
SOMEONE's in the hospital cafeteria, SOMEONE comes in with a congrats balloon.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS176
She snatches the balloon.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS178
they walk past the doctor.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS180
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk up outside.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS184
SOMEONE looks at his phone a message from SOMEONE reads, "You’re placed in 30. "
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS186
He and SOMEONE lay side-by-side in bed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS187
SOMEONE leans over and snuggles closer.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS189
As she gets dressed she smiles and steps closer to SOMEONE who's sitting up in bed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS190
He presses his lips together thoughtfully,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS191
a smile spreads across his face.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS192
Grinning she puts on her top.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS193
Beside her car he kisses her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS194
She gets in her car. A neighbor walks up with his dog.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS195
They guy shakes his head and walks by.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS209
SOMEONE's on the couch.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS210
SOMEONE and SOMEONE have wild sex in a variety of locations. At work SOMEONE receives a text.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS211
She looks at SOMEONE's penis through 3D glasses.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS214
In the operating theater SOMEONE lies on the operating table. SOMEONE shines a light on his naked body and runs her finger along his leg.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS216
In a park near the water, SOMEONE and SOMEONE have a barbecue with some of their friends. SOMEONE throws a Frisbee to SOMEONE and runs at her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS217
He wrestles her to the ground.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS220
SOMEONE tosses the salad.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS222
SOMEONE frowns and sends a text message to SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS224
He has really small hands,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS228
he smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS229
SOMEONE and SOMEONE load the car.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS234
He parks in front of the garage door and goes inside. SOMEONE's lying on the couch holding his hands and feet in the air and slowly moving them back and forth.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS235
He wiggles his toes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS237
SOMEONE's at work.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS240
She chases her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS241
At the hospital, SOMEONE goes to the lobby where her sister SOMEONE is waiting.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS242
She's wearing an engagement ring,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS244
SOMEONE beams. SOMEONE frowns unsurely and nods.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS245
At home, SOMEONE has made herbal teas.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS246
SOMEONE goes to the intercom.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS249
SOMEONE opens the lobby door and hurries upstairs holding a box of cupcakes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS250
SOMEONE opens the apartment door
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS251
and SOMEONE cautiously steps in. SOMEONE's curled up on the couch in pain.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS254
She nonchalantly shrugs.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS255
SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE on her bed and tries to feed her soup.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS256
She has a spoonful.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS258
SOMEONE lies on his side with his arms around SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS259
She wakes looks right him
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS260
and pries herself free.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS261
She looks at him earnestly.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS262
He looks away from her and grabs his coat.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS263
Smiling bitterly he picks up his sneakers.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS264
In the park.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS265
At the hospital.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS266
A man looks at SOMEONE surprised.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS268
the city is a sea of lights.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS269
SOMEONE gets out of a black car at the hospital Christmas party at the plush W Hotel.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS271
He opens the passenger door for SOMEONE
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS273
and then opens the door again, SOMEONE smiles - touched.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS277
SOMEONE goes over and taps him on the shoulder.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS281
SOMEONE smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS283
SOMEONE walks up to her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS284
SOMEONE wraps her arms around SOMEONE and kisses him on the mouth.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS287
He twirls her under his arm.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS291
she takes another call.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS294
wearing a pretty purple strapless dress SOMEONE totters to a taxi in her high heels.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS299
He carries them over to SOMEONE and SOMEONE,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS303
he smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS305
He goes outside
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS306
and stands face-to-face with SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS307
She stares at him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS308
SOMEONE comes out.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS310
SOMEONE and SOMEONE follow him inside.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS312
SOMEONE carries SOMEONE inside,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS314
she nibbles his lips.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS315
She kisses him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS318
The cast and crew are gathered around SOMEONE who's sitting at the piano.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS320
SOMEONE stares at his father.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS322
SOMEONE blows out the candles on the cake which has the painting The Creation of SOMEONE by Michelangelo.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS330
At the hospital, SOMEONE runs to SOMEONE who's with Dr. SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS331
SOMEONE lies on a bed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS332
He gives it to SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS333
SOMEONE pops a pill and looks at SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS334
She slaps his cheek.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS335
SOMEONE head-butts the table.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS336
SOMEONE looks touched.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS338
SOMEONE raises his eyebrows
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS339
They walk out.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS340
SOMEONE's stunned.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS341
SOMEONE gives an embarrassed smile and a wave.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS343
She turns and gives SOMEONE an inquiring look,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS344
she nods.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS346
He smiles and steps closer for a kiss.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS347
She looks unsure and sighs,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS348
she walks off.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS349
A smartly dressed SOMEONE sits on the bonnet of his car waiting outside the hospital,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS350
SOMEONE walks up wearing a raincoat over a shimmering silver shirt dress.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS351
Her long brown hair hangs lose.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS352
SOMEONE steps up to her
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS353
with his hands behind his back.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS354
He holds up a bunch of carrots.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS355
They drive through town. SOMEONE sits with the carrots lying next to her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS356
She holds up a card,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS357
stuck to it was sticking plasters
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS358
is a cutout picture of a human heart.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS359
He hands her a document.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS363
He goes straight in the hole.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS366
She takes the shot,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS367
the ball hits an angled block,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS368
takes a shot, left turn, nudges against the concrete curb, and heads straight for the hole.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS370
The ball passes through a tube beneath the shrubbery and rolls straight toward the hole.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS374
In a diner, they both suck through straws. SOMEONE gets an extra straw.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS375
SOMEONE grabs a handful of straws and has a big slurp of the chocolate milkshake.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS376
She wipes his lip and licks her finger.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS377
They gaze at each other.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS378
Avoiding his gaze she leans forward and has a drink.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS379
Later, SOMEONE drives along smiling. He glances at SOMEONE who stares ahead.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS380
Preoccupied, she looks out at the window to her side.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS381
They walk through the urban light instillation at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS382
A rectangular arrangement of 202 vintage street lamps from the city all painted gray.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS384
They stand facing each other.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS386
She slaps his chest.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS387
A security guard breaks them up. SOMEONE walks away and SOMEONE jumps on his back,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS388
the guard runs over to them he breaks them up a second time.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS389
SOMEONE drives SOMEONE up outside the hospital.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS390
They both sit staring ahead stony faced.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS391
Tears glistened in SOMEONE's eyes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS392
SOMEONE undoes her seat belt. She turns towards SOMEONE, but doesn't look at him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS393
She gets out of the car and walks towards the hospital.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS394
She stops beneath the red and white emergency sign and looks back,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS395
SOMEONE drives away.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS396
Still in her pretty silver dress SOMEONE walks into the hospital.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS398
In a daze, she slowly walks past the front desk.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS400
SOMEONE sees her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS402
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE concerned. Clutching her coat she wanders down the corridor oblivious to Dr. SOMEONE, who glances around at her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS404
SOMEONE is having a candle lit dinner with SOMEONE. SOMEONE comes in.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS409
In SOMEONE's bedroom, he pulls a chair up for her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS410
She sits decisively.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS411
She smiles he sits facing her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS413
Six weeks later. At the hospital,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS417
SOMEONE stands leaning against the worktop in a kitchen area. SOMEONE doesn't acknowledge her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS418
SOMEONE goes outside.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS420
SOMEONE looks around at Dr. SOMEONE as he walks by.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS421
SOMEONE drives along a highway by the ocean with her mom SOMEONE beside her. SOMEONE's new boyfriend, Bones, is sleeping on the backseat. He's a thick-set old guy with a mustache and a ponytail.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS422
SOMEONE looks back and smiles. SOMEONE frowns disapprovingly and blinks.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS429
They drive over a long bridge by the ocean,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS430
then along a palm tree-lined road.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS431
Under the pale blue sky the ocean has a shimmering silver sheen.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS432
They turn up a driveway through lush gardens.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS433
On the sound stage, the cast of SOMEONE's show, Secret High, perform a prom dance number.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS435
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and Wallace are also there watching.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS436
Young couples dance together elegantly.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS439
As the number comes to a close, dancers surround the male and female leads, SOMEONE and SOMEONE, and slowly raise their arms.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS443
a satisfied smile spreads across SOMEONE's face. SOMEONE and SOMEONE both elegantly dressed in white kiss passionately.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS445
At SOMEONE's wedding rehearsal dinner,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS450
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS451
SOMEONE smiles fondly. She grabs SOMEONE's phone and hands it to her.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS454
He looks tense. His eyes glaze. SOMEONE calls SOMEONE as he stares at his phone, which SOMEONE holds aloft. At the other end of the line SOMEONE waits expectantly. SOMEONE hangs up and sits on a bench.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS459
With a look of disbelief SOMEONE slowly lowers her phone.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS463
She smiles at him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS467
She stares ahead intently.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS469
Lights glow beneath the porch roof.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS470
SOMEONE switches off the car headlights and gets out, Wearing a pretty pale lilac SOMEONE dress.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS476
SOMEONE sighs and creeps out from behind the bush.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS479
She walks down the steps to the road. She calls SOMEONE.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS481
SOMEONE gets in the car.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS482
They sip red wine, then lean in for a kiss at the same time, and bash heads.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS483
Faces on the couch, SOMEONE leans close and kisses SOMEONE forcefully on the mouth.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS485
She kisses him, then frowns.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS486
She stands and unbuttons her shirt.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS487
He checks his phone. SOMEONE frowns.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS488
SOMEONE stands with her shirt hanging off and clicks her fingers.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS490
SOMEONE drives along the freeway listening to SOMEONE's Period mix.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS492
She munches from a large box of doughnut holes. She has sugar-frosting smushed around her mouth.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS493
She grabs her phone, a message from SOMEONE reads, "Call me. "
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS495
She makes the call. SOMEONE meets SOMEONE and her little dog at the hospital.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS496
She frowns.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS497
She shakes her head.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS498
He looks away bewildered.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS499
She holds out the fluffy white Pomeranian.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS500
SOMEONE takes Freckles and walks off. With a look of distaste, SOMEONE wipes her hands together and goes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS501
With Freckles hidden inside his blue cardigan
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS503
SOMEONE sneaks past reception.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS504
SOMEONE covers Freckles completely with his cardigan and heads along a corridor.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS505
He walks into a room where SOMEONE lies in a slightly tilted bed SOMEONE shuts the door.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS508
SOMEONE opens his cardigan and puts Freckles on the bed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS509
SOMEONE sits beside the bed.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS511
SOMEONE wearily shakes his head.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS512
SOMEONE smiles,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS513
he holds Freckles up close to his face.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS514
SOMEONE stands and gently touches SOMEONE's brow.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS515
SOMEONE wanders out and SOMEONE strokes the dog. He smiles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS517
SOMEONE walks along beneath the covered walkway with the red and white emergency sign at the end of it.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS518
He makes a phone call.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS519
SOMEONE gets out of the car and walks over to him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS521
He steps closer then frowns. He gestures for her to wipe the sugar frosting from beside her mouth and she does that.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS522
She blinks back tears.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS523
SOMEONE's chest heaves. SOMEONE stares at her with tears glistening in his eyes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS526
They go to each other and kiss passionately.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS527
SOMEONE cups her hands around the back of SOMEONE's neck and pulls him closer.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS528
They squeeze each other tight and kiss tenderly.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS529
They both smile.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS530
A massive breakfast of pancakes and waffles.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS531
SOMEONE cuts herself a big helping of pancakes. SOMEONE frowns.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS533
They drive along the coast road.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS535
They get out of the car.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS536
SOMEONE's still in the pale lilac SOMEONE dress. SOMEONE wears jeans and a t-shirt.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS539
They stand side-by-side and watch the proceedings.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS540
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE smiling nervously.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS541
With a wry smile he looks down and takes her hand in his
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS542
gently knitting their fingers together.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS545
SOMEONE frowns anxiously.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS546
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and his two dads all hug.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS548
The door opens and she stares distastefully at an elderly gentleman.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS549
She cautiously enters the elevator
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS551
and the door starts to close.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS553
A guy runs up, stops the door with his briefcase, and gets in. He's followed by several more people.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS554
Suddenly, Vanessa is surrounded by elderly men and women. She looks decidedly uncomfortable and makes a bid for freedom.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS556
The door closes.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS558
In a sunny park, SOMEONE pulls SOMEONE close and they kiss passionately,
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS560
then nonchalantly walks off.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS561
SOMEONE gives a weary look and follows him.
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS570
Fully clothed, he behind her with his arm around her
NO_STRINGS_ATTACHED_DVS571
they sleep peacefully.