With his hand on the fence.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS22
Under his brother's glare, SOMEONE stops and faces him once more,
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS23
revealing a flood of brilliant light.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS24
at Poseidon,
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS25
then walks past the door's broken pieces and down a few steps to the doorway.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS26
The hundreds of broken pieces fly back up and reform the door, sealing off the light.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS28
A title swoops into view.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS29
The Lightning Thief.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS30
The image dissolves to a teenage boy who sits comfortably on the bottom of a swimming pool.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS37
Later in class, a frumpish woman writes a quote on the chalkboard,
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS39
then peers at the quote.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS40
Read the letters of the Shakespearean line jumble on the chalkboard.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS42
SOMEONE arrives at a white brick apartment building.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS43
Our view ascends along a fire escape.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS46
He faces his mother.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS47
A frustrated SOMEONE steps outside onto the fire escape and scans the street below.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS48
Metropolitan Museum of Art
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS49
to the pillared entrance.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS50
SOMEONE accompanies his buddy who makes his way up the front steps on his crutches.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS51
SOMEONE notices the human Poseidon watching him from across the street.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS52
he shrugs.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS53
Words at the top, which jumble to read,
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS55
back to his peers, then follows Ms. SOMEONE out.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS56
Her clothes burst off and she morphs into a demonic six-winged creature. SOMEONE dives onto the floor as the creature swoops to another perch.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS57
With SOMEONE on the floor, he grabs his shoulder, then scoots away as the monster bares her fangs at him. She flies out, smashing through a high window.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS59
SOMEONE's friend stabs SOMEONE's foot with the tip of his crutch, then whacks him in the groin.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS60
Now at dusk. SOMEONE drives the other two across the SOMEONE Washington Bridge.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS61
Our view descends to a herd of cattle.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS62
A beast with horns,
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS63
A car swerves and rolls onto its roof, then slides to a spinning top.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS64
SOMEONE stomps out the rear window. The giant horned beast charges in their direction. SOMEONE crawls out.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS65
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE and SOMEONE over a fence.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS66
As they race across the clearing, SOMEONE looks back to see the minotaur lift her car overhead and throw it.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS67
It hits the ground just ahead of them, bounces end-over-end and lands in a heap.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS68
SOMEONE looks up and notices ancient Greek words, which transform to read, Camp Half-Blood,
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS69
A translucent wall of energy stops SOMEONE.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS73
SOMEONE gapes.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS75
SOMEONE takes out the pen, which transforms into a sword. The minotaur crushes SOMEONE with its fist and she vanishes in a plume of bright smoke. The beast
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS76
SOMEONE swipes wildly at it, then somersaults away from a punch but crashes into the ground. He strikes again, and the minotaur backhands him into a tree. As the beast charges, SOMEONE gets up and dodges. The minotaur hits the tree trunk headfirst. With his left horn stuck, the minotaur yanks itself backwards. The horn snaps in two and the beast collapses, leaving the broken off tip lodged in the tree. SOMEONE spots his sword near the minotaur then hurries around the tree and grabs the horn. SOMEONE pulls out the horn tip and stabs the charging beast in the chest. The wounded minotaur straightens then falls on its back. SOMEONE drops the horn.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS78
SOMEONE catches him. With his eyes closed, SOMEONE's head hangs to the side.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS79
Two rows of cots line opposite walls in a spacious medical tent.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS80
While medical workers tend to their patients.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS81
He blinks groggily and rubs his eyes.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS82
SOMEONE sits up in his cot.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS83
Glancing around he takes in his surroundings. He sees a person bandaging a patient's leg and a hand sponging a woman's forehead.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS91
Outside people bustle around the campgrounds.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS95
Archers almost shoot them.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS108
His gaze drifts past her to another teenage girl being attached by a cluster of warriors. He gapes as she ducks a swinging sword from one fighter, then evades a blow from another and holds him at sword point.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS109
He and SOMEONE stand at the edge of the clearing and look out at the distant lakeshore. A herd of creatures gallops along the water.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS110
They hurry to the centaur, who bears the teacher's upper body.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS111
Now SOMEONE slows his pace as they reach a courtly-logged boathouse.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS112
A lofty breezeway at its center leads from the shore onto the water.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS113
They look at the boathouse.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS118
He grabs the three-pronged spear by its shaft and examines it.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS124
SOMEONE sidesteps impatiently as SOMEONE turns and shoots a tentative look over his shoulder.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS126
SOMEONE wears chest armor as he follows SOMEONE to the training field.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS127
The students gather their weapons and form a crowd in front of SOMEONE.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS129
Helmets line up.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS130
They charge through the woods with their swords in one hand and their shields in the other.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS131
A group of soldiers with blue crested helmets races through the trees.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS132
A blue soldier jumps off a boulder and knocks a red opponent to the ground.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS133
SOMEONE and SOMEONE race off, leaving the mass of battling warriors behind.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS134
A red soldier charges up and SOMEONE ducks his sword. As SOMEONE fights the warrior a second opponent comes up from behind and tears off his helmet.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS135
SOMEONE starts to run away but the soldier jumps out and strikes at him. SOMEONE falls back and kicks him away.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS136
More sons of Ares surround the blue soldiers.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS137
SOMEONE fights off two opponents while SOMEONE swordfights nimbly and dodges a blow. SOMEONE pushes him out of the way and sweeps out a warrior's leg.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS138
SOMEONE bashes an opponent to the ground and stares disbelievingly.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS139
He drops to his knees at the water's edge and dips his hands in the stream.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS140
Palms to his face he notices a red flag hanging from a pole on the opposite bank.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS141
Which splashes at his knees as he moves across the stream.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS142
As he stumbles back, SOMEONE and SOMEONE appear on the bank, some distance away.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS143
SOMEONE parries his blows, then elbows him in the chest.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS144
Red warriors gather behind SOMEONE as SOMEONE blocks another swing then knees her opponent.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS145
SOMEONE advances, slicing SOMEONE's arm and cutting his leg.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS146
SOMEONE ducks and strikes his armor. He falls to his knees and she kicks him to the ground.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS147
SOMEONE watches him over her shoulder.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS148
Pump their fists and wave their swords. She glances back at SOMEONE.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS149
Our view hovers over him and spins slowly as we descend upon him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS151
Her lips parted curiously as SOMEONE dips his hand in the water.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS152
then moves to his shoulder.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS153
Water glistens on SOMEONE's cheek as the gash on his face closes up.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS154
He glances from the sword in his hand, the healed cut on his palm.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS155
heave[unclear]s as she stares with wide eyes.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS156
SOMEONE hurriedly joins the gathered warriors on the banks to watch.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS157
In slow motion one of them charges at him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS158
He defeats two more opponents then spins around and strikes an attacking soldier in the chest.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS160
SOMEONE nods proudly.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS161
The son of Poseidon blocks his opponent's sword with his own, then elbows him in the back.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS162
SOMEONE aims his weapon at her, its tip stopping within inches of her throat.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS163
The two battle fiercely, parrying and dodging each other's blows
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS164
then pulls SOMEONE's sword from her grasp and turns its blade against the back of her neck.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS165
As SOMEONE saunters away he twirls his sword like a propeller blade at his side.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS166
He makes his way through a crowd of red soldiers who part to let him by.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS167
The two opponents guarding the red flag.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS168
He takes a flag on its wooden pole.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS169
Beside him, SOMEONE gives a nod and raises his staff in congratulations.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS170
A pig on a spit over a fire.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS171
SOMEONE holds up SOMEONE's arm like a boxing champion as they push through the crowd toward a refreshment table.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS173
Winged demon emerges from the burst of fire.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS174
Flames surround its lower body and dance across its broad wingspan.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS175
A fireball appears in the demon's hand. He hurls it at a food table which explodes. SOMEONE and SOMEONE step back.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS176
One explodes a few feet from SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS177
SOMEONE's eyes narrow. SOMEONE watches Hades with an odd expression.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS178
A ball of flames appears in his palm and he lowers it for SOMEONE to see.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS180
Hades bursts into flames which rise into the air and disappear.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS181
The satyr meets his friends gaze and nods. SOMEONE turns away and closes his eyes.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS182
SOMEONE slings his backpack over his shoulder as he leaves the boathouse.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS183
Arrows in a canvas sack.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS184
Now they arrive at an open-air home similar to the boathouse, decked out with gauzy drapes and burning candles.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS185
Side-by-side flat screens display SOMEONE's video game. Electronics clutter a nearby table.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS186
The shoebox and blows dust of the lid
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS187
A pair of Chuck Taylor High Tops with wings.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS188
SOMEONE drops the shoe in the box and the newcomer quickly closes it.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS189
Across the top of the map.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS190
As his friends edge away, SOMEONE slides his arm through its straps and grasps its handle.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS191
A Greyhound bus pulls over at a deserted stop.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS192
SOMEONE uses his crutches as he, SOMEONE and SOMEONE exit at the side of the road.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS193
Now a weathered sign reads Auntie Em's Garden Emporium. A breeze blows dead leaves across the store's parking lot as the teens arrive.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS194
Life-sized statues of men and women in ancient Greek attire adorn entryway.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS195
They pass under a welcome sign and enter a stone gray clobbered building.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS196
It's crawling with mice.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS197
And peers into a freestanding fountain.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS198
And SOMEONE ventures farther into the greenhouse.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS199
Outside SOMEONE wanders down a path, bordered with overgrown vegetations and statues of people in Medieval and Renaissance fashions.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS200
Tall plants block SOMEONE's view on either side as she heads farther back.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS201
Inside, SOMEONE finds a statue of a Satyr with ram's horns.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS203
As SOMEONE's and SOMEONE's path cross, they collide and hit the ground.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS204
A tall woman in a turban and oversized sunglasses blocks their path.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS205
The woman's eyes turn into granite like stone that spreads over her entire body. SOMEONE wriggles her wrist in the woman's rock-hard grasp. SOMEONE and SOMEONE hide behind a nearby statue.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS206
SOMEONE watches her reflection in his Smartphone.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS207
SOMEONE circles SOMEONE, then squats down and lifts her face close to hers.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS208
Chasing him, SOMEONE halts at an intersection, then instinctively turns. SOMEONE crouches behind a statue and holds up his phone. As SOMEONE arrives nearby it catches her reflection.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS209
She shoves the statue, which knocks into another, creating a domino effect that topples an entire row. The last statue traps SOMEONE.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS211
As SOMEONE reaches for his sword, SOMEONE kicks it away, hauls him to his feet and pulls him close.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS212
An antiquated pickup barrels into the greenhouse, plowing through statues. SOMEONE dives for cover and SOMEONE falls. Behind the wheel SOMEONE sits up, her eyes clamped shut.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS213
As the dust clears, SOMEONE rolls over among the broken statues and crawls toward SOMEONE.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS214
Standing she peers quizzically at her reflection.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS215
SOMEONE gapes as he swings his sword.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS217
SOMEONE's severed head lies on the ground by SOMEONE's phone and her lifeless hand.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS218
A bracelet with a green shimmering pearl coils around SOMEONE's wrist.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS219
Over the southeastern states a small-labeled drawing of a columned building blazes into view.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS220
The truck veers into the path of an oncoming big rig.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS221
SOMEONE swerves away from the big rig, then cuts across approaching traffic as he returns to the proper lane.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS222
SOMEONE sits at the bottom of the pool, clasping his bent knees.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS224
Hades sweeps an enormous demonic hand through her form, obliterating it in a ball of flames.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS225
He lowers a hand back into the pool and touches his fingertips to hers.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS226
A glistening stream of water trickles up from his hand to her arm.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS227
SOMEONE shuts the curtains and faces him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS228
Later the truck turns down a road bordered with well-tended flowering trees and shrubs.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS229
Where a pristine replica of the long, multi columned Parthenon stands.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS230
Now children play around a man making giant soap bubbles on the park lawn.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS231
Centennial Park. The Parthenon. Entrance and parking.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS232
As they approach the Parthenon's entrance
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS235
Now sunlight fans out across the marble floor as a pair of doors swing open.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS236
Features a beautiful warrior goddess with long curls spilling out from under her crested helmet.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS237
Its Greek text translates to read Athena.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS238
Gleams from the center of a gold band encircling Athena's helmet.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS239
The teens emerge.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS240
SOMEONE shoots another custodian.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS241
She takes down one janitor after another. Her final dart hits a janitor's thigh and he falls from a tall ladder.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS242
Later SOMEONE drags the janitor across the polished floor, pulling him behind a line of columns.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS243
with his hands together.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS244
He flails his limbs, struggling for control as he soars at the statue.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS245
As he slips down the front of Athena's robes, he catches himself on a marbled lock of hair.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS246
The shoes wings flutter as SOMEONE scrambles up the front of the statue, using Athena's hair and folds of her robe as hand and foot holds.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS249
He removes the pearl from its setting.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS250
Mist rises around the custodians as they drift close together.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS251
Grey hide underneath.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS252
The teens nervously edge back as the janitors bodies join into one, their necks stretching and coiling upward to create a five-headed SOMEONE like beast.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS253
The teens dug behind a row of columns. The hydra heaves flames at them.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS254
As he tries to shake the fire out, the pearl slips from his grasp. It rolls away and settles on top of a floor grate.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS255
Then dons his shield and draws his sword.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS256
Another head disarms SOMEONE, who scrambles back.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS258
SOMEONE bashes the heads with his shield, then runs out brandishing his sword. His sneakers lift him into the air where he continues his assault.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS259
But he flies out of its path.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS260
Then slices through its neck.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS262
SOMEONE barrels aside, then hacks through its neck. The head lands beside the mammoth body.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS263
The center ones spew fire at the teens.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS264
They take cover behind the columns.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS265
She draws another arrow, shoots again and pierces one of the hydra's eyes. It turns to pursue her and she darts away.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS266
As SOMEONE runs in the opposite direction, one of the heads spots him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS267
SOMEONE reaches for the pearl, misses and faces the charging hydra.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS268
SOMEONE scrambles behind a pedestal, flings away his smoking shield and examines his scorched hand. He peeks out at the pearl.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS269
Spews fire and he takes cover again.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS270
SOMEONE edges away, then notices two water fountains on a nearby wall.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS271
SOMEONE shuts his eyes. A hydra head swivels around the corner, fiery light crackling in its throat.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS272
Water gushes out, quickly flooding the floor. Under the teen's control it forms a wall between him and the hydra. As it pushes the creature back, SOMEONE creeps out, snatches the pearl and joins his friends. Grabbing his backpack he leads them to the exit.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS273
SOMEONE faces the hydra. From his bag he produces SOMEONE's head. As the hydra spews twinjets of fire at him, he raises the dead woman's sunglasses, exposing her eyes. An invisible barrier halts the flames about a foot from her stare.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS274
Her snakes go limp.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS275
His two friends stare as well. The hydra's heads become motionless as they turn to stone.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS276
SOMEONE lowers SOMEONE's head and his awestruck friends step up behind him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS277
Now a TV in a diner shows a news report as the young heroes eat.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS282
Now the pickup travels past an airport tarmac situated across the street from a sign reading Welcome to Fabulous Las Vegas, Nevada.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS283
As the truck drives through the strip
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS284
a fountain jets water in front of a cluster of towering hotel/casinos.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS285
They pass a row of older casinos blaring flashy lights.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS286
Fireworks blossom over a pair of high rises lit in a pinstriped pattern.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS287
An illuminated logo shows a dark pink dome-shaped flower over the words Lotus Hotel and Casino.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS288
Below the pickup pulls into an extravagantly lit drop-off area with limos and taxis.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS289
Inside a lavish buffet with a chocolate fountain overlooks a brand new black Maserati on a rotating platform.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS290
The teens eye the sports car, then head to the casino's crowded gaming area.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS291
Elaborate roller coasters and a SOMEONE wheel loom behind a fountain.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS292
As they move on a waitress intercepts them with a tray of pink hors d'oeuvre.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS294
Wide eyes shifting.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS295
With a raised eyebrow SOMEONE looks around as he slowly chews, then grins merrily.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS296
Now, SOMEONE struts through the casino, flanked by an entourage of gorgeous women.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS297
And another feeds him a lotus flower.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS298
A waitress presents a tray of lotus flowers to them.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS299
Now SOMEONE reclines in a plush white bathrobe with cucumber slices over his eyes. A buxom manicurist files his nails, while a pedicurist paints his cloven hooves cherry red.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS300
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE look on.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS301
He drops into a split, then springs up using only his goat legs.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS302
Perfectly synchronized series of movements.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS303
As he moves through the casino a waitress intercepts him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS304
He reaches a crowded video game arcade and pauses, gazing about.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS305
He stops at a pinball machine played by a thin young man with long, corn silk hair.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS306
He turns away and heads through a 1950s themed recreation area.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS307
He passes a craps table, then comes to a roulette game.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS308
A softly glowing green pearl sits nestled in one of the slots. As SOMEONE stares at it a waitress swoops in behind him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS309
SOMEONE eyes him wearily.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS310
Wearing an earpiece the bellhop speaks discreetly into a small microphone.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS311
SOMEONE returns to the club and finds SOMEONE about to eat a lotus flower.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS312
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE off. SOMEONE holds his crutches out as he runs separately. A group of guards surround him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS313
SOMEONE kicks a guard with both feet then fights off two more with his crutches. As they run into the gaming area, SOMEONE shoulder checks a casino worker. SOMEONE grabs a pool queue and swings it like a staff. She takes down a guard. SOMEONE leaps on to the roulette table, fights off two casino workers and grabs the pearl.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS316
The sports car plows through a pair of glass doors and speeds out of the brightly lit drop-off area. Cutting through a busy intersection, the Maserati swerves into the flow of traffic, then races past the other cars.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS317
A blaze of lights sears words next to the Southwestern coast.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS318
SOMEONE clenches the steering wheel. The Maserati weaves around the other cars as it speeds down the strip.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS319
Drive carefully. Come back soon.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS320
The sports car races through a barren desert landscape under a sky darkened with storm clouds.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS321
Thunderheads swirl over the iconic Hollywood sign.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS322
The radio plays a news report.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS323
Later the teens scramble along the base of its freestanding letters.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS324
Graffitied Greek letters rearrange themselves to form a message in English.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS325
Then stares past the sign,
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS326
where the earth grumbles away to make a door sized fissure.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS327
Cavernous space.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS328
Glow from circular recesses in the walls.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS329
As the teens follow a path along a broad, tranquil river
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS330
fill the doorway behind him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS331
They find a gaunt man in a monk like robe standing in a rowboat.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS332
his bony features.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS333
SOMEONE leads his friends over.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS334
It bursts into flames.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS336
The ferryman looks at him then extends his hand.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS337
And the man closes his bony fingers around them.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS338
As the teens take their seats the ferryman pushes away from the dock.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS339
The boat exits through a freestanding letter H in a towering hillside sign that reads Hell.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS340
SOMEONE points at a trail of floating objects.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS341
then releases it into the stream of discarded objects.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS342
on the jagged edge of a cliff.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS343
He shifts his gaze to an ominous mansion, which looms on a column of rock in the middle of the gorge.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS344
Old-fashioned lamp posts bookend either side of a docking area.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS345
Climb out of the boat.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS347
A three-tiered fountain sits in the foyer.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS350
He gulps.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS351
Now the teens follow SOMEONE into an enormous sitting room.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS352
Carved reliefs of bound, emaciated men flank a tall fireplace.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS353
He wears a leather vest and pants, and a black shirt with stylishly tattered sleeves. Facing SOMEONE, he spreads his arms.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS354
He morphs into the giant winged demon.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS356
Then gives Hades an apologetic smile.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS357
He picks up a globe made of bones and smashes it on the ground. The shattered pieces dissolve into smoke.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS358
Cloud takes on human form and materializes into SOMEONE.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS359
Flickers from behind the shield's arm strap.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS360
Then holds him out at arm's length and gazes tearfully at him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS361
Their attention to Hades.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS362
SOMEONE and SOMEONE also watch as the god of the underworld stoops down and shifts the arm strap aside on the shield.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS363
which grows longer as he pulls it out.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS365
They stalk closer, backing SOMEONE and the others toward the souls.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS366
Pushing the group to within a few feet of the fire.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS367
SOMEONE skips.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS368
They stop their advance and the fireplace grate closes behind the group.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS369
With the bolt clutched in her hand, SOMEONE kneels beside Hades.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS371
Taking the bolt from SOMEONE he retrieves the glowing pearls from his pocket.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS374
He, SOMEONE and SOMEONE place their pearls on the floor, then crush them under their feet.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS375
Billows out, engulfing their legs and travels up their bodies.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS376
which snakes its way out of the room.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS377
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch as the smoky trail disappears.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS378
She wiggles an inviting finger.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS379
A smoking trail zooms through the night sky making its way past the pointed art deco crown of the Chrysler Building.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS380
It swoops through the protective fence that surrounds the Empire State Building's observation deck.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS381
Then morphs into SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS382
SOMEONE points to dark storm clouds gathering above the building's pinnacle.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS384
Hovering in the air, SOMEONE swings his legs around and kicks SOMEONE in the head.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS385
The Lightning Thief pulls out his sword. Sparks fly as SOMEONE deflects his blow with a lightning bolt.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS386
SOMEONE kicks him, knocking him to the ground. The bolt falls from his hand.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS387
But SOMEONE swoops past her and grabs it.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS389
The three companions fall to the floor as lightning zaps the safety barrier behind them.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS390
With a power hungry smile, SOMEONE blasts away a chunk of the deck.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS394
SOMEONE scrambles to his backpack and pulls out his own pair of flying sneakers.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS395
He spots a helicopter rising in his direction and takes aim with the bolt.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS396
A flying SOMEONE knocks him from the ledge, and they plummet past the observation deck,
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS397
circle each other and come together again in a fierce grasp.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS398
SOMEONE swings at SOMEONE's face, then pins him against the building. The SOMEONE's back grinds against the wall as he continues to plunge downward.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS399
SOMEONE lands on a slanted roof.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS400
He steers himself toward an unfinished skyscraper.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS401
SOMEONE shoots it with lightning as SOMEONE swoops through an open floor.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS403
SOMEONE bursts through a wall and grabs him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS404
It tumbles out of the building.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS405
He soars back toward the Empire State Building his shoes' wings beating furiously.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS407
SOMEONE throws a dagger. It slices off one of SOMEONE's wings. The hero plummets, losing his grip on the bolt. As it tumbles toward a rooftop with a glowing skylight.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS408
As it tumbles toward a rooftop with a glowing skylight.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS409
Then weakly pushes himself up on all fours.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS410
In the bolt.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS412
Eyeing a water tower behind SOMEONE, SOMEONE shuts his eyes. The SOMEONE grins smugly.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS413
He takes aim.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS414
Turning, SOMEONE sees water jet from its splitting seams. The tank's cap flies off and its contents gush out in a swirling arc.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS415
Another vat nearby bursts open and the two streams converge. SOMEONE unleashes water from two more tanks, and it all combines to form a giant flowing barrier around the rooftop.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS416
The son of Poseidon holds the water at bay on either side of himself.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS417
SOMEONE flings his hands forward. The SOMEONE fires, but the water rushes in at him. It douses the charge and engulfs him. Energy crackles within the swirling mass. The maelstrom tosses SOMEONE about like a toy and the bolt wrenches from his grasp.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS418
Which evaporate in the nighttime air.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS419
SOMEONE bends over, resting his hands on his knees.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS420
Water rises to form a trident in the hero's hand. Catching the SOMEONE around the throat it sends him flying out into a river.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS421
Catching the SOMEONE around the throat it sends him flying out into a river.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS422
SOMEONE's winged sneakers flap uselessly beside it.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS423
SOMEONE carries the bolt in one hand and his sword in the other as he lands on the observation deck.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS424
In a supply closet, SOMEONE flips some switches on an electrical panel. Across the room two shelving units part to reveal double doors, which slide open, displaying the interior of an elevator.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS425
The Greek letter Omega gleams in the center of a sun emblem.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS426
The lights flicker as they brace themselves inside the turbulent chamber
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS427
Then burst from its pinnacle.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS428
Our view drifts past storm clouds to four towering pillars stationed around a stone booth on a platform.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS429
And SOMEONE steps out with SOMEONE.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS430
The base of a magnificent palace illuminating its columned facade.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS431
Timepiece sits in the center of a grand hall.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS432
While SOMEONE watches from a throne.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS433
The gods obediently take their seats in a semi-circle of white chairs. SOMEONE rises from his throne at the center and eyes the timepiece.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS434
A clockwork second hand rotates above panes of glass. With astrological markings.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS436
Casts onto the diminutive figures of the teens. The gods tower over them at more than 30 feet.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS438
SOMEONE, Poseidon, and the goddess with the long brown curls stare down at the teens.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS439
The demigods rush forward to meet him. He leans down and holds out his monstrous hand.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS440
In SOMEONE's hand the bolt grows in size and intensity.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS442
SOMEONE glances at a brown haired god who blinks confusedly.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS443
At Poseidon.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS444
Then shifts his proud gaze to his son.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS445
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE, who firmly holds SOMEONE's stare.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS447
To his seat.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS448
The beautiful goddess eyes the bolt-toting god as he sits.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS449
SOMEONE touches the boy's shoulder.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS451
Poseidon morphs into water and catches up with his son in human form.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS452
Poseidon extends his arm and they shake hands while sharing an amicable stare.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS453
Then he walks off
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS457
They stop walking as they notice SOMEONE sword fighting four male students at the same time.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS459
As SOMEONE continues across the lawn, more students pat his back.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS460
Blood caked on her shoulder.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS461
Then raises his hand.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS462
But SOMEONE snatches his sword.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS464
She keep sword at his throat.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS465
They each twirl their weapons in preparation and position themselves for a fight.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS466
SOMEONE blocks two of his strikes and swipes back at him.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS467
Our view widens to take in all of the battling demigods on the training field.
PERCY_JACKSON_LIGHTENING_THIEF_DVS468
We keep pulling back until our view encompasses the entire clearing, the surrounding forest and the lakeshore, which meanders off into the distance.