The thieves hustle out.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS17
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE and SOMEONE toward the distant
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS18
SOMEONE hands her an arrow.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS19
As the youngster keeps watch as his cohorts escape. Then, leans back and fires.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS20
The flaming arrow arcs through the air and lands.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS22
He defiantly tips his head back, then runs out the gate.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS23
SOMEONE halts by the barn. Her statuesque features, sullen. Inside, grain spills from a dangling punctured sack.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS25
Now, light flickers on another calligraphy parchment. King SOMEONE the Lion Heart, bankrupt of wealth and glory, is floundering his way back to England after ten years on his crusade.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS27
In slow motion, he fires.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS28
tears toward us in a burst of dust. A title. SOMEONE Hood. The man lowers the bow.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS29
Now, three hooded archers tromp out of a green forest. They tote small game bundled upside down on strings. The archer in the lead, a strapping man with an unshaven jaw, hikes them across a muddy road.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS30
A military camp,
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS31
The third archer hails distant horsemen. Beyond the encampments stands a stone fortress. Words appear. Chalice Castle, France, 1199 A. D. Now, with his hood pulled off his
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS35
galloped toward the castle.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS36
the defender aims across
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS37
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hop off the gate.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS38
SOMEONE walks off with his arm around SOMEONE. Now, at another castle, words appear.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS39
Tower of London. Royal Palace.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS40
Regal middle aged woman wearing a wimple strides down a hallway.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS41
She passes a string of rosary beads to a hand maid. She confronts an apple cheeked young woman in an elegant gown listening at
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS42
The regal woman bursts into the room.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS43
She yanks back the writhing sheets on the bed.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS44
Titles. Alas, it's done.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS45
She pulls the sheet over the girl's face.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS46
mistress dons the sheet again.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS47
SOMEONE looks away uncomfortably.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS48
Wrapped in the sheet, the mistress sits in SOMEONE's lap.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS49
In the king's tent.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS50
one of three cups and swirls them around each other on a board.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS51
SOMEONE reaches for the cups, but the man stops him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS52
then whips off the first cup.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS53
Eyeing SOMEONE, he yanks up another cup.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS54
The brawny man stares at the archer tauntingly then, lifts the middle cup.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS55
SOMEONE hesitantly lifts his gaze.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS56
SOMEONE's friends stand. They kneel again as SOMEONE and his opponent get to their feet. SOMEONE faces the archer.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS57
SOMEONE winces, squeezing his eyes shut, then lifts his head. As his brawny opponent stares at the ground, SOMEONE locks gazes with the monarch.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS58
As the king steps closer, SOMEONE bows his head.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS59
Morning. SOMEONE and his three cohorts sit and
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS60
there at the castle on the adjacent hill as the English army
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS61
Now, a lone horseman races through the
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS62
As the rider reaches a camp
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS63
Banks of the Seine, France. He dismounts. An imposing man with a closely trimmed beard greets him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS64
The rider turns over his sword. His dark, deep set eyes gazing from his helmet. On the river bank, a cooks serves oysters and wine to a man in a black and gold tunic.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS65
The imposing man presents SOMEONE who lowers his hood to reveal a bald head and raven like features.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS66
Philip of France. The king beckons.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS67
Keeping his watchful gaze fixed on Philip, SOMEONE approaches and sits beside him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS68
In English, please. Philip slurps down an oyster.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS69
He pries at it with a knife.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS70
Blood stains the oyster.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS71
He offers the bloody oyster to SOMEONE who takes it.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS72
He eyes the pearly and crimson flesh.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS74
SOMEONE eats the oyster
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS75
iThere s fire from below and he ducks behind a parapet
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS76
crossbow and aims.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS78
Across the way SOMEONE sees them. A physician arrives.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS79
wine skin and passes is to SOMEONE. The loyal knight puts it to the wounded king's lips and pours the liquid into his mouth. SOMEONE gulps it down.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS80
SOMEONE mournfully bows his head. SOMEONE stares slack jawed, then turns and breaks into a run. He dashes towards the stocks.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS81
SOMEONE hammers pegs out of the stocks, freeing the man.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS82
Tucked among the trees follows the group. Words appear.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS84
that his sword lodged at the end of its wired wrapped hilt, an octagonal belongings.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS85
SOMEONE ducks.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS86
The imposing Frenchman joins him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS87
A man nods and steps away.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS88
moves along the looting men. One takes a golden emerald ring from a victim's finger.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS89
He flips aside a crusader's chain mail hood, but finds an unfamiliar face. Now, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE gripping the spear in his own gut.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS90
SOMEONE grips the spear shaft.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS92
his gaze to the restless white horse.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS93
A grizzled man finds it, but the animal flees
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS94
he grabs SOMEONE's ankle.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS95
He spits at SOMEONE's feet.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS96
Elsewhere, SOMEONE leads his companions through the woods. They each carry camp supplies.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS97
men carry long bows. As they reach a path, they king's horse approaches at a full gallop. SOMEONE steps out before it.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS98
But the Frenchman rides out
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS99
SOMEONE sets off in fast pursuit, leading his peers along a winding trail.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS100
sight where the Frenchmen busily loot their victims.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS101
SOMEONE turns. In the woods, SOMEONE and his men creep halfway down the hill. They draw their bows and fire, killing a number of looters.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS102
SOMEONE flees, urging his goateed
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS103
over his shoulder and the arrow grazes his cheek.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS104
the carnage. The red haired archer finds a knight's purse empty, then salvages a small cup. A few feet uphill, the brawny man checks on SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS105
SOMEONE follows the faint cry to SOMEONE, clutching the spear pinning him to the ground. The knight's chest heaves and a few coins lies scattered beside him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS106
as SOMEONE plucks the nearby sword from the ground. Kneeling, he lays it on SOMEONE's chest as his companions look on. The bright sun halos SOMEONE as he regards the knight.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS107
unnoticed SOMEONE's horse returning.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS108
SOMEONE frowns to himself and swallows hard.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS109
SOMEONE turns his face skyward. His eyes widen. His blood stained lips quivering.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS110
The knight's jaw goes slack and his eyes half close.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS111
SOMEONE tightens his jaw. Reaching down, he gently closes SOMEONE's eyes. He makes the sign of the cross, then notices a spot of blood at the center of his palm.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS112
SOMEONE notices a small rectangular case hanging from SOMEONE's shoulder. He opens it. shakes out a folded piece of parchment and unfolds
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS113
map of western of France with a red line stretching between its northern and south western coasts. SOMEONE stands staring at it thoughtfully.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS114
By the king's horse, SOMEONE holds the crown aloft. He sets it on his head with a grin. It covers his eyes.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS115
SOMEONE faces each of his companions.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS116
Later, at the head of a fresh grave, a simple wooden cross stands marked with a J.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS117
Other shallow graves dot the hill. As his companions step away, SOMEONE sets a helmet by SOMEONE's grave. Now, as a rider approaches a humble country chapel, a word appears - Nottingham.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS118
Friar turns as SOMEONE arrives and faces a second clergyman.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS119
With a subtle glare, she leaves the preacher. Upon her approach, the friar humbly bows his round jowly head.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS120
Sitting on a bench, SOMEONE holds him in an appraising gaze.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS121
Marching toward the exit, SOMEONE pauses by Father SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS122
proceeds to the heavy door and yanks it open. Glancing back
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS123
Father SOMEONE and SOMEONE follow her out. As she mounts a dark horse, the father gazes wearily at her. Behind him, SOMEONE watches with an admiring smile as she rides away.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS124
He eyes a bug flying near his face.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS125
A cart sits loaded with straw beehives. SOMEONE frowns quizzically.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS126
encampments set in view of a ship at the water's edge. A man on board spies their approach.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS127
man with wind tousled curls strides up to the edge of the deck and watches the approaching
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS134
SOMEONE frowns. In a hazy flashback, a tow headed boy runs into a crowd.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS135
As two more force a man to his knees. On the ship, SOMEONE plants the SOMEONE sword downward. He remembers a soldier carrying the boy away, then
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS136
reflects sunlight. Words appear - the Tempts Estuary, England.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS137
In the ship, light seeps between the deck on SOMEONE
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS138
who sleeps below with his arms wrapped around his sword.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS139
Rubbing his eyes, he sees SOMEONE and SOMEONE asleep on the floor nearby.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS140
his mouth opened as he sleeps.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS141
SOMEONE rises and peers outside.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS142
SOMEONE hurriedly heads back into the cabin and wakes his sleeping friends.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS143
Now, in the royal palace, Queen SOMEONE strides to a pair of SOMEONE windows in a stone alcove. She sees the approaching ship.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS144
She turns to a servant.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS145
The servant curtsies and heads off. Queen SOMEONE steps away from the windows.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS146
They bow as the queen approach.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS147
A band master holds up his hand and four drummers stop.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS148
He heads toward the queen.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS150
SOMEONE steps into the light and swaps a look with his goateed comrade.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS151
SOMEONE works his jaw. Back at the dock, SOMEONE draws nearer
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS152
Reaching her, he drops to one knee and holds out the covered crown.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS153
the red and gold flag, Queen SOMEONE finds SOMEONE's helmet underneath ringed by the English crown. Prince SOMEONE's lips part as he eyes it. His mother stutters. SOMEONE's French mistress averts her gaze and reaches for the prince's hand. She squeezes it.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS154
SOMEONE and his comrade join the crowd and see the queen holding the fallen monarch's battle crown.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS155
Prince SOMEONE drops to one knee and prayerfully folds his hands. His mother sets the helmet upon his head.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS156
SOMEONE glances heavily at SOMEONE, then stands.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS157
the crowd obeys. He faces SOMEONE whose head remains bowed.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS158
SOMEONE lifts his head slightly.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS159
SOMEONE briefly meets his gaze.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS160
SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE subtly head off.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS161
King SOMEONE removes one of his rings and holds it up. SOMEONE drops on to one knee. SOMEONE offers the ring, then retracts it.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS162
SOMEONE looks up uneasily. King SOMEONE blinks.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS163
He taps the ring on his helmet.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS164
He slides the ring back on his finger.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS165
SOMEONE takes his mistress's hand.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS166
The crowd parts for the king and SOMEONE withdraws. King SOMEONE spots SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS167
The scar at the corner of SOMEONE's mouth.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS168
SOMEONE takes his mistress's hand. He eyes SOMEONE's comrade as they pass.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS169
The goateed man stands. He and SOMEONE watch as the procession heads off. SOMEONE
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS170
SOMEONE finds the bearded wavy haired nobleman addressing him and steps closer.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS171
SOMEONE shakes his hand.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS172
SOMEONE narrows his eyes.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS173
He meets his goateed comrade's gaze.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS174
The man nods and heads off. SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE, then turns away. Later, SOMEONE rides
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS175
Now, in the lush green fields of Nottingham, Lady SOMEONE
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS176
farmer leading a horse and plow.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS177
Taking the Clydesdale's bridle,
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS179
The Sheriff parallels SOMEONE as she plows.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS180
He yanks SOMEONE close
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS181
He kisses her, but she bites him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS182
She spits.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS183
The sheriff rides off and two other men on horseback follow.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS184
Lady SOMEONE nervously covers her mouth.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS185
She turns toward the forest and sees a group of bare chested boys running away.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS187
Kneeling at ground.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS188
SOMEONE counts coins.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS189
SOMEONE solemnly faces his friends.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS190
He shifts his gaze to the other men, then turns back to SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS191
Daytime. At the royal palace.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS192
SOMEONE takes the French woman's hand.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS193
SOMEONE looks on.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS194
King SOMEONE rises from his throne.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS195
He waves off his courtiers who bow and hurry out leaving the Royal family, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and one other chancellor.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS196
his crown, hangs it at the back of his throne and sits.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS197
SOMEONE moves from his place beside the king's throne.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS198
Queen SOMEONE watches as the bald man strolls to the center of the room. SOMEONE furrows his brow.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS199
SOMEONE gives him a look, then faces King SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS200
SOMEONE stares.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS201
The queen slaps his face. Grabbing his cheek, King SOMEONE stumbles. Queen SOMEONE storms out. SOMEONE's mistress eyes her as she leaves, then turns her haughty gaze to her husband. The king brushes his cheek.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS202
He glances at SOMEONE. As he steps toward SOMEONE, he rubs his cheek again with the back of his hand.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS203
A man in a white mantle and coif joins them. King SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a patronizing look.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS204
The white robed official extends a hand.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS205
SOMEONE slides an oval ring from his finger and sets it in the chancellor's palm. He frowns at King SOMEONE who dismisses him. SOMEONE bows.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS206
SOMEONE watches with a smirk. Straightening, SOMEONE glances at him, then strides off. SOMEONE takes the ring from the chancellor. He tosses it in the air as he turns to his bald friend. Later, SOMEONE heads down a corridor.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS207
SOMEONE catches up. SOMEONE spreads his arms wide.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS208
He lowers his arm arms and turns partway to the conspirator watching him from the corner
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS209
SOMEONE strolls pass SOMEONE, then faces him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS210
SOMEONE shifts his weight and extends his arm showing SOMEONE the oval ring in his hand. He lifts his brow arrogantly, then continues down the corridor. As he heads away, he spreads his arms imitating SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS211
SOMEONE faced soldier.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS213
green forest, SOMEONE and his men ride their horses along a path.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS214
He sees more boys running through the trees.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS216
They arrive onto a grassy hillside.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS217
as they arrive at the village of modest straw roofed huts
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS218
SOMEONE's dome shaped hive sit on
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS219
SOMEONE dismounts.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS220
just a few copulating thrusts
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS221
SOMEONE glances up a hill.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS222
Holding SOMEONE's sword, SOMEONE shifts his eyes thoughtfully, then gives a nod.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS223
SOMEONE gapes after him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS224
away from his face as he watches SOMEONE leave.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS225
SOMEONE docks another bee.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS226
The men pay SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS227
heads up the hillside through the remnants of the stone archway.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS228
As he gallops down a dirt
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS229
loaded with straw. He rides through an entryway and a stone
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS230
Two geese shuffle away from him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS231
SOMEONE hammering out.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS232
SOMEONE stops behind SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS233
staring down at her. SOMEONE
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS234
SOMEONE looks over her shoulder, appraises SOMEONE, then resumes her work.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS235
SOMEONE gets to her feet.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS236
As he dismounts and faces her.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS237
SOMEONE averts her gaze.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS238
She quickly turns her back to him. With a stoic expression, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE through a gate into the castle courtyard. She stumbles and her face falters.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS239
She catches herself and rubs her chest.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS240
Now, they enter a stable area.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS241
SOMEONE gestures to a servant.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS242
SOMEONE hands over the white horse's reins, then unfastens SOMEONE's sword from its saddle. SOMEONE removes her shoes and sets them on a
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS243
Her shoulders heave.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS244
SOMEONE pours water into a shallow pan. SOMEONE takes a seat and washes her feet, glancing uncomfortably at the archer.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS245
summoning a breath.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS246
His lips stuttering hesitantly.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS247
a door to a stone colonnade, then faces the archer sternly.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS248
hunter's jaw hangs slack.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS249
his hand around the hilt of SOMEONE's sword. SOMEONE draws it halfway from its sheath, his eyes gazing off tearfully.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS250
The aging nobleman hobbles to his daughter-in-law, cradles her head and tenderly presses his lips to her temple.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS251
and SOMEONE treads toward him. SOMEONE's fingers find the archer's neck, then face. He sweeps one hand down SOMEONE's forehead, then touches his brow with both thumbs. His fingers drift appraisingly down the visitor's temples.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS252
Later, in a bath chamber, steam rises from a large vat. Two maids bustle out leaving SOMEONE and SOMEONE alone.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS253
She halts in the doorway.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS254
She turns back to SOMEONE at the door.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS255
Her gaze darts as she arches her brow, affecting an air of indifference.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS256
The archer stands stiff as she unbuttons a clasp at this throat. She lays the ends of the chain mail hood on his shoulders.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS257
She obediently removes the cape like garment and sets it down, then yanks out the lacings of his tunic setting it aside as well. She works on his chain mail sleeve. SOMEONE watches tenderly. Later, he bends at the waist and worms his way out of the mail hauberk. SOMEONE crouches, tugging it off over his head, then falls on her rear when it finally drops to the floor.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS258
wearily gets up and unlaces the back of his long tunic. Now, she works it off of him as he bends over. Freed from the garment, he straightens and faces her bare chested. His burly pecs heave beneath his broad shoulders.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS259
Brushing past him, she strides
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS260
The widow give SOMEONE a final glance before heading out. The archer rinses his hands and face, then beams.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS261
laces his boot. Now, servants hurry out of the kitchen carrying bowls of food into the banquet hall.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS262
SOMEONE fetches the wine in a pitcher of water. At the table, SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS263
SOMEONE waters down SOMEONE's wine.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS264
She studies SOMEONE from across the table.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS265
averts her eyes from the archers gaze.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS266
SOMEONE obliviously sips his watered down wine. SOMEONE watches, then glances at SOMEONE and leans back in his chair.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS267
The shore. From several tall arch shaped
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS268
spy peeks out at them. He watches stoically
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS269
backs away and crouches at a wooden cage. He opens a hatch on top, then reaches inside.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS270
He pulls out a pigeon.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS271
into a slender pouch on the birds leg and releases it. It flaps away into the night.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS272
He entered the kitchen and SOMEONE closes the door on them. In the banquet hall, a wolf hound
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS273
blazing fire on the hearth, SOMEONE sheaths his sword as SOMEONE approaches. She folds her hands at her waist.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS274
She trumps off toward a stairwell. Lounging in a chair, SOMEONE watches her go.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS275
Her lips part irritably. She strides to the center of the room to address him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS276
She gives a mocking curtsy, then storms off, shoving her fingers in her mouth.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS277
ahead of her, she trots upstairs with her skirts hiked up.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS278
inscrutably then glances at the fire and bites his lower lip. He picks up SOMEONE's sword and eyes the inscription on the hilt - until lambs become lions. Later, he treads into SOMEONE's bed chamber. Warm light flickers on a hefty four poster bed. Curtains separate it from a sitting area in front of a fireplace where SOMEONE tosses bedding to the floor and eyes the archer haughtily.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS279
She gestures at the bedding, then strides to the curtains toward her bed.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS280
She whips the curtains shut and SOMEONE plods over to the bedding with the dogs.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS281
SOMEONE lights a candle.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS282
SOMEONE glances at the curtains. Back lit by the candle, the sheer fabric offers a thinly veiled view of SOMEONE stepping out of her dress. SOMEONE lies down in front of the fire and pets a wolf hound lying next to him. Resting his head on his hand, he looks to the curtain. SOMEONE's silhouette pulls another layer off over her head, leaving her clad only in her chamois. SOMEONE politely rolls onto his back and looks away. Now, the bare branches of towering trees sway against the sky. SOMEONE leaves a camp and prowls into the misty woods.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS283
A figure rises from the darkness. Moonlight gleaming on his conical helm. He and SOMEONE hike the short distance toward each other.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS285
The Frenchman smirks and steps to SOMEONE's side and gestures toward the forest.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS286
Dozens of armed French soldiers appear in the mist and head toward them. Daytime. In a dove cote, a shaggy bird keeper, as they flutter away, he seizes one.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS287
and the aid plucks the tiny scroll from the pouch on its leg.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS288
SOMEONE carefully unrolls the scroll as the aid looks on behind him. The noble man raises a magnifying lens and reads news of the French soldiers landing.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS289
Meanwhile, at SOMEONE castle, SOMEONE
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS290
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's sword.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS291
with a wry huff. Later, SOMEONE rides the king's white steed.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS292
hair billowing behind her.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS293
horses at a cross roads between fields.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS294
ride past the man at a market stall.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS295
A woman joins them.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS296
SOMEONE nods and glances uncomfortably at SOMEONE as they ride on.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS297
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE, SOMEONE and Little SOMEONE bathing at a trough. SOMEONE splashes
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS298
SOMEONE trots over to them ahead of SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS299
The tall woman and two of the dancing beauties emerge from doorways nearby. Noticing SOMEONE, they quickly retreat.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS300
She smirks at SOMEONE and rides off. He wears a bashful smile.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS301
SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride up to the church where men load sacks
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS302
A rat faced deacon nearby glares at SOMEONE as he sips from a tin mug. SOMEONE leans into Tuck.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS303
A slow smile spreads across SOMEONE's pudgy cheeks.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS304
SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride off.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS305
Later, in his living quarters, SOMEONE pours a cup of mead. From a copper pot standing over an open flame, he lifts away a stick tied with mulling sacks and gives his concoction a stir. SOMEONE enters, sets down a bucket near several sleeping men and ambles over to Tuck, who hands him a cup.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS306
They each take a swig of the friar's concoction.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS307
They tap cups and finish their drinks.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS308
SOMEONE strides back to his bucket, picks it up and splashes water in the sleeping men. They bolt upright. It's SOMEONE, Little SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS310
Now, at twilight, carts of grain make their way along a narrow road through the woods. Several guards
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS311
upon a hooded figure with a long bow.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS312
SOMEONE also emerged.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS313
Hanging from a tree, SOMEONE
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS314
Merry Men ride off with the grain.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS315
shuffle along with tiny steps. Now, puffy clouds reflect the moonlight, casting a gentle glow on Nottingham's fields as the Merry Men plot to reclaim the grain. In slow motion, SOMEONE marches down a row of furrowed soil, tossing seed by the handful from a sack slung over his shoulder.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS316
other patch of soil, SOMEONE drizzles grain from his fingertips. Little SOMEONE works beside SOMEONE who wears a joyful grin.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS317
turning on the spot as rain begins to fall upon the fields. It starts gently, then quickly gathers force as lightning flashes overhead.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS318
SOMEONE sits by the hearth in the banquet hall. A fiery glow illuminating her noble features as she gazes downward. At her feet, SOMEONE sleeps on the floor in an undershirt, a blanket covering him from the waist down. He wakes.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS319
She crouches beside SOMEONE and draws the blanket up over his shoulder. Under his tender stare, her warm smile fades.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS320
form silhouetted against the fire. Her gaze lingers on SOMEONE as she sidles away. She turns her back to him and strides across the great hall, her arms swinging stiffly at her sides. He watches from the floor as she pauses. Her fair skin resplendent in the glow of a moonlit window. She glances back toward SOMEONE with parted lips, then continues out. Now, as legions of soldiers march double time through the woods,
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS322
archers arrive.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS323
proclamation on the cross.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS324
We watch SOMEONE and his men terrorize.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS327
On the floor, he rolls onto his back.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS328
dropping an iron chandelier on him. Now, SOMEONE arrives in a windblown field
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS329
The Queen Mother turns.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS330
As SOMEONE joins her, a servant pours water from a kettle.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS331
She hands of the owl to an attendant.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS332
Now, SOMEONE's mistress sits in the light of a blazing fire as SOMEONE addresses her.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS333
Later, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS334
He moves in close to her face, seething.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS336
With glistening eyes, SOMEONE looks down to find SOMEONE holding a dagger to her own heart. He closes his hand over hers and stares into her eyes, taking in her earnest gaze. His face ceases tearfully. The spotless dagger falls to the floor.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS337
He embraces her. His mouth devouring hers in a passionate kiss. Now, a hooded rider arrives at the edge of Nottingham.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS338
He pauses briefly, glancing over his shoulder. Later, as he arrives at a blacksmith's forge, a glimpse beneath his hood reveals him as SOMEONE's goateed accomplice.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS339
as a man enters
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS340
The goateed Frenchman enters glowering from beneath his hood.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS341
The sheriff's male servants depart, but a crone dressed in black remains at the table. The Frenchman advances, pulling his hood back. He takes out a letter and offers it to the sheriff. The lawman hesitates, then snatches it from his hand. He slices open its wax seals with a knife and unfolds the pages. His brow lifts in shock as he reads.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS342
The Frenchman glowers.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS343
SOMEONE walk their horses through a village farm.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS345
As she reaches for her horse, he joins her at her side. He gives her a boost into the saddle, then gently sets her foot in a stirrup.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS346
SOMEONE shyly looks away.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS347
SOMEONE mounts his horse and she leads him onward.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS348
The mill's large wooden wheel. SOMEONE looks over her shoulder to find her companion pausing to take in his surroundings. He meets her gaze and she gives a coy warm smile. SOMEONE watches her with a furrowed brow, then rides up to meet her. Now, as SOMEONE trains a horse in a muddy field, words appear.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS349
SOMEONE's newly trained horse prances past
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS350
Meanwhile, SOMEONE and his men
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS352
From his saddle, SOMEONE leans closer to his adviser.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS353
distinctive scar on his cheek, joins SOMEONE at his side.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS354
Now, in a tent, SOMEONE taps excess water off the dagger and carefully proceeds to shave with it. His goateed comrade approaches and SOMEONE meets him in the entryway.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS355
SOMEONE's jaw hangs slack. He shifts his cagey eyes and nods resolutely.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS356
His comrade smiles and heads off. SOMEONE faces a messenger.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS358
The messenger stands, gives a slight bow and strides off. SOMEONE
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS359
toward his shaving mirror, studying his scarred reflection.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS360
He put a hot splint to his facial scar.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS361
The archer pours two mugs.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS362
Both men drink.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS363
This is her with a peaceful gaze and she reaches out.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS365
Now, the orphans of the wood jog through a nearby field. They hide behind a short rise and spy on the village festivities. One dirt smeared adolescent, gripping a pole arm, eyes the village with a jealous longing pout. More armed boys run past. Later, in SOMEONE's bed chamber, two mice forage a table of picked over food. One mouse madly cycles his hind legs to climb up into a footed bowl.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS366
SOMEONE listens, seated at SOMEONE's bedside.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS367
Father and son make hand prints in wet mortar. SOMEONE reads an engraving.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS368
Stone is laid on the base of a cross at Barnsdale.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS369
SOMEONE hugs his son SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS370
He tosses him in the air.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS371
SOMEONE studies the old man uneasily, then blinks his eyes shut and swallows. The flash back continues.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS372
Young SOMEONE jogs through a crowd. A gloved hand wearing a chain mail sleeves pats his shoulder.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS373
SOMEONE's father bravely faces the authorities.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS374
A younger SOMEONE gazes solemnly. SOMEONE surrenders his sword to a soldier as two others force him to his knees
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS375
brings it down. Back in the present, SOMEONE's face ceases tearfully. He hangs his head.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS376
SOMEONE knits his brow sympathetically.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS377
SOMEONE lifts his gaze.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS378
He holds SOMEONE's hand and rests his brow upon it. Morning in the banquet hall.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS379
A messenger bows.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS380
The messenger bows and heads out.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS381
SOMEONE watches from the staircase.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS382
SOMEONE stretches out his arms. SOMEONE steps into his embrace and the elderly man pats his back.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS383
Later, SOMEONE rides up
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS384
SOMEONE smiles his thanks as SOMEONE heads off.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS385
He turns his white horse and rides away.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS386
to leaded glass window and gazes out through the diamond shaped panes. SOMEONE leads his men out of the courtyard and rides around the corner toward the homestead entryway.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS388
King SOMEONE arrives.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS389
King SOMEONE draws his sword halfway from its sheath and offers its hilt to the baron.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS390
SOMEONE glares.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS391
Now, SOMEONE rides into the charred ruins at Barnsdale. The intricately carved stone cross stands unharmed in the deserted village center. SOMEONE stares at it as he rides closer. The archer dismounts and his men follow suit.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS392
SOMEONE ties his horse to a wooden beam, then treads toward the cross and the stone steps forming its base. He studies it uneasily.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS393
Dropping his eyes to the ground, he crouches and plants one hand in the mud.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS394
SOMEONE lifts his face.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS395
He remembers his father lifting his face as the soldier bring him to his knees. The archer bows his head, then looks back to the cross.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS396
He stands and draws his sword.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS397
With the pummel, he hammers four corners of a stone step set on the octagonal base of the monument.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS398
SOMEONE wedges the blade underneath the stone, levers it upward and leans it back.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS399
underside bears the engraving. Rise and rise again until lambs become lions. In the border, the archer finds a child sized hand print beside that of a grown man. He slips his hand into his father's print. It fits perfectly.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS400
He slowly straightens, then sheaths his sword.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS401
Beside him, SOMEONE studies the engraving.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS402
SOMEONE strides forward.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS403
SOMEONE and King SOMEONE see SOMEONE and his men at the back of the assembled town's people
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS404
The king sneers.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS405
King SOMEONE winces thoughtfully, then leans toward SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS406
He looks out to the crowd.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS407
village and people scatter.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS410
soldier discovers a closet packed of food.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS411
He shuffles toward the door, gripping a sword
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS412
He enters the courtyard.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS413
SOMEONE gazes sorrowfully.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS414
SOMEONE stalks toward the old man and licks the edge of his grotesque arrow scar. He leans close and gives a taunting smile.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS416
SOMEONE stabs a legionnaire shield
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS417
they lock blades. The blind man
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS418
He knocks SOMEONE down causing the bald thug from behind.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS420
He collapses face down.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS421
the man extends his hand.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS422
Meanwhile, in the woods, the masked boys creep towards the village. The lead boy crouches and watches the legionnaires violently rounding up
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS423
His eyes peer solemnly from his beastly mask. Now, soldiers shove SOMEONE into a building and yank
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS424
He struggles to open it.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS425
He fearfully throws it down.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS426
SOMEONE stands in the shadows.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS427
She edges out.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS428
sword belt dropped from his waist. SOMEONE dashed
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS429
bolted shut. She turns, putting her back to it as the Frenchman advances. Smiling rakishly, he removes his gloves. SOMEONE tries to dart past,
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS430
He leans in close. SOMEONE recoils as he paws her face and smells her neck.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS432
Meanwhile, French soldiers. Inside, several women are looking around.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS433
On the ground, a drunk Frenchman playing a drum falls over. In the shed, SOMEONE raises her skirts above her knee boot revealing her milky white leg. The Frenchman snarls lustily and sinks down before her. As he leans his head toward her raised skirts, a sickened scowl overtakes SOMEONE's face and she plunges a dagger into the back of his neck.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS434
but she kicks him down.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS436
SOMEONE leads
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS438
teen orphan pokes his head through and extends a hand.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS439
SOMEONE retrieves the Frenchman's belt and passes it up sword first. Grabbing its leather strap, she
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS440
several orphans climb down from the roof.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS443
They pass an infant through a window.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS444
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pick off Frenchmen.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS446
as he walks pass the the crowd,
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS447
SOMEONE sees a cart arriving, pulled by her Clydesdales. noticing SOMEONE as she approaches the cart.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS448
Two pepper haired farm hands meet her. With a mournful gaze, one them holds out Sir SOMEONE's sword. SOMEONE purses her lips as she stares at the fallen man's weapon. Accepting it, she manages a stoic nod. SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE. Facing the servants, SOMEONE thanks them with a nod. SOMEONE arrives behind her.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS449
As she faces him, her brow furrows woefully. She holds up the sword and hangs her head. SOMEONE steps closer and the devastated woman lays her brow on his shoulder. He gently cups her head and shuts his eyes.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS450
Now, laid out in an open wicker coffin, Sir SOMEONE's body lies clad in snowy robes and surrounded by greenery. One hand holds his sword upon his chest. SOMEONE tucks a sprig under his wrist and lays a hand fondly upon his. As servants stand ready with lit torches, she climbs down from the pyre. SOMEONE and his friends respectfully look on him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS451
The flames spread quickly devouring the stacked hay and greenery. The fire and smoke soon blot the dead nobleman from view.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS452
Beneath the overcast sky, the mourners watch the blaze situated before the ruined stone arch.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS453
Later, SOMEONE addresses SOMEONE as he readies his horse.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS454
SOMEONE regards her squarely. He steps closer.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS455
She allows a faint coy smile. SOMEONE moves in close and her lips meet his repeatedly sharing eager tender kisses.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS456
They part slightly. Their noses brushing against each other. SOMEONE stares lovingly at her and draws a deep breath. SOMEONE joyfully plants another kiss on his lips and takes a step back. As his mounted friends look on a few yards off, SOMEONE climbs astride his horse. He gazes down at the noble woman who smiles at him serenely. Her blue eyes sparkling.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS457
She beams after him as he leads his three trusted friends down the country road. SOMEONE proudly watches his departure.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS459
He sits up.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS460
hand ready by conical pyres of wood.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS463
SOMEONE follows the soldier's
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS464
soldiers light the nearest pyre.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS465
pyre's ignite one after another in sequence. Foot soldiers patrol close to the surf
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS467
Now, we soar over hills blanketed with emerald green
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS468
green hillside, marked with white horse.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS469
Across a rolling field, mounted troops ride into view.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS470
SOMEONE leads the others off the path.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS471
In full armor, SOMEONE and King SOMEONE ride out to meet SOMEONE and his companions.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS472
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap look.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS473
we watch the army advance.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS474
the narrow beach front dotted by the signal fires, the rocky cliffs behind them.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS475
Several dozen ships dot the coastal waters.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS477
capsizes, spilling armored men into the slope leading down to the beach.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS480
The archers take aim.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS482
The new comer leads a number of mounted troops on to the beach.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS484
mysterious leader who lifts the helmet's visor
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS485
SOMEONE stops short. SOMEONE resolutely holds
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS486
She flips down her visor and returns to the battle.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS493
He seizes another in a choke hold
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS494
She glares at SOMEONE
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS497
A dead soldier pierced by arrows.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS498
SOMEONE races to SOMEONE and finds her laying still in the water. Standing beside her, he raises his bow.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS499
SOMEONE rides away from the battle. SOMEONE draws back an arrow.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS500
The arrow soars free. We ride the
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS501
SOMEONE's neck as he rides in the
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS502
he lifts her upper body cradles her.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS503
As he raises her visor, a drop of his blood falls on her pale skin. Water gurgles from her mouth. SOMEONE pulls her closer and her helmet falls off revealing a leather
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS504
touches her face and she opens her
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS505
Blood trickles from his wounded head to her porcelain cheeks. He pulls away and strokes her face. She wraps an arm around him and
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS506
On shore, SOMEONE cradles SOMEONE in his arms as he trudges
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS507
He eyes the king, then points to SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS508
King SOMEONE sees SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS509
a French battle flag sinks to the ocean floor.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS511
Now, in London. King SOMEONE hold his hand as they walk side by side into the towers outer courtyard. They approach two thrones on a canopied platform. At the front of the crowd, SOMEONE and Queen SOMEONE bow as the young couple passes. SOMEONE occupies one throne while King SOMEONE stands in front of his and reads the charter. As he runs a finger down the document, SOMEONE and Queen SOMEONE watch tensely.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS512
King SOMEONE lifts his gaze to the crowd.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS513
SOMEONE shifts uneasily.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS514
SOMEONE interjects.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS515
The tyrant turns away from the crowd.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS516
Now in Nottingham, peasants bundle golden sheaves of wheat and cart them off. The sheriff and his men ride into town.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS517
in a tree bearing several dog eared decrees.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS518
He unrolls a document and reads.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS519
The crowd watches as the sheriff uses one hand to steady the decree on the tree trunk.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS520
The villagers remain still.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS521
The sheriff stares fearfully into the surrounding forest. Now, SOMEONE rides his white steed among the trees. As he heads deeper into the woods, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS522
SOMEONE carries a deer over his shoulders.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS523
SOMEONE and some orphan boys step a pace with SOMEONE as well.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS524
as high above their heads and watches them pass. They arrive at a makeshift village of straw roofs and stick walled huts deep in the forest.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS525
She spoons medicine into a young boy's mouth. She pats
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS526
other orphan sits. She watches
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS527
boys gather around SOMEONE.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS528
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE watching him and heads toward her. She smiles.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS529
He wraps one arm around her waist and she does the same to him.
ROBIN_HOOD_DVS530
They turn in a circle.