American border MPs exchange a North Korean man for the blonde woman and her escort.
SALT_DVS18
He nods toward an unshaven man.
SALT_DVS19
He hurries toward the border.
SALT_DVS20
The blonde woman gazes stoically at the unshaven man. Her colleague glances at her, his brow arched.
SALT_DVS21
As they pass the South Korean soldiers at the raised barricade, she blinks tearfully. The unshaven man takes a step forward his expression inscrutable.
SALT_DVS22
She strides toward the civilian who stares anxiously at her injured face. Jagged geometric pieces of the image separate from each other like shards of glass. The central pieces slide together and form a title as the picture around them fades to black. Salt. Now pedestrians pass a high-rise apartment building. Words appear, Washington D. C. present day. In an apartment, the civilian works at a kitchen table, his cheeks now smoothly shaven. A scruffy dog yawns in a dog bed behind him. The blonde peeks at the man from around the doorway. Her sultry eyes study him lovingly from above her high cheekbones and pouty lips. On the table, a tarantula climbs up the wall of a terrarium. The man looks up at the woman and smiles.
SALT_DVS23
She pours a mug of coffee.
SALT_DVS25
The dog eyes her as she hugs her husband from behind then leans over his shoulder and kisses him on his lips and forehead.
SALT_DVS27
Now in her cubical at Rink Petroleum, the blonde woman watches an instructional video.
SALT_DVS28
Her colleague steps up.
SALT_DVS29
She shows a folded paper napkin.
SALT_DVS30
Later, they head through the lobby.
SALT_DVS31
A security monitor shows their names, SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS33
They rescan their IDs and pass back through the security gate. Now in a hallway, all three approach two other men.
SALT_DVS35
Drop their cellphones in a metal box and enter an observation area overlooking an interrogation room.
SALT_DVS37
SOMEONE watches him closely.
SALT_DVS38
A monitor shows his brain activity.
SALT_DVS40
SOMEONE picks up a pack of cigarettes and an ashtray then inserts a small radio receiver into her ear. She adjusts it outside the interrogation room.
SALT_DVS41
She heads through the door.
SALT_DVS42
She places the ashtray and cigarettes on the table beside the defector then takes a seat opposite.
SALT_DVS43
The grizzled, middle-aged Russian notes her diamond wedding ring.
SALT_DVS45
He locks her sunken eyes on her.
SALT_DVS50
SOMEONE leans toward her.
SALT_DVS51
Subtitles - I came here to tell you a story.
SALT_DVS52
I don't like stories.
SALT_DVS55
The Soviet couple peers down at us sobbing.
SALT_DVS56
In a hospital corridor, SOMEONE clutches SOMEONE inconsolably.
SALT_DVS58
An image of flowers lying on a tiny grave dissolves into a helicopter soaring over a dreary river dotted with eyelets.
SALT_DVS59
He wears a ring.
SALT_DVS60
The chopper arrives at a fortress.
SALT_DVS61
The children kiss his ring.
SALT_DVS63
A boy's hand shoots up.
SALT_DVS64
A child with a scarred cheek raises his hand. The spymaster whips him savagely. Back in the present.
SALT_DVS68
SOMEONE gives a slow nod.
SALT_DVS69
SOMEONE gives an amused smile.
SALT_DVS71
In the observation room, SOMEONE and SOMEONE look up sharply.
SALT_DVS72
SOMEONE storms out of the interrogation and into the observation room.
SALT_DVS73
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE who gapes at her. SOMEONE eyes her colleagues worriedly then strides forward
SALT_DVS74
into the hall and retrieves her cellphone from the metal box.
SALT_DVS76
He gestures toward the interrogation room.
SALT_DVS77
SOMEONE ushers the blonde agent into the now vacant room.
SALT_DVS78
He shuts the door and faces SOMEONE. In the interrogation room, SOMEONE paces. Through a window she observes the two men conversing animatedly in the hall.
SALT_DVS81
Now a green light briefly flashes red. The CIA officer and a security escort lead SOMEONE through a door and into a hallway. At an elevator, the CIA officer waves his ID card in front of a scanner and hits a call button.
SALT_DVS82
Enter it and the doors close.
SALT_DVS84
And brutally with the blade. Meanwhile.
SALT_DVS85
SOMEONE paces in the interrogation room.
SALT_DVS86
In the hallway.
SALT_DVS87
SOMEONE sees a security officer speaking with SOMEONE and SOMEONE. As the men hurry out of sight, she fidgets. She checks her cell then slides it shut and shifts her eyes around the sparse room.
SALT_DVS88
With her as she anxiously taps her phone against her hand.
SALT_DVS89
With her back to the door, she sits on the edge of the table. A flashing red light pulses through the window from the hallway.
SALT_DVS91
She looks up at a security camera in the corner and snaps her fingers.
SALT_DVS92
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter a security hub where a monitor shows SOMEONE in the elevator shooting his victims in the head.
SALT_DVS93
She shows a photo.
SALT_DVS95
A monitor shows SOMEONE in the hallway.
SALT_DVS98
SOMEONE abruptly turns away.
SALT_DVS100
The security camera catches her.
SALT_DVS103
It's blocked. SOMEONE turns to his aide.
SALT_DVS106
SOMEONE scowls at the security monitors. Now more panels merge close, cutting SOMEONE off. She turns down another corridor. Back in the security hub.
SALT_DVS107
Control panel by the elevator blinks off as SOMEONE approaches. She glances up at a security camera.
SALT_DVS108
She sprays it with a fire extinguisher.
SALT_DVS110
As SOMEONE exits, SOMEONE glances at the security officer.
SALT_DVS112
SOMEONE eyes a series of monitors.
SALT_DVS113
Now SOMEONE idly spins the wheels of an upturned office chair as she looks through a glass wall into another corridor. She heads over. A monitor shows her approaching.
SALT_DVS114
SOMEONE sprays the camera then searches bottles on a cart of cleaning supplies. In the security hub.
SALT_DVS116
SOMEONE heads into a room with the fire extinguisher and some bottles of cleaning solutions.
SALT_DVS117
SOMEONE opens a janitorial closet and removes a bottle from a cabinet. As the overhead lights flicker on, she glances up at a camera. She slides off her panties and uses them to cover its lens. Then tips over a table and unscrews one of its metal legs. Meanwhile, SOMEONE reads her file.
SALT_DVS118
Covert Operations. Division: Russia. Current Cover: Vice President of Products and Development, Rink Petroleum. Special Skills: Close quarter combat, applied explosive techniques. Parents killed in car accident, December 24th, 1988. After release from North Korea, married German national SOMEONE Krause.
SALT_DVS119
In the security hub, SOMEONE makes a call.
SALT_DVS122
She pours cleaning solutions into a trashcan. The TAC team reaches a security barrier.
SALT_DVS124
Desk chair. Outside the room.
SALT_DVS128
The tactical team prepares to storm the room.
SALT_DVS129
Wearing a mask, SOMEONE nods to a team member.
SALT_DVS130
Pulls the pin from a gas canister. Hiding behind a corner, SOMEONE peeks around at the sealed interrogation room doors.
SALT_DVS131
As the doors slide open
SALT_DVS132
SOMEONE takes out the tactical team.
SALT_DVS134
Gun a window shattering its glass pane.
SALT_DVS137
A security feed shows SOMEONE outside the building.
SALT_DVS138
She races barefoot in front of traffic. As she darts past a bus stop, some of the waiting commuters stare after her. Slowing briefly, SOMEONE glances back at the Rink Petroleum building. In the security hub.
SALT_DVS140
A window shows SOMEONE tossing down his bulletproof vest as he returns.
SALT_DVS143
Waving her hand, SOMEONE flags down a Beltway cab and climbs in back.
SALT_DVS146
SOMEONE removes the SIM card from her phone and repeatedly bends it in half.
SALT_DVS147
The taxi driver eyes her suspiciously in his rear view mirror as she destroys it. Glancing up, she catches him watching and he quickly looks away.
SALT_DVS148
She tosses the SIM card on the floor. Shutting her eyes, she gently pounds the back of her head against the seat back then recalls SOMEONE showing her photographs of SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS151
He hands her SOMEONE's book on Spiders.
SALT_DVS153
To the high-rise.
SALT_DVS154
Now inside the building, an elevator's door slide open and SOMEONE peeks into a hallway. She scurries to her apartment door where she slides a hidden key from the frame. As she enters the apartment, she grabs a tan overcoat from the hall and puts it on. Creeping to the living room, she pauses in a doorway to pick up a pair of boots. She carries them in her hands as she searches the apartment.
SALT_DVS155
She passes a framed photo of the couple embracing.
SALT_DVS156
Her gaze swivels from a hallway to the vacant living room.
SALT_DVS157
SOMEONE runs over and she pats him.
SALT_DVS159
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE scurries to an overturned chair. On a table beside it, she spots a half-eaten sandwich and an unfinished beer. SOMEONE wags his tail expectantly as SOMEONE hurries to an adjacent room.
SALT_DVS160
Outside, agents flood out of vehicles and head toward the building.
SALT_DVS161
Apartment, SOMEONE lowers a panel from the underside of a table, revealing a hidden gun. She grabs it.
SALT_DVS162
her chest, finding a backpack, she slings it over her shoulder then jerks her gaze to the door.
SALT_DVS163
SOMEONE scampers over.
SALT_DVS164
He follows her down a hall and into a dark room. Meanwhile, the tactical team arrives on her floor with their guns drawn.
SALT_DVS169
Using a bust statuette, he knocks away the remaining glass. On the wall just outside, SOMEONE climbs.
SALT_DVS170
She grabs an air conditioning unit and crosses to its other side. As SOMEONE leans out the window.
SALT_DVS171
Presses her back to the wall, hiding behind the air conditioner. He sweeps his gaze over the U-shaped courtyard then looks to the ground roughly ten stories below.
SALT_DVS172
Stretches her leg across a cornered gap to another windowsill. Hugging the wall, she sidesteps to the next window. Her toes deftly feeling for its latch.
SALT_DVS173
Now she reaches a window of a fire escape. Peeking inside, she sees a young girl in headphones doing homework at a table.
SALT_DVS174
SOMEONE waves at her oblivious neighbor. As the young girl shifts her gaze, she notices the woman outside and returns the wave. SOMEONE beckons and the girl heads over.
SALT_DVS177
She puts a pair of jeans on under her skirt.
SALT_DVS179
Her friendly smile fades as SOMEONE catches her gaze. Staring at the dog, she remembers a butterfly soaring over SOMEONE's head in a pavilion filled with lush vegetation. He approaches a wandering SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS180
He wears a mild boyish smile.
SALT_DVS181
Later, he shows her a bulbous black spider resting in a glass-encased web.
SALT_DVS183
Donning glasses, SOMEONE peers excitedly at the spider.
SALT_DVS184
SOMEONE smiles, watching the spider pick its way up to a twig housing its web.
SALT_DVS185
Back in the present, she walks down a sidewalk, a knit cap pulled over her hair. Leaving her building, SOMEONE spots her.
SALT_DVS188
SOMEONE sprints away.
SALT_DVS191
SOMEONE reaches a subway entrance and dashes down an escalator.
SALT_DVS195
Then halts at the side of an SUV.
SALT_DVS198
Now draws his gun and pursues SOMEONE on foot.
SALT_DVS199
As another SUV arrives
SALT_DVS203
On a trailer of a passing semi with a hard bounce.
SALT_DVS204
SOMEONE, as he fires again.
SALT_DVS207
And two officers get out.
SALT_DVS209
Pulls herself up to a stable position then crouches and gets her bearing.
SALT_DVS211
Saw in the overpass and the agents scramble out. The tanker approaches below. Flanked by agents aiming their guns, SOMEONE leans out toward her.
SALT_DVS217
Spies the pursuing SUV then runs off between two lanes of unmoving cars.
SALT_DVS220
And then wrenches the throttle.
SALT_DVS221
SOMEONE speeds off between the lanes of traffic.
SALT_DVS223
She expertly stirs the motorcycle as it whisks around a vehicle.
SALT_DVS224
In the SUV, SOMEONE takes a few steadying breaths.
SALT_DVS226
SOMEONE gets a text.
SALT_DVS227
Evelyn SOMEONE was injured during the Moscow car crash that killed her parents.
SALT_DVS229
In the bathroom, SOMEONE kicks a feminine hygiene product dispenser off the wall. It opens as it lands and she takes a pad. Facing a mirror, she unwraps it. Then lifts her bloodstained shirt to reveal a gunshot wound at the top of her hip. She applies the pad to the injury then tucks it into her waistband. Shutting her eyes, she remembers lying on top of SOMEONE in bed. They kiss and wrestle playfully.
SALT_DVS232
Inside, SOMEONE watches a newscast.
SALT_DVS233
She remembers riding in the back of an SUV in Korea with SOMEONE's concerned gaze fixed on her.
SALT_DVS234
She faces him, revealing her bruised swollen eye.
SALT_DVS235
She cheerfully shuts her eyes and shakes her head.
SALT_DVS238
She woefully meets his gaze.
SALT_DVS245
SOMEONE gives a loving smile. Beaming tearfully, SOMEONE rests her head against her folded hands. SOMEONE holds her by the crook of her elbow. Taking his hand, she presses her lips to it. SOMEONE leans close and kisses the top of her blonde head. Back in the present, SOMEONE shifts her listless gaze. Now at a hotel's check-in desk.
SALT_DVS246
On a hallway, the housekeeping woman removes garments from a rack of laundered clothes and takes them into a guest's room.
SALT_DVS247
Passing the rack, SOMEONE snatches a garment in each hand without breaking her stride. Now she arrives at her deluxe room with the clothes draped over her arm.
SALT_DVS248
Depositing her backpack on the bed, she moves through the space, examining it with a keen perceptive gaze. She peers into a bathroom then returns to the bedroom and removes her knit cap.
SALT_DVS249
SOMEONE retrieves a jewelry box from a plastic bag containing cash and passports. She removes a set of false teeth from her mouth then takes out a pair of darkly tinted contact lenses from her pale blue eyes.
SALT_DVS250
Now she lays out an assortment of handguns,
SALT_DVS251
ammunition and hardware on the bed.
SALT_DVS253
She presses a button on the square component and a red light illuminates.
SALT_DVS254
Later SOMEONE uses a needle to draw clear venom from the spider. By her open laptop, a printer ejects a page headed, Subway System Access Tunnels. A blueprint reads Detail: St. SOMEONE Subdivision, and highlights a steam vent. Nearby, another print out bares the heading, Church Tunnels. SOMEONE crosses to a window, pulls the drapes aside a few inches and peers out. St. Bartholomew's Cathedral stands almost directly across the street, softly illuminated by outdoor flood lamps. Gazing wistfully at it, SOMEONE remembers swearing in as a CIA agent.
SALT_DVS255
Back in the present, she dyes her hair dark. Daytime, rooftop secret service snipers monitor a funeral procession.
SALT_DVS258
Across the street, a woman with dark brown hair looks on. As we revolve around her, we recognize SOMEONE's high cheekbones and bee-stung lips. At the cathedral entrance, SOMEONE stands between SOMEONE and a balding man. At the curb, a secret service agent opens a car door. Matveyev gets out and solemnly looks around. SOMEONE watches him proceed toward the entrance, flanked by a secret service detail.
SALT_DVS259
She steps away. Matveyev pauses, casting about his weary gaze.
SALT_DVS260
SOMEONE moves through the crowd, keeping an eye on him. From the church entrance, SOMEONE catches a glimpse of her. He narrows his eyes, trying to get a better look but she slips out of view.
SALT_DVS262
The military dress uniforms carry a flag draped casket.
SALT_DVS263
They bring the coffin to the church's entry way. Matveyev follows, flanked by his security.
SALT_DVS264
And speeds through a subway tunnel. On board, a female police officer turns.
SALT_DVS265
The fugitive pretends to read a folded newspaper.
SALT_DVS267
SOMEONE drops the newspaper by the door and moves away as it smolders.
SALT_DVS270
Now in the cathedral, a gray-haired man plays an organ. In front of him, dozens of men and women in the choir wear white robes and hold songbooks as they sing soberly.
SALT_DVS271
In the congregation, Matveyev greets a middle-aged woman with auburn hair.
SALT_DVS272
He approaches a lanky man in a row behind her.
SALT_DVS273
The commander-in-chief moves aside, Matveyev sidles into his row and nods at the first lady.
SALT_DVS274
He eases past her and stands at her side. At the front of the cathedral, the flag draped casket lies before the apse. In front of it, a soldier in dress uniform ends a salute and marches away.
SALT_DVS275
The congregation and choir take their seats. The U. S. president kisses his wife then treads forward and tenderly lays his hand on the casket. On a mezzanine balcony, SOMEONE gazes down on the nave as the president moves toward a podium.
SALT_DVS276
SOMEONE watches from a security hub in the sacristy.
SALT_DVS277
He peers into the nave.
SALT_DVS278
SOMEONE radios in.
SALT_DVS279
SOMEONE jogs through an access tunnel with a low ceiling. In the cathedral.
SALT_DVS281
As the steam fills a chamber beneath her, she reaches a door and peeks through its window into a hallway. Two security agents enter from another door.
SALT_DVS282
He back down. His partner attacks once more but SOMEONE kicks him unconscious and runs off with his gun. Now Matveyev takes the podium. In a stairwell, SOMEONE dashes up several flights.
SALT_DVS288
In the crypt, a door cracks open and SOMEONE peeks out. She aims a tiny mirror down the hallway and spots a security agent striding up. As the man reaches for his gun, the door swings open and SOMEONE leaps out. She boots him backward. Knees the weapon out of his hand.
SALT_DVS289
Crouching, SOMEONE fires through the downed man, using him like a silencer.
SALT_DVS290
Nails the approaching agent in his bulletproof vest.
SALT_DVS294
Shoots another mechanism. In the cathedral, guests panic. Meanwhile, SOMEONE draws his gun. In the crypt chamber, SOMEONE attaches one of the detonator components to a brick of explosives. She tosses it upward and it magnetically adheres to a chandelier's base on the ceiling. In the mezzanine, SOMEONE radios in.
SALT_DVS296
In the crypt, SOMEONE shines his flashlight at a dead guard. A cloud of dust fills the hallway ahead. Now in the smoke-filled organ chamber.
SALT_DVS297
SOMEONE aims her gun through the cloud of dust and faintly glimpses Matveyev's form. She shoots him. In the hallway.
SALT_DVS298
SOMEONE reacts to the sound and moves toward it. In the organ chamber, his flashlight glows through the dust. Its wavering beam glares brighter and
SALT_DVS300
Her calm aim, hold steady.
SALT_DVS301
She raises her hands, aiming the gun harmlessly at the ceiling then lets it drop.
SALT_DVS302
Other agents enter.
SALT_DVS303
A supervisor radios in.
SALT_DVS304
Later outside.
SALT_DVS305
He uses his cell.
SALT_DVS310
The two men lock gazes. SOMEONE glances quizzically after SOMEONE and heaves a sigh. Now the three vehicle police convoy moves down a vacant city street. Later, it crosses the 59th Street Bridge. In the back seat, SOMEONE blinks.
SALT_DVS311
Eyes. The lead cruiser veers to one side and passes a U-Haul truck.
SALT_DVS312
SOMEONE tips her head back and studies the cruiser behind him in a rear view mirror.
SALT_DVS313
In a flashback.
SALT_DVS314
A girl enters a dormitory.
SALT_DVS315
Bandages conceal her features.
SALT_DVS316
She climbs into a bed next to SOMEONE's.
SALT_DVS317
Moonlight glows on his scarred cheek.
SALT_DVS319
One ramming his head into the window.
SALT_DVS322
SOMEONE winces, bracing herself.
SALT_DVS323
The SUV tips and smashes down onto all four wheels. Inside, SOMEONE steals a key ring from the driver's belt. Bystanders tread toward the passenger side of the SUV as SOMEONE slips out the driver's side. As two men rush to help the driver, she hides and unlocks the handcuffs. Later, she strides casually away with her hands in her pockets.
SALT_DVS324
As the sleeper agent sunders pass the sidewalk vendor's hat rack, she steals an ushanka-style fur cap. Later, clouds fill the bright afternoon sky. Passengers sit calmly on a ferry.
SALT_DVS326
And her shoulders wrapped in a knee length fur lined shawl. Sunlight flares on the misty air, starkly outlining her profile against the sea and the sky.
SALT_DVS328
Bandages still cover much of her swollen face.
SALT_DVS329
Young SOMEONE halts on his way out and she kisses his ring.
SALT_DVS330
He hurries off down a long corridor. As the young girl stares longingly after him, a smooth featured man strides up.
SALT_DVS331
Back in the present, SOMEONE stares off over the water. Later, the passengers file off the ferry, past a TV showing a newscast.
SALT_DVS332
In a junkyard.
SALT_DVS333
SOMEONE and others watch TV.
SALT_DVS338
Give her a warm embrace. SOMEONE strokes SOMEONE's cheek.
SALT_DVS339
She kisses his ring. Cradling his hand and both of hers, she takes a stroll with him across the salvage yard.
SALT_DVS341
They hug again.
SALT_DVS344
Is around a floating barrel and angles toward a boxy barge. A henchman wielding a rifle stands guard on its deck. SOMEONE studies him coolly.
SALT_DVS346
SOMEONE beams. As SOMEONE leads her across a catwalk, her smile falters. She surveys some men working at a table beneath them.
SALT_DVS348
He gestures her forward.
SALT_DVS349
With a warm smile, SOMEONE proceeds down a set of stairs. Her Russian mentor follows close behind.
SALT_DVS350
Reaching a dimly lit corridor, SOMEONE turns to find two thugs lifting a large circular hatch on the floor.
SALT_DVS351
Her cool smile gone she ventures further in. SOMEONE trails his former protégée, observing her closely. The thugs step aside from the raised hatch. As SOMEONE peers down through the opening, a flashlight turns on to reveal SOMEONE bound with a chain.
SALT_DVS352
A crimson rag gags his mouth. As SOMEONE stares at her husband, SOMEONE steps up beside her, scrutinizing her response. SOMEONE gazes up at her. His gray eyes wide. SOMEONE maintains her stony expression.
SALT_DVS353
SOMEONE mashes his teeth around his gag as he stares pleadingly at his wife. She faces SOMEONE and her bee-stung lips curl into a cold smile.
SALT_DVS354
A thug aims his rifle at her.
SALT_DVS355
As SOMEONE turns away, her smile fades.
SALT_DVS356
And then turns, a guard wrenches a valve.
SALT_DVS358
Watching her husband's head thrash, SOMEONE struggles to fight back tears welling in her eyes.
SALT_DVS359
She looks up at a guard in a suit, aiming a handgun at her. Blinking, she clears her eyes and faces SOMEONE without a hint of grief.
SALT_DVS362
They drink their vodka.
SALT_DVS363
To our family, sister. The man beside him nods to her.
SALT_DVS364
In a flashback, SOMEONE glimpses young boys dressed in identical stripe shirts. Back in the present, SOMEONE escorts her into a radio room.
SALT_DVS365
Some more vodka.
SALT_DVS366
He marks a map.
SALT_DVS369
Rams over and over. SOMEONE's head slips forward and the bloody bottle drops to the floor. SOMEONE's gaze darts.
SALT_DVS370
She strides across the room and opens several cases of weapons. Then slaps a click into the butt of a handgun.
SALT_DVS374
Falls dead beside his wounded comrade in a suit. As the terrified survivor struggles to crawl away, SOMEONE moves over him.
SALT_DVS375
With gun, the man convulses then falls limp. SOMEONE turns away with a stony expression. Holding her gun at a ready, she steps to the edge of the stairwell. She checks a corridor for survivors then drops her gaze downstairs.
SALT_DVS376
A dozen charred victims killed in the grenade blast lie in heaps around the open hatch.
SALT_DVS377
SOMEONE's gaze softens. She stares at the dark shimmering water flooding the chamber below.
SALT_DVS378
Her glistening eyes stare wistfully. In a flashback, SOMEONE wears a bridal veil. She giggles and buries her face against the shoulder of SOMEONE's neatly pressed suit.
SALT_DVS381
Man in dress uniform steps up to SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS382
She stares at him blankly.
SALT_DVS383
She recalls the young boy with the scar on his cheek lying in the bed next to hers.
SALT_DVS384
The man shows his scarred cheek.
SALT_DVS385
In a seat facing her.
SALT_DVS389
He hands her a badge.
SALT_DVS390
He shows a blueprint.
SALT_DVS397
SOMEONE holds her palms together as he cups her hands in his.
SALT_DVS398
She locks eyes with him impassively. Nighttime. An aerial view shows the lights of Washington D. C. glowing around the dome of the capital building. Now SOMEONE drives an SUV up to a checkpoint, a guard hurries over.
SALT_DVS400
One show SOMEONE with his alias, the other a young man named SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS402
SOMEONE turns and lifts his arms.
SALT_DVS403
The security agent runs a detection wand over him then lets him through.
SALT_DVS404
SOMEONE watches her wave the wand over his colleague.
SALT_DVS405
SOMEONE turns revealing his soft features and bee-stung lips. The impostor grabs her service cap and attaché case from a security conveyor belt then walks beside SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS407
With the president.
SALT_DVS408
The group boards an elevator. Back with the others.
SALT_DVS409
As the adviser heads to the elevator, SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS410
Later, SOMEONE throw SOMEONE to the floor.
SALT_DVS411
The closing elevator doors, SOMEONE spies SOMEONE in her disguise. SOMEONE presses a remote then explodes.
SALT_DVS412
In the hall. In the elevator.
SALT_DVS413
In a smoke-filled hallway, SOMEONE rolls over and pushes herself onto her knees.
SALT_DVS414
She grabs a set of keys and a gun off a fallen agent then hurries upstairs.
SALT_DVS415
Adding herself in a room, she tears off her jacket.
SALT_DVS416
SOMEONE shifts his eyes thoughtfully.
SALT_DVS417
SOMEONE removes her false ears.
SALT_DVS419
She rips it away from her nose and mouth. Back in the elevator.
SALT_DVS420
The group hurries down a hall.
SALT_DVS421
Meanwhile, SOMEONE sneaks downstairs.
SALT_DVS422
The agent uses his radio.
SALT_DVS423
Meanwhile hiding against the wall by the stairs, SOMEONE peers around the corner and sees a tactical team shuffling pass. Back with the president.
SALT_DVS424
Agents hurry the president down a hall. SOMEONE sprints along at another.
SALT_DVS425
Turning a corner, the president and his men approach an elevator.
SALT_DVS426
They rush inside.
SALT_DVS427
A guard station in the hall.
SALT_DVS429
She pries the doors open and peers down into the shaft of the descending car. Her gaze sweeps to the metal framework along the walls and she leaps onto a crossbar.
SALT_DVS430
Then jumps to a lower beam in the opposite corner. Continuing in this manner, she gradually descends floor by floor.
SALT_DVS431
SOMEONE glances toward the ceiling.
SALT_DVS432
An agent checks the entryway.
SALT_DVS433
Meanwhile, SOMEONE tightrope-walks along the beam in the elevator shaft. At the bunker door.
SALT_DVS434
In the shaft, SOMEONE sees two parallel rails running down a wall. Squeezing between them, she slides down like an elevator on its tracks. In the bunker corridor.
SALT_DVS435
SOMEONE reaches the bottom of the shaft. Now the heavily reinforced bunker door swings open.
SALT_DVS436
He addresses a bunker guard.
SALT_DVS437
As the president and his entourage walk through the doorway, the guard enters a code on a keypad.
SALT_DVS440
Using the stolen ID card, she unlocks the gate. Meanwhile.
SALT_DVS441
The president and his men head to the emergency operation center. With them, a military aide carries a briefcase, its handle tethered to his wrist.
SALT_DVS442
Satellite images appear.
SALT_DVS444
The military aide sets his briefcase on the table.
SALT_DVS445
And opens it and presses his thumb on a fingerprint scanner inside.
SALT_DVS447
Back in the emergency operation center.
SALT_DVS448
Secret service agent James joins a woman wearing a headset.
SALT_DVS450
Enters a code on the control pad.
SALT_DVS451
Meanwhile, SOMEONE hurries down a corridor. As two agents draw closer, she charges. She barrels one over then punches the other.
SALT_DVS452
The first agent slams her.
SALT_DVS453
The first agent and he falls. As he reaches for his gun
SALT_DVS455
He knocks down the other agent as well. In the operation center, the scanner verifies the President's palm print. The Secretary of Defense holds a phone receiver in each hand. At the Pentagon, military officials watch a news report.
SALT_DVS456
A general picks up a red handled phone. Meanwhile, the Secretary
SALT_DVS457
Of Defense hands one receiver to the president and the other to military aide.
SALT_DVS458
He sits and types on his computer
SALT_DVS459
Code matches the general's.
SALT_DVS461
The general hangs up.
SALT_DVS462
In the bunker with a two dead agents. Now Jenks turns to the lead bunker officer.
SALT_DVS464
Through a doorway, they see Officer Dryers body fall to the ground.
SALT_DVS465
SOMEONE steps away from it.
SALT_DVS466
The President gapes. Outside the operation center, SOMEONE shifts her eyes. Back inside, SOMEONE aims his gun at the President.
SALT_DVS467
He lowers himself into a chair. His eyes wide.
SALT_DVS468
Over the table and SOMEONE shoots her. Meanwhile, SOMEONE approaches the room.
SALT_DVS469
SOMEONE shoots him. Peering through a window, SOMEONE sees the commander-in-chief fall out of his chair. As SOMEONE removes his jacket, SOMEONE's gaze scans the room and takes in the dead body sprawled behind a control counter.
SALT_DVS470
SOMEONE settles into a seat at the nuclear warfare computer.
SALT_DVS471
SOMEONE presses a button on the wall intercom. Her eyes focused on her old colleague as he types.
SALT_DVS472
He looks over.
SALT_DVS473
SOMEONE smiles at him. He lifts his brow.
SALT_DVS474
On the computer.
SALT_DVS477
Who uses a blowtorch on the reinforced door. Now a status bar shows the authorization reaching 29%.
SALT_DVS478
SOMEONE approaches the window separating him from SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS481
SOMEONE stares into her pleading eyes. His jaws set tightly. Her breath fogs the glass.
SALT_DVS482
A tiny smile touches SOMEONE's lips and he nods. As he turns from the window, he spots a news report on the monitor. A caption underneath footage of Matveyev reads, Russian President alive.
SALT_DVS484
SOMEONE turns back to the window and steps closer. On the other side, SOMEONE stares unapologetically.
SALT_DVS485
He leans his arms against the glass and looks into her eyes.
SALT_DVS486
SOMEONE defiantly lifts her chin.
SALT_DVS487
SOMEONE's lips spread into a smile.
SALT_DVS488
SOMEONE fires a handgun at the bulletproof window.
SALT_DVS489
Her bullets create a cluster of snowflake-like impressions in the glass. She drops her emptied handgun and raises an automatic rifle. As her shots fail to shutter the window, SOMEONE strolls back to the nuclear
SALT_DVS490
Warfare computer.
SALT_DVS491
And smashes the butt of her rifle.
SALT_DVS492
In glass then notices a control pad by the door in the operation center.
SALT_DVS493
She heads down a hall. SOMEONE glances
SALT_DVS495
Into the biometric scanner.
SALT_DVS496
His hand down on the scanning pad.
SALT_DVS501
SOMEONE breaks part of the wall away to reveal an electronic device inside. She removes some wires from it. In the operation center, SOMEONE waits against the wall beside the door with his pistol in hand.
SALT_DVS503
In the operation center.
SALT_DVS505
She sinks to the floor.
SALT_DVS506
SOMEONE marches to the controls. Scrambling to her feet.
SALT_DVS508
A round kick, rushes to the launch controls and types.
SALT_DVS510
Slams her down on the table.
SALT_DVS512
SOMEONE lunges to the launch controls
SALT_DVS513
Tap a link cord. She get shot
SALT_DVS514
SOMEONE lies face down watching tensely.
SALT_DVS515
SOMEONE keeps his weary gaze fixed on SOMEONE. Taking her into custody, an officer yanks down her shirt and finds a bulletproof vest. Later, SOMEONE passes SOMEONE and his men in a corridor.
SALT_DVS516
As SOMEONE gets led past, she jerks her chin up at SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS517
He stares after her. Down the hall.
SALT_DVS518
Now the agents escort SOMEONE of a curving flight of stairs to a landing, where SOMEONE lingers with the SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS519
He slips a pair of scissors from the SOMEONE's bag then locks eyes with SOMEONE.
SALT_DVS523
Secret service agents haul SOMEONE back up.
SALT_DVS524
The agents back SOMEONE against the wall.
SALT_DVS527
They shove her in and then one wraps a blanket around her shoulders.
SALT_DVS528
She finds SOMEONE seated across from her.
SALT_DVS531
Away from the rising helicopter, followed by another chopper
SALT_DVS532
SOMEONE gazes listlessly out the window. Her nose, cheek, and mouth stained with dark blood clots. She sees the Washington Monument pass by. A red light blinking at its apex. SOMEONE studies her with a thoughtful gaze. The helicopters rise high above the city, silhouetted against a rose and indigo sky.
SALT_DVS534
The agents look away uneasily.
SALT_DVS535
The bald man avoids his hostile glare. SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE wearily. Her narrowed eyes glistening. He shifts angrily in his seat. SOMEONE coldly straightens and looks him in the eye.
SALT_DVS538
His chest heaving, SOMEONE shifts his bewildered gaze then looks to SOMEONE again.
SALT_DVS539
SOMEONE looks away. His lips tightly pursed.
SALT_DVS541
He takes out his cell and eyes the display. It reads, Urgent message - fingerprints place SOMEONE on barge where SOMEONE was killed. SOMEONE looks up at the mysterious woman, who watches him with a steady earnest gaze. His brow creased. He puts the cellphone back in his pocket.
SALT_DVS544
SOMEONE lowers his gaze to the handcuff around SOMEONE's wrist restraints. As he looks up at her blood stained face, her eyes glisten and she displays a big smile.
SALT_DVS545
SOMEONE studies her resolute expression.
SALT_DVS546
Craning his neck, he looks pass her to the FBI agents. He glances down again at SOMEONE's restraints then eyes the bald man. He talks on a headset. A window shows their approach over the Potomac River. SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a meaningful look which she registers coldly.
SALT_DVS548
SOMEONE stares at him and he directs her gaze toward the window.
SALT_DVS549
Seeing a river below, she discreetly unbuckles her seat belt. SOMEONE watches her gravely.
SALT_DVS550
His lips screwed tightly. He glances out of the Potomac then directs her gaze to the door. It bears a semi-circular emergency release handle. Swallowing, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE's finger tap deliberately against his leg. She steals herself with a deep breath. As SOMEONE's hand closes into a fist, she lunges for the emergency release.
SALT_DVS552
His brow furrowed. He stares into the water. It shows no sign of the mysterious woman.
SALT_DVS553
Searching fruitlessly for SOMEONE, SOMEONE allows a smile and gives a satisfied nod.
SALT_DVS555
They turn away from the Potomac's rocky bank.
SALT_DVS556
The river's edge, hands caress at a snow blanket of rock as slim figure wades through the knee-deep water. SOMEONE rushes a shore and dashes through the woods, pumping her shackled arms. Leaning briefly against a tree trunk, she glances over her shoulder. She breathes hard through her parted lips. Her wet short hair clinging to her head. Her feet carry her over the forest snowy ground.
SALT_DVS557
She watches SOMEONE's helicopter leaves the Potomac and its bordering wetlands. She ventures onward.