In the cockpit.
SANCTUM_DVS15
Covered valley.
SANCTUM_DVS16
Humongous hole in the Earth.
SANCTUM_DVS19
Inside the cave, a fair-haired man floats in shallow water.
SANCTUM_DVS20
Wearing only a wet suit, he goes through the motions of checking his equipment.
SANCTUM_DVS21
He shakes his head, then lifts it out of the water.
SANCTUM_DVS22
The fair-haired man gently swims across the rocky pool and climbs onto a ledge. A lanky man wearing a climber's helmet sits nearby. He gets up and moves a large backpack.
SANCTUM_DVS23
SOMEONE hands a camera to a goateed guy wearing a Ramones t-shirt.
SANCTUM_DVS24
The goateed guy leaves a canopy-covered station and steps past the two divers.
SANCTUM_DVS25
At the foot of another pool, he sets a shoebox-sized camera into the water.
SANCTUM_DVS26
He leaves the pool and sits behind a computer housed inside an orange plastic case.
SANCTUM_DVS27
Nearby, SOMEONE helps the female diver strap a rebreather to her back.
SANCTUM_DVS28
She gets a reading on a handheld device.
SANCTUM_DVS29
SOMEONE gets up from his station and faces her with his hands on his hips.
SANCTUM_DVS30
She nods.
SANCTUM_DVS31
SOMEONE joins them.
SANCTUM_DVS32
They help the brunette out. Now, the locals guide the group through ankle-high water. Men carry oxygen tanks in the opposite direction.
SANCTUM_DVS33
He hands a tank to a local.
SANCTUM_DVS34
The balding man takes off his hat and faces SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS35
SOMEONE shrugs.
SANCTUM_DVS36
He shakes his head and steps past.
SANCTUM_DVS37
He continues on.
SANCTUM_DVS38
SOMEONE taps SOMEONE with his hat.
SANCTUM_DVS39
Inside the cave, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE at another computer station.
SANCTUM_DVS40
He points to his schematic of the cave.
SANCTUM_DVS41
He calls up a map.
SANCTUM_DVS43
SOMEONE approaches a native.
SANCTUM_DVS44
The brunette notices a penned-in wild boar, a local woman sitting on a path, and two young men wearing grass skirts.
SANCTUM_DVS45
SOMEONE greets a camera crew.
SANCTUM_DVS48
In a tent office, they view a computer animation of the complex cave system.
SANCTUM_DVS50
At forward base, the female diver prepares.
SANCTUM_DVS51
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE over his shoulder. Lowering his gaze, he turns to face him.
SANCTUM_DVS52
SOMEONE leaves the computer station to approach SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS53
They all look to SOMEONE who checks the computer.
SANCTUM_DVS54
SOMEONE returns to the computer.
SANCTUM_DVS55
He shows a liquor bottle.
SANCTUM_DVS56
As the others at forward base laugh, SOMEONE gives a smirk.
SANCTUM_DVS57
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS58
He views his disgruntled son onscreen.
SANCTUM_DVS59
SOMEONE shuts off the feed. SOMEONE sits back. Later, he prepares for the dive.
SANCTUM_DVS60
He sets his rebreather backpack.
SANCTUM_DVS61
SOMEONE eyes him.
SANCTUM_DVS62
She holds his hands.
SANCTUM_DVS64
He helps fasten her harness.
SANCTUM_DVS65
SOMEONE chucks a cellphone into the cave.
SANCTUM_DVS66
SOMEONE shakes his head.
SANCTUM_DVS67
She shares a smile with SOMEONE, then looks to SOMEONE and jumps backward over the edge.
SANCTUM_DVS68
As SOMEONE rappels down the vertical wall, SOMEONE watches her from above.
SANCTUM_DVS69
He looks back at SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS70
He steps off of the edge and falls face down.
SANCTUM_DVS72
About halfway down, SOMEONE catches up with SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS73
Surface, SOMEONE brings SOMEONE another cellphone.
SANCTUM_DVS74
He dives over the edge with open arms and falls into the dark abyss.
SANCTUM_DVS75
He lowers the phone.
SANCTUM_DVS77
It shines in through the distant aperture.
SANCTUM_DVS78
Returns to his work. SOMEONE and SOMEONE look on.
SANCTUM_DVS79
They each continue their descent. At forward base, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS82
SOMEONE releases Virgil into the pool and the robot sets off after the diver.
SANCTUM_DVS83
He watches them go underwater.
SANCTUM_DVS84
a pale flashlight shines over the darkened rocks as a diver emerges from a narrow passage.
SANCTUM_DVS85
Flap of his swim fins propels the lead diver through the water. SOMEONE follow, shining her flashlight over the rock walls.
SANCTUM_DVS86
A single spotlight shines up from the floor as SOMEONE leads them through the darkened chamber.
SANCTUM_DVS89
At the other base camp, SOMEONE dunks a teabag into a mug.
SANCTUM_DVS90
Seated on a rock, he waits for SOMEONE and SOMEONE to reach the bottom.
SANCTUM_DVS91
Finger and he grins.
SANCTUM_DVS92
Water, SOMEONE detaches an air cylinder from the decompression chamber.
SANCTUM_DVS95
SOMEONE looks back at SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS96
Mask. His shadow appears on the rock wall.
SANCTUM_DVS98
Meanwhile, SOMEONE and SOMEONE rappel down a craggy shaft.
SANCTUM_DVS99
Sitting back in her harness, her feet pressed against the rock wall.
SANCTUM_DVS102
SOMEONE descends another shaft. At forward base, SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a mug while SOMEONE
SANCTUM_DVS103
watches the divers on the monitor.
SANCTUM_DVS105
She eyes a tunnel blocked by a cluster of rocks. As SOMEONE clears the entrance, Virgil lines up behind them.
SANCTUM_DVS106
Last rock and gazes into a dark passageway.
SANCTUM_DVS107
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE watch the monitor. Meanwhile, SOMEONE climbs out of shallow water onto a rock ledge where SOMEONE stands filming a cavern with a video camera.
SANCTUM_DVS109
She sits on the ledge above.
SANCTUM_DVS110
The tusk on a necklace.
SANCTUM_DVS113
SOMEONE unclips his extra oxygen tank and pushes it away.
SANCTUM_DVS116
He struggles through the narrow tunnel.
SANCTUM_DVS117
He follows close behind her, rebreather also removed from her back.
SANCTUM_DVS118
He works a joystick.
SANCTUM_DVS120
He flippers as she struggles forward.
SANCTUM_DVS121
As she pushes her rebreather, its pack snags on a rock.
SANCTUM_DVS123
SOMEONE continues on and SOMEONE follows.
SANCTUM_DVS124
Now in an area enveloped by darkness, a beam of light shines out, its radius growing larger as SOMEONE emerges from the tunnel into a cavern.
SANCTUM_DVS126
A wall below the tunnel. As SOMEONE emerges behind him, SOMEONE anchors a guide line to the cavern wall.
SANCTUM_DVS130
SOMEONE shines a flashlight.
SANCTUM_DVS131
Pointing his finger, he swirls it in a circle.
SANCTUM_DVS132
SOMEONE heads back to the tunnel.
SANCTUM_DVS133
As she sucks in a mouthful of water.
SANCTUM_DVS134
And then her body jerks.
SANCTUM_DVS136
Virgil glides over to SOMEONE who turns, peering out at SOMEONE from the monitor.
SANCTUM_DVS137
He squeezes his eyes shut. SOMEONE watches the monitor with a grave look and SOMEONE shifts his gaze away.
SANCTUM_DVS138
Now, SOMEONE' body floats against the decompression chamber outer wall.
SANCTUM_DVS140
His eyes fixed on his lifeless colleague.
SANCTUM_DVS141
Now at forward base, SOMEONE lugs a rebreather pack ashore as SOMEONE and SOMEONE come out of the water.
SANCTUM_DVS142
Sitting on the rock, the monitor replays SOMEONE's struggle with SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS143
SOMEONE steps into view, his brow creased in anguish.
SANCTUM_DVS144
SOMEONE sees his father standing at the water's edge, his arms cradling SOMEONE limp body.
SANCTUM_DVS145
SOMEONE and SOMEONE lifted on to the rocks.
SANCTUM_DVS146
Above ground, wind bellows through trees and lightning flashes.
SANCTUM_DVS147
Back at forward base, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE under the tent.
SANCTUM_DVS148
SOMEONE tries the radio.
SANCTUM_DVS149
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a sidelong glance, then sits beside SOMEONE who eats rice from a pot.
SANCTUM_DVS150
SOMEONE turns off the radio.
SANCTUM_DVS151
He sits heavily beside his son, pulls the cork from his tequila bottle, and takes a swig.
SANCTUM_DVS152
With his head bowed, he holds the bottle out to SOMEONE who takes it and drinks.
SANCTUM_DVS153
The young man swallows then lets out a deep breath.
SANCTUM_DVS154
SOMEONE lifts his head but avoids his son's gaze.
SANCTUM_DVS155
SOMEONE clenches his jaw and his nostrils flare. SOMEONE stands.
SANCTUM_DVS156
SOMEONE taps SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS159
Tribal shaman elder lifts his face to the dark sky. Rain pours down on him.
SANCTUM_DVS160
The aerial shows the deluge plummeting into the cave's pitch black mouth.
SANCTUM_DVS162
His feet splashing in muddy water.
SANCTUM_DVS163
And SOMEONE eyes the boar tooth torch around his neck.
SANCTUM_DVS164
He tries to yank it off then glares at it.
SANCTUM_DVS165
As he tugs again.
SANCTUM_DVS166
He tilts his head alertly.
SANCTUM_DVS169
SOMEONE takes the lead.
SANCTUM_DVS170
At forward base, SOMEONE sits in front of the monitor swigging from his bottle. Sweeping his gaze around the cave, he wipes his mouth the back of his hand then picks up a flashlight. He glides his beam up a wall to a crevasse in the rock.
SANCTUM_DVS171
SOMEONE joins him. Sitting in front of the monitor, he eyes the onscreen footage of St. Jude's Cathedral where Virgil's light shines up a towering shaft toward the rippling surface of the air bell.
SANCTUM_DVS172
SOMEONE drinks from the tequila bottle.
SANCTUM_DVS173
Meanwhile, SOMEONE stops at a comm station.
SANCTUM_DVS178
Leaks through cracks, raining into the cave. SOMEONE gazes around.
SANCTUM_DVS181
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look up the shaft with their headlamps.
SANCTUM_DVS185
His companions stare gravely.
SANCTUM_DVS186
SOMEONE looks around.
SANCTUM_DVS190
SOMEONE tearfully bares his teeth.
SANCTUM_DVS191
He looks his son in the eye and gives a small nod.
SANCTUM_DVS192
Looking up, SOMEONE notices the boulder sealing off their exit.
SANCTUM_DVS193
On the upper edge blows out shooting sparks and leaving the falls in darkness.
SANCTUM_DVS195
SOMEONE pants in an agonized SOMEONE. Later, the team arrives back at the dark, flooded base camp.
SANCTUM_DVS198
SOMEONE packs.
SANCTUM_DVS200
SOMEONE rushes to a floating body bag and gently pulls it open to reveal SOMEONE' lifeless face.
SANCTUM_DVS202
SOMEONE watches, He remove the dead woman's wetsuit.
SANCTUM_DVS204
She folds her arms across her chest and stubbornly plants her feet.
SANCTUM_DVS205
SOMEONE gravely looks from her to SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS208
Searching the area for supplies, SOMEONE heads around a large flowstone feature and halts. Two motionless legs float before him.
SANCTUM_DVS211
Pulling him into the light, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE's face pulverized beyond recognition.
SANCTUM_DVS212
The Eye opens.
SANCTUM_DVS213
SOMEONE hurries over.
SANCTUM_DVS214
He crouches by his gravely injured colleague.
SANCTUM_DVS215
SOMEONE queasily turns away.
SANCTUM_DVS216
SOMEONE drags SOMEONE away.
SANCTUM_DVS217
SOMEONE drags SOMEONE back.
SANCTUM_DVS219
The injured man wraps an arm around his friend's shoulder.
SANCTUM_DVS223
Then pushes against his throat. Maintaining his hold, the older man bites his lip.
SANCTUM_DVS224
SOMEONE's hand grabs his shoulder again, flexes weakly, and goes limp.
SANCTUM_DVS225
Now underwater, we peer up at four pairs of legs silhouetted against the light above the surface. There feet clad in flippers, they lazily tread water. Back at the large flowstone feature, SOMEONE crouches over his euthanized friend.
SANCTUM_DVS226
Now we float up toward the lazily kicking legs.
SANCTUM_DVS228
He lowers his goggles.
SANCTUM_DVS233
As their headlamps descend, the cave goes dark.
SANCTUM_DVS235
Now, SOMEONE leads the way through the narrow passage leading to the Devil's Restriction.
SANCTUM_DVS237
SOMEONE swims into view, pulling at the rocks beneath him. His father takes his hand, places it on the guide line, and gives the okay signal. SOMEONE returns the gesture. His father swims on, leading him through the winding passage.
SANCTUM_DVS238
SOMEONE passes the decompression chamber.
SANCTUM_DVS239
From a distance, we watch the team of divers recede into the murky depths.
SANCTUM_DVS241
A light on her rebreather pack glows green.
SANCTUM_DVS243
While SOMEONE soberly looks on. SOMEONE goes next, shoving his gear in before him.
SANCTUM_DVS249
The Restriction and swims in after it. Left alone, SOMEONE worriedly shakes her head and looks away.
SANCTUM_DVS250
SOMEONE's flippered feet paddle out of view.
SANCTUM_DVS251
Effort, she pushes her gear into the restriction.
SANCTUM_DVS252
Ahead, shimmering green light grows visible from around a bend.
SANCTUM_DVS255
Her eyes wide behind her goggles. Up ahead, SOMEONE pushes himself through the exit. His father hovers in St. Jude's Cathedral waiting for him.
SANCTUM_DVS257
Ahead, SOMEONE joins Franks, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE outside the tunnel exit.
SANCTUM_DVS258
With her fists. In the Cathedral, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE worriedly.
SANCTUM_DVS260
The others continue to wait in one line.
SANCTUM_DVS261
Grabs hold and jerks at it. Outside the tunnel, the exit shows no sign of her approach. SOMEONE taps his boss on the shoulder. As SOMEONE faces him, he points at his own eyes then at the restriction. SOMEONE shakes his head, wags a finger, then swims toward the tunnel himself.
SANCTUM_DVS263
A headlamp beam appears from the darkness.
SANCTUM_DVS264
SOMEONE turns to look as SOMEONE crawls into view.
SANCTUM_DVS265
He swims forward. SOMEONE rubs her arm.
SANCTUM_DVS268
Then jerks his thumb upward. Now, a beam of light shines toward the rippling surface of the air bell above.
SANCTUM_DVS269
SOMEONE removes his mouthpiece.
SANCTUM_DVS271
On to the rocky bank, He pulls of an elastic band strapping a flashlight to his arm and turns on his helmet's secondary light.
SANCTUM_DVS272
Drips from his wetsuit as his lamp sweeps over the cavern. With an awestruck smile, he ventures forward.
SANCTUM_DVS273
The pool next and finds the financier wandering out of view.
SANCTUM_DVS274
The young man climbs up on an underwater ledge and raises his flippered feet.
SANCTUM_DVS275
Hiking over a ridge, SOMEONE finds a vast cavernous passageway ascending before him.
SANCTUM_DVS277
Dwarfed to a minuscule size by his surroundings.
SANCTUM_DVS280
And SOMEONE covers her with the metal tissue-thin space blanket.
SANCTUM_DVS282
He sits him down and hands him a rebreather. SOMEONE puts it to his mouth. Stepping away, SOMEONE reaches into his supply pack and pulls out a knife with a six inch blade.
SANCTUM_DVS284
SOMEONE grimly switches off his helmet lamp, so does SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS285
Now, SOMEONE wakes up from a nap.
SANCTUM_DVS286
SOMEONE rubs SOMEONE's foot as she sits under the metallic blanket.
SANCTUM_DVS287
A veiny red discoloration on his left pack. As SOMEONE whispers to himself eyes closed, SOMEONE sits by him.
SANCTUM_DVS288
SOMEONE breaks off muttering and opens his eyes. SOMEONE shivers.
SANCTUM_DVS289
She flashes a meek smile. SOMEONE confers with SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS291
The six inch knife in the ground is almost completely submerged.
SANCTUM_DVS292
Now, we drift over a rippling subterranean pond as the group crosses a cavern as big as a covered stadium.
SANCTUM_DVS293
SOMEONE steps out from behind a pitch black wall and shines his helmet light across a rocky passage. Water rains down lightly inside the sleek room-sized space.
SANCTUM_DVS294
SOMEONE climbs over a rock barrier carrying a yellow supply bag.
SANCTUM_DVS295
Just footsteps behind, SOMEONE follows.
SANCTUM_DVS296
SOMEONE comes next, then SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS297
Bringing up the rear, SOMEONE stops and adjusts his helmet light. SOMEONE looks back at his hesitant friend who makes a fist and presses on.
SANCTUM_DVS298
Rocky partition and peers down a fairly spacious passageway, his helmet light striking the rain-like mist. He then sidles to his right and trains his light beam down a smaller tunnel.
SANCTUM_DVS302
SOMEONE marches on, saddled with gear. He stumbles.
SANCTUM_DVS304
SOMEONE continues up an incline.
SANCTUM_DVS307
They share a grin and SOMEONE leads them ahead.
SANCTUM_DVS308
SOMEONE's gaze grows mildly sullen and distant.
SANCTUM_DVS309
As SOMEONE eyes him squarely, SOMEONE deflects the order with a brotherly smirk.
SANCTUM_DVS312
He looks at more shimmering blood on his palm and makes a fist.
SANCTUM_DVS313
He closes his eyes and nods.
SANCTUM_DVS314
SOMEONE continues on wearing a bulky white rebreather on her back.
SANCTUM_DVS316
On a ledge above them, SOMEONE hauls up his gear.
SANCTUM_DVS317
SOMEONE arrives.
SANCTUM_DVS318
SOMEONE and SOMEONE go looking for him.
SANCTUM_DVS319
SOMEONE leads the way into another rocky den.
SANCTUM_DVS320
A crude carving reads "George was here".
SANCTUM_DVS321
Blood trails from SOMEONE's mouth.
SANCTUM_DVS322
Light from his partner's helmet dwindles on the dying man.
SANCTUM_DVS323
The last of the light fades out, leaving us in total darkness.
SANCTUM_DVS324
Now, SOMEONE snaps photographs of the cave walls.
SANCTUM_DVS325
SOMEONE sits on a boulder nearby.
SANCTUM_DVS326
As SOMEONE returns with his camera, SOMEONE notices him.
SANCTUM_DVS327
SOMEONE hands supplies up to his father.
SANCTUM_DVS328
SOMEONE looks on uncertainly.
SANCTUM_DVS329
His father leaves SOMEONE who sits up, wincing.
SANCTUM_DVS330
A mildly defiant grin fades from SOMEONE's face. SOMEONE rubs his neck.
SANCTUM_DVS331
A slack-jawed SOMEONE drops his hand on his lap.
SANCTUM_DVS332
He looks at SOMEONE who sadly gazes at the floor. SOMEONE squeezes SOMEONE's shoulder then leaves his side.
SANCTUM_DVS333
SOMEONE fixes the collar of his vest and hangs his head.
SANCTUM_DVS334
Now, SOMEONE marches alone through another cavern, his helmet light shines over a winding path through the uneven rock floor. SOMEONE's light shines about 50 yards up ahead.
SANCTUM_DVS335
SOMEONE appears just inside it.
SANCTUM_DVS336
The veteran caver peers through the opening into another darkened chamber. He sets down his yellow supply bag.
SANCTUM_DVS337
Catch up and set down their own gear. As SOMEONE crawls through the opening, his helmet light dims out. He holds his hand before it to verify. SOMEONE and SOMEONE rest.
SANCTUM_DVS339
Walls bears some irregularities. SOMEONE spots a ledge and opening across the cauldron.
SANCTUM_DVS340
Out of the trickling chamber, SOMEONE peers into it.
SANCTUM_DVS341
SOMEONE blows on her hands.
SANCTUM_DVS342
SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS343
Later in the cauldron chamber, SOMEONE hangs from a rope and harness. The others watch him through the oval hole.
SANCTUM_DVS345
He goes to another ledge below.
SANCTUM_DVS346
Water rains down on him. SOMEONE feeds out some slack.
SANCTUM_DVS348
To some coiled rope on his hip. The young man scans the chamber walls.
SANCTUM_DVS349
Down at the churning pool, gets a hold on the wall, and leans out far under a light waterfall.
SANCTUM_DVS351
SOMEONE gives him some more slack and SOMEONE repositions himself on the ledge.
SANCTUM_DVS355
He extends his left foot to another crag about three feet away.
SANCTUM_DVS360
He feeds him a few more inches. SOMEONE finds a secure position and studies the wall.
SANCTUM_DVS364
He keep kimself onto the ledge.
SANCTUM_DVS365
Water splashes from below.
SANCTUM_DVS367
SOMEONE looks up from the ledge below.
SANCTUM_DVS368
SOMEONE and SOMEONE on the other side.
SANCTUM_DVS370
SOMEONE shines a flashlight on her.
SANCTUM_DVS373
Now, as SOMEONE coils a handful of rope, he glances at SOMEONE who stares off with a stunned gaze, his head propped on his hand.
SANCTUM_DVS374
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a disbelieving glance. SOMEONE sets down his ropes and looks across the way.
SANCTUM_DVS375
His son sits on a ledge, his mouth set in a line and his eyes staring blankly. SOMEONE's chest heaves.
SANCTUM_DVS376
SOMEONE glares at him.
SANCTUM_DVS377
Tears stream down SOMEONE's cheeks.
SANCTUM_DVS378
His face hardens.
SANCTUM_DVS379
SOMEONE glances away.
SANCTUM_DVS380
SOMEONE's brow furrows.
SANCTUM_DVS381
SOMEONE meets his gaze and holds it.
SANCTUM_DVS382
He sits on a ledge below Josh's, resting his hands on his knee.
SANCTUM_DVS383
He shifts his eyes.
SANCTUM_DVS384
Under his father's steady gaze, SOMEONE's chin trembles. His face contorts in anguish.
SANCTUM_DVS385
SOMEONE moves to his son's ledge and crouches. He places a hand on SOMEONE's shoulder.
SANCTUM_DVS386
He rubs his cheek.
SANCTUM_DVS387
Pulling SOMEONE close, he hugs him.
SANCTUM_DVS388
Squeezes his eyes shut.
SANCTUM_DVS389
SOMEONE glares at the father and son.
SANCTUM_DVS390
Shifting his jaw, SOMEONE pulls away.
SANCTUM_DVS391
He meets his father's gaze and nods.
SANCTUM_DVS396
SOMEONE stumbles as he makes his way over the uneven ground.
SANCTUM_DVS397
Trudging past stalagmites, he and SOMEONE find an underwater cave on the opposite side of the chamber. At the water's edge, SOMEONE bends at the waist, resting his hands on his legs.
SANCTUM_DVS398
As they stare at the dark water, SOMEONE joins them.
SANCTUM_DVS399
He scans the submerged cave, then takes off his bag and lets it fall to the ground.
SANCTUM_DVS402
He dives into the water.
SANCTUM_DVS403
As SOMEONE swims around a corner in a narrow passageway, SOMEONE catches up and grabs on to his leg.
SANCTUM_DVS406
But finds the cave ceiling above, holding him underwater.
SANCTUM_DVS407
His hands feeling for a break in the rock.
SANCTUM_DVS408
SOMEONE eyes the water surface.
SANCTUM_DVS410
Path of light pierces the darkness at the cave's entrance and he swims toward it.
SANCTUM_DVS414
His own headlamp off his helmet and replaces it with his son's.
SANCTUM_DVS415
SOMEONE shifts his somber eyes.
SANCTUM_DVS416
SOMEONE stares off.
SANCTUM_DVS417
SOMEONE's lips spread into a smile and he nods.
SANCTUM_DVS418
He gives a wide grin.
SANCTUM_DVS419
SOMEONE looks away.
SANCTUM_DVS420
Pushing out his jaw, he gives a thoughtful look, then abruptly shifts his gaze to a section of the cave's wall near SOMEONE. He stands, sniffing the air.
SANCTUM_DVS421
SOMEONE watches his son head to an eye-level cavity in the rock. Reaching inside, SOMEONE touches a dark, muddy substance, then lifts his fingers to his nose.
SANCTUM_DVS422
Smiling, he turns to his father and smears some of the sludge on his cheek. SOMEONE looks up.
SANCTUM_DVS423
He joins SOMEONE by the cavity.
SANCTUM_DVS424
Self into the hole.
SANCTUM_DVS425
Later, he and SOMEONE climb a narrow gap between two rock faces, pressing their backs to one and gripping the other with their hands and feet.
SANCTUM_DVS426
Lifting his foot, SOMEONE finds a hold.
SANCTUM_DVS427
SOMEONE grabs a piece of jutting rock.
SANCTUM_DVS428
SOMEONE straightens, pushing himself higher.
SANCTUM_DVS429
SOMEONE rests his back on the rock.
SANCTUM_DVS430
He leans against his arm.
SANCTUM_DVS431
Drops of water splash against their helmets, SOMEONE turns to his father and meets his gaze with a broad grin.
SANCTUM_DVS432
He blinks against the falling water, his chest heaving. As his son's light glows on his face, SOMEONE looks away and swallows.
SANCTUM_DVS433
He resumes climbing.
SANCTUM_DVS434
The climbers' lights as they ascend the narrow chimney.
SANCTUM_DVS435
His body to bridge the gap.
SANCTUM_DVS436
With a hand gripping each rock face, SOMEONE steps on to his father's thigh,
SANCTUM_DVS437
body, and grabs a ledge. SOMEONE grits his teeth as SOMEONE's weight bears down on him.
SANCTUM_DVS438
SOMEONE pulls himself onto the ledge.
SANCTUM_DVS443
The light on SOMEONE's helmet torch fades out.
SANCTUM_DVS444
He checks for his light's reflection on his palm.
SANCTUM_DVS445
SOMEONE lifts his hand to the light on his own helmet and switches it off.
SANCTUM_DVS446
Darkness envelopes the climbers.
SANCTUM_DVS447
Now, SOMEONE's helmet light emerges from darkness, illuminating the walls of a tunnel as he crawls through it.
SANCTUM_DVS448
Follows without a light, his figure disappearing in the blackness behind his father.
SANCTUM_DVS449
Ahead, the walls of the tunnel widen and the ceiling rises slightly.
SANCTUM_DVS450
As SOMEONE moves forward, his light fades out.
SANCTUM_DVS452
He turns on his wristwatch's light and it glows on his determined face. Holding its button down, he creeps forward, no longer crawling but crouched under the low ceiling.
SANCTUM_DVS453
He stumbles, then winces and stops walking.
SANCTUM_DVS454
SOMEONE pauses beside him and SOMEONE shoots him a glance.
SANCTUM_DVS455
He lowers himself to the ground and leans against the tunnel's wall, then releases the button for his watch light.
SANCTUM_DVS456
As SOMEONE lifts his hand, a trace of light reflects on his palm and fingers.
SANCTUM_DVS457
He shifts his gaze to SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS458
SOMEONE looks at his son, his profile traced in a glimmer of light. The climber stare down the tunnel where more light gleams of its jagged walls.
SANCTUM_DVS459
Daylight bathes their faces as they emerge from a fissure and step into a cavern.
SANCTUM_DVS460
At its center, a brilliant shaft of sunlight glows down through a hole in its high ceiling.
SANCTUM_DVS461
As they walk toward it, SOMEONE removes his helmet.
SANCTUM_DVS462
SOMEONE removes his helmet as well and his father lifts his face to the hole. Insects flutter around the blazing sunbeam.
SANCTUM_DVS463
Above ground, vegetation lines the hole's perimeter.
SANCTUM_DVS464
SOMEONE lowers his gaze from the natural skylight and notices a weathered military vehicle sitting below it.
SANCTUM_DVS465
SOMEONE climbs on to the tank.
SANCTUM_DVS466
He peers down its hatch, then straightens.
SANCTUM_DVS467
Rain falls on SOMEONE's face as he looks up.
SANCTUM_DVS468
Leaps off the tank, landing in soft, muddy ground. Together, he and SOMEONE crouch and examine some skeletal remains.
SANCTUM_DVS469
Later, a view through the skylight shows towering trees below a cloudy sky. Pale light glimmers on raindrop
SANCTUM_DVS470
as they fall into the cavern. Squatting, SOMEONE fills a container with oil from the tank, then looks over at SOMEONE who strikes a flint under the shelter of a wheel well. He lights a makeshift torch then grins.
SANCTUM_DVS471
As SOMEONE rises with his flaming cylindrical container in hand, SOMEONE shoves fabric into the top of his own oil-filled container.
SANCTUM_DVS472
SOMEONE lights his father's torch with his own and they lift them as if toasting.
SANCTUM_DVS473
With a thoughtful frown, SOMEONE glances at his father.
SANCTUM_DVS474
Now, a wide view shows pale light shining through the hole casting the cavern in a purple-tinged glow.
SANCTUM_DVS475
Holding his makeshift torch, SOMEONE glances around and follows his son into a tunnel. As the light from his flame disappears, our view glides to writing etched in the side of the tank, "Frank and SOMEONE were here. See ya. "
SANCTUM_DVS476
Later, orange light from SOMEONE's torch flickers on the rock walls as he leads his father through the tunnel. It widens and he climbs down a ledge, his eyes squinting into a dim chamber.
SANCTUM_DVS477
Smiling, he crouches beside a body of water.
SANCTUM_DVS478
Slipping, SOMEONE slides down the ledge on his rear.
SANCTUM_DVS479
SOMEONE looks over.
SANCTUM_DVS480
SOMEONE rises and SOMEONE shifts his helmet as his son follows the river.
SANCTUM_DVS481
Now with their torches held out, the climbers take careful steps shuffling across muddy ground.
SANCTUM_DVS482
Looking down, SOMEONE pauses and furrows his brow. He crouches to examine some abandoned gear.
SANCTUM_DVS483
He glances at SOMEONE who drops his supply bag and crouches by the equipment as well. Setting down his torch, he checks a gauge.
SANCTUM_DVS484
He test a dive light.
SANCTUM_DVS485
Now, SOMEONE's feet splash in shallow water as they hike into another chamber.
SANCTUM_DVS486
Their light shine on SOMEONE.
SANCTUM_DVS487
Smeared in dirt, SOMEONE grins as he crawls over to them. SOMEONE glares down at him.
SANCTUM_DVS488
SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
SANCTUM_DVS489
He gives SOMEONE a frenzied look.
SANCTUM_DVS490
SOMEONE sets down his bag and SOMEONE rummages through it, finding a bag of food.
SANCTUM_DVS491
Turning away from SOMEONE, SOMEONE moves through the chamber, his eyes scanning the ground.
SANCTUM_DVS492
SOMEONE's light falls on SOMEONE's body, her eyes staring lifelessly.
SANCTUM_DVS493
SOMEONE's expression crumbles and SOMEONE turns to see SOMEONE's pale and swollen face.
SANCTUM_DVS494
Dribbles a handful of dried food into his mouth.
SANCTUM_DVS495
Gaze at SOMEONE's discarded rebreather pack, SOMEONE finds three light sticks inside.
SANCTUM_DVS496
As SOMEONE shoves more food into his mouth, SOMEONE rises.
SANCTUM_DVS497
SOMEONE watches them leave.
SANCTUM_DVS500
SOMEONE's eyes widen and his grip goes slack.
SANCTUM_DVS501
Man panting beside him.
SANCTUM_DVS503
Shaking his head, SOMEONE returns to his back, his hand pressed to his son's cheek.
SANCTUM_DVS504
SOMEONE pats SOMEONE's hand.
SANCTUM_DVS505
Young man turns to see SOMEONE rising to his feet nearby holding a glow stick.
SANCTUM_DVS506
SOMEONE glares. SOMEONE averts his gaze, giving a dumbfounded shake of his head. As SOMEONE trembles
SANCTUM_DVS507
on the ground struggling to breath, SOMEONE watches, heaving a sigh. Tears well in his eyes.
SANCTUM_DVS508
As SOMEONE steps away, SOMEONE's glare follows him.
SANCTUM_DVS509
SOMEONE shrugs with resignation, shaking his head at the cave walls. He dives into the pool and disappears.
SANCTUM_DVS510
SOMEONE stares after him.
SANCTUM_DVS511
His father's side, SOMEONE drops to his knees and cradles his head in his hand.
SANCTUM_DVS512
SOMEONE grimaces.
SANCTUM_DVS513
SOMEONE lowers him into the pool.
SANCTUM_DVS514
Gently supports SOMEONE's head.
SANCTUM_DVS515
SOMEONE lies flat, buoyed by the water.
SANCTUM_DVS516
Sobbing, SOMEONE shakes his head.
SANCTUM_DVS517
As SOMEONE's hand grips his son's arm, SOMEONE's lips tremble.
SANCTUM_DVS518
Meanwhile in the underwater cave, SOMEONE, illuminated by the green light of the glow stick feels his way along the rocks above with clenched teeth.
SANCTUM_DVS519
Emerging in open water, he does a breaststroke toward the murky
SANCTUM_DVS520
Back in the cave, the oil candle's flame slowly extinguishes, leaving the area in darkness.
SANCTUM_DVS521
Break in half, bathing everything in a green glow. He sets the stick aside as his father shivers in the water.
SANCTUM_DVS522
Nods slowly. SOMEONE's pursed lips form a brief, loving smile.
SANCTUM_DVS523
He sets his jaw.
SANCTUM_DVS524
SOMEONE lays his forearm below SOMEONE's chin and gently applies pressure.
SANCTUM_DVS525
Underwater, a flurry of bubbles rises. SOMEONE struggles to hold back sobs.
SANCTUM_DVS528
Now in slow motion, submerged under gently lapping ripples, SOMEONE's grip loosens on his son.
SANCTUM_DVS529
SOMEONE looks down at him, lips parted.
SANCTUM_DVS530
He withdraws his hand from his father's, letting it fall back into the murk.
SANCTUM_DVS531
SOMEONE's right hand half-rises from the cloudy water. Sliding his hand from his father's forehead, SOMEONE lifts his body to the surface.
SANCTUM_DVS532
Under the green illumination of the glow stick, the young man blinks, gazing sadly.
SANCTUM_DVS533
With one hand pressed to his father's chest, SOMEONE bends down and plants a tender kiss on his forehead.
SANCTUM_DVS534
He rises, drawing his arms back and allows his father's body to float away.
SANCTUM_DVS536
Now underwater, SOMEONE emerges from a cavern, clutching a glow stick and the air cylinder.
SANCTUM_DVS537
Rise from the valve as he raises it to his lips and takes a hit.
SANCTUM_DVS538
SOMEONE inhales once again from the tank.
SANCTUM_DVS539
Coming out from around a bulging rock, he sees SOMEONE's body wedged against the ceiling up ahead.
SANCTUM_DVS540
SOMEONE crawls over jagged rocks beneath SOMEONE's lifeless, dangling arms.
SANCTUM_DVS542
Now, SOMEONE arrives at a narrow crevasse.
SANCTUM_DVS543
He takes another hit from the tank, then continues on.
SANCTUM_DVS544
Further on, SOMEONE stares resolutely forward as he feels his way along the jagged.
SANCTUM_DVS545
Glow stick dies out.
SANCTUM_DVS546
Now, SOMEONE clutches the boar tooth torch which emits a soft, warm glow.
SANCTUM_DVS547
Kicking his flippers, he continues on along a rocky passage.
SANCTUM_DVS548
As SOMEONE squeezes through a small opening, he raises the canister valve.
SANCTUM_DVS549
Narrow as he furiously twist the nozzle, then discards the tank.
SANCTUM_DVS550
With his cheeks puffed out, he edges his way up along a jutting wall of rock.
SANCTUM_DVS551
These bubbles emerge from small craters. SOMEONE crawls over and presses his lips to one.
SANCTUM_DVS554
From above, SOMEONE's face breaks the water's surface.
SANCTUM_DVS555
Inhales deeply from another air bubble.
SANCTUM_DVS557
A distant bluish light expands and shines across the big shape of SOMEONE's body.
SANCTUM_DVS558
Wincing, he re-submerges with a shake of his head.
SANCTUM_DVS559
As his near-motionless body rotates underwater, the young man shuts his eyes.
SANCTUM_DVS560
He begins to sink downward.
SANCTUM_DVS561
His body wavers.
SANCTUM_DVS562
Now, SOMEONE appears wearing his helmet light.
SANCTUM_DVS563
He smiles.
SANCTUM_DVS564
A view from underwater reveals shafts of light breaking on the pool's surface, cutting through the murk from a crevasse above.