Now, in a club, two women in old-fashioned costumes perform a traditional dance with fans in front of a DJ.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS37
Amid dancing guests, Sebastian and SOMEONE chat with their boss and a grey-haired man.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS38
Outside, a young woman in a bulky knit cap with a pompom on top makes a call on her cellphone.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS39
She wears her hair loose around her round, soft features.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS40
She looks up at the club with a furrowed brow.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS41
The young woman heaves a grim sigh.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS42
Her eyes fixed on the club, she lowers the phone sadly.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS43
Now, traffic speeds along an overpass beneath the dark nighttime sky.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS44
In the far right lane,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS45
the casually dressed young woman rides a bicycle.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS46
Her feet work the pedals in a steady rhythm,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS47
her tasseled scarf billowing behind her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS49
At a turn, she narrowly avoids a bus and a taxi.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS50
Her front wheel weaves unsteadily along the pavement.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS51
As cars whisk past at high speed, she reaches a busy street.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS53
As we ride with her, the vehicles blur and distort.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS54
Flashing headlights fill our view.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS56
Now, we gaze out over the city.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS57
In a dark bedroom, a cellphone lights up on a night stand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS58
In bed, SOMEONE nestles close to Sebastian.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS59
She stirs, wakes, and picks up the cellphone.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS60
The young woman glances at her sleeping partner as she answers.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS61
SOMEONE gets up.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS62
Subtitles. Miss SOMEONE is on her bike and was hit by a taxi.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS63
SOMEONE anxiously ends the call. Daytime.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS64
We gaze past the Oriental Pearl Tower and the adjacent Huangpu River to the hazy city.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS65
Traffic moves smoothly along the streets. At Hongking Hospital, SOMEONE bumps into a nurse.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS66
Reaching a hall, she peers down one end.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS67
Looking the other way, she breaks into a jog and joins a tall woman.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS68
The woman faces a window to a room.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS69
Following her gaze, SOMEONE finds an unconscious SOMEONE covered in casts and bandages.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS70
SOMEONE enters the room and leans over the injured woman.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS71
She reaches down to touch her but her hand hovers inches away.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS72
SOMEONE straightens and shifts on her feet.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS73
She brings the back of her hand to her mouth and squeezes her eyes shut.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS74
Swaying unsteadily, she turns away.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS75
SOMEONE leans against the bed rail in a grief-stricken slouch.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS76
Later, she sits by a window.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS78
She stares vacantly.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS83
In a sunlit living room, SOMEONE and SOMEONE dance around as teenagers. Words appear.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS84
1997, Shanghai.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS85
Clad in matching red and white tracksuits, they snack on buns out of a brown paper bag.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS87
An elegant older woman marches in.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS89
She takes the bag and holds it up.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS90
SOMEONE timidly avoids her gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS93
She takes SOMEONE's hand. The girl yanks it free.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS95
The stepmother faces SOMEONE's friend.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS99
She marches out.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS100
SOMEONE starts to follow, but SOMEONE discreetly steps in her path.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS101
SOMEONE slips past her, gazing after the older woman.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS102
Facing SOMEONE, she sticks out her tongue.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS103
Her friends nods and gives her an encouraging push.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS104
Now, SOMEONE's stepmother plays a record.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS107
Leaving the turntable, she starts to cross the tastefully decorated room.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS108
She pauses and faces her guest.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS109
Leaning against a far wall,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS110
SOMEONE reluctantly shuffles over to the older woman.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS111
As she gets closer, she stares at the floor.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS113
The stepmother moves in close.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS115
A smart girl like you with a bright future shouldn't have to spend all your time with her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS116
The stepmother leans in intimidatingly, a SOMEONE smile plastered on her exquisitely made up features.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS117
As she speaks, SOMEONE stares at her stained teeth and painted lips.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS118
Now, we peer out a window.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS119
SOMEONE's eyes rise into view and she peeks inside.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS120
She scans the area carefully.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS122
She slips a note in between the pane and the sill, and gently pounds the window frame.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS123
With a faint mischievous smirk, she sinks out of view.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS124
Now huddled by the window, SOMEONE opens the note.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS125
The SOMEONE characters translate to "Come and meet my family for dinner".
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS127
SOMEONE beams softly, folds the note shut, and gazes out the window with a hopeful smile.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS129
Now, the two friends walk down a narrow alley.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS131
Holding SOMEONE's hand, SOMEONE leads her through a doorway and across a small courtyard.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS132
Now, at a humble kitchen table.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS133
SOMEONE's father smiles with the girls.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS135
Her mother brings a small pot and lifts the lid. SOMEONE inhales the steam.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS137
SOMEONE serves her friend a dumpling.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS143
Now, a long reed with a heavy bud at the end taps on SOMEONE's window.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS144
Clutching it, SOMEONE also holds an umbrella.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS145
A pretty, young woman opens the window and the girl ducks down.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS147
Sitting close to her aunt, SOMEONE notices an antique slipper the size of a small child's foot.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS148
Three-inch golden lilies.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS149
SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a look.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS150
They hook pinkies. Now, at a modest office,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS151
a man at a desk hands the girls a CD case.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS155
SOMEONE takes up a pen and signs the bottom.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS156
She passes the contract to SOMEONE, who adds her signature.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS157
In the present day, SOMEONE sits by SOMEONE's hospital bed, thoughtfully reading through some papers as sunlight pours in through the windows.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS158
A woman in a white coat arrives.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS159
SOMEONE's bag is at reception.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS161
SOMEONE smiles politely and the hospital staffer goes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS162
The young professional flips through a few more papers, then flips their binder shut.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS163
Now, SOMEONE's hand gingerly pulls open a large black leather satchel and finds the items within encased in clear plastic bags.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS165
she finds a stack of orange and white note cards.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS166
SOMEONE sets it aside with a puzzled frown.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS167
Digging deeper in the satchel, she pulls out a dark gray garment.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS168
She takes part of it from its plastic encasement.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS169
It looks like a man's suit jacket.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS170
SOMEONE's brow furrows and she continues sorting through her friend's belongings.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS171
Next, she pulls out a manuscript.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS172
She takes it from its bag and holds it up with a frown.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS173
The cover page reads simply "Untitled by SOMEONE Liao".
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS174
SOMEONE flips through the pages and reads silently.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS175
This is the story of SOMEONE and SOMEONE,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS176
two girls born in the same month, on the same day.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS177
Their feet bound on the same day.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS178
Now, SOMEONE drives.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS180
SOMEONE comes to a stop.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS181
She notices a little girl in a blue tunic sitting nearby.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS182
She wears her bangs short, the rest of her hair in a long braid.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS183
She faces SOMEONE, her bare feet resting on a stool.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS187
Hands wrap a black swath of fabric over the girl's toes and pulls hard.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS188
Another adult firmly holds the tearful recoiling girl's shoulder as the person continues binding her feet.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS189
The girl looks to the woman holding her shoulder.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS193
In another home, a woman squeezes a little girl's toes together as she tightly wraps a bandage around the child's foot.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS195
The girl bites her lip, her eyes filling with tears, and shoots a pleading glance at a stern-faced woman watching them.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS197
The stern-faced woman stares down at the seated girl.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS198
The child blinks and the woman lifts her to her feet.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS200
With her lips parted in pain,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS201
the little girl faces a pair of doors. She takes a step, then hunches over.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS204
Hobbling forward, the little girl tries to run outside.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS205
A lady servant stops her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS208
SOMEONE takes small steps.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS209
Only through pain SOMEONE you find beauty.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS210
Only through suffering SOMEONE you find peace.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS211
With SOMEONE and her mother.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS214
She extends her hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS215
SOMEONE takes a few small slow steps.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS216
Her mother grabs her hand and pulls her forward.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS218
SOMEONE pushes on.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS221
As the little girl turns and hobbles in the other direction,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS222
her mother gives a gentle push.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS223
Crisscrossed bandages around SOMEONE's ankles hold her bindings tight.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS225
Now, in bed, SOMEONE thrashes under her covers.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS227
Meanwhile, at her home, SOMEONE whimpers as she lies under a blanket on the floor.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS228
Turning onto her other side, she faces a sleeping sibling.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS229
One of SOMEONE's bound feet gets out below her blanket, its bandage is stained with blood.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS231
A crowd watches as porters carry a sedan chair into their neighborhood.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS232
SOMEONE's mother and father wait just outside their home.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS234
SOMEONE stands in the doorway with a servant.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS235
A plump woman dressed in a colorful SOMEONE robe pushes aside the curtain on the enclosed litter and steps out.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS236
Later, she examines SOMEONE's tiny, stunted foot inside her lotus shoe.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS241
She leans on her cane and eyes SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS250
SOMEONE blinks her solemn eyes at the matchmaker.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS252
The plump woman nods, then turns to the door.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS254
A servant places the privileged girl in a seat beside her new laotong.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS256
SOMEONE and SOMEONE both stare straight ahead for a long moment, then, in unison, shift their curious eyes toward each other.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS257
Now, they write at a table.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS260
SOMEONE gazes across the table at SOMEONE's paper.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS263
Later, as the girls lie in bed together, SOMEONE traces characters on SOMEONE's bare back.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS268
Now, side by side at a water basin, they wipe their faces with wash cloths.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS269
The water reflects their images. SOMEONE with buns on either side of her head,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS270
SOMEONE with her simple braid.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS272
Snowflakes drift down and the girls try to catch them.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS273
Now, they kneel at a shrine.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS274
The Temple of Gupo Fair is a holy place. We are here today in front of Gupo to write your laotong contract and make your vows of eternal commitment.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS275
She opens a fan with writing on it. The girls read.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS278
The matchmaker closes the fan.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS279
Now, the girls write side by side, their eyes intent on their careful brush strokes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS281
they set their papers in a fire.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS282
The matchmaker bows.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS284
In the present, SOMEONE sits at SOMEONE's bedside, gazing at her unconscious friend.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS286
A bedside lamp shines its harsh light on SOMEONE's bruised face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS287
SOMEONE shifts her woeful eyes to her own lap and tilts her head thoughtfully.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS288
Her gaze drifts to SOMEONE's hand which rests over.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS289
Sliding her own hand on top of her laotong's, SOMEONE gives it a gentle squeeze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS290
She clutches SOMEONE's limp hand between both of hers,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS291
then rests her cheek against them and closes her eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS292
Now, at a restaurant.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS293
SOMEONE sits across a table from her parents.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS295
Her mother pauses as she eats, frowning at her daughter's sullen downcast gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS308
She gives her parents a determined look.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS310
SOMEONE sits at her car, staring off absently.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS311
She takes out her phone and dials.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS312
She lifts it to her ear and waits.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS313
She hangs up.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS315
Now, at her apartment, a pile of pages from SOMEONE's manuscript rests on a couch.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS316
SOMEONE sits beside it. The remaining pages settled on her crossed leg.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS317
With her elbow on the arm of the couch, she props her cheek on her hand as she reads.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS318
In the story, SOMEONE, now a young woman, brushes characters onto a panel of a paper fan.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS324
With a thoughtful smile, SOMEONE finishes writing and props her cheek on her hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS325
Now, a group of women sit around a table decorating the edges of a red bridal bed blanket.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS326
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE, who sits beside her sewing.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS328
The privileged young woman gives her friend a sly smile and averts her gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS329
Now alone together, they arrange a bouquet.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS332
SOMEONE stares at her worried friend, who clutches her hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS334
She tries to stifle a chuckle.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS336
SOMEONE shoves her friend, then allows a smile.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS337
Now, in the daytime, a procession of women with their faces hidden behind red scarves exit SOMEONE's home through a doorway adorned on each side with a red banner.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS338
Behind them, SOMEONE holds SOMEONE's arm and guides her outside.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS339
A red scarf hangs over SOMEONE's bridal crown,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS340
veiling her face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS343
With SOMEONE at her side, the bride takes cautious steps over the threshold, then stops in front of her parents.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS348
She eyes her daughter through the red veil.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS350
She bows her head. SOMEONE starts to guide the bride away, but SOMEONE stops.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS351
SOMEONE tugs on her arm,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS352
but her laotong remains in place.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS353
SOMEONE turns back to her parents.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS357
With SOMEONE tugging her arm, SOMEONE reluctantly moves on, but her face remains turned toward her cheerful mother.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS360
The two friends walk past townsfolk gathered to watch the procession, then stop at a gateway in a brick wall that encloses the property.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS362
Standing there, Madame SOMEONE gives SOMEONE an expectant look.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS364
The young bride turns to her laotong, the beaded fringe on her veil swaying back and forth.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS366
Reaching into the loose sleeve of her robe, SOMEONE withdraws a folded paper fan and holds it out to her friend.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS367
SOMEONE takes it, then lifts her gaze to her laotong's.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS368
SOMEONE helps her slide the fan down her own sleeve.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS369
She rests her hand on the bride's.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS373
SOMEONE pushes aside her veil's fringe.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS375
Her friend grabs her wrist and lowers her hand from the veil.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS376
Swallowing, SOMEONE gives her laotong a sad look.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS377
Still clutching the bride's hands, she glances into the street,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS378
where musicians play by a waiting sedan chair.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS379
Smoke billows into the air as firecrackers pop.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS380
Now, SOMEONE sits at the edge of a curtained state bed, her hands folded in her lap.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS382
A young man walks over and lifts off her veil, revealing her elaborate bridal crown.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS383
A mountain of fruit rests on top, and a second veil of dangling beads offers a semi-obscured view of her nervous face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS384
As the groom sits beside his new bride, she scoots a few inches away from him.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS388
He lowers his disappointed gaze, then shoots her a tentative glance.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS389
He gently grabs the skirt of her robe
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS390
closed together tightly.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS391
SOMEONE blinks behind the beaded fringe of her bridal crown as her husband kneels and lifts her tiny foot.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS392
He lowers his face to her red lotus shoe.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS394
Closing his eyes, he gently kisses and caresses her foot.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS395
SOMEONE tries to pull it away, but he holds tight.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS396
He kisses her instep again.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS397
SOMEONE withdraws and he glances up at her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS398
Sitting up next to his bride again, he tosses his braid over his shoulder and grabs her hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS399
SOMEONE tries to pull it away but he holds firm.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS400
Avoiding his gaze, she stops struggling and blinks resignedly.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS401
One year later. An elderly couple sits on either side of a table facing us. The man lights a pipe.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS404
Standing in a hallway, a pregnant SOMEONE eavesdrops on the conversation.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS410
She exits the room and sees SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS412
She exits past her shy daughter-in-law.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS413
Later, SOMEONE folds a robe in her bedroom while her husband pours tea at a small table.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS418
SOMEONE shifts her concerned gaze away.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS420
With his eyes averted from his wife, he takes a sip of tea.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS421
He rests the cup just below his lips as he swallows, then turns to SOMEONE with a furrowed brow and finds her gazing at him.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS423
She lowers her solemn eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS425
Now in the present. SOMEONE shifts her handbag's shoulder strap as she climbs some steps leading to a set of glass doors.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS428
IPushing one open, she enters an art gallery. n the foyer, a well-dressed man sits at a table covered in artwork.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS429
He chats with another man.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS433
With a nod, she heads back to an exhibit room where she finds a gallery worker hanging black and white images of disfigured feet on a crisp white wall.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS435
Walking deeper into the room, SOMEONE eyes a display podium holding pairs of tiny lotus shoes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS437
On another wall, a drawing of a fan sits below writing in images detailing Chinese tradition.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS438
SOMEONE examines real paper fans sitting atop a row of display podiums.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS439
She gazes at the writing on the spread panels of one.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS440
A short-haired woman dressed in all black
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS441
with a straight line of bangs over her eyebrows approaches.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS451
SOMEONE notices a projection on a wall.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS453
Moving closer to the bright panel, she sees rows of Chinese characters.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS454
As a gallery worker scrolls through text on a laptop,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS455
the projected image moves as well.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS456
This is a new interactive nu shu program.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS457
As Claire scrolls downs the rows of characters on a second laptop,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS458
SOMEONE gazes at the projection.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS459
The light casts a pale glow on her delicate face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS460
Now, SOMEONE opens a jewelry box drawer and takes out a paper fan.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS461
Later, she sits at a table and writes on it.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS462
A baby rests beside her in a bassinet.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS466
Spreading open the fan, SOMEONE reads her friend's message.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS469
Now, SOMEONE's mother-in-law sits at the head of the table of a group of women doing embroidery work.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS474
Her mother-in-law's eyes remain on her stitching.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS476
SOMEONE blinks, then averts her heartbroken gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS479
She looks up at her mother-in-law, who turns to her with an unyielding expression.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS480
Setting down her embroidery hoop, the matronly woman lifts a lid off her teacup.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS482
Steam wafts out.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS487
Later, SOMEONE paces with hobbled steps and wrings her hands as she waits in a dim hallway.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS488
A servant girl rushes over.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS490
SOMEONE slides the folded fan out from her sleeve.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS492
She places SOMEONE's hands around it.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS493
The servant girl nods.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS494
Clutching the fan to her chest,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS495
she cautiously glances around, then hurries off down the hall.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS496
SOMEONE watches her disappear down a staircase,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS497
then turns her look.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS502
Now, SOMEONE pushes open a gate's wooden doors. Hurrying to a sedan chair, she takes SOMEONE's arm as the woman exits the litter.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS503
A porter tilts it forward,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS504
allowing her to step over the wooden rails in front.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS505
SOMEONE accompanies her through the open gate.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS506
SOMEONE makes her way across a bridge outside a temple, then turns to the young servant.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS508
As SOMEONE returns to the gate,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS509
a woman approaches SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS511
SOMEONE joyfully clasps her hands around her friend's.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS512
Now, they each add a fresh stick of incense to a pot filled with the smoldering tokens.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS513
The two friends kneel, press their hands together in prayer, and bow their heads.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS514
Later, they sit on a bench.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS516
Her head hung low, SOMEONE nods morosely.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS520
SOMEONE glances at her troubled friend, then takes her hands and shifts her gaze straight ahead.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS521
SOMEONE lifts her eyes to her laotong's calm face and twitches a tender smile.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS525
Now, a door closes SOMEONE into a room.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS528
SOMEONE sinks to her knees. With an anguished look, she peers through a crack, then slumps against the thick wooden door.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS529
In the present, as SOMEONE sits asleep with her head propped against a wall, a female hand reaches out and gently brushes her long bangs from her face then taps her shoulder.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS530
SOMEONE wakes and looks up at the visitor.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS531
SOMEONE's aunt sits beside her on a bench in the hallway.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS532
She lets out a breath.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS533
SOMEONE glances at her ashamedly.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS534
She watches sympathetically as SOMEONE hangs her head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS536
SOMEONE lowers her gaze and stares at the floor, lost in thought.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS537
Our view gently drifts toward her worried face framed by thin strands of her raven hair.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS538
Now, SOMEONE sits alone at a table.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS540
She dips a brush in ink, then begins to write on a fan spread open before her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS543
In another room, an old man lies on his side, smoking a long-stemmed pipe.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS546
SOMEONE spies on him from a cracked open door.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS547
Our view drifts from the old man's pinched, intoxicated face to the pipe in his hand and a burning opium lamp nearby.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS548
SOMEONE shuts the door.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS549
The image dissolves to SOMEONE as she opens the fan to the many columns of Chinese lettering in its folds.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS552
SOMEONE gazes thoughtfully at the message,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS553
then shuts the fan and touches it to her chin.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS554
She dreamily closes her eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS556
As she gently presses the fan to her cheek, the image fades to black.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS557
Now, two years later.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS558
Our view drifts from an open burning stove to SOMEONE,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS559
who stares off thoughtfully with an infant strapped to her back.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS560
She lowers her disheartened gaze, then removes a closed fan from the sleeve of her blue robe.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS561
She opens it and begins to read.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS565
Now, SOMEONE stands at a window.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS567
She watches two men carry a body outside, then lowers her gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS568
Beyond an empty dinner table, a hysterical woman walks past an open door with a baby in her arms.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS569
Bringing a tea pot to the table, SOMEONE watches her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS570
Lady SOMEONE staggers backward into view at the doorway as her daughter-in-law prepares the tea.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS578
She follows after her mother-in-law.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS580
Wearing white cloth over her nose and mouth, SOMEONE tends to Lady SOMEONE, who lies in bed.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS583
As SOMEONE feeds the sick woman, an old man peeks in through a door.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS584
Upon seeing them, he covers his mouth and steps back out.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS585
Now, SOMEONE carries a tray of food through a darkened hall.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS586
She sets it down, then approaches a door and peeks inside.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS587
A light from within the room shines on her face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS597
SOMEONE covers her mouth in distress.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS598
Now, a view through a barred upper floor window shows a man lying dead in the street below.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS599
SOMEONE peers outside with the soft daylight shining on her face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS600
Now, a woman with a cloth over her nose and mouth uses a stick to pick up an article of clothing from a pile and drop it into a small fire burning in the middle of a patio.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS601
SOMEONE steps into view with her face covered as well.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS602
She watches the incineration.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS603
SOMEONE runs in through a gate.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS605
She bows respectfully.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS607
SOMEONE looks toward the gate.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS608
Later, a couple bows ceremoniously to her and her husband,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS609
who now wears a mustache and smokes a pipe.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS610
Master and Lady SOMEONE passed away.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS611
They both succumbed to the plague.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS612
On this day of the new year, we became Master and Lady SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS613
A second couple bows to them and walks off.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS614
The center portion of her lips painted red, SOMEONE wears an elegant black silk robe with a royal blue yoke and elaborate silver jewelry.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS615
She maintains an emotionless expression as the villagers continue to pay their respects.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS617
In present day, the identically featured SOMEONE drives her car through the city.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS618
She peers out the passenger window.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS619
Passing some scaffolding and a few partly torn down buildings,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS620
she spots a few distant skyscrapers and a tall crane beyond the rundown neighborhood.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS621
A lone three-story house stands in the middle of a construction site.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS623
Now inside, SOMEONE cautiously approaches a door with her purse in hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS624
She knocks.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS625
She turns for the exit.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS626
Mrs. SOMEONE opens the door, fixing her hair.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS627
Noticing SOMEONE, she straightens her bath robe.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS660
In flashback, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch a news report.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS661
Today, the stock market hit a new low due to the liquidation of Peregrine Investments.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS662
In the living room, Mr. SOMEONE paces.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS664
SOMEONE peers into the room.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS666
SOMEONE shakes her head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS671
Mr. SOMEONE shifts his trouble gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS672
He turns and ambles across the room to a window, posts his arm on the wall, and hangs his head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS673
SOMEONE opens a door and peeks into the room.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS674
Glancing around, she spots her father by the window.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS675
She crosses to him, shuffling past a mantle adorned with framed pictures and an ornamental clock.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS676
He wipes his face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS677
SOMEONE takes a step closer.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS678
The market goes up and down.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS680
She holds her father's hands.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS683
Mr. SOMEONE nods and they hug.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS684
Resting her chin on his shoulder,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS685
SOMEONE holds her father tight and gazes off thoughtfully.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS686
Now holding three incense sticks,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS687
Mrs. SOMEONE bows repeatedly before a small altar with a framed photograph of Mr. SOMEONE surrounded by candles, flowers, and bowls of fruit and rice.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS688
She sets the incense sticks in a dish.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS689
Among other mourners, the aunt steps past her and nods.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS690
Mrs. SOMEONE follows her with her eyes as she sits beside SOMEONE and rubs her back.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS691
The bereaved daughter rests her head on SOMEONE's shoulder.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS692
A male mourner walks across our view of the best friends.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS696
She wipes her nose.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS697
And to do this in his own home.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS698
She shakes her head, then looks at SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS699
His daughter won't speak to me.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS700
She isn't even studying for the college entrance exam.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS702
The teary-eyed girl shifts in her seat.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS703
Now at night.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS704
SOMEONE consoles her friend, who wipes her eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS705
SOMEONE cries on her shoulder.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS706
SOMEONE's eyes glisten with tears and she lowers her saddened gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS707
Later, she sleeps in SOMEONE's bed with her arm draped over her friend.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS708
Now at school, they cross the hallway with other students. SOMEONE grabs her friend's arm.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS709
SOMEONE watches her hurry down the hall.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS711
Later, in a classroom, SOMEONE sits amongst other students taking the test at their desks. Behind her,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS712
a teacher paces an aisle.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS713
SOMEONE folds back the sleeve of her flannel shirt and checks her watch,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS714
then peers across the room.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS715
Returning her attention to the test, she chews on the pen.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS716
A heading reads "Listening Comprehension".
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS717
SOMEONE begins to write.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS720
SOMEONE shifts in her seat again and resumes her work.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS721
At night, a band performs under a low arched ceiling.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS722
SOMEONE and SOMEONE make their way through a tightly packed crowd of fans waving their arms overhead.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS723
They duck under a low archway to a side room with a tiled wall.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS724
She hugs SOMEONE, who looks past her with a worried expression.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS725
SOMEONE steps back in front of her friend.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS726
She leads her taller friend back through the frenzied crowd toward the stage.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS727
Flood lights on the arched cement walls give the tunnel-like performance space a blue tint.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS728
Now, in her kitchen, Mrs. Wei chops vegetables.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS731
She sets down her knife, wipes her hands, then answers the door.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS734
The bespectacled man produces and envelope and hands it to her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS735
Mrs. Wei opens it, then removes and unfolds a letter.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS736
She reads. Shanghai Education Board. Disciplinary Notice.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS737
Later, she faces her pigtailed daughter.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS740
SOMEONE walks out.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS751
SOMEONE hangs her head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS753
Mrs. Wei storms off, leaving her daughter standing alone on the balcony with her head down.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS754
Now, a commercial jet taxis to a gate.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS756
Elsewhere at the airport, the two friends face each by a window, sharing a long gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS757
SOMEONE forces a smile.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS758
SOMEONE turns and wheels her suitcase through a set of automatic doors underneath the sign for Terminal 1.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS759
SOMEONE takes a couple of steps to the side, watching her friend go.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS760
The automatic doors slide shut behind SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS761
SOMEONE turns away and ambles off alone.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS762
Now, our view rises from a customer's menu to find SOMEONE working as a waitress in a pink uniform.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS764
In the restaurant's kitchen, our view descends from a metal counter to find SOMEONE studying while on break.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS766
She brushes a strand of hair behind her ear, then jots a note on a pad over a textbook.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS767
Now, SOMEONE crosses a courtyard to a wooden mailbox on a wall.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS768
She produces a key, unlocks a padlock, and opens the box to find an envelope inside.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS769
Brightening, she takes it out and studies it.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS771
Now dressed for an interview, SOMEONE stands up as Sebastian walks another female applicant out of his office.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS772
At night, SOMEONE sits at a cubicle in the darkened office.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS773
She sets a few file aside, picks up a document, then leans back in her chair and reads.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS776
In the present, SOMEONE sits at SOMEONE's bedside reading the manuscript.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS778
Finishing a page, she sets it down by her lap among several others.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS779
Later, SOMEONE crosses to a window overlooking the city.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS780
She rests her hand on the sill and peers outside.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS781
On the busy street below,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS782
four men carry a red palanquin litter along the sidewalk.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS783
SOMEONE shifts her thoughtful gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS784
The image dissolves to a  river, beyond which stands a high cliff.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS785
A palanquin gets carried across the far bank.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS786
SOMEONE rides inside peering out a window.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS790
Now, SOMEONE opens a wooden gate.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS791
She sighs excitedly, expelling a foggy breath.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS795
SOMEONE takes her friend's hands and presses them against her heart.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS796
Behind them, villagers look on.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS799
SOMEONE nods.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS800
SOMEONE leads her by the hand into a courtyard.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS801
SOMEONE observes her shabby surroundings and deflates.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS802
The friends pass a single cow standing off to the side.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS803
A rooster meanders.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS804
Beyond a steaming wok over a fire pit, slaughtered animal carcasses hang from hooks.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS805
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS807
SOMEONE nods.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS810
SOMEONE looks sadly at her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS813
SOMEONE glances down, then looks hesitantly at SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS817
the two friends sit at a table working with vegetables.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS818
Across the hay-strewn courtyard, SOMEONE's husband corrals a pig with a stick.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS819
He kicks the animal's rear and locks it in a pen.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS820
SOMEONE watches him.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS821
The burly man carries a leafy vegetable across the yard.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS822
He tosses it onto the woman's table then marches off.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS823
Now at a dinner table, SOMEONE feeds one of her daughters.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS824
SOMEONE sits at her other side.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS825
The butcher glowers over his bowl as he shovels food into his mouth.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS826
SOMEONE musters a smile for her laotong.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS827
Across the table, her husband shakes sauce off a round dumpling and bites into it.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS828
SOMEONE lowers her disapproving gaze to her bowl.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS829
The butcher slurps down his tea in one gulp.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS831
As he leaves the table, SOMEONE gets up and follows him to a doorway.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS834
He looks past his wife to SOMEONE,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS835
who lowers her unhappy gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS837
Later, in the dark, the well-to-do guest lies in a humble bed, her eyes open.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS839
SOMEONE hesitantly rolls over and leans her head over the edge of the bed.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS840
Light filtering between the floor boards glows on her delicate features.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS841
She leans a little further to see below.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS842
In the room beneath her, the shirtless butcher lies on top of SOMEONE and thrusts.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS844
She clings to him tightly, her eyes closed and her lips parted.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS845
SOMEONE watches them.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS846
SOMEONE's hand gently caresses her husband's back.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS847
SOMEONE returns to her shadowy bed and rolls over to face the ceiling.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS848
Her eyes close and her chest heaves beneath the thick blanket.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS849
SOMEONE lets her hand drift up to her own face,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS851
Her fingertips awkwardly touching her skin, As they trail down her bare throat,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS853
Her other arm crosses her chest, she gathers the blanket up close to her chin.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS855
In the present day, SOMEONE's feet slip off a pair of black high-heeled shoes and rest on a white carpet.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS856
One bare foot rubs the other ankle.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS857
SOMEONE's hand reaches down and massages one foot.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS858
She lifts it up across her knee
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS859
and gently caresses the backs of her toes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS860
Her soft downturned gaze remains fixed on the moment of self-care.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS863
Her gaze growing distant.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS864
In the butcher's house, her 19th century counterpart sleeps curled up in the humble bed.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS865
She stirs awake and looks around.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS866
The noblewoman sits up, her long hair loose around her shoulder.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS867
She peers down toward the lower floor, then shifts her puzzled gaze and gets up.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS868
Smoke, wind, and sunlight stream in from a round hole in the wall serving as a window. SOMEONE approaches it, raising a hand over her nose and mouth as she peers out.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS869
The Taiping rebels are coming.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS870
A little later, she goes downstairs disheveled and confused.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS877
He rushes off.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS879
The butcher drags an old woman from another room.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS880
SOMEONE grabs her friend.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS888
The butcher steps close.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS889
He picks SOMEONE up.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS891
He carries the resistant noblewoman out.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS892
Later, the butcher leads an ox-drawn cart down a narrow road packed with fleeing refugees.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS893
The cart carries his family and many belongings.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS897
SOMEONE helps him gather bulging sacks.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS899
A sack in each powerful arm, the butcher leads his family farther on as panicking villagers race past.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS900
Now, he and a couple of small boys arrive at a refugee campsite.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS901
Behind him, SOMEONE and SOMEONE aid his mother.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS904
The butcher hurries back to them, takes sacks from the old woman's back,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS905
and leans them against a rock.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS906
The younger women lead her over.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS907
Lay her down here.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS908
They rest the old woman on a mound of filled sacks.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS909
SOMEONE lifts her up as the butcher stuffs another sack beneath her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS910
He briskly caresses his mother's face, then aces SOMEONE with a grave expression.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS915
The butcher picks up a boy.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS916
He SOMEONE take care of your mama.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS917
The little boy nods.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS918
The butcher gives him a hearty kiss, sets him down, and strides off.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS919
SOMEONE and SOMEONE gaze after him.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS920
At night, SOMEONE faces her laotong.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS923
The noblewoman bends down and removes her ornate slipper,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS924
revealing her tiny bound foot still wrapped in bandages.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS925
She massages her big toe and winces.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS926
As she sits up, SOMEONE strokes her hair.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS929
SOMEONE strokes her friend's shoulder.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS930
Now, the refugee women sit huddled around a campfire.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS932
Seated close to each other, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare into the flames with listless expressions.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS933
They barely sing.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS934
A couple of small white flakes drift down from above.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS935
A few more dart past, carried by the wind.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS936
The two friends stop singing and peer up.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS937
They share a grave look, then lean over and adjust the blankets covering the children at their feet.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS938
SOMEONE observes SOMEONE's attention to her sons and rubs her shoulder appreciatively.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS939
The two women share a tender look and SOMEONE takes her hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS941
At dawn, the snow falls heavily on the camp.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS942
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and her children lie huddled together under heavy blankets near the mouth of a cave.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS943
The butcher returns and tethers the cow to a tree.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS945
He finds his young son on the end without his share of the covers.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS946
The father dusts snow off the child's clothes and adjusts the blanket to cover him.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS947
Patting the boy's hand, he pauses.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS948
The father lays a hand on his son's head, then touches his face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS949
The child lies unresponsive.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS950
The butcher lowers the blanket and cranes his face close to the boy's.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS951
The father sits back on his knees.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS952
He hefts the boy's limp body and rocks him in his arms.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS954
As he gets to his feet, his son's head rolls back limply and one arm dangles from his grasp.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS955
The butcher clasps his son tightly to his chest.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS956
He looks down at his lost child.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS957
Staggering slightly, he plods away from the others.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS958
Behind him, SOMEONE wakes to see her husband grimacing skyward.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS959
She rushes over.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS961
She cradles the boy's lifeless face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS962
The butcher shoves her away, then grabs her by the tunic and flings her aside.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS964
SOMEONE runs after her husband. SOMEONE follows.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS965
Now awake, the rest of the family watches gravely.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS966
Now, the two laotongs sit face to face in the cave mouth.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS967
SOMEONE dabs gently at SOMEONE's bruised, swollen eye.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS969
Beyond them, snow continues to fall on the wooded campsite.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS971
SOMEONE pauses, her fingertips trailing down her friend's soft, round cheek.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS972
She tenderly brushes wisps of loose hair out of SOMEONE's face, then lowers her hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS973
She regards her friend compassionately, her eyes glistening.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS975
SOMEONE's eyes well up as she and her sister regard each other.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS976
A tear trails down SOMEONE's cheek.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS977
SOMEONE swallows, tilts her head, and presses her brow to her sister's.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS978
SOMEONE closes her eyes and brushes her cheek against her laotong's smooth skin.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS980
She bows her head, her soft features pinching in a grief-stricken frown.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS981
SOMEONE reaches out, cradles her face in her hand,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS982
and gently lifts her head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS984
SOMEONE absently meets her laotong's loving gaze, then leans back.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS985
Her melancholy face falling out of view.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS986
SOMEONE looks on mournfully.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS987
In the present, SOMEONE lies draped over SOMEONE's hospital bed,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS988
sleeping with her hand over some of the manuscript pages.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS989
Daylight from the windows accentuates her pale complexion as she slumbers.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS990
A few stray wisps of her black hair obscure her delicate face,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS991
which rests on her own outstretched arm.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS992
Her jackets hangs slung over her chair's backrest
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS993
and her right hand clutches a few more pages.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS994
The rest of the stack lies on SOMEONE's blanketed lap.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS995
SOMEONE slumbers on.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS997
Nearby, a monitor tracks her friend's vitals.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS998
At night, in SOMEONE's car.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS999
Staring off, she shifts her attention to the traffic ahead and pulls her car forward.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1000
Now, we gaze at a Shanghai freeway from a distance.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1001
The tightly-packed headlights shine brightly beneath the night sky.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1002
Beyond them, a vast mass of skyscrapers stands mostly darkened.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1003
Now, in a club.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1004
A girlish singer in a slinky black dress leaves the stage and flirts with patrons on the dance floor.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1005
On the periphery, a ruggedly handsome man of Anglo descent sports close cropped hair and a nice suit.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1006
He finds SOMEONE on a love seat where a man with a grey beard awkwardly fails to chat with her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1007
A gold-framed oil portrait hangs upside down behind them.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1008
The handsome man sits.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1009
The grey-bearded playboy gives a disappointed shake of the head and leaves.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1010
The handsome man offers SOMEONE a brief sad smile.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1011
She lowers her mirthless gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1012
SOMEONE leans forward, his demeanor stoic and polite.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1014
She hesitantly meets his tender brown-eyed gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1015
She looks away remorsefully.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1016
Now, traffic passes outside Hongking hospital.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1017
Inside, SOMEONE smirks uneasily.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1018
SOMEONE stands close by in the corridor.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1019
She takes a deep breath.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1020
SOMEONE studies his expression, then bows her head demurely.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1021
SOMEONE crosses to SOMEONE's door, opens it, and passes through.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1022
SOMEONE paces in the hall, then peers after him.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1024
The well-dressed man shuffles to the bed and sinks down on its edge.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1025
His hands rest on his knees as he slouches,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1026
looking down at the comatose woman.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1027
SOMEONE reaches an arm across her legs and rests his hand on the other side.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1029
SOMEONE turns away, putting her back to the corridor wall, and blinks heavily.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1030
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit side by side munching corn on the cob.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1031
They watch TV and read magazines.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1032
Words appear. Six months earlier.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1038
SOMEONE reaches for her friend's chest and tickles her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1039
SOMEONE wrenches away, then playfully smacks SOMEONE's head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1040
Now in business attire, SOMEONE works at a desktop computer. Sebastian strolls in with a smile.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1041
SOMEONE lowers an amazed grin.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1042
Now at a bar lit dramatically by lemony yellow light bulbs, SOMEONE takes two shots onto the near empty dance floor and hands one to SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1043
In slinky party dresses, they SOMEONE to the music and swivel their hips as they drink.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1044
SOMEONE flips her long hair and sidles closer to her laotong, her eyes closed in sensual pout.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1045
SOMEONE tosses her hair over her shoulders and tilts her head back.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1046
Later, they sip their shots.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1047
Now, in a back room, SOMEONE sits back in a plush chair and kicks off her high heels.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1049
As she settles in, SOMEONE saunters over with a liquor bottle in one hand, a drink in the other.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1050
She sets the bottle down and sits next to her best friend.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1051
SOMEONE regards her with a smile.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1052
They clink glasses and sip the clear iceless drinks.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1053
SOMEONE gently pushes her friend's head away. SOMEONE glares.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1054
Now at a fancy dinner club, SOMEONE stands in the spotlight before a band.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1055
Sharing a table, Sebastian and SOMEONE applaud.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1056
Dancing couples take to the floor.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1057
As an amused SOMEONE and Sebastian watch from their distant table, SOMEONE crosses the dance floor.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1058
SOMEONE arrives at a table and points at its occupant.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1059
Sinking down to a chair, he sits close to SOMEONE and sings to her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1060
She adopts a sullen pout,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1061
then brushes her hair back and faces him with a coy hint of a smile.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1062
At their table, Sebastian claps good-humoredly.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1063
A stunned SOMEONE looks on uneasily.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1064
SOMEONE chuckles.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1065
As SOMEONE leans in, SOMEONE turns away.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1066
She raises her fingers to her lips, shifts her coquettish gaze, and grants him a chaste kiss.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1067
SOMEONE sets down his mic, takes SOMEONE's hand, and leads her to the dance floor where he yanks her in close.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1068
As SOMEONE stares tensely, SOMEONE seizes the club owner's head and pulls him into a long, sensual kiss.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1069
SOMEONE gives a showman's smile, extends his arm in a mock shrug, and melts into the embrace.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1070
His hand drifts to her waist, then slips down her slinky dark pink dress.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1071
He caresses her shapely bottom.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1072
SOMEONE takes a strained breath and bows her head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1073
Later, SOMEONE saunters down a softly-lit hallway.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1074
SOMEONE follows her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1075
Now facing a mirror, SOMEONE dabs tinted gloss on her full lips, then smiles at herself.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1076
She leaves the restroom to find SOMEONE waiting outside.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1077
SOMEONE stares at her with disbelief, then shakes her head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1078
SOMEONE withdraws gently, her gaze softening.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1079
SOMEONE marches down the hallway, her head bowed. SOMEONE stares after her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1080
She turns away.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1081
Shifting her increasingly troubled gaze,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1082
she sets her jaw stubbornly.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1083
Back at the butcher's house in the 19th century,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1084
SOMEONE opens a heavy pair of wooden doors,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1085
then accompanies SOMEONE as she shuffles out with a somber expression.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1087
SOMEONE sighs gravely, her face still bruised.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1089
Her laotong stands motionless.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1090
SOMEONE faces her and takes her hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1092
Her friend doesn't look at her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1093
SOMEONE's eyes blink heavily.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1094
So much has happened in the years we were apart.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1095
SOMEONE listens with a gentle gaze, her head tilted to one side.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1099
SOMEONE gives a solemn, understanding nod,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1100
then looks down at their clasped hands.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1101
SOMEONE shuffles around to face her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1104
Hand in hand, they leave the doorway.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1106
SOMEONE displays a wounded scowl.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1108
SOMEONE halts, her brow knitted.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1112
SOMEONE stares at her, then timidly works her full lips.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1114
SOMEONE's chest heaves and she lowers her gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1115
She leads her laotong onward with a pinched expression.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1122
Beyond the open gate, the noblewoman's servants ready her palanquin.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1124
SOMEONE affectionately strokes her friend's arm.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1125
There are things about men you SOMEONE never know.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1126
There are matters you do not understand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1127
SOMEONE abruptly turns away and marches through the gate.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1128
SOMEONE follows.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1131
The rebels have been stopped.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1132
She pauses at the threshold, gazing out over the countryside.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1135
Eyes glistening, SOMEONE faces her laotong imploringly.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1136
SOMEONE clasps hands with her and looks uncertainly toward the palanquin.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1138
SOMEONE slowly turns and looks at her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1139
She takes a deep breath, then gently withdraws her hands from SOMEONE's trembling grasp.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1140
The noblewoman's eyes glisten but she gives an accepting nod and bows her head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1141
Now, SOMEONE and three other women sit at the side of a river beating wet clothes with clubs.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1145
SOMEONE glances at her, then shakes her head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1147
She and the other woman wring out a garment.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1148
SOMEONE takes another sopping wet article of
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1159
She takes a deep breath as a breeze blows wisps of hair across her face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1160
She raises her club and beats the laundry stoically.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1161
Now at the SOMEONE house, Yang Gong helps SOMEONE downstairs to a foyer where the woman from SOMEONE's village waits.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1164
SOMEONE reluctantly reaches into the folds of her clothing.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1165
My sister asked me to return this to you.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1166
She holds the folded fan out to the noblewoman.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1167
SOMEONE takes it and studies it with a knitted brow.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1168
SOMEONE gives a troubled frown as she peers at it over her lady's shoulder.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1169
SOMEONE turns the fan in her hands, her chest heaving.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1171
She looks up at SOMEONE with glistening eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1172
Avoiding her imperious gaze,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1173
the messenger apologetically bows her head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1175
Her features set in a dazed expression, SOMEONE turns away.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1176
SOMEONE reaches for her, but the noblewoman wrenches her arm out of her grasp and climbs the stairs alone.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1177
Now in a dark space,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1178
she opens the fan in a shaft of gentle light and reads.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1182
Three sworn sisters in Jintian have promised to love me as I am.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1183
You need not worry about me anymore.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1184
Now, steam rises from bowls of food on a table.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1185
SOMEONE steps into view, her head jutting forward and her arms at her sides.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1186
She pauses by a window and gazed outward.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1188
Clutching the fan in one hand, she raises it to her waist and rests it on her other palm.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1189
She stares off with a dazed, stricken expression.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1190
Silhouetted against a window, she swallows hard,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1191
then slowly doubles over and grasps a chair at the head of the table.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1192
She sinks down, turning her back to us as she rests her head against her hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1193
The fan drops from her grasp.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1195
Now in her apartment, SOMEONE continues reading the manuscript.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1196
She sets one page aside and peruses the next with glistening eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1197
A tear rolls along the side of her nose and another streams down her cheek.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1199
several fans covered in writing sit on an open bundle of plain white cloth.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1200
SOMEONE sits slouched at the table.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1201
while SOMEONE stands in attendance nearby.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1202
The noblewoman waves feebly at the fans.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1206
She bundles up the fans and carries them away.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1207
SOMEONE sits motionless as gentle firelight glows on her listless face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1209
In a gathering room, several women sit around a table with a bright red table cloth.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1210
Words appear. Six months later.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1212
The gathered women sew and enjoy refreshments as they sing.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1213
One nods and smiles to SOMEONE, who sits apart.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1214
The noblewoman politely returns the gesture and makes an effort to sing along.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1215
SOMEONE arrives.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1217
She grimly steps away.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1218
SOMEONE lifts her gaze, her eyes shining, as SOMEONE comes in with her Jintian sisters.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1222
An older woman speaks.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1223
Thank you for traveling all this way to celebrate our daughter's wedding.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1224
SOMEONE humbly bows her head.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1225
The mother of Cousin Yan gestures to a row of chairs and the newcomers sit.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1226
SOMEONE watches her estranged laotong with shining eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1227
SOMEONE keeps her gaze fixed slightly downward,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1228
avoiding everyone else's stare.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1229
SOMEONE resumes the song.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1230
SOMEONE's gaze drifts cautiously in SOMEONE's direction.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1231
Her estranged laotong stares at the floor, her jaw set tight.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1232
A servant arrives with a tray of refreshments and serves the newcomers.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1233
SOMEONE's shoulders heave slowly beneath her ornate gown.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1235
Moving hesitantly, she ventures a look at SOMEONE through her glistening eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1236
Her old friend looks down,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1237
Responding to her gregarious Jintian sisters with faint smiles and nods.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1238
SOMEONE averts her wounded gaze and stands.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1239
The bride, her mother, and a few other guests take notice as she shuffles past the table.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1240
SOMEONE pauses, turning her face slightly in SOMEONE's direction.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1241
She continues onward, leaving the party.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1242
Now, SOMEONE wanders into the 19th century gathering room.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1243
She stops and turns.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1245
Across the room, SOMEONE sits alone.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1246
She raises her head slowly and looks at SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1247
The contemporary woman regards her sadly.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1249
From across the room, the two women of different eras hold each other's gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1250
Now, traffic proceeds down a narrow city street.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1251
At the gallery, SOMEONE's aunt walks SOMEONE through the exhibit on Chinese foot binding.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1252
Large square black and white photographs of bare mutilated feet cover one wall.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1253
Now, a plain brown high-rise stands crowded among similar buildings beneath an overcast sky.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1255
an old woman in a bath robe leads SOMEONE up a dank stairway.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1257
They proceed down a hallway with chipping paint.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1259
They pass rows of frosted glass windows, then arrive at an apartment with shoddily whitewashed brick walls.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1261
The landlady leaves.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1262
SOMEONE steps through the doorway into the apartment and pauses to take in her surroundings with a grave expression.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1263
Heading further in, she passes a mirror dotted with stickers and photographs.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1264
Exposed wiring drapes across the crumbling brick walls.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1265
SOMEONE passes a half-finished painting on an easel,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1266
then a low unmade bed tucked in a corner.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1267
Later, she sits at a desk littered with several stacks of books, manuscripts, and documents.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1268
SOMEONE flips through the pages of a small spiral bound notebook.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1270
We drift closer to her and find her lips slightly pursed as she reads.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1272
In the notebook, a pen and ink sketch depicts a delicate tree amidst a desolate landscape.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1274
On the opposite page, an illustration shows light from an oncoming train shining brightly from a round tunnel.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1275
SOMEONE turns to the next page
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1276
and finds it filled with writing.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1277
Near the back cover, she discovers a folded letter addressed to her.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1278
We see SOMEONE sitting in a red tinted bathtub. she sinks down slowly under the water.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1279
Back at the desk, Shutting the notebook,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1282
she notices a photograph tucked beneath the scattered pages of a manuscript draft. She pulls it out.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1286
It features her and SOMEONE as teenagers clad in their matching red track suits.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1288
SOMEONE looks up at him and nods, her chest heaving beneath her black wool coat.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1289
SOMEONE stares at her, then averts his stricken gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1290
SOMEONE looks up at him, her eyes wide and shining.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1291
SOMEONE gives a stoic nod, then turns away,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1292
his handsome features set in a haggard frown.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1293
He gently leads her onward.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1294
Now sitting on her bed at home, SOMEONE removes the gray men's suit jacket from the plastic bag.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1295
The finely-tailored garment unfolds gracefully as she holds it up.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1296
Standing, she puts it on.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1297
She wraps it tightly around her slender torso and hugs it close over her chest.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1298
Her head droops forward and her eyes close as she strolls over to a sunny window.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1299
She sways dreamily on her feet, then lifts her head and slips her hands into the pockets with a heavy sigh.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1300
Looking down, she pulls out a small brass key with a circular toggle
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1301
and a small, round plastic coil.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1302
SOMEONE frowns quizzically as she turns it in her fingertips.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1303
Now, a pair of wood-framed glass doors bear stenciled Chinese characters.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1304
Reversed letters beneath read "Yangtze Bath".
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1305
SOMEONE steps through the doors.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1307
She crosses a waiting area and approaches a front desk.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1309
His locker number is 173.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1311
The burly bathhouse attendant stops eating and listens with a lifted brow.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1312
We're not open yet. They're still cleaning.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1313
Leading her into a room, he turns to a worker.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1316
The worker stops spreading towels over loungers and leaves.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1319
SOMEONE gives a tiny bow and the man returns the gesture.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1320
She waits as he heads off.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1322
She makes her way to a bank of wooden lockers and skims her gaze over their numbers.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1324
she slides the key into its lock and pulls open the door.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1326
she finds a modest shrine in memory of SOMEONE's father.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1327
A rectangular wooden plaque stands upright
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1328
bearing the man's photo and a panel of Chinese writing.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1329
A few blue silk roses and pieces of citrus surround it.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1330
SOMEONE lifts a folded fan of the locker's shelf.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1332
She opens it, spreading its creased paper panels and finds writing on each one.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1334
Flipping it over, she sees writing on only half of the back panels.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1337
She blinks her sad eyes and closes the fan.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1338
Her gaze falls on something else in the locker and she tilts her head for a better look.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1339
On the bottom shelf, she finds a stack of typed pages.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1340
Taking them out, she reads the cover page "SnowFlower And The Secret Fan. "
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1342
SOMEONE flips to the next page and reads,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1343
her intent eyes fixed on her friend's completed manuscript.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1344
The end of this story is about things of the heart that SOMEONE never change.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1346
Within the story, a girl stands in the doorway of SOMEONE's home.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1347
As SOMEONE leads SOMEONE over, the girl enters and drops to her knees.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1350
My mother is very sick.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1351
She calls for you in her sleep.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1352
SOMEONE's eyes fill with tears.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1353
Gazing up at her, SOMEONE's daughter grimaces woefully.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1354
A tear slides down her cheek.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1355
SOMEONE kneels down to the girl.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1356
But she has other sisters.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1357
She has no other sisters. She misled you.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1358
She never had another laotong.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1359
For ten years, she was only their teacher.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1360
She has only one sister of the heart.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1361
The girl's face crumbles in sobs as she grabs SOMEONE's hands.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1363
SOMEONE averts her gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1365
SOMEONE gazes off sadly.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1367
Now, in a modest bedroom, SOMEONE lies on a sleeping platform with her hands folded on her chest.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1368
Three women at her bedside leave.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1369
As SOMEONE enters, SOMEONE's eyes remain closed.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1370
SOMEONE hobbles to the raised bed,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1371
her gaze fixed on her estranged laotong.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1372
She pauses by SOMEONE's feet,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1373
then inches closer.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1374
She lowers herself to the edge of the platform and leans over SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1376
Brow creased, SOMEONE stares down at her weakened sister.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1378
SOMEONE blinks, then looks at SOMEONE through half closed eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1380
SOMEONE clutches her dying sister's hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1381
Tears spill from her eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1382
She gently squeezes SOMEONE's fingers as she gazes at the ailing woman.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1383
Now, SOMEONE lies down beside SOMEONE on the bed.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1384
She stretches her arm over her friend and holds her gently.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1386
SOMEONE and SOMEONE's daughter stand just outside the front door.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1390
SOMEONE finds a closed fan in the basket.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1393
SOMEONE opens it, revealing the columns of hand-painted characters on its panels.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1394
She flips it over and gazes at the half-filled span of back side panels.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1395
SOMEONE's bearded husband sits nearby,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1396
watching his wife's laotong with a gentle gaze.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1398
Later, in SOMEONE's bedroom, golden light shines through the windows,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1399
casting a warm glow on SOMEONE's face.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1400
She gazes at SOMEONE, who lies peacefully by with her eyes closed and her hands folded on her stomach.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1401
Now, SOMEONE leans over her sister,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1402
letting her face hover just inches from SOMEONE's.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1403
She extends her trembling fingers and rests them upon her laotong's cheek.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1405
Now, tears shine in SOMEONE's eyes as she stares off with a distant expression.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1406
When SOMEONE returned home after SOMEONE's funeral,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1407
she looked at the fan and could not allow things to end as they had,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1408
so she opened a new panel,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1409
dipped her brush, and wrote a final inscription.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1410
As a tear runs down SOMEONE's cheek,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1411
she calmly works a bamboo stylus on a panel of the open fan,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1412
leaving several characters in black ink.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1414
In the present, SOMEONE reads the manuscript page with doleful eyes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1415
Still clutching the folded fan,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1416
she lowers the sheet of paper and stares off.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1418
An aerial view focuses on gleaming traffic and crowded highway lanes.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1419
The world is always changing.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1420
Every day it's changing.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1421
Everything in life is changing.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1422
We have to look inside ourselves to find what stays the same.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1423
A view of a bustling sidewalk shows two girls walking arm in arm.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1428
In a park, elderly women sit together on a bench.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1431
Shanghai skyscrapers jut into the hazy sky.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1433
At home, facing a window, SOMEONE holds the fan and traces characters with her fingertip on the glass pane.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1439
SOMEONE gazes out into a balcony where she imagines SOMEONE and SOMEONE at a table doing embroidery together.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1441
Their 19th century attire contrasts with Shanghai's modern skyline behind them.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1442
The women smile as they stitch.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1443
SOMEONE glances at her laotong,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1444
then shifts her gaze to SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1445
She opens her mouth to speak.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1446
SOMEONE offers SOMEONE a smile instead.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1447
SOMEONE lifts her steady eyes to her modern day counterpart
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1448
and holds her gaze with a plain and tranquil expression.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1449
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand side by side with their faces turned to each other.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1450
SOMEONE gazes at her sister,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1451
whose eyes are closed.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1453
SOMEONE shifts her attention to the cityscape before them.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1454
SOMEONE turns and both women stare out at the glittering metropolis.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1455
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's hand.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1457
Now, in the hospital, SOMEONE lies beside a bandaged and bruised SOMEONE.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1458
SOMEONE's eyes pool with tears. SOMEONE's remain closed.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1464
And we SOMEONE be sisters for 10,000 years.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1465
Our view looks down on the two friend's faces.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1467
Closing her eyes, SOMEONE lifts SOMEONE's hand onto her stomach.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1468
She places the fan in the young woman's palm,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1469
then closes her fingers around it.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1470
She covers SOMEONE's hand with her own.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1471
As SOMEONE lies shoulder to shoulder with SOMEONE,
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1472
the injured woman's eyelids slowly lift.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1473
SOMEONE stares ahead.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1476
Her eyes still closed, squeezes her sister's hands.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1478
Her lips spread into a sleepy smile. Staring at the ceiling, SOMEONE gives a weary blink.
SNOW_FLOWER_FD_DVS1480
Brilliant light washes over their faces and blanches the screen to pure white.