SOMEONE opens up a glowing capsule.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS14
Faces appear on it like a nesting doll.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS15
His depiction wears Victorian suit.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS16
SOMEONE hikes across the Serengeti. Later, he hands a silver-dragon figurine to village boy.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS17
He presents the figurine to a young swami. The boy studies it curiously. Later, SOMEONE leaves
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS19
New York City, 2000.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS21
SOMEONE draws on his window a picture of a gorilla being attacked by three airplanes. A few rows behind him, a perky blond girl laughs with her friends. Nicolas Cage. A chubby
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS22
The drawing lines up with the Empire State Building outside. The blond girl offers a smile.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS23
SOMEONE gives a smitten grin. The girl looks back to her friends. SOMEONE turns to the chubby boy, who gives him a thumbs up. A title appears with a dragon forming an S. The Sorcerer's Apprentice. Now outside, the kids sit facing New York Harbor. SOMEONE Baruchel.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS24
Other school kids pass it along.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS25
girl receives it. It reads, "Check one. I would like to be SOMEONE's friend or girl
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS26
SOMEONE knits her brow and peers at him down the row of students. He smiles meekly. SOMEONE grins and marks the note, hiding her answer.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS28
He leaves the note on a concrete planter as the class heads off. SOMEONE starts toward it.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS29
The note sticks to the tire of a passing bicycle.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS30
he dashes after it.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS31
halts and plucks off the note.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS32
SOMEONE chases it, barreling around a corner
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS34
She tosses it aside. SOMEONE follows the note through a narrow alley and emerges on a street littered with hundreds of loose notes.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS37
SOMEONE rubs a dusty Arabian oil lamp, then picks it up. A tray tips over, dropping a decanter. The panicked boy jumps.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS38
but SOMEONE catches it.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS39
The stringy-haired sorcerer slowly faces the boy, studying him, then brushes past.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS40
SOMEONE's jaw drops.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS41
Struggling to peek over his shoulder, he turns in circles.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS42
He treads toward SOMEONE and eyes him uncertainly, then drops his gaze to a small black box. The sorcerer opens the lid, revealing the silver-dragon figurine. He gently picks it up and sets it in the palm of his hand.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS43
SOMEONE turns away and pads toward the doors. They swing shut by themselves.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS44
He returns to SOMEONE and hesitantly picks up the dragon. The sorcerer watches closely. As SOMEONE holds the tiny dragon in his palm, it comes to life, sleepily shakes its head, and flaps its metal wings.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS45
It crawls to the back,
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS46
A green gemstone studs its back.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS47
Now, SOMEONE hurries downstairs into a basement. He kneels in front of the brick supporting the stairs and waves his hands. A red veneer crumbles away, revealing ancient darker bricks beneath.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS48
SOMEONE studies his dragon ring, turning it to catch the light. With each movement, boxes on a high shelf quake. SOMEONE jerks his hand to one side and the boxes tumble off the shelf. As he makes a light knocking motion, a wall buckles.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS49
He does it harder and the wall shatters. The doll falls to the floor.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS51
SOMEONE opens a door in the bricks and slides out SOMEONE's ancient spell book. Upstairs, SOMEONE picks up the nesting doll and studies the painting of SOMEONE's unhappy face. The SOMEONE magically unseals.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS52
The boy drops it and the two halves of the outermost nesting doll open. A roach crawls out, then another. Hundreds of roaches pour out of the doll and scuttle into a heap.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS53
The roaches, now numbering in the thousands, swarm into a growing tower.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS54
It takes on a man head and top hat. He takes a breath and becomes real.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS55
The last roaches melt into his skin and scurry into his mouth.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS56
A blue jewel topping his cane.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS57
SOMEONE pins him to the ceiling.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS58
SOMEONE points to it. SOMEONE grabs his cane and blasts him backwards.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS59
SOMEONE plummets.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS60
SOMEONE hides.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS61
The innermost doll now shows a man with a high forehead and long fingernail
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS62
He has a bulky rings on their right index.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS64
He snaps the horn off a unicorn's skull and defends
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS65
SOMEONE topples over. A jar falls off.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS66
He fires it at SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS68
SOMEONE side with his cane, He fireballs at SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS69
Behind SOMEONE falls toward the door, cradling the SOMEONE. SOMEONE notices him.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS70
he grabs SOMEONE's leg and reels into the urn,
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS71
The lid shuts.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS72
SOMEONE rushes outside and hurls the SOMEONE away.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS73
He follows his teacher into the store. They find everything back to normal.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS74
SOMEONE looks around and notices the SOMEONE Dynasty urn standing upright.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS75
teacher steers him back outside.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS76
Back in the shop, the lid sits tightly atop the urn. Beneath its tapered neck, warlike paintings adorn its bulbous body. Among the angry and fearful faces, a man with shaggy hair like SOMEONE's grips the shoulder of a goateed man holding a cane aloft. Cut to black. Words appear Ten Years Later, to the Day. An alarm clock reads, 7:00.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS77
A young man fumbles to turn it off, then finds a full-grown bulldog lying on his chest.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS78
turns off his wristwatch.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS79
He scratches the dog's ear. Later, his roommate tosses him a gift.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS80
He takes socks from a bureau.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS81
The dragon ring lies beneath.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS82
SOMEONE shows a wolf calendar.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS83
Now in a classroom, SOMEONE assembles his mushroom-like device.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS84
He collects pages off the floor, then moves among the lecture seats, where a paper sits at a young woman's feet.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS85
Agog, SOMEONE sweeps his gaze up her stockinged legs to the blond woman's lovely face.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS86
She looks away. With a nod, SOMEONE turns to head off, then turns back and furrows his brow. The woman's blue eyes briefly meet his gaze.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS87
She nods.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS88
She blinks confusedly.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS89
Now in a posh apartment, the SOMEONE Dynasty urn stands by a hall doorway. As a gray-haired man passes, the urn quivers. The man returns and stares at it. The urn's side depicts the fighting sorcerers. Meanwhile,
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS90
he catches up to her on the sidewalk.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS92
Lightning flashes, striking a metal tower on
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS93
SOMEONE draws their attention.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS94
SOMEONE gapes.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS96
SOMEONE and another guy stare blankly. SOMEONE nods, then uses a control pad.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS97
SOMEONE pumps his fist.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS98
He averts his bashful gaze.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS99
SOMEONE collects his jacket and umbrella, then glances at SOMEONE, who gives a shrug and a smile. Looking away, SOMEONE nods awkwardly.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS100
He turns on a radio.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS101
SOMEONE stands inside a protective chamber.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS102
City lights glimmer in the night. In the posh apartment, the gray-haired man glares at the trembling urn.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS103
The ash cloud hovers.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS104
A man appears with brows and goatee. Smoke puffs from his mouth.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS105
She falls off.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS106
He lifts the urn to a window.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS108
As the urn plummets, another stream of ash flies from it.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS110
SOMEONE steps onto a sidewalk
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS111
he glances at a crowd gathered around the broken urn
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS112
SOMEONE stops and stares at the Chrysler Building, its illuminated crown agleam in the night eagles mounted on a high.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS114
He places his open hand on its back.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS115
Meanwhile, SOMEONE enters his apartment, flips on a lamp, and sets down his belongings. As he opens the fridge and peeks inside, SOMEONE watches from the other room. Squinting, SOMEONE notices a report put up on his fridge. It reads, SOMEONE Stutler, Fourth Grade, B-, The Life of Napoleon Bonaparte.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS116
his hand and a knife flies into it.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS117
SOMEONE bolts for the closed door.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS118
He then stands and races outside. SOMEONE spots SOMEONE's wolf calendar.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS119
As SOMEONE races
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS120
he pauses and looks at his apartment. His jaw drops as
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS121
SOMEONE rushes up some stairs, then stops on a landing, and watches the wolves advance past the man entering the apartment building.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS123
subway station door, SOMEONE swipes his card.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS124
One wolf leans upright on the revolving door's bars. SOMEONE sprints away. Now, a wolf
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS125
open a door and leads the others onto a subway platform.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS126
SOMEONE enters behind them. SOMEONE hides on the sunken subway tracks.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS127
He looks across the track and sees a wolf.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS128
As the wolves leap for SOMEONE, Two puppies land on his chest.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS130
As SOMEONE shifts his eyes, a giant talon knocks him
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS131
SOMEONE looks down.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS132
SOMEONE rises
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS133
commands a newspaper to fly flat onto the train driver's
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS134
climbs onto the eagle
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS135
He quickly dives off the tracks. He stares after SOMEONE. Now at the Chrysler Building, pigeons flutter off the
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS136
He leans over the balcony railing.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS137
The full-bodied eagle heads back to its corner on
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS138
It transforms into the decorative
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS139
SOMEONE picks up a pigeon.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS140
He binds the pigeon's leg.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS141
SOMEONE releases the bird.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS142
He turns away.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS144
SOMEONE holds SOMEONE's gaze. The young man shifts his eyes, then nods.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS145
SOMEONE strides past SOMEONE, to the decorative eagle, and climbs onto it.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS146
As SOMEONE flutters
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS147
at an impound garage.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS148
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE's vintage Rolls.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS149
Now, SOMEONE drives the dusty Rolls.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS150
SOMEONE swerves.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS151
meter maid recoils from a burning ticket.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS152
Meanwhile, SOMEONE strolls from an alley to the former Arcana Cabana, its front window now aglow with neon signs.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS153
SOMEONE closes his eyes.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS154
He reviews the past.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS155
SOMEONE sees SOMEONE tossing the doll.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS156
SOMEONE's smoky vision shows an old Chinese woman finding the SOMEONE. Its outermost portrait still shows the man with long fingernails. In reality, headlight
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS157
the man  got shot through his windshield. SOMEONE shifts his eyes.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS159
Now, yellow-and-red confetti fills the air and round red lanterns hang above the street.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS160
a team of puppeteers operating.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS161
SOMEONE grimaces as SOMEONE heads into a building and up a flight of stairs.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS162
Two spectators stare curiously at SOMEONE and he nods at SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS163
Inside the building, SOMEONE cautiously heads toward a door marked with Chinese writing. He pauses and waves his hand over it. As he makes his way into a shop, a butterfly flits off a table. SOMEONE runs his hand over various items, then stops in front of a figurine covered in acupuncture needles. He waves his hand around it. The elderly woman from SOMEONE's replay of the past steps out from behind a curtain.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS164
Subtitles appear Your hair is beautiful.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS165
The long-finger nailed man appears.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS166
Hundreds of acupuncture needles rise.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS167
The bare-chested man rises.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS168
SOMEONE looks up at the window.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS169
SOMEONE bolts. SOMEONE runs his curled nails over a dragon-shaped buckle on his belt. It starts to move. Meanwhile, the dragon puppet in the parade.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS171
SOMEONE blows confetti over the street.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS172
invisibility for everyone, including
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS173
As SOMEONE races into a hair salon. SOMEONE narrowly escapes.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS174
Meanwhile, SOMEONE crosses the curio shop. As SOMEONE hides around a corner, the strands of a beaded curtain take the SOMEONE by the neck and arms.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS176
SOMEONE leaps out the window. Meanwhile, the dragon chases SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS177
SOMEONE points his ring at the sorcerer. The dragon draws closer.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS179
SOMEONE shows a smidge with his fingers.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS180
The dragon climbs up the building toward SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS181
He closes his eyes. Light glows from SOMEONE's ring.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS182
He finds himself in the puppet's
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS183
his hands victoriously.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS184
SOMEONE stares down at the SOMEONE. The next doll shows a Puritan girl. SOMEONE approaches.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS185
SOMEONE watches from the curio shop window and sees SOMEONE wearing SOMEONE's ring.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS186
Two NYPD cruisers arrive on the scene.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS188
As two cops approach, SOMEONE and SOMEONE are suddenly dressed as policemen.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS189
SOMEONE lifts his brow. One of the cops stares at SOMEONE, who tips his hat.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS190
The officers head past the imposters.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS191
Now, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in his Phantom.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS192
SOMEONE eyes the ring on his finger. SOMEONE watches him steadily.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS193
The sorcerer gives a pleased smile.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS194
SOMEONE's car pulls
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS197
SOMEONE sets the SOMEONE down and it becomes invisible.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS198
He presents a matchbox-sized book.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS199
He unfolds it repeatedly.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS200
It doubles in size each time.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS201
He gives the now-enormous tome to SOMEONE, who
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS202
SOMEONE opens the big book.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS203
It depicts SOMEONE in a cowardly scream.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS205
SOMEONE obeys. Standing in the center of the turnaround-circular platform, SOMEONE raises his hands. The lights dim.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS206
The sorcerer flourishes his hands.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS207
SOMEONE wills the flames down to the level of his wrist,
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS208
then guides them with his hands.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS209
Fiery light within the larger circle. SOMEONE stands
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS210
Picking his way over the now ankle-high green flames, he joins SOMEONE at the circle's center.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS211
He tosses some to SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS212
He notices SOMEONE wearing an identical pair.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS213
Now, a neon sign over a burger stand reads, "The Corner. " A figure with a walking stick approaches as two customers leave with their order. Inside, the fry cook pauses. On the griddle, pentagrams
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS214
sear themselves into the tops of two burgers. The cook looks over his shoulder at the customer window. Later, he stands with SOMEONE
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS215
in SOMEONE's lab
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS216
SOMEONE wears a catcher's mask and pad
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS218
it falls to the ground.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS220
The recoil from another knocks him over.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS221
A bulb bounces off the padding over SOMEONE's
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS222
plasma ball returns and hits him again. Now, we peer up at a gold-trimmed high rise. Inside, SOMEONE slips into a luxurious penthouse.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS223
A poster featuring a man with spiky bleached hair gives the name, "Drake Stone. "
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS224
A trophy reads, "Magician of the Year 2009. " In a parlor, a woman paints his nails black.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS225
Other female attendants turn.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS226
A bald man leaves with him.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS227
Doffing his hat, SOMEONE steps forward.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS228
Now, SOMEONE shoots a fire
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS229
a flame in his upturned palm.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS230
He blows it like a kiss
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS231
SOMEONE nods and smiles.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS232
SOMEONE, knocking him onto his back.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS233
Now on an outdoor bench, SOMEONE takes several sandwiches from a paper bag.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS234
SOMEONE turns and gawks as SOMEONE leaves a nearby building.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS235
The young man shifts his rueful gaze. He eyes SOMEONE with a furrowed brow, then springs up and hurries after her.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS236
SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter a subway station.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS237
SOMEONE takes a deep breath and chases the mugger.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS238
revolving gate. SOMEONE locks it
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS239
Now SOMEONE rejoins SOMEONE, passing two cops.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS240
He holds up his fists. A train arrives.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS241
He boards it.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS242
SOMEONE gapes.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS243
SOMEONE gazes wistfully after the departing train. As we revolve around him, we discover SOMEONE glowering behind his shoulder.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS244
Daytime. At the Wall Street Bull sculpture, SOMEONE thoughtfully takes in his surrounding
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS245
He finds SOMEONE signing autographs for fans
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS246
leaves them.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS247
SOMEONE grimly touches the bull statue.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS248
An NYU sticker decorates it. Now, SOMEONE levitates in a chair.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS249
He leaves. Now, his Rolls
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS250
the stone gargoyle. From the driver's seat, SOMEONE peers at his
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS251
old storefront. Later, he descends the spiral stairway into the basement, which is now stocked with boxes and printing supplies. Crouching at the wall beneath the stairs, he moves a poster board aside.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS252
He arcs his hands before the bricks, exposing a hatch. Opening it, he pulls a canvas bag from compartment, reaches inside, and pulls out a roll of muslin. He gingerly unrolls it to reveal an arcane depiction of a spell being cast.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS253
Now, SOMEONE puts the scroll back and takes out a red-velvet bundle. He unfolds it to reveal a delicate drop-pendant necklace. Back at the lab, SOMEONE sets up a network of cables around a metal cage in the SOMEONE Circle.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS254
SOMEONE enters the cage.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS255
SOMEONE joins him.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS256
At the turn of a dial, the lights fade out. SOMEONE types a command on a computer.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS257
Plasma zaps the cage from all directions. SOMEONE ducks, then stares.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS259
SOMEONE regards her tenderly, then types in a new command.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS260
SOMEONE's jaw drops.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS261
Her eyes widen and she gawks at SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS263
Later, a banner outside a building reads, "New York University Athletics. " SOMEONE and SOMEONE stroll up.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS265
He walks her to a yoga class.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS267
Later in a men's room, SOMEONE approaches him.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS268
He gives the floor a scuffing kick
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS269
grabbing SOMEONE by the collar
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS270
He walks away, but SOMEONE stays pinned
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS271
SOMEONE flexes his fingers, then propels his hands forward.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS272
SOMEONE obeys his arriving master.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS273
SOMEONE corners him.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS274
SOMEONE opens his mouth to speak.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS275
SOMEONE presses the knob of his walking stick to his lips.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS276
He backs off a step and lowers the magical cane. SOMEONE glares darkly at the evil magician.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS277
The young man shakes his head and screws his mouth up.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS278
fluid impresses SOMEONE
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS279
SOMEONE propels SOMEONE into a stall.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS280
pause on their way downstairs.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS281
Meanwhile, trapped in the mirror, SOMEONE sees a student walk by.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS282
He knocks on the surface causing it to ripple.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS283
The student nods uneasily, flashes a meek smile, and faints.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS284
Now, we view illustrations in the Incantus.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS285
He ignites the SOMEONE Circle.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS286
SOMEONE regards SOMEONE's ring on his finger. Now at an NYU
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS287
SOMEONE arrogantly taps a clerk's computer with his cane.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS288
The clerk grows mesmerized by the glowing gemstone on his cane.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS289
As SOMEONE irritably rolls his eyes, SOMEONE's grin fades. The clerk locates SOMEONE's record.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS290
In the lab, SOMEONE sits down.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS291
SOMEONE sees his dog chewing on some cables.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS292
SOMEONE beckons his apprentice.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS293
They study the retrieved scroll.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS294
They both take a look at the bulldog gnawing at one of the Tesla coils.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS295
A wall clock reads, 7:45.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS296
cleaning supplies from a storage cage, a push broom
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS297
later, he mops up the spilled soda.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS298
now reads, 7:50.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS299
He eyes takeout containers and a pizza box. Tank pees on the floor.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS300
His gaze lands on the Incantus. Later, the book lies open under his finger. As a circle of low red flames burns around him, SOMEONE scoops his ring-bearing hand upward, directing the
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS301
at a distant mop. The mop stands, then bobs up and down. SOMEONE waves his hand like a conductor.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS302
broom which nudges a push broom awake. Both join the mop and the mop stands alertly on three
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS304
It pirouettes, disturbing Tank from
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS306
A stack of dirty plates levitates over to the sink
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS308
Two unsupervised mops come alive at the storage cage.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS309
SOMEONE finishes taking a shower and towels dry.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS310
Wearing a plain-white shirt, he runs an electric toothbrush down his tongue.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS311
Now zipping up a hooded sweatshirt and wearing SOMEONE's ring, he returns
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS312
Dozens of mops slosh his Tesla equipment.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS313
A hovering spray bottle sprays SOMEONE's face.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS316
Four electrical wall outlets sink the rising water
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS317
His shadow on the wall shows him swinging, but the mop head strings dodge each blow.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS318
pushes on his butt. As SOMEONE eyes him curiously, he hangs his head.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS319
As he covers his face, both sneaky mops imitate him. Downstairs
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS320
spreading his arms wide from the balcony. All of the enchant
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS322
SOMEONE angrily looks away, his jaw clenching in a defiant expression. SOMEONE reflects.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS323
SOMEONE removes his ring.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS324
He thrusts a hand in the direction of an empty chair. Nothing happens.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS325
He fetches his sneakers.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS326
He changes out of his pointy footwear. Now in the city.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS327
SOMEONE follows a sidewalk by himself. Later, he passes a park.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS328
Farther along, he approaches a window to a coffee house marked, "Communication Cafe. " He spies SOMEONE inside, conversing cheerfully with a group of girlfriends.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS329
SOMEONE turns away sadly and leaves. SOMEONE spots him in a mirror.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS330
She turns to find him walking away, then excuses herself from her friends.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS331
Now, the Chrysler Building's art deco apex gleams in the night. On the lofty observation ledge, a service light glows amber in contrast to a row of stark floodlights. SOMEONE steps out to the handrail, smirks sadly, and removes SOMEONE's ring. He joggles it in his cupped hand as he faces the breathtaking cityscape. SOMEONE arrives behind him. As SOMEONE winds up to throw the ring, she interjects.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS332
He pockets it.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS333
She lets him lead her to the railing.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS334
Back at the dripping-wet lab, SOMEONE dries off the Incantus.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS335
SOMEONE arrives.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS336
SOMEONE notices his black fingernails.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS337
He moves to the opponent beats him to the punch. As SOMEONE slams into the circular-coil array, copper bands fasten around
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS338
binding him. SOMEONE morphs into SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS339
SOMEONE descends a staircase.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS340
He flashes SOMEONE a snide smirk, then give
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS341
SOMEONE appear and SOMEONE casts them across the lab to search for the SOMEONE
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS342
around his right wrist, turning them
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS343
SOMEONE guides his magical smoke across an equipment table. The gray gases reveal the contours of the SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS344
As SOMEONE reaches for it, SOMEONE magically snatches it away.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS345
Now, SOMEONE magically propels four throwing knives at SOMEONE. The knives stop inches his face.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS346
SOMEONE stands on the catwalk, using SOMEONE's ring.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS350
On SUV, SOMEONE glances back over his shoulder
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS351
He shakes his ring.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS352
Ferrari picks up speeds.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS353
They pass Do Not Enter signs.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS354
Struggling to see through the fog,
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS356
the smoke clears a bit as the vehicles emerge from the tunnel and speed down the city streets.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS358
plummets and they off.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS360
He climbs out of the Pinto.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS361
Finding the garbage truck empty, SOMEONE approaches a crowd of onlookers.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS362
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder as he strides casually down the sidewalk.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS363
SOMEONE touches a plain-faced woman, giving her SOMEONE's likeness. SOMEONE halts and their eyes meet.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS364
As he stops her, she instantly changes back to the middle-aged New Yorker.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS365
As she walks away, SOMEONE approaches with Tank.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS366
Later, SOMEONE shows SOMEONE more illustrations in the Incantus.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS368
In the Middle Ages, SOMEONE lowers her cloak's hood.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS369
She admires a necklace in a market.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS370
SOMEONE gawks, taking in SOMEONE's words.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS371
He shows SOMEONE the jewel-drop-pendant necklace from the market.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS372
SOMEONE steps away, leaving the Incantus open on SOMEONE's lap.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS373
The apprentice shakes his head.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS374
In SOMEONE's penthouse, the two SOMEONE eye the SOMEONE on a glass desk.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS375
It shows the Puritan girl.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS376
He touches his walking stick to his neck.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS377
He slides SOMEONE's ring onto his cane and touches the jewel knob to the SOMEONE. A searing line slices the doll around the middle and Abigail's portrait burns. Now, SOMEONE deejays at the radio station.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS378
visitor glowers at her through a window. As SOMEONE swivels in her chair, the girl suddenly appears beside her in Puritan attire.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS379
Her eyes glow red and she smirks.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS380
SOMEONE gives him an earnest look.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS381
He holds out his right fist, which bears SOMEONE's ring.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS382
They bump knuckles.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS383
Meanwhile, he stalks toward her.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS384
As they move out of view, light flashes.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS385
Abigail is dead. He grabs her pentagram necklace.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS386
Now, one of the double doors.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS388
SOMEONE past a painting of SOMEONE on a throne, attended by a panther and a gorgeous worshipful woman.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS389
They split up. SOMEONE peers through a doorway. We hover behind SOMEONE's glass desk as we watch him step into the opulent private office. He sees a map spread out on the desk, with a SOMEONE Circle drawn around one section labeled, Forbidden Domain.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS390
As he crosses a black Persian carpet.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS391
It grows thick and viscous.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS392
Meanwhile, SOMEONE eyes two brass sculptures flanking a fireplace.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS393
Looking around, he notices the SOMEONE sitting on a small pedestal in front of the hearth. With a shrug, he crouches to it and reaches out, then hesitates.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS394
He wags his finger shrewdly, then rubs his face. He abruptly grabs the SOMEONE and looks around warily.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS395
He sees a faded rendering of a female on its black surface.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS396
He turns it around to find the likeness of SOMEONE's beloved.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS398
SOMEONE gulps back
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS399
a winch reels in the chain, pulling him free. Back in the foyer, SOMEONE holds out SOMEONE's ring and SOMEONE magically snatches it.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS400
He offers up the SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS401
SOMEONE draws it to himself.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS402
He releases SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS404
SOMEONE arrives and looks around.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS405
He takes in SOMEONE's sorry expression, then shuts his eyes.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS406
SOMEONE walks out to the terrace. His apprentice follows.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS407
He hops up on the ledge.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS408
The sorcerer turns, facing SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS409
He shuts his eyes, spreads his arms wide, and falls backward.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS410
confronts SOMEONE inside SOMEONE's penthouse.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS411
Now, SOMEONE makes out with a young woman.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS412
As his girlfriend steps out, he answers his cell.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS413
Now in the lab, SOMEONE brings a box.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS414
He hands SOMEONE a wrapped cloth.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS415
SOMEONE reads an attached note.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS416
He glances at SOMEONE, then holds up the drop-pendant necklace and anxiously knits his brow.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS417
Meanwhile, in Battery Park, SOMEONE mounts the steps to a tiered platform-like fountain. The spouting water ceases and he places the SOMEONE on the highest tier.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS418
He steps back, the gem on his cane glowing.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS419
The nesting doll wavers.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS421
She opens her exotic eyes to reveal glowing pupils.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS422
SOMEONE picks up the empty SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS423
She closes her dark-lashed eyes and raises both arms.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS424
SOMEONE creeps
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS425
of energy streak off a dish atop a high rise as the car comes to a stop below portal.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS431
On a rooftop.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS432
SOMEONE stares up at a tall antenna. A dish hangs near the top. Back at the park.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS433
It chases the fleeing sorcerer.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS434
it snorts, fogging the glass.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS435
into the van and flings it aside.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS436
SOMEONE climbs toward the top of its framework and feebly kicks at the dish. Back at the park,
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS437
gram containing arcane rune
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS438
In an overgrown cemetery, two of the smoke trails meet and electrocutes the evil magician.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS441
Now, clouds of black darken the sky above.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS442
Smoke shoots into an ancient ossuary piled with human
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS443
SOMEONE's form presides over the flaming fountain.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS446
SOMEONE rushes forward and cradles her fallen form.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS447
As he tenderly touches SOMEONE's forehead, his ring glows green. He then moves his fingers to his own forehead. As he goes back and forth between the two, streaks of light fly out of SOMEONE's face and into his own. He kisses her, sucking a fine cloud of dust into his nose and SOMEONE's face, briefly appears in the particle stream.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS449
She become alive as the last of it gets absorbed.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS450
SOMEONE's eyelids flutter open. She gazes up at her wincing lover.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS451
He staggers to his feet and tosses the SOMEONE to SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS452
His eyes transform.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS453
His face seizes and he crumples to his knees. As his head tips back, the
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS454
SOMEONE collapses onto the ground.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS455
materializes from the smoky cloud.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS456
knocks him off his feet and sends him tumbling. SOMEONE stares at him worriedly, then faces
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS457
As he fires them, the shoot past SOMEONE and hit a power shed.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS458
The bolts pass through
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS459
She melds herself back together.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS460
SOMEONE cowers as their burst impacts push him backward.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS462
One cable reaches a lamppost.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS463
cable twines up a lamp.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS464
It arcs off the lamppost like Tesla coils and strikes SOMEONE. An aerial view shows plasma flick.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS465
SOMEONE shoots lightning from his hands.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS467
it vanishes in a puff. SOMEONE slumps weakly as the wind blows away the last bits of dust.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS468
He finds SOMEONE hunched over the fallen sorcerer. She soberly looks up at the apprentice, her raven-black hair whipping in the wind. SOMEONE shakes his head.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS469
He tearfully clenches his jaw.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS470
Taking a seat on one of the steps to the fountain, he thoughtfully raises his hands, then lets them flop back down. SOMEONE leans close to SOMEONE, her face hovering inches from his, and tenderly strokes his cheek. Our view rises about the grieving Merlinians. SOMEONE resolutely tightens his lips.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS471
He strides forward.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS472
As he throws up his hands, a ring of fire suddenly appears around SOMEONE.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS473
SOMEONE smiles.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS476
He defeatedly hangs his head. One of his hands clenches into a fist, while the other remains on SOMEONE's chest. The ring of fire flickers feebly around them. SOMEONE looks on in anguish as SOMEONE shakes his head.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS477
She clutches her hands to her mouth.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS478
SOMEONE wraps the necklace around SOMEONE's hand and squeezes his fist.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS479
SOMEONE hurries into the circle and helps her lover to his feet. SOMEONE steps away as they embrace and share a tender kiss. SOMEONE cups the back of SOMEONE's head in her hand. As he raises the necklace, she sweeps her hair out of the way, allowing him to fasten it around her neck. SOMEONE ambles to the park gate and finds SOMEONE's hat lying on the sidewalk. He picks it up.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS480
SOMEONE sprints around a corner and seizes him in a hug.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS481
They lock lips in a breathless kiss. SOMEONE pulls away with a smile.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS482
SOMEONE kisses her again.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS483
The steel eagle lands on the ground.
SORCERERS_APPRENTICE_DVS484
eagle soars among the tops of skyscrapers, with SOMEONE and SOMEONE riding on its back.