A man with long blonde hair and sideburns steps out and cups his hands over his mouth as if to check his breath.
SUPER_8_DVS27
The man walks to a house's, his front door, glances over his shoulder at SOMEONE, then runs his fingers through his hair.
SUPER_8_DVS28
SOMEONE drops his gaze as the man walks inside.
SUPER_8_DVS29
The front door flies open as dark-haired SOMEONE leads the struggling SOMEONE out of the house in handcuffs, and shoves him into the back of a squad car.
SUPER_8_DVS30
SOMEONE watches his father speed off in a police car with its lights flashing.
SUPER_8_DVS31
SOMEONE gazes down at the necklace in his hand, and closes the locket.
SUPER_8_DVS32
Four months later.
SUPER_8_DVS33
On a sunny day, children stream out of Lillian Middle School toward waiting cars and businesses.
SUPER_8_DVS34
On a large sign, Have a Great SOMEONE. Wearing a backpack, SOMEONE walks up to a burly boy with short brown hair.
SUPER_8_DVS35
SOMEONE scans a script.
SUPER_8_DVS36
Open-mouthed, SOMEONE pauses then walks on.
SUPER_8_DVS38
In a film, a boy wearing glasses and a trench coat grapples with a blond boy with blank bulbous eyes. The first boy takes out a pistol, but the blond boy knocks it away.
SUPER_8_DVS39
He turns and slams the blond boy against several nails protruding from a wall.
SUPER_8_DVS40
Blood pours from the blond boy's mouth.
SUPER_8_DVS41
Sitting in a bedroom, SOMEONE turns to the burly boy.
SUPER_8_DVS44
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a magazine.
SUPER_8_DVS45
Mr. SOMEONE glances at his blonde wife as SOMEONE leaves.
SUPER_8_DVS46
Outside, dusk falls as SOMEONE pedals his bicycle across a neighborhood street
SUPER_8_DVS47
SOMEONE pedals back to his own house.
SUPER_8_DVS48
The police cruiser sits parked in the driveway.
SUPER_8_DVS49
SOMEONE walks into the kitchen and glances at an empty table.
SUPER_8_DVS50
He moves into the living room then walks down a hallway.
SUPER_8_DVS51
SOMEONE peers around an open door, his father sits on the edge of a bathtub with his head in his hands.
SUPER_8_DVS52
SOMEONE stands and closes the bathroom door.
SUPER_8_DVS54
SOMEONE blinks then looks down.
SUPER_8_DVS55
Later at SOMEONE's Diner, SOMEONE passes a brochure to SOMEONE as they sit at the counter.
SUPER_8_DVS56
SOMEONE takes a swig from a beer bottle and glances at his son.
SUPER_8_DVS57
SOMEONE turns and studies the brochure.
SUPER_8_DVS58
SOMEONE stares at his father who looks away.
SUPER_8_DVS59
SOMEONE's eyes pass over the brochure for a baseball camp
SUPER_8_DVS60
and rest on the gold necklace in his left hand.
SUPER_8_DVS61
SOMEONE glances at the necklace then wipes his mouth with a paper napkin
SUPER_8_DVS62
and rests his chin on his clasped hands.
SUPER_8_DVS63
Later in SOMEONE's bedroom, a digital clock radio displays the time -
SUPER_8_DVS65
With a thin brush, SOMEONE paints a figurine of The Hunchback of Notre Dame.
SUPER_8_DVS66
SOMEONE uses a walkie-talkie.
SUPER_8_DVS67
Later, SOMEONE and his four friends sit on a grassy hill.
SUPER_8_DVS68
SOMEONE throws a thin object.
SUPER_8_DVS69
The boy stand as blonde SOMEONE pulls up in a yellow muscle car.
SUPER_8_DVS70
SOMEONE locks eyes with SOMEONE, then turns and shakes her head.
SUPER_8_DVS71
SOMEONE smiles.
SUPER_8_DVS72
Later, SOMEONE drives the boys up a rural road.
SUPER_8_DVS73
SOMEONE passes SOMEONE a stick of licorice, she eats it. Her reflection appears in a rear-view mirror as she stares at SOMEONE in the backseat.
SUPER_8_DVS74
The car pulls into the parking lot of a brightly lit but isolated train depot.
SUPER_8_DVS75
As SOMEONE steps out and hurries toward the depot, the boy wearing glasses holds up script pages.
SUPER_8_DVS76
A breeze blows a few pages away.
SUPER_8_DVS77
SOMEONE frames the location with his open hands.
SUPER_8_DVS78
Blonde SOMEONE unpacks a bag.
SUPER_8_DVS79
Opening a tackle box holding makeup, SOMEONE stands in front of SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS80
He rubs foundation on her cheek.
SUPER_8_DVS81
SOMEONE pulls back her long hair and ties it in a bun.
SUPER_8_DVS82
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE as he rubs a makeup sponge on her face.
SUPER_8_DVS83
She glances at the other boys sitting a short distance away.
SUPER_8_DVS84
SOMEONE stops and slowly lowers his hand.
SUPER_8_DVS85
Smiling, SOMEONE closes her eyes as SOMEONE applies more makeup.
SUPER_8_DVS86
SOMEONE lights a string of firecrackers.
SUPER_8_DVS88
SOMEONE and SOMEONE read scripts.
SUPER_8_DVS89
SOMEONE speaks without consulting her script.
SUPER_8_DVS90
The boys' mouths fall open as they watch nearby.
SUPER_8_DVS91
The tall bespectacled SOMEONE wearing a suit, tie, and brimmed hat stares trance-like at SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS92
SOMEONE swallows hard.
SUPER_8_DVS93
SOMEONE wipes his eye, then turns toward SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS94
SOMEONE runs to the edge of the platform and peers toward a train approaching in the distance.
SUPER_8_DVS96
The short SOMEONE stands behind the camera as the actors take their positions.
SUPER_8_DVS97
The train approaches the depot at full speed. Holding a boom microphone, SOMEONE smiles as the train zips past a few feet away.
SUPER_8_DVS98
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE, who smiles and nods.
SUPER_8_DVS99
SOMEONE glances beyond the train where a pickup truck bounces down a dirt road toward the tracks.
SUPER_8_DVS100
The truck turns onto the track and speeds toward the oncoming train.
SUPER_8_DVS101
The train slams into the truck and derails.
SUPER_8_DVS102
As the front train cars rise into the air and crash into poll, the boys drop the camera and scurry down the platform.
SUPER_8_DVS103
The speeding train bucks and twists as cars detach and crash.
SUPER_8_DVS104
As the rear of the train comes apart, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE turn back. SOMEONE stands rooted.
SUPER_8_DVS106
SOMEONE dashes aside as a cart wheeling train cart clips the depot.
SUPER_8_DVS107
SOMEONE and brown-haired Preston crawled under the platform as the other boys flee.
SUPER_8_DVS108
One train cart slams like a missile into the side of the depot, exploding the building to splinters.
SUPER_8_DVS109
SOMEONE rains from the sky as more cars flip through the air and crash in flames.
SUPER_8_DVS110
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE sprint through the burning wreckage as cars continue to pile up.
SUPER_8_DVS112
One train car slams into the back of a tanker car launching the cylindrical tank into the sky.
SUPER_8_DVS113
The tank crashes and explodes in front of the fleeing boys.
SUPER_8_DVS114
Running from the flames, SOMEONE separates from SOMEONE and SOMEONE and dashes into a SOMEONE field.
SUPER_8_DVS115
He stops as a piece of flaming wreckage marked Explosive lands in front of him.
SUPER_8_DVS116
SOMEONE turns to run but a massive explosion knocks him to the ground.
SUPER_8_DVS117
He lies faced down with his hands over his head.
SUPER_8_DVS120
SOMEONE looks up as a train car lying on its side a few yards away shudders and rocks.
SUPER_8_DVS121
Standing, SOMEONE grips the locket necklace in his shaking left hand.
SUPER_8_DVS122
The train car's thick door blows of its hinges and flies into the air, then lands and sticks into the ground behind SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS123
Wide-eyed, SOMEONE stares at the train car.
SUPER_8_DVS124
He looks around himself then heads back.
SUPER_8_DVS125
Lying on its side the camera continues to run.
SUPER_8_DVS126
Thick smoke blows across the crash site as SOMEONE returns to the destroyed depot. With its headlights still on SOMEONE's car stands undamaged a few feet away.
SUPER_8_DVS129
SOMEONE climbs over the twisted train tracks and finds Preston standing near SOMEONE on the other side.
SUPER_8_DVS130
Holding one hand over his heart Preston turns.
SUPER_8_DVS131
SOMEONE gives a thumbs up as he vomits.
SUPER_8_DVS132
As SOMEONE and SOMEONE rejoin the others SOMEONE glances down at a piece of wreckage covered in blood.
SUPER_8_DVS133
SOMEONE staggers toward the SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS134
As the dirt-smeared boy stare at the blood SOMEONE walks up behind him.
SUPER_8_DVS135
SOMEONE blinks then smiling wide turns and faces her.
SUPER_8_DVS136
SOMEONE reaches under the wreckage.
SUPER_8_DVS138
Grinning, SOMEONE holds up his destroyed makeup kit then tucks the locket necklace into his pocket.
SUPER_8_DVS139
Small white cubes litter the ground, SOMEONE picks up one of them.
SUPER_8_DVS140
SOMEONE sticks the cube into his jacket pocket then follows the others up onto one of the wrecked train cars.
SUPER_8_DVS141
Small fires burned throughout the vast crash site.
SUPER_8_DVS142
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder and points.
SUPER_8_DVS143
The twisted remains of the pickup truck lie a short distance away.
SUPER_8_DVS144
A bald man covered in blood sits slumped against the truck's steering wheel.
SUPER_8_DVS145
SOMEONE creeps toward the motionless man.
SUPER_8_DVS146
As SOMEONE touches the man his arm falls and a piece of paper drops from his hand.
SUPER_8_DVS147
SOMEONE jumps back then stoops and picks up the paper. The boys walk up as SOMEONE unfolds it.
SUPER_8_DVS149
They all leap back as Dr. SOMEONE reaches toward them.
SUPER_8_DVS150
Dr. SOMEONE takes out a revolver.
SUPER_8_DVS151
A group of people holding flashlights approaches in a distance.
SUPER_8_DVS152
The children flee as Dr. SOMEONE points the gun at them.
SUPER_8_DVS153
As SOMEONE runs to the car SOMEONE and SOMEONE retrieve the camera and other equipment. SOMEONE grabs his makeup kit.
SUPER_8_DVS154
The men with flashlights draw nearer.
SUPER_8_DVS155
Some carry assault rifles.
SUPER_8_DVS156
The boys pile into the car and SOMEONE backs out and speeds off.
SUPER_8_DVS157
Wearing an Air Force uniform with the name tag SOMEONE on the chest a commander in a beret watches SOMEONE's car drive away.
SUPER_8_DVS159
He stoops and picks up an empty Super 8 film box, then with his brow furrowed stares after the car.
SUPER_8_DVS160
They pass a SOMEONE gas station.
SUPER_8_DVS161
Later, SOMEONE drops the boys off on a street outside SOMEONE's house.
SUPER_8_DVS162
SOMEONE holds out one of the white cubes which is comprised of smaller cubes, SOMEONE takes it.
SUPER_8_DVS164
SOMEONE looks down and shakes her head
SUPER_8_DVS166
She drives away. SOMEONE stands on the sidewalk and watches her go.
SUPER_8_DVS167
Later inside, SOMEONE fondles the cube as he soaks in a bathtub and stares at the ceiling.
SUPER_8_DVS168
Outside, viewed from a hilltop, lights illuminating buildings and streets throughout town briefly flicker and flare.
SUPER_8_DVS169
SOMEONE awakes in bed.
SUPER_8_DVS170
Sitting on his desk the white cube vibrates.
SUPER_8_DVS171
Later, SOMEONE spills dog food as he overfills a bowl on the kitchen floor.
SUPER_8_DVS172
Later still, flipping through script pages
SUPER_8_DVS173
SOMEONE runs across the street to SOMEONE's house.
SUPER_8_DVS174
SOMEONE's sister wears a midriff top and skimpy shorts.
SUPER_8_DVS175
SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE who watches a television news program.
SUPER_8_DVS176
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride bicycles across a wide bridge.
SUPER_8_DVS177
A camera repair shop.
SUPER_8_DVS178
SOMEONE uses a telephone.
SUPER_8_DVS179
Holding a script SOMEONE stands on SOMEONE's front porch.
SUPER_8_DVS180
SOMEONE turns as Mr. SOMEONE pulls up on his yellow muscle car.
SUPER_8_DVS181
Mr. SOMEONE walks up to SOMEONE and shakes his head.
SUPER_8_DVS182
Mr. SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE then walks into the house,
SUPER_8_DVS183
SOMEONE lowers her head.
SUPER_8_DVS184
Her father steps out again.
SUPER_8_DVS185
SOMEONE turns and follows her father into the house.
SUPER_8_DVS186
SOMEONE reappears at the screen door.
SUPER_8_DVS187
SOMEONE steps forward.
SUPER_8_DVS188
On a grassy hill, SOMEONE fires a cap gun at SOMEONE who is dressed like a zombie.
SUPER_8_DVS189
SOMEONE stands beside SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS190
They gazed down at the train crash site far below.
SUPER_8_DVS191
SOMEONE carries off SOMEONE's tripod and camera.
SUPER_8_DVS192
SOMEONE aims the camera at the crash site and peers through the lens as a helicopter hovers overhead.
SUPER_8_DVS193
Later, SOMEONE and the boys eat in a diner.
SUPER_8_DVS194
SOMEONE blinks and stares at the table.
SUPER_8_DVS195
At the crash site, Air Force personnel wearing thick rubber gloves dust off white cubes and pack them into crates.
SUPER_8_DVS197
One airman monitors the cubes with a Geiger counter.
SUPER_8_DVS198
A forklift operator loads sealed crates onto a transport truck.
SUPER_8_DVS199
Nearby, SOMEONE follows Colonel SOMEONE out of a tent.
SUPER_8_DVS201
Later at the police station, SOMEONE stands beside the sheriff's desk.
SUPER_8_DVS202
SOMEONE looks down as the gray-haired sheriff walks off.
SUPER_8_DVS203
At night the sheriff drives his cruiser into the SOMEONE gas station.
SUPER_8_DVS204
Inside, the young clerk reads while listening through headphones to a portable cassette player.
SUPER_8_DVS205
The clerk stares at his book as sheriff throws a candy bar at his head,
SUPER_8_DVS207
SOMEONE flinches.
SUPER_8_DVS208
The sheriff pays for the candy bar and walks out.
SUPER_8_DVS209
At the pump, he leans against his car as he fills it with gas.
SUPER_8_DVS210
The sheriff lifts his head and gazes around himself then takes a few steps toward the road.
SUPER_8_DVS211
A pack of about a half a dozen dogs of mixed breeds races past the sheriff.
SUPER_8_DVS212
He places his hands on his hips as glances back into the darkness.
SUPER_8_DVS213
The sheriff leaps as the lights on his cruiser flash. He reaches into the car and turns off the power.
SUPER_8_DVS214
The sheriff turns toward a dumpster standing beside the gas station. Placing one hand on his gun he creeps toward it.
SUPER_8_DVS216
He draws his weapon as the dumpster slides across the parking lot. Inside, SOMEONE bobs his head as he listens through his headphones.
SUPER_8_DVS217
The sheriff's cruiser bounces violently.
SUPER_8_DVS218
The station lights flicker then come back on.
SUPER_8_DVS219
SOMEONE glances outside then slowly removes his headphones.
SUPER_8_DVS220
Lights inside the gas station continue to flicker on and off as SOMEONE steps outside and walks toward the sheriff's car.
SUPER_8_DVS221
The police cruiser's smoking hood is smashed in and one of the front tires lies nearly sideways.
SUPER_8_DVS222
SOMEONE walks around the car to the pumps.
SUPER_8_DVS223
Leaking oil and other fluids stain the pavement.
SUPER_8_DVS224
SOMEONE appears upside down as something stalks him.
SUPER_8_DVS225
SOMEONE lifts the gas pump handle off the ground then turns and freezes.
SUPER_8_DVS226
SOMEONE trips as lurches away, he gets to his feet and scrambles back inside the gas station.
SUPER_8_DVS227
In a spray of breaking glass, SOMEONE is yanked to the floor and violently pulled down the aisle.
SUPER_8_DVS228
Elsewhere, wearing dark-eyed zombie makeup SOMEONE examines herself in a mirror.
SUPER_8_DVS229
SOMEONE and SOMEONE slap hands then run off together.
SUPER_8_DVS231
The lights inside SOMEONE's house flicker.
SUPER_8_DVS232
SOMEONE smiles then makes her face go slack and tilts her head sideways.
SUPER_8_DVS233
SOMEONE stares at her as she creeps toward him.
SUPER_8_DVS234
Jerking, she holds up her hands and steps closer.
SUPER_8_DVS236
SOMEONE looks away as she pretends to bite his neck.
SUPER_8_DVS237
She steps back and they exchange smiles.
SUPER_8_DVS238
SOMEONE's smile fades as SOMEONE steps away.
SUPER_8_DVS239
SOMEONE watches from across the room.
SUPER_8_DVS240
Meanwhile, SOMEONE steps out of the destroyed gas station.
SUPER_8_DVS241
SOMEONE uses a walkie-talkie.
SUPER_8_DVS242
A car salesman opens the hoods of cars missing their engines.
SUPER_8_DVS243
Other citizens crowd around SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS244
The people drift away as SOMEONE walks to the front of the lot and gazes into the street
SUPER_8_DVS245
where military transport trucks roll through the center of town.
SUPER_8_DVS246
In the back of one truck, soldiers wearing berets use electronic instruments.
SUPER_8_DVS247
Elsewhere, SOMEONE rides his bicycle to a transmission tower standing in a field.
SUPER_8_DVS248
His sets down his bike and walks in knee-high grass.
SUPER_8_DVS249
He gazes around the area.
SUPER_8_DVS250
In town, SOMEONE stops outside a public building and pins a piece of paper to a large notice board,
SUPER_8_DVS251
Missing Dog - SOMEONE. Please call Deputy Lamb or SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS252
He blinks and steps back.
SUPER_8_DVS253
Dozens of notices for missing pets filled the entire board.
SUPER_8_DVS254
SOMEONE returns home where his father sits with other officers at the dining table.
SUPER_8_DVS255
SOMEONE drops a flashlight, the men turn and stare at him.
SUPER_8_DVS256
The lights flicker and dim.
SUPER_8_DVS257
SOMEONE speaks into his walkie-talkie.
SUPER_8_DVS258
SOMEONE and SOMEONE use walkie-talkies.
SUPER_8_DVS259
One of SOMEONE's siblings topples.
SUPER_8_DVS260
Meanwhile, a utility truck drives up a dark rural road.
SUPER_8_DVS261
Standing in a lift bucket SOMEONE repairs a high power transformer.
SUPER_8_DVS262
He turns and stares toward the adjacent junkyard which is obscured behind trees then returns to his repairs.
SUPER_8_DVS263
He turns again as something falls beyond the tree line.
SUPER_8_DVS264
Automobile frames and other large objects fly into the night sky.
SUPER_8_DVS265
A washing machine sails high and lands near SOMEONE's repair truck in the street.
SUPER_8_DVS266
Using a joystick SOMEONE raises the lift bucket as high as it SOMEONE go.
SUPER_8_DVS267
He peers through the trees but the junkyard is shrouded in darkness.
SUPER_8_DVS268
The repair truck's headlights flicker as do nearby lamps.
SUPER_8_DVS269
SOMEONE jiggles the joystick.
SUPER_8_DVS270
A huge creature rears up, something strikes the truck smashing the windshield, SOMEONE vanishes.
SUPER_8_DVS271
At a town meeting, SOMEONE stands on a small stage.
SUPER_8_DVS272
A white-haired man stands and takes the microphone.
SUPER_8_DVS274
SOMEONE returns to the police station.
SUPER_8_DVS275
SOMEONE stares as another officer leads Mr. SOMEONE away.
SUPER_8_DVS276
Elsewhere, SOMEONE picks up clothes off the floor as SOMEONE steps into his bedroom.
SUPER_8_DVS277
SOMEONE turns over a test graded C-. He picks up a model train car and hands it to SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS278
SOMEONE turns and stares at SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS279
A mustached deputy spreads out a map.
SUPER_8_DVS280
A brown-haired officer adjusts the radio dial.
SUPER_8_DVS281
The boys film a scene outside a house swarming with soldiers.
SUPER_8_DVS283
Inside SOMEONE's house, SOMEONE points through a window at the children on the street as SOMEONE pulls up in his cruiser.
SUPER_8_DVS284
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchanged glances as SOMEONE takes the camera off the tripod.
SUPER_8_DVS285
SOMEONE places SOMEONE in his cruiser's backseat and tosses the camera onto the front seat. As SOMEONE storms toward the house SOMEONE points to her chest and mouths, "Was it me?"
SUPER_8_DVS286
SOMEONE wearing a beret shakes his head.
SUPER_8_DVS287
SOMEONE stares blankly at SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS288
SOMEONE turns to leave.
SUPER_8_DVS289
From the car, SOMEONE watches his father return to the colonel who extends his hand.
SUPER_8_DVS290
The two men shake hands.
SUPER_8_DVS291
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE return home.
SUPER_8_DVS292
Tears well up in SOMEONE's eyes as he stares at his father.
SUPER_8_DVS293
SOMEONE's face twitches as he stares back then turns and leaves.
SUPER_8_DVS294
A tear runs down SOMEONE's cheek.
SUPER_8_DVS295
Inhaling, he wipes the tear away.
SUPER_8_DVS296
Later, SOMEONE rides his bicycle into a fenced cemetery.
SUPER_8_DVS297
He pedals over grass and around grave markers.
SUPER_8_DVS298
At night, SOMEONE sits against his mother's headstone.
SUPER_8_DVS299
SOMEONE Lamb. May 26th
SUPER_8_DVS300
1943-February 3rd, 1979.
SUPER_8_DVS301
Beloved wife and mother.
SUPER_8_DVS302
SOMEONE holds up his mother's necklace and peers inside the open locket.
SUPER_8_DVS303
SOMEONE gazes into the distance.
SUPER_8_DVS304
Leaping to his feet, he takes his flashlight out of his backpack and shines it across the cemetery onto a shed.
SUPER_8_DVS305
Strange lights flash inside its windows.
SUPER_8_DVS306
SOMEONE turns and runs.
SUPER_8_DVS307
Meanwhile, SOMEONE drives his cruiser through a gate and onto Lillian airfield. Soldiers aiming assault weapons surround SOMEONE's car.
SUPER_8_DVS308
SOMEONE steps out.
SUPER_8_DVS310
Inside a temporary military hospital, Colonel SOMEONE stands beside Dr. SOMEONE's bed.
SUPER_8_DVS311
Covered in cuts and bandages SOMEONE stares up at him.
SUPER_8_DVS312
SOMEONE leans over SOMEONE pausing inches from his face.
SUPER_8_DVS313
As he walks away SOMEONE glances at another soldier,
SUPER_8_DVS314
the man steps forward and injects the contents of a syringe
SUPER_8_DVS315
into SOMEONE's IV line.
SUPER_8_DVS316
Restraints hold SOMEONE's arms and legs as he spasms,
SUPER_8_DVS317
SOMEONE falls motionless.
SUPER_8_DVS318
SOMEONE wakes in his bedroom.
SUPER_8_DVS319
He climbs out of bed and trips as he makes his way across the room.
SUPER_8_DVS320
SOMEONE opens his window for SOMEONE who stands outside.
SUPER_8_DVS321
SOMEONE climbs through the window, stepping beside the white cube on SOMEONE's desk as she hops down.
SUPER_8_DVS322
Suddenly, a movie projector switches on as the power returns.
SUPER_8_DVS323
Reaching for the projector, SOMEONE lets his hand fall.
SUPER_8_DVS324
SOMEONE leans forward onto her knees and peers at the film.
SUPER_8_DVS325
On a screen, a brown-haired woman smiles as she holds an infant boy.
SUPER_8_DVS326
She coos at the baby as he chews on the locket dangling from a necklace around her neck.
SUPER_8_DVS327
Later, the woman blows out a candle on a cupcake as the baby wears a party hat.
SUPER_8_DVS328
The baby cries and the woman picks him up and cradles him in her arms.
SUPER_8_DVS329
Later, the boy is about kindergarten age
SUPER_8_DVS331
places his height on the wood.
SUPER_8_DVS332
Sitting in front of a Christmas tree, the boy opens presents as the woman puts on her necklace.
SUPER_8_DVS333
The camera zooms in on SOMEONE's mother's face as she smiles.
SUPER_8_DVS334
In the film, SOMEONE's mother tips him upside down as they play outdoors.
SUPER_8_DVS335
She looks up at the camera and smiles then turns away.
SUPER_8_DVS336
Tears well up in SOMEONE's eyes.
SUPER_8_DVS337
In the film, young SOMEONE waves both hands as he squirms in his mother's lap.
SUPER_8_DVS338
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE who bites her bottom lip as she cries.
SUPER_8_DVS339
SOMEONE's mother pushes him on a swing as the screen turns white
SUPER_8_DVS340
then the film ends.
SUPER_8_DVS341
Both children turn as the white cube on SOMEONE's desk begins to vibrate.
SUPER_8_DVS342
SOMEONE wiped her eyes as she and SOMEONE peer at the cube.
SUPER_8_DVS343
SOMEONE picks up a paintbrush and prods the vibrating cube then glances at SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS344
The cube flies across the room and punches a hole through a poster of the Space Shuttle on SOMEONE's bedroom wall.
SUPER_8_DVS345
The children stands and peer through the hole
SUPER_8_DVS346
which frames the town's water tower in the distance.
SUPER_8_DVS347
SOMEONE gulps and glances at SOMEONE then stares at the hole again.
SUPER_8_DVS348
Later, SOMEONE turns the key in her front door and slips inside.
SUPER_8_DVS349
She shuts the door, sets the keys on a hall table, and tiptoes toward a staircase.
SUPER_8_DVS350
SOMEONE freezes.
SUPER_8_DVS351
She walks into the living room where her father sits in a chair and smokes,
SUPER_8_DVS352
a whisky bottle stands on the chair's armrest.
SUPER_8_DVS353
SOMEONE runs outside, grabs her bike, and takes off down the dark street.
SUPER_8_DVS354
Her father staggers after her but SOMEONE rides on.
SUPER_8_DVS355
She races down a street lined with cars.
SUPER_8_DVS356
SOMEONE glances over her shoulder as headlights appear behind her, she pedals faster.
SUPER_8_DVS357
Driving the yellow muscle car her father turns down the side street after her.
SUPER_8_DVS358
SOMEONE stops and turns around then rides back up the street.
SUPER_8_DVS359
Her father turns his head as he drives past her.
SUPER_8_DVS360
His father smashes into a parked car,
SUPER_8_DVS361
SOMEONE stops and looks back at the smoking wreck.
SUPER_8_DVS362
Covered in blood her father stirs behind the steering wheel,
SUPER_8_DVS363
SOMEONE fights back tears.
SUPER_8_DVS364
Something lifts SOMEONE and her bike into the air.
SUPER_8_DVS365
Her father jerks on his door handle but it doesn't budge.
SUPER_8_DVS367
He throws himself out of the passenger's side door then scrambles to his feet.
SUPER_8_DVS369
He runs back to SOMEONE's bike which lies on the pavement.
SUPER_8_DVS370
He looks around himself. There's no sign of SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS371
Elsewhere, using a flamethrower a soldier sets a field on fire.
SUPER_8_DVS372
At the camera shop, SOMEONE collects his developed film.
SUPER_8_DVS373
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE then walks out.
SUPER_8_DVS374
They boys pedal their bicycle across the street, past a fence, and under the legs of the town's massive water tower.
SUPER_8_DVS375
High above them a small dent is punched into the water tank's side.
SUPER_8_DVS376
Back at his house, SOMEONE plays the developed film footage.
SUPER_8_DVS377
Both boys turn toward the movie screen.
SUPER_8_DVS378
Standing in front of the projector, SOMEONE gazes at images on SOMEONE's shirt.
SUPER_8_DVS379
SOMEONE nudges him out of the way.
SUPER_8_DVS380
On the screen, a gigantic creature climbs out of the crashed train car.
SUPER_8_DVS381
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE then runs and grabs the reel of film off the projector.
SUPER_8_DVS382
Outside, armed military personnel swarm the streets as SOMEONE and SOMEONE mingle with other citizens.
SUPER_8_DVS383
A white-bearded man points to smoke billowing on the horizon.
SUPER_8_DVS384
People race around then scramble into cars stuffed with luggage as soldiers oversee the evacuation.
SUPER_8_DVS385
A soldier hands a piece of paper to SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they step onto a bus.
SUPER_8_DVS386
A caravan of military vehicles leads buses out of town as large container trucks drive in from the opposite direction.
SUPER_8_DVS387
SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride in the bus as it drives through the countryside then follows a line of vehicles into Greenville Air Force Base.
SUPER_8_DVS388
Inside the fenced compound, people stream into a cavernous aircraft hangar.
SUPER_8_DVS389
The two boys are swept along with the crowd as soldiers herd them into a large waiting area.
SUPER_8_DVS390
SOMEONE's mother pushes through the crowd toward the boys.
SUPER_8_DVS391
Elsewhere in the hangar, Mr. SOMEONE lies on a cot in a triage section.
SUPER_8_DVS392
SOMEONE hurries over and kneels beside him.
SUPER_8_DVS393
SOMEONE's eyes widened as he glances around himself.
SUPER_8_DVS394
Later, SOMEONE stands with his four friends.
SUPER_8_DVS395
SOMEONE's blonde sister sits beside the long-haired camera shop clerk.
SUPER_8_DVS396
Later, he leads the boys through the parking lot.
SUPER_8_DVS397
With his shirt unbuttoned SOMEONE waits in a holding cell.
SUPER_8_DVS398
A soldier griping a rifle opens the door.
SUPER_8_DVS399
The armed soldier follows SOMEONE down a hallway.
SUPER_8_DVS400
SOMEONE turns and elbows the soldier in the face, he grabs the soldier's rifle, and knocks him out with its butt.
SUPER_8_DVS401
Later, wearing the soldier's uniform SOMEONE runs through the building and approaches a window.
SUPER_8_DVS402
He peers out at two soldiers filling a tanker with fuel.
SUPER_8_DVS403
SOMEONE cocks the rifle.
SUPER_8_DVS404
As two soldiers talk nearby a bullet strikes the tanker which explodes.
SUPER_8_DVS405
While soldiers scramble, SOMEONE runs outside and steps into a military truck.
SUPER_8_DVS406
He drives along a dirt road beside a pasture then stops.
SUPER_8_DVS407
He hops out and watches as a convoy of military vehicles drives on another road beyond the pasture.
SUPER_8_DVS408
On a rural highway, SOMEONE passes the boys and SOMEONE, the camera shop clerk, who speed in the opposite direction.
SUPER_8_DVS409
SOMEONE makes a sharp right turn onto a dirt road.
SUPER_8_DVS410
At dusk, SOMEONE drives through town and parks outside the middle school.
SUPER_8_DVS411
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE who sits in the front passenger seat.
SUPER_8_DVS412
Toting a tire iron the boys run across the parking lot and climb over a tall chain-link fence.
SUPER_8_DVS413
SOMEONE hurries over to a small trailer and pulls on its locked doors.
SUPER_8_DVS414
SOMEONE tries to break the lock of with the tire iron.
SUPER_8_DVS415
SOMEONE grabs the tire iron and breaks the lock.
SUPER_8_DVS416
SOMEONE opens the doors revealing film reels and other items.
SUPER_8_DVS417
Inside a classroom, the boys sit with several notebooks and movie reels at a long table.
SUPER_8_DVS418
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a photo.
SUPER_8_DVS419
SOMEONE turns toward a movie screen.
SUPER_8_DVS420
In a move, men in white lab coats stand in a huge hangar.
SUPER_8_DVS421
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE who plays an electronic football game.
SUPER_8_DVS422
SOMEONE places a cassette labeled April 8th in a tape player.
SUPER_8_DVS423
SOMEONE hands a document to SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS424
A creature reaches through the cage bars and lifts SOMEONE skyward.
SUPER_8_DVS426
The film strip and cassette stop. SOMEONE and the others gaze at the classroom door, armed soldiers burst into the room.
SUPER_8_DVS427
Outside in his car, SOMEONE smokes a joint and listens to the radio with his eyes closed as military vehicles drive past.
SUPER_8_DVS428
In the school, SOMEONE and his friends step into the hallway.
SUPER_8_DVS429
SOMEONE, the mustached SOMEONE, and several commandos approach.
SUPER_8_DVS430
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's backpack and removes firecrackers.
SUPER_8_DVS431
SOMEONE turns and stares at SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS432
SOMEONE reaches into SOMEONE's pocket and pulls out the locket necklace.
SUPER_8_DVS433
SOMEONE puts the locket in his own pocket.
SUPER_8_DVS434
SOMEONE turns and walks off. The commandos usher the boys outside and onto a bus.
SUPER_8_DVS435
The driver closes the bus door.
SUPER_8_DVS436
SOMEONE watches the bus pull away in his rearview mirror.
SUPER_8_DVS437
SOMEONE uses a CB radio.
SUPER_8_DVS438
He slinks down in his seat.
SUPER_8_DVS439
Still wearing the uniform, SOMEONE arrives at the evacuation hangar.
SUPER_8_DVS440
A passing soldier nods to him.
SUPER_8_DVS441
SOMEONE walks past a dark-haired boy sitting with other children.
SUPER_8_DVS442
Deputy SOMEONE hurries over.
SUPER_8_DVS443
They step behind a curtain.
SUPER_8_DVS444
As Preston sits reading a magazine, SOMEONE approaches and bats it away.
SUPER_8_DVS445
Preston holds up a film reel. On the speeding bus, a soldier speaks into a handset.
SUPER_8_DVS446
SOMEONE hands up SOMEONE's documents to SOMEONE who sits behind him.
SUPER_8_DVS447
In a holding cell at the back of the bus,
SUPER_8_DVS448
SOMEONE and the other boys peer through the glass at the soldiers.
SUPER_8_DVS449
SOMEONE turns toward his friends.
SUPER_8_DVS450
The bus rocks then tilts onto one set of wheels.
SUPER_8_DVS451
As the driver turns the steering wheel the bus lands upright on all its wheels.
SUPER_8_DVS452
The boys and soldiers toss violently, with a flat tire the bus slows as the driver brakes.
SUPER_8_DVS453
The bus slides to a stop.
SUPER_8_DVS454
SOMEONE assembles a rifle.
SUPER_8_DVS455
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS456
SOMEONE studies the gun.
SUPER_8_DVS457
SOMEONE holds the rifle in front of SOMEONE who glances at SOMEONE then takes the gun.
SUPER_8_DVS458
SOMEONE points toward the driver.
SUPER_8_DVS459
With a furrowed brow the driver glances back at SOMEONE then reaches for the handle and opens the bus door.
SUPER_8_DVS460
Standing under the bus flickering lights SOMEONE lifts the rifle.
SUPER_8_DVS461
He inches down the aisle toward the open door. The wide-eyed boys followed his movements.
SUPER_8_DVS462
Moving closer to the door, SOMEONE stops and glances back at SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS463
The creature grabs SOMEONE and knocks him from one side of the bus to the other.
SUPER_8_DVS464
The rifle fires a dart which strikes the glass door of the holding cell cracking it.
SUPER_8_DVS466
SOMEONE reaches toward the driver as the creature pulls SOMEONE out through the bus door, SOMEONE vomits.
SUPER_8_DVS467
The creature rocks the bus as the driver tries to start the engine.
SUPER_8_DVS468
The driver pumps the gas pedal, the creature slams against the bus, and knocks it over onto one side.
SUPER_8_DVS469
SOMEONE hangs by his seat belt as the other boys stand.
SUPER_8_DVS470
The boys unlocked the seat belt and help SOMEONE down.
SUPER_8_DVS471
SOMEONE tries to open the cell door.
SUPER_8_DVS472
Lying a mid-broken glass SOMEONE gazes at the dead soldier beside him and stands.
SUPER_8_DVS473
The creature climbs on top of the bus and rocks it from side to side.
SUPER_8_DVS474
SOMEONE talks into his handset.
SUPER_8_DVS476
SOMEONE pulls on the bus' rear door.
SUPER_8_DVS477
As SOMEONE returns to the holding cell door SOMEONE approaches and pulls on it from the opposite side.
SUPER_8_DVS479
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS480
Everyone turns and watches the creature reach for the driver and crush him.
SUPER_8_DVS481
SOMEONE glances up at a cracked window.
SUPER_8_DVS482
Sitting on SOMEONE's shoulders SOMEONE pounds on the cracked glass with his elbow.
SUPER_8_DVS483
Meanwhile, the creature rips seats out of the bus as it makes its way toward SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS484
SOMEONE cocks the rifle. In the cell, SOMEONE pounds harder on the glass.
SUPER_8_DVS485
As SOMEONE breaks the glass shard rained down on his friends. SOMEONE and SOMEONE pushed SOMEONE up through the window and on the top of the bus.
SUPER_8_DVS486
SOMEONE helps pull out SOMEONE and SOMEONE who kicks SOMEONE in the face.
SUPER_8_DVS487
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pull SOMEONE up through the window. The boys run alongside of the bus.
SUPER_8_DVS488
One by one the boys jump off the bus then run across the road together.
SUPER_8_DVS489
Inside the bus, SOMEONE fires at the creature as it approaches.
SUPER_8_DVS491
SOMEONE backs up toward the holding cell door, he shakes the rifle as it runs out of ammunition.
SUPER_8_DVS492
SOMEONE tosses the gun aside and smiles briefly as the creature pauses.
SUPER_8_DVS493
The creature lunges toward SOMEONE pressing him against the cell door.
SUPER_8_DVS494
Outside, the boys watches the creature climbs out of the bus and runs off.
SUPER_8_DVS495
In the evacuation center, two soldiers grab Mr. SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS496
SOMEONE leads Mr. SOMEONE away.
SUPER_8_DVS497
Kneeling on the road near the bus SOMEONE pulls the locket necklace from SOMEONE's jacket pocket.
SUPER_8_DVS498
Holding his pack SOMEONE climbs out of the bus.
SUPER_8_DVS499
A car speeds toward the bus.
SUPER_8_DVS500
SOMEONE stands as SOMEONE pulls up and steps out of his car.
SUPER_8_DVS501
SOMEONE glances at the wrecked bus.
SUPER_8_DVS502
Later, SOMEONE drives through town.
SUPER_8_DVS503
SOMEONE sleeps between SOMEONE and SOMEONE, the other boys sit in back.
SUPER_8_DVS504
Ahead, an armored tank fires at the car SOMEONE swerves into a driveway as the tank passes behind them.
SUPER_8_DVS505
More tanks drive down the street and fire their guns. Leaving SOMEONE in the car the boys jump out and run through a yard and down a path.
SUPER_8_DVS506
On the street, a helmeted soldier talks into a transceiver.
SUPER_8_DVS507
A missile explodes nearby. A few blocks away, the boys run past houses and across more lawns.
SUPER_8_DVS509
They jumped over a chain fence and into a backyard.
SUPER_8_DVS510
As they run through a back gate they stop as an exploding tank tumbles across the ground toward them.
SUPER_8_DVS511
The boys change direction, soldiers run down the street past a large two-story houses as missiles zoom around them.
SUPER_8_DVS512
The boys sprint across a playground toward the house. Behind them, tanks roll across the playground crushing play equipment.
SUPER_8_DVS513
The boys rush into the house and run upstairs.
SUPER_8_DVS514
SOMEONE peers out kitchen windows.
SUPER_8_DVS515
SOMEONE chugs a soda.
SUPER_8_DVS516
A blast takes out the wall next to the boys and knocks them to the floor.
SUPER_8_DVS517
SOMEONE crawls over to SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS518
SOMEONE pulls a tie back off a curtain and hands it to SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS519
SOMEONE stands.
SUPER_8_DVS520
SOMEONE nods.
SUPER_8_DVS521
SOMEONE runs over.
SUPER_8_DVS522
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run off.
SUPER_8_DVS523
SOMEONE and SOMEONE run down the street as fire and smoke fill the night sky.
SUPER_8_DVS524
Across town, they run into the cemetery and over to the caretaker's shed which has several sets of doors.
SUPER_8_DVS525
They pull up on one door which doesn't budge.
SUPER_8_DVS526
They move to another door.
SUPER_8_DVS527
They moved to a set of double doors and ram them with their shoulders.
SUPER_8_DVS528
They bust the doors open revealing a huge hole in the ground.
SUPER_8_DVS529
They gaze into the hole which leads straight down.
SUPER_8_DVS530
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS531
SOMEONE dumps firecrackers and boxes of sparklers out of his backpack.
SUPER_8_DVS532
SOMEONE lights one sparkler and tosses it into the hole.
SUPER_8_DVS533
The sparkler falls into the deep pit and lands on the bottom about 50 yards below.
SUPER_8_DVS534
Elsewhere, SOMEONE drives a military jeep. Sitting in the passenger seat
SUPER_8_DVS535
Louis SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS536
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE who stares straight ahead,
SUPER_8_DVS537
SOMEONE turns away.
SUPER_8_DVS538
The two men exchange glances.
SUPER_8_DVS539
In the shed, SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb down a rope into the hole.
SUPER_8_DVS540
SOMEONE lights another sparkler and glances around at several tunnels.
SUPER_8_DVS541
SOMEONE turns.
SUPER_8_DVS542
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE through a tunnel they pass underneath another huge hole on the floor of a house where a lamp flickers.
SUPER_8_DVS543
SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach the opening to a huge underground chamber.
SUPER_8_DVS544
They gaze into the chamber which is filled to electric wiring, other equipment and batteries.
SUPER_8_DVS545
As they move closer SOMEONE turns and finds himself face-to-face with Sheriff Pruit who hangs upside down.
SUPER_8_DVS546
SOMEONE clamps his hand over SOMEONE's mouth and pulls him behind a rock.
SUPER_8_DVS547
Dozens of bodies hang upside down in the chamber.
SUPER_8_DVS548
SOMEONE studies the bodies' faces.
SUPER_8_DVS549
SOMEONE's eyes widened, SOMEONE's jaw drops.
SUPER_8_DVS550
Inside the chamber, the creature works on a machine while eating a human leg.
SUPER_8_DVS551
Across the chamber, SOMEONE hangs upside down.
SUPER_8_DVS552
Carrying a lit sparkler SOMEONE runs into another tunnel.
SUPER_8_DVS553
SOMEONE pulls fireworks out of his backpack.
SUPER_8_DVS554
He lays out different fireworks on the ground and connects them with a line of gun powder.
SUPER_8_DVS555
He glances up as the creature pulls down a woman wearing hair rollers.
SUPER_8_DVS556
SOMEONE runs around to the other side of the chamber and watches the creature.
SUPER_8_DVS557
SOMEONE takes out a cigarette lighter and tries to ignite it.
SUPER_8_DVS558
From across the chamber, SOMEONE keeps an eye on SOMEONE who continues to strike the lighter.
SUPER_8_DVS559
The creature pulls SOMEONE down.
SUPER_8_DVS560
SOMEONE ignites the lighter.
SUPER_8_DVS561
He lights the fuse on a chain of fireworks, grabs his backpack, and runs off.
SUPER_8_DVS564
The creature leaves SOMEONE on the ground and investigates.
SUPER_8_DVS565
SOMEONE runs over to SOMEONE and shakes her.
SUPER_8_DVS566
SOMEONE raises his hand and hesitates then slaps SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS567
SOMEONE opens her eyes.
SUPER_8_DVS568
She sits up.
SUPER_8_DVS569
SOMEONE studies SOMEONE's face then hugs him.
SUPER_8_DVS570
SOMEONE stares straight ahead then closes his eyes.
SUPER_8_DVS571
The woman wearing hair rollers sits up nearby.
SUPER_8_DVS572
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pull down Sheriff SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS573
Elsewhere, the creature moves through a tunnel as the light from fireworks flickers on the walls.
SUPER_8_DVS574
SOMEONE darts through the tunnel and glances back at the creature.
SUPER_8_DVS575
Back in the large chamber, Sheriff SOMEONE shines a flashlight.
SUPER_8_DVS576
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and Tina the woman wearing rollers followed the sheriff past the creatures collection of wires and other equipment then into a tunnel.
SUPER_8_DVS578
SOMEONE lead them around a curve.
SUPER_8_DVS579
SOMEONE runs out of a side tunnel.
SUPER_8_DVS580
The creature appears behind SOMEONE, grabs him, and tosses him far away.
SUPER_8_DVS581
SOMEONE turns and runs.
SUPER_8_DVS582
SOMEONE and SOMEONE follow close to SOMEONE while Tina lags behind.
SUPER_8_DVS583
The creature chases them through the tunnel, grabs Tina, and throws her aside.
SUPER_8_DVS584
Reaching a dead end they turn and gazed down the empty tunnel.
SUPER_8_DVS585
The creature appears around the corner.
SUPER_8_DVS586
SOMEONE and SOMEONE clammer against the tunnel wall.
SUPER_8_DVS587
SOMEONE stands still and stares at the creature.
SUPER_8_DVS588
The creature lurches closer and closer toward the three children.
SUPER_8_DVS589
Cowering beside SOMEONE, SOMEONE frowns as she glances from the creature to SOMEONE who marches toward the creature.
SUPER_8_DVS590
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS591
SOMEONE gazes up at the creature.
SUPER_8_DVS592
The creature picks up SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS593
The creature lifts SOMEONE close to its own face and studies him.
SUPER_8_DVS594
SOMEONE's hair moves as the creature breathes on him.
SUPER_8_DVS595
A covering on the creatures eyes slides upward.
SUPER_8_DVS596
The creature stares at SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS597
Behind the creature a machine in the chamber switches on.
SUPER_8_DVS598
The creature glances away then turns back to SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS599
The creature lowers SOMEONE to the ground, glances at the children, then speeds back to the chamber.
SUPER_8_DVS600
SOMEONE steps toward SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS601
Later above ground, the children run along a street into the center of town.
SUPER_8_DVS602
On a corner, a metal trash can shakes then flies off toward the water tower.
SUPER_8_DVS603
The children walk past armed soldiers who stare skyward as various metal objects - large and small - fly toward the tower.
SUPER_8_DVS604
The windows of the camera shop shatter as cameras and other metal objects fly out.
SUPER_8_DVS605
A soldier's dog tag rips of his neck.
SUPER_8_DVS606
Sliding along the street as if ice skating, another soldier clings to his rifle as it flies toward the tower.
SUPER_8_DVS607
The soldier rises then let's go of his gun and falls to the ground.
SUPER_8_DVS608
In the car lot, car headlights flashed. The doors on a cargo truck containing containers of cubes burst open.
SUPER_8_DVS609
The cubes fly out and sail into the sky.
SUPER_8_DVS610
Lying on the ground, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE watch as the cubes assemble in the sky.
SUPER_8_DVS611
Everyone stands and stares into the sky as the cubes come together forming parts of the creature's ship.
SUPER_8_DVS612
The ship's spotlights shine down on the street.
SUPER_8_DVS613
The ship nears completion as cubes rise from different trucks throughout town.
SUPER_8_DVS614
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE gets out and peers up at the forming ship.
SUPER_8_DVS615
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk together toward SOMEONE and SOMEONE who exchange glances.
SUPER_8_DVS616
SOMEONE hurries up to SOMEONE, places his hands on the sides of his son's face.
SUPER_8_DVS618
He hugs him, SOMEONE shuckles over to SOMEONE.
SUPER_8_DVS619
Her eyes filled with tears as she hugs her father.
SUPER_8_DVS620
Still hugging his own father SOMEONE gazes up at the ship.
SUPER_8_DVS621
The soldiers watch the fully formed ship as it prepares to fly away.
SUPER_8_DVS622
SOMEONE closes his eyes as he and SOMEONE embrace.
SUPER_8_DVS623
SOMEONE opens his eyes and steps back.
SUPER_8_DVS624
The locket necklace rises from his pocket.
SUPER_8_DVS625
SOMEONE grips the necklace chain as the locket moves toward the ship.
SUPER_8_DVS626
SOMEONE stares at the locket which opens revealing a photograph of SOMEONE's brunette mother holding SOMEONE as a baby.
SUPER_8_DVS627
SOMEONE cries as he studies the picture.
SUPER_8_DVS628
SOMEONE places one hand on SOMEONE's shoulder.
SUPER_8_DVS629
SOMEONE lets go of the chain,
SUPER_8_DVS630
The locket sails up toward the tower.
SUPER_8_DVS631
Loaded with metallic objects
SUPER_8_DVS632
the water tower implodes.
SUPER_8_DVS633
Water showers down on the people in the street.
SUPER_8_DVS634
Parts of the water tower's metal frame fall to the street.
SUPER_8_DVS635
The creature climbs up the tower and into the ship which flies away.
SUPER_8_DVS636
On a sidewalk, SOMEONE hobbles along and holds onto SOMEONE as they gaze up at the ship.
SUPER_8_DVS637
In his car, SOMEONE stirs.
SUPER_8_DVS638
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand side by side and watch the ship fly off.
SUPER_8_DVS639
SOMEONE closes his hand around SOMEONE's hand then squeezes.
SUPER_8_DVS640
Still gazing skyward they both smile.
SUPER_8_DVS641
Above, the ship's spotlight shine through clouds of smoke floating in the night sky.
SUPER_8_DVS656
Dressed in a suit and hat, SOMEONE walks up to the chalk outline of a body drawn around a pool of blood.
SUPER_8_DVS657
A key card for Romero Chemical. In an office, Preston uses a phone.
SUPER_8_DVS658
SOMEONE puts on his hat and stands then shakes Preston's hand.
SUPER_8_DVS659
As SOMEONE leaves Preston picks up the phone.
SUPER_8_DVS660
SOMEONE walks in to Building 47 and turns on a flashlight.
SUPER_8_DVS661
Old factory equipment fills the warehouse.
SUPER_8_DVS662
Costumed as a zombie, SOMEONE creeps up behind him.
SUPER_8_DVS663
SOMEONE and SOMEONE grapple.
SUPER_8_DVS664
SOMEONE takes out a gun but SOMEONE knocks it away.
SUPER_8_DVS665
SOMEONE turns and slams SOMEONE against several nails protruding from a wall. Blood pours from SOMEONE's mouth.
SUPER_8_DVS667
Later, SOMEONE dials a telephone.
SUPER_8_DVS668
A model train sits on tracks.
SUPER_8_DVS669
Firecrackers explode inside the modeled train, flaming train cars tumble over gravel.