Headlights glow behind them.
THE_VOW_DVS35
The couple kisses passionately.
THE_VOW_DVS37
The driver side window shatters. The slipping truck veers right, and the pushed car slams into something.
THE_VOW_DVS38
Still seen in slow motion the brunette woman appears weightless as she drifts headfirst toward the windshield.
THE_VOW_DVS40
It shatters on contact. She lands halfway outside, face down on the hood.
THE_VOW_DVS41
The front bumpers crushed against a utility pole.
THE_VOW_DVS45
Later, emergency personnel wheel the unconscious couple into a hospital on stretchers.
THE_VOW_DVS46
Words appear. Inspired by true events.
THE_VOW_DVS47
In the ER a doctor intubates the wife while another cuts the husband's shirt.
THE_VOW_DVS48
In a corridor, three guys and two women anxiously heed the words of a nurse. The husband briefly opens his eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS49
Four years ago.
THE_VOW_DVS50
In a government building the broad shouldered man waits in line.
THE_VOW_DVS51
He sees his future wife with dark chin length hair leaving the counter ahead of him.
THE_VOW_DVS52
As she passes, he glances after her. Their gazes meet.
THE_VOW_DVS53
They share a smile.
THE_VOW_DVS54
Now he catches up with her, wearing a hip straw fedora.
THE_VOW_DVS55
She turns and finds him right there.
THE_VOW_DVS56
He holds it out.
THE_VOW_DVS57
He notices a sticker on her car.
THE_VOW_DVS58
She smiles, he drops his gaze and grins sheepishly.
THE_VOW_DVS59
She opens her car door.
THE_VOW_DVS60
She looks him in the eye.
THE_VOW_DVS61
Considering, she allows an amused smile.
THE_VOW_DVS62
She nods and he grins brightly.
THE_VOW_DVS63
She closes her driver side door and triggers her keychain remote.
THE_VOW_DVS64
Later in a dine-in spot called SOMEONE Mnemonic,
THE_VOW_DVS65
SOMEONE hides two chocolates from a box behind his back.
THE_VOW_DVS66
They each take a bite from a chocolate.
THE_VOW_DVS67
She offers her glass of red wine.
THE_VOW_DVS68
As he takes a sip, she plucks the straw fedora off his head and tries it on herself.
THE_VOW_DVS69
He tweaks the brim lower on her brow, and she wipes chocolate off his mouth.
THE_VOW_DVS70
At another SOMEONE, a pale and red-nosed SOMEONE shrugs her open sweater onto her shoulders and serves drinks.
THE_VOW_DVS71
She frowns at a box left on a table by a window.
THE_VOW_DVS72
She wipes her nose with a tissue, then heads over.
THE_VOW_DVS73
Finding a photo of herself on the box's lid,
THE_VOW_DVS74
she lifts her gaze and sees her handsome companion standing outside in the pouring rain.
THE_VOW_DVS75
He gestures and she opens the gift.
THE_VOW_DVS76
She reads a note on a box of tissues.
THE_VOW_DVS77
She finds medicine.
THE_VOW_DVS78
She takes out a photo of SOMEONE holding a guitar.
THE_VOW_DVS79
Holding his gaze, she presses the photo to her chest. Finding another note, she reads.
THE_VOW_DVS80
She pulls out a sexy lingerie bask with a black laced trimmed bust.
THE_VOW_DVS81
Holding it up, she purses her lips and mocks a seductive expression.
THE_VOW_DVS82
SOMEONE grins.
THE_VOW_DVS83
SOMEONE glances around, then hurriedly lowers the lingerie.
THE_VOW_DVS84
With a wave, SOMEONE heads away.
THE_VOW_DVS85
SOMEONE’s reflection in the window shows her loving smile as she waves back.
THE_VOW_DVS87
SOMEONE holds an arm out of a car window, as SOMEONE drives. She tickles him.
THE_VOW_DVS88
His eyes squint merrily as he leans back laughing.
THE_VOW_DVS89
SOMEONE beams at him, SOMEONE’s grin wilts and he clenches his jaw. SOMEONE stares.
THE_VOW_DVS90
With a smile, SOMEONE hits a switch. As she puts her power window up she holds SOMEONE’s gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS91
In the present, a CT machine scans an unconscious SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS94
At his wife’s bedside,
THE_VOW_DVS95
he returns her wedding ring to her finger. A ventilator tube juts from her mouth.
THE_VOW_DVS96
In a flashback, SOMEONE exits an apartment and finds her in an alley.
THE_VOW_DVS97
She feeds a stray cat.
THE_VOW_DVS98
She heads inside.
THE_VOW_DVS99
SOMEONE’s three guy friends join them.
THE_VOW_DVS100
SOMEONE serves her pancakes with words spelled in blueberries.
THE_VOW_DVS101
He adjusts a few berries, clarifying the message, Move in, with a question SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS102
SOMEONE beams and SOMEONE’s guy friends swap happy looks.
THE_VOW_DVS103
She kisses SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS104
Now SOMEONE wears a wedding veil.
THE_VOW_DVS105
They stand with friends in a gallery.
THE_VOW_DVS106
He takes out his vows. Grinning, SOMEONE shows her identical SOMEONE Mnemonic menu. SOMEONE’s guy friends, a brunette woman with a beauty SOMEONE and a few others witness the event.
THE_VOW_DVS107
Beaming, SOMEONE nods. Their friends smile.
THE_VOW_DVS108
Their officiating friend spots two guards.
THE_VOW_DVS109
The newlyweds share a quick kiss, then flee the museum gallery with their small group of friends. The guards chase them.
THE_VOW_DVS110
Hurrying up a flight of stairs, SOMEONE drops his SOMEONE Mnemonic menu and pauses to snatch it up.
THE_VOW_DVS111
Outside, he holds SOMEONE’s hand as they race across a footbridge.
THE_VOW_DVS112
The guards give up the chase.
THE_VOW_DVS113
A sign below reads, The Art Institute of Chicago.
THE_VOW_DVS115
In Millennium Park, SOMEONE and SOMEONE kiss under the steel, bean shaped archway of cloud gate.
THE_VOW_DVS116
A wider view shows people strolling the plaza around the 40-foot high sculpture.
THE_VOW_DVS117
Their warped figures reflected on its seamless, chrome like surface. In another flashback,
THE_VOW_DVS118
SOMEONE works a mound of clay on the table in an art studio.
THE_VOW_DVS119
Her pulled back hair is now shoulder length.
THE_VOW_DVS120
With a frustrated look, she smacks the unfinished sculpture, then shoves the table away.
THE_VOW_DVS121
SOMEONE enters and turns off the stereo.
THE_VOW_DVS122
SOMEONE stomps irritably.
THE_VOW_DVS123
SOMEONE holds up a piece of clay, shaped like a person.
THE_VOW_DVS124
He makes the tiny figure dance.
THE_VOW_DVS125
SOMEONE playfully bites her neck.
THE_VOW_DVS126
He tickles her sides and she sinks to the floor in the fetal position.
THE_VOW_DVS127
He eyes clay on a table.
THE_VOW_DVS128
Nodding, SOMEONE gives him a tender smile.
THE_VOW_DVS129
She points at a different table.
THE_VOW_DVS130
She eyes the subject of his commentary.
THE_VOW_DVS131
Grinning, she cups his face in her hands and presses her lips to his abashed smirk.
THE_VOW_DVS132
As they kiss, she lies back on the floor, pulling him down on top of her.
THE_VOW_DVS133
He brushes his fingers over her hair,
THE_VOW_DVS135
then lowers his lips to her neck.
THE_VOW_DVS136
She pulls up his shirt to reveal his toned back, and works it over his head.
THE_VOW_DVS139
His fingers move to the buttons on her top.
THE_VOW_DVS140
Sunlight glows through the studio windows as SOMEONE lies asleep face down on SOMEONE’s chest. A rumpled sheet covers their waists.
THE_VOW_DVS141
SOMEONE stirs and caresses his wife’s arm with his thumb.
THE_VOW_DVS142
In the present, SOMEONE breaths with a nasal cannula as she lies in bed.
THE_VOW_DVS143
Wound scars barely show on the right side of her face.
THE_VOW_DVS144
SOMEONE stands with SOMEONE’s doctor at the foot of the bed.
THE_VOW_DVS145
The brunette shifts her groggy gaze, then closes her eyes and winces.
THE_VOW_DVS146
SOMEONE’s eyes grow misty.
THE_VOW_DVS147
SOMEONE gives him an uncertain look.
THE_VOW_DVS148
SOMEONE turns to the doctor.
THE_VOW_DVS149
SOMEONE addresses the question to SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS150
He shoots her doctor a glance.
THE_VOW_DVS151
SOMEONE eyes him expectantly.
THE_VOW_DVS152
The real doctor turns to SOMEONE who returns a nonplussed glance.
THE_VOW_DVS153
The physician watches as SOMEONE’s distressed husband takes a seat at his wife’s bedside.
THE_VOW_DVS154
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE with perplexed eyes, and he meets her gaze solemnly.
THE_VOW_DVS155
She glances away.
THE_VOW_DVS156
He touches her arm, but she pulls it back with an alarmed look.
THE_VOW_DVS157
SOMEONE drops his dejected gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS158
The doctor observes closely.
THE_VOW_DVS159
SOMEONE lifts her hand and stares at the gold rope designed wedding ring on her finger.
THE_VOW_DVS160
She shifts her shocked eyes to SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS161
Now he exits to the hall.
THE_VOW_DVS162
He storms off.
THE_VOW_DVS163
Now in a corridor, SOMEONE paces by a vending machine, clenching and unclenching his fists.
THE_VOW_DVS164
He leans against the machine.
THE_VOW_DVS165
With his back against it, he sinks to the floor.
THE_VOW_DVS166
He touches the wedding band around his finger, then wrings his hands.
THE_VOW_DVS168
SOMEONE enters a waiting room and finds SOMEONE asleep on a couch.
THE_VOW_DVS169
She pokes his shoulder with one finger.
THE_VOW_DVS170
Waking, he hurriedly sits up and rubs his face.
THE_VOW_DVS171
She flashes a nervous grin.
THE_VOW_DVS172
Smiling he collects his belongings.
THE_VOW_DVS173
He takes her to the cafeteria.
THE_VOW_DVS174
SOMEONE frowns dubiously.
THE_VOW_DVS175
SOMEONE shifts her shocked gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS176
She moves down the serving line. Now, SOMEONE’s friends visit at the hospital.
THE_VOW_DVS177
A guy throws a packaged salad at another.
THE_VOW_DVS179
The girl with the beauty SOMEONE crouches in front of SOMEONE and looks up at him.
THE_VOW_DVS180
SOMEONE gazes downward.
THE_VOW_DVS182
he reclines in the large, industrial room, serving as his and SOMEONE’s trendy Bohemian apartment.
THE_VOW_DVS183
Now, he arrives in the recovery ward with a tote bag and strides cheerfully to SOMEONE’s curtained off bed.
THE_VOW_DVS184
Pulling the curtains aside,
THE_VOW_DVS185
he finds the bed crisply made and unoccupied.
THE_VOW_DVS186
He goes to the nurse’s station.
THE_VOW_DVS187
Leaving the recovery area, SOMEONE breaks into a run.
THE_VOW_DVS188
Now in a comfortable private suite,
THE_VOW_DVS189
an elegant older couple regards SOMEONE coldly.
THE_VOW_DVS190
SOMEONE’s mother kisses her hand.
THE_VOW_DVS191
In the cafeteria.
THE_VOW_DVS192
SOMEONE meets her gaze reluctantly.
THE_VOW_DVS193
SOMEONE hangs his head.
THE_VOW_DVS194
SOMEONE leaves the table and he gestures helplessly.
THE_VOW_DVS195
Standing he gathers their things.
THE_VOW_DVS196
SOMEONE shrugs and shakes her head.
THE_VOW_DVS197
She moves off.
THE_VOW_DVS198
SOMEONE briefly hangs his head then takes a deep breath.
THE_VOW_DVS199
Now SOMEONE enters the VIP recovery room, clad in a short crocheted sweater dress and boots.
THE_VOW_DVS200
Her doctor arrives.
THE_VOW_DVS201
Meanwhile, SOMEONE runs through the hospital.
THE_VOW_DVS202
SOMEONE hurries in.
THE_VOW_DVS203
Her brow knitted, SOMEONE blinks at SOMEONE. He lowers the phone.
THE_VOW_DVS204
SOMEONE stares at him, her gaze softening.
THE_VOW_DVS205
Lowering her thoughtful eyes, SOMEONE puffs her cheeks out then exhales.
THE_VOW_DVS206
Her parents glower.
THE_VOW_DVS207
SOMEONE fixes his fond eyes on his wife.
THE_VOW_DVS208
Now, as he drives her through the city, SOMEONE faces her side view mirror. She briefly lifts her bangs back and studies the scar at her hairline.
THE_VOW_DVS209
Noting her husband’s earnest expression, SOMEONE yields a shy smile. An elevated train passes nearby.
THE_VOW_DVS210
SOMEONE smiles wistfully.
THE_VOW_DVS211
SOMEONE averts her surprised, slack-jawed gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS212
At night, SOMEONE shuts her door for her as she gets out of his 80s era Wagoneer.
THE_VOW_DVS213
He shyly walks her to their apartment’s entrance.
THE_VOW_DVS214
He leads her in to a foyer, then gestures.
THE_VOW_DVS215
As he shuts the door and carries their things, SOMEONE wrings her hands and ventures warily into the living room.
THE_VOW_DVS216
SOMEONE’s eyes widen. The girl with the beauty SOMEONE hugs her.
THE_VOW_DVS217
The lovely woman recovers her smile.
THE_VOW_DVS218
The wedding officiant.
THE_VOW_DVS219
As SOMEONE hurries off, SOMEONE watches her go. SOMEONE follows his wife.
THE_VOW_DVS220
Later, the guests file out.
THE_VOW_DVS221
SOMEONE sees off a trendy couple, then withdraws into the apartment and shuts the door.
THE_VOW_DVS222
At a dressing table, SOMEONE’s fingers glide over a drawing of a reclined female figure in a sketchbook.
THE_VOW_DVS223
Quaint odds and ends litter the surface.
THE_VOW_DVS224
SOMEONE’s reflections shows in a small round mirror trimmed along the bottom with photos and illustrations.
THE_VOW_DVS225
She picks up a bottle of perfume, and gives it a sniff.
THE_VOW_DVS226
SOMEONE approaches and sits in a nearby armchair.
THE_VOW_DVS227
Her gaze anguished, SOMEONE shuts her eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS228
SOMEONE gets up and leaves the room.
THE_VOW_DVS230
Staring ahead, SOMEONE’s features twist in a remorseful SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS231
In the living room, a shirtless SOMEONE covers his bare feet with a nappy blanket
THE_VOW_DVS232
and curls up beneath it on a couch.
THE_VOW_DVS233
SOMEONE remains at the dressing table.
THE_VOW_DVS234
She props her chin on her fist.
THE_VOW_DVS235
An artfully made, queen sized bed lies unoccupied behind her.
THE_VOW_DVS236
On the couch, SOMEONE stares off with a melancholy gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS237
Now, the sun shines brightly outside their converted warehouse building.
THE_VOW_DVS238
Inside a framed photo of a shirtless SOMEONE stands beside a baroque vanity mirror painted yellow.
THE_VOW_DVS239
The frame of a much larger wall mirror is home to several more candids, lovingly tucked in place.
THE_VOW_DVS240
SOMEONE approaches in a towel and spies a photo of her tattooed back.
THE_VOW_DVS241
She anxiously locates the swirling crescent shaped fish tattoo on her actual back.
THE_VOW_DVS242
SOMEONE steps away from the mirror.
THE_VOW_DVS243
On the living room couch, SOMEONE stirs groggily and wakes.
THE_VOW_DVS244
He sits up and throws off the blanket.
THE_VOW_DVS245
He rests his elbows on his knees,
THE_VOW_DVS246
then stands and plods bare bottomed across the room.
THE_VOW_DVS247
As SOMEONE puts on a bra, her naked husband straggles by, rubbing his eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS248
SOMEONE cracks up.
THE_VOW_DVS249
Smiling, SOMEONE shuts himself in an adjacent bathroom.
THE_VOW_DVS250
Now, a door opens to reveal SOMEONE wearing a Chicago Cubs sweatshirt and a sporty ponytail.
THE_VOW_DVS251
She enters the kitchen.
THE_VOW_DVS252
Sitting at the island, SOMEONE beams at her.
THE_VOW_DVS253
She opens a cabinet.
THE_VOW_DVS254
SOMEONE continues through the kitchen, opening the high cabinets one at a time.
THE_VOW_DVS255
SOMEONE watches her intently.
THE_VOW_DVS256
She notices.
THE_VOW_DVS257
SOMEONE notices fresh fruit, coffee, and French toast on the island.
THE_VOW_DVS258
SOMEONE sits at a place setting.
THE_VOW_DVS259
SOMEONE nods and sets down a newspaper.
THE_VOW_DVS260
SOMEONE shrugs inquisitively.
THE_VOW_DVS261
SOMEONE bites his lip and stifles a boyish smile.
THE_VOW_DVS262
SOMEONE nods demurely.
THE_VOW_DVS263
As SOMEONE gets the coffee pot his wife bites into a strip of bacon.
THE_VOW_DVS264
SOMEONE stares at the bacon.
THE_VOW_DVS265
She sets it down and picks bacon bits off her tongue.
THE_VOW_DVS266
SOMEONE steps toward his wife, hesitates, and pats her back.
THE_VOW_DVS267
He heads for the door.
THE_VOW_DVS268
Going out, he glances at her repeatedly.
THE_VOW_DVS269
SOMEONE offers a small wave and he shuts the door.
THE_VOW_DVS270
Left alone, she bites into a strip of bacon.
THE_VOW_DVS271
Now SOMEONE’s Wagoneer pulls up outside a converted garage with corrugated metal walls and a red door.
THE_VOW_DVS272
Inside, SOMEONE works at a soundboard.
THE_VOW_DVS273
SOMEONE comes in and deposits his things near the door.
THE_VOW_DVS274
SOMEONE hangs his head unhappily.
THE_VOW_DVS275
At the apartment, SOMEONE slides aside a grated door, protecting shelves of records, books, and DVDs.
THE_VOW_DVS276
She finds a sticky note from SOMEONE attached to one disc’s box. It reads More Evidence.
THE_VOW_DVS277
She winces as she watches.
THE_VOW_DVS278
SOMEONE laughs at her recorded comment.
THE_VOW_DVS279
In the video, SOMEONE holds up her menu.
THE_VOW_DVS280
SOMEONE sorrowfully covers her mouth.
THE_VOW_DVS281
Later, she clutches a hard-covered book to her chest, as she strides into SOMEONE Mnemonic.
THE_VOW_DVS282
Crouching in front of a display case, she eyes shelves of pastries, then straightens.
THE_VOW_DVS283
She points,
THE_VOW_DVS284
she grins. Now she exits with her purchase.
THE_VOW_DVS285
At a store across the street, SOMEONE pays a florist.
THE_VOW_DVS286
Outside SOMEONE Mnemonic, SOMEONE glances around without seeing him, then heads down a sidewalk.
THE_VOW_DVS287
SOMEONE takes his bouquet of flowers and hurries in another direction.
THE_VOW_DVS288
Later, SOMEONE stands by a stairway to an L-train platform and looks around in confusion.
THE_VOW_DVS289
Meanwhile, SOMEONE arrives at their apartment.
THE_VOW_DVS290
Elsewhere in the city, SOMEONE stands at a bustling intersection and blinks her frustrated eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS292
At the apartment, SOMEONE spots his wife’s cellphone left on the kitchen island. He picks it up and checks its display,
THE_VOW_DVS293
then heads outside.
THE_VOW_DVS294
On the sidewalk out front, he glances around, then breaks into a run.
THE_VOW_DVS297
SOMEONE enters a restaurant equipment store and approaches a worker at a counter.
THE_VOW_DVS298
SOMEONE continues his search.
THE_VOW_DVS299
Now a car pulls up in front of SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS300
Her mother beckons.
THE_VOW_DVS301
Climbing into the convertible Mercedes, SOMEONE hugs her.
THE_VOW_DVS302
They drive off.
THE_VOW_DVS303
Later at the apartment, SOMEONE waits in the living room area and anxiously rubs his head.
THE_VOW_DVS304
SOMEONE arrives wearing a classy, contemporary dress and a half sleeved cardigan.
THE_VOW_DVS306
SOMEONE strides over.
THE_VOW_DVS307
SOMEONE gives a helpless shrug.
THE_VOW_DVS308
SOMEONE bows his head then meets her imploring gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS309
SOMEONE trudges out of the kitchen.
THE_VOW_DVS310
Later he drives her through an upscale neighborhood.
THE_VOW_DVS311
She holds the bouquet he purchased.
THE_VOW_DVS312
SOMEONE blinks.
THE_VOW_DVS313
She mulls it over.
THE_VOW_DVS314
They approach a Tudor style house.
THE_VOW_DVS315
Now in a dining room, SOMEONE casually displays a ring on her finger.
THE_VOW_DVS316
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE who mouths, It’s okay.
THE_VOW_DVS317
Already seated, SOMEONE stands awkwardly, then sits again.
THE_VOW_DVS318
SOMEONE raises his glass with the others.
THE_VOW_DVS319
SOMEONE gives a wry look.
THE_VOW_DVS320
SOMEONE eyes her lovingly, and she twitches an uneasy smile.
THE_VOW_DVS321
SOMEONE nods equivocating.
THE_VOW_DVS322
SOMEONE gives her fiancé a look.
THE_VOW_DVS323
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare at him with blank expressions.
THE_VOW_DVS324
SOMEONE gives a puzzled shrug.
THE_VOW_DVS325
Later, patrons queue up outside a chic bar.
THE_VOW_DVS326
Entering, SOMEONE and SOMEONE trail behind SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS327
SOMEONE waves at a blonde, who averts her gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS328
SOMEONE glances over.
THE_VOW_DVS329
They reach a table.
THE_VOW_DVS330
Three women greet them.
THE_VOW_DVS331
SOMEONE slaps SOMEONE on the back.
THE_VOW_DVS332
SOMEONE observes the group, tentatively.
THE_VOW_DVS333
Turning, SOMEONE stares with an enamored look.
THE_VOW_DVS334
A clean-cut blonde man in a suit holds her gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS335
SOMEONE smirks.
THE_VOW_DVS336
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE who gives SOMEONE a haughty glance on his way to the bar.
THE_VOW_DVS337
As the reunited friends chat, SOMEONE stands awkwardly apart.
THE_VOW_DVS338
Later, at his recording studio.
THE_VOW_DVS339
SOMEONE frowns dizzily.
THE_VOW_DVS340
Now they sit outside.
THE_VOW_DVS341
SOMEONE glances over, then shrugs.
THE_VOW_DVS342
SOMEONE stares off thoughtfully.
THE_VOW_DVS343
Now, an L-train trundles over a bridge. Riding on board, SOMEONE glances out her window, as her train crosses an intersecting rail line.
THE_VOW_DVS344
Later, elevator doors open and she strides past a reception desk in an upscale office.
THE_VOW_DVS345
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE on the phone in his office. They swap a wave.
THE_VOW_DVS346
Facing his ex, he grins from ear to ear.
THE_VOW_DVS347
He gestures cordially, and SOMEONE takes a seat in front of his desk.
THE_VOW_DVS348
Sitting behind it, he shoots her a quizzical look.
THE_VOW_DVS349
Wincing, SOMEONE glances away.
THE_VOW_DVS350
He rises.
THE_VOW_DVS351
He half-sits on the front of his desk.
THE_VOW_DVS352
Averting her gaze, SOMEONE nods disappointedly.
THE_VOW_DVS353
They both stand.
THE_VOW_DVS354
With a bashful smile, SOMEONE hugs him.
THE_VOW_DVS355
He hesitates then wraps his arms around her and wraps his arms around her and rests this chin on her shoulder.
THE_VOW_DVS356
As they inch apart, SOMEONE cradles the back of his head and they kiss.
THE_VOW_DVS358
Blinking back tears, she struggles to remain composed.
THE_VOW_DVS359
She bites her lip.
THE_VOW_DVS361
Later, at the apartment, she kneels on the dining table, adding photographs to rows of images organized in front of her. Other photos lie in disarray behind her.
THE_VOW_DVS363
SOMEONE enters.
THE_VOW_DVS364
He kisses her cheek, which unsettles her.
THE_VOW_DVS365
As she rests her elbows on the table, he rubs her shoulders.
THE_VOW_DVS366
He tickles her and she jumps.
THE_VOW_DVS367
He ducks into their bedroom.
THE_VOW_DVS368
She stares after him.
THE_VOW_DVS369
Standing just out of view by the doorway, SOMEONE clenches a fist. SOMEONE shifts her sad eyes, then turns away.
THE_VOW_DVS372
SOMEONE pours herself coffee then walks to SOMEONE who reads the paper.
THE_VOW_DVS373
She sits in front of him.
THE_VOW_DVS374
Smiling, he heads off. Outside they walk an alley.
THE_VOW_DVS376
Entering the studio, SOMEONE gazes around the spacious, rugged room, cluttered with works in progress and supplies. One bronzy 10-foot sculpture, shaped vaguely like a mermaid bears a pebbled texture. Sketches hang out of a few half-open drawers and a dresser 10 drawers high.
THE_VOW_DVS377
They explore the room.
THE_VOW_DVS378
SOMEONE examines a treelike nymph sculpture.
THE_VOW_DVS379
Its trunk resembles a woman’s torso.
THE_VOW_DVS380
SOMEONE gives a sad smile.
THE_VOW_DVS381
She edges past an industrial pedestal fan.
THE_VOW_DVS382
She wrings her hands, eying a feminine sculpture in repose.
THE_VOW_DVS383
He moves to her unfinished piece.
THE_VOW_DVS384
He offers a sculpting knife.
THE_VOW_DVS385
Standing at a partially-formed clay sculpture, SOMEONE gives a tense look.
THE_VOW_DVS386
He bounces over to the stereo and turns it on.
THE_VOW_DVS387
He dances back to SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS388
As SOMEONE trudges back to the stereo, SOMEONE heaves a ponderous breath.
THE_VOW_DVS389
SOMEONE slams down the sound system’s control deck.
THE_VOW_DVS390
SOMEONE straightens and peers morosely at him.
THE_VOW_DVS391
She drops her admonished gaze. He shrugs.
THE_VOW_DVS392
With an exasperated look, he heads to the door.
THE_VOW_DVS393
SOMEONE watches him leave the studio,
THE_VOW_DVS394
then blinks her troubled eyes. She turns away from the unfinished sculpture.
THE_VOW_DVS395
Outside, SOMEONE trudges down the alley. His hands curl tensely as they swing at his sides.
THE_VOW_DVS397
In the studio, SOMEONE eyes the section of wall covered in drawings and other artwork,
THE_VOW_DVS398
then faces her towering, treelike sculpture.
THE_VOW_DVS399
She eyes its twisted trunk with branches jutting out from the top, like hair on its head.
THE_VOW_DVS400
Lowering her gaze, she strides for the door and irritably tosses down a piece of clay on her way out.
THE_VOW_DVS401
Now, SOMEONE’s Wagoneer rounds a corner by the apartment.
THE_VOW_DVS402
At home, SOMEONE writes in a notebook.
THE_VOW_DVS403
She tears out a sheet.
THE_VOW_DVS404
She folds it hurriedly as SOMEONE walks in.
THE_VOW_DVS405
SOMEONE faces the bathroom. Seated at her desk, SOMEONE stands nervously.
THE_VOW_DVS406
SOMEONE goes to a bag on the bed.
THE_VOW_DVS407
Her father SOMEONE exits the bathroom.
THE_VOW_DVS408
SOMEONE continues packing.
THE_VOW_DVS409
SOMEONE carries two bags out.
THE_VOW_DVS410
SOMEONE puts down his shoulder satchel and regards SOMEONE with a wounded expression.
THE_VOW_DVS411
SOMEONE averts his considerate gaze, shakes his head and shifts on his feet.
THE_VOW_DVS412
SOMEONE gives a relieved grin and nods.
THE_VOW_DVS413
Coming forward, she obliges warmly.
THE_VOW_DVS414
She steps back, smiles at SOMEONE and leaves.
THE_VOW_DVS415
Her husband turns on the spot.
THE_VOW_DVS416
His jaw clenches, agonizing.
THE_VOW_DVS417
Now a penlight shines directly on SOMEONE’s jade green eye.
THE_VOW_DVS418
She looks to SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS419
Her mom looks away worriedly then puts on a smile.
THE_VOW_DVS420
Her smile tenses.
THE_VOW_DVS421
She moves stiffly past SOMEONE’s doctor and leaves the room.
THE_VOW_DVS422
Under the doctor’s compassionate smile,
THE_VOW_DVS423
the young woman briefly hangs her head.
THE_VOW_DVS425
SOMEONE takes a deep breath.
THE_VOW_DVS426
At the studio, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE as she works a recording session.
THE_VOW_DVS427
Teens play on the other side of the glass.
THE_VOW_DVS428
SOMEONE wears a suit jacket and narrow tie worn over a crisp white shirt.
THE_VOW_DVS429
SOMEONE flips a control board switch.
THE_VOW_DVS430
Lily’s gaze softens, sympathetically.
THE_VOW_DVS431
SOMEONE marches out.
THE_VOW_DVS433
Outside the Thornton’s mansion, elegant guests attend an engagement party in an immaculately tended back yard.
THE_VOW_DVS434
Passing SOMEONE, SOMEONE happens upon SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS435
Nearby, SOMEONE glowers.
THE_VOW_DVS436
As he leaves, SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS437
He smirks cryptically.
THE_VOW_DVS438
As he steps away, SOMEONE beams after him.
THE_VOW_DVS439
Now, SOMEONE strolls the patio, sipping a glass of red wine.
THE_VOW_DVS440
He turns.
THE_VOW_DVS441
Her styled hair has highlights.
THE_VOW_DVS442
He stares at her groomed and lightened tresses.
THE_VOW_DVS443
Behind SOMEONE, SOMEONE and a blonde woman converse with SOMEONE Thornton.
THE_VOW_DVS444
Now, at home, SOMEONE puts on a dark blazer over a muted blue button down, then picks up a tie.
THE_VOW_DVS445
Later, he walks a demurely dressed SOMEONE to his Wagoneer.
THE_VOW_DVS446
SOMEONE chuckles as he strides briskly around the car.
THE_VOW_DVS447
Later, under gleaming skyscraper windows, the SUV pulls into a space in a deserted civic parking lot
THE_VOW_DVS448
situated before a crosswalk.
THE_VOW_DVS449
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE, then looks around uncertainly.
THE_VOW_DVS450
Her husband regards her with a tender gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS451
SOMEONE responds with a warm appreciative smile.
THE_VOW_DVS452
Now at SOMEONE Mnemonic, the front window shows SOMEONE and SOMEONE enjoying a meal and wine at a table for two.
THE_VOW_DVS453
He presents chocolates.
THE_VOW_DVS454
She smirks inquisitively.
THE_VOW_DVS455
She selects a chocolate, then pops it in her mouth.
THE_VOW_DVS456
She frowns.
THE_VOW_DVS457
As SOMEONE chews the second truffle her eyes light up with a surprised smile.
THE_VOW_DVS458
She turns the box of chocolates to face SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS459
SOMEONE eats one, SOMEONE pops another in her mouth.
THE_VOW_DVS460
SOMEONE takes a deep breath, then tries another.
THE_VOW_DVS461
SOMEONE skeptically chews another truffle.
THE_VOW_DVS462
A fleck of truffle filling drops from her mouth onto her hair.
THE_VOW_DVS463
They both crack up.
THE_VOW_DVS464
SOMEONE reaches for the fleck. SOMEONE rocks in her seat.
THE_VOW_DVS465
Later, in the night air,
THE_VOW_DVS466
SOMEONE’s SUV halts on a narrow lane in a quaintly lit public park.
THE_VOW_DVS467
He smiles at SOMEONE and directs her gaze out the windshield.
THE_VOW_DVS468
SOMEONE unbuttons his shirt and SOMEONE’s smile fades.
THE_VOW_DVS469
He removes his shirt.
THE_VOW_DVS470
He sets a small wetsuit beside her and regards her with a subdued, wily smile.
THE_VOW_DVS471
SOMEONE frowns, intrigued.
THE_VOW_DVS472
SOMEONE unbuckles her safety belt, then writhes in her seat, working her demure dress off over her head.
THE_VOW_DVS473
SOMEONE takes a peek.
THE_VOW_DVS475
SOMEONE shakes her hair out.
THE_VOW_DVS476
SOMEONE turns.
THE_VOW_DVS477
He laughs as she dashes out in her bra and panties. Grabbing blankets and towels he hustles after her and does high steps to get out of his jeans.
THE_VOW_DVS478
SOMEONE runs into the water up to her ankles and bids a hasty retreat.
THE_VOW_DVS479
Clad in biker briefs, SOMEONE grabs her around the waist and carries her back in.
THE_VOW_DVS480
Joining hands they run further out into the glistening lake.
THE_VOW_DVS481
SOMEONE plunges in and SOMEONE submerges up to her shoulders.
THE_VOW_DVS482
SOMEONE lifts both her feet and her upper body dunks up to her chin.
THE_VOW_DVS483
Now he helps SOMEONE up and gives her a piggyback ride ashore.
THE_VOW_DVS484
Grabbing a towel and blanket, he wraps both around her.
THE_VOW_DVS485
SOMEONE hurries back into his car and he follows.
THE_VOW_DVS486
SOMEONE wraps a blanket around his shivering shoulders and laughs with SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS487
SOMEONE considers, then envelops her hands in both his own.
THE_VOW_DVS488
He blows on her fingers then kisses them tenderly.
THE_VOW_DVS490
Now at the apartment, keys slide along the dining table. At its far end, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sway in an embrace.
THE_VOW_DVS491
SOMEONE smiles fondly.
THE_VOW_DVS492
In the soft light of the streetlamps outside, he plants two tender kisses on her lips.
THE_VOW_DVS494
Leaning close, she brushes SOMEONE’s blanket off his shoulders, while letting her own fall to the floor.
THE_VOW_DVS495
Standing in their underwear, they kiss again.
THE_VOW_DVS496
SOMEONE smiles up at him sweetly, and his parted lips find hers.
THE_VOW_DVS497
The young woman wraps an arm around her husband’s bare shoulder
THE_VOW_DVS498
and he cradles her head in his hand.
THE_VOW_DVS499
SOMEONE’s hand finds his cheek and caresses it softly.
THE_VOW_DVS500
As they make out, we look on from the far end of the table.
THE_VOW_DVS501
Our view sinks into the shadows.
THE_VOW_DVS502
Now, SOMEONE helps SOMEONE out of his car.
THE_VOW_DVS503
SOMEONE heads toward her parents' house.
THE_VOW_DVS504
She faces him.
THE_VOW_DVS506
Her smile gone, SOMEONE shifts her uneasy gaze. SOMEONE shakes his head earnestly.
THE_VOW_DVS507
SOMEONE hunches her shoulders and looks away.
THE_VOW_DVS508
She meets his gaze with a gentle smile.
THE_VOW_DVS509
SOMEONE lingers on the spot, shifting boyishly on his feet as his wife enters her parents’ home.
THE_VOW_DVS510
As she shuts the door, he turns away and steps around his car.
THE_VOW_DVS511
Inside the house, SOMEONE sets down her keys and takes off her shoes.
THE_VOW_DVS512
In the next room, SOMEONE waits up seated with a book.
THE_VOW_DVS513
SOMEONE smiles sadly, her eyes welling up.
THE_VOW_DVS514
SOMEONE shakes her head tearfully.
THE_VOW_DVS515
SOMEONE gives her a hug.
THE_VOW_DVS516
On a sunny day, SOMEONE walks with his friends.
THE_VOW_DVS517
At the Thornton’s.
THE_VOW_DVS518
SOMEONE brings SOMEONE a folder.
THE_VOW_DVS519
SOMEONE’s mother joins them.
THE_VOW_DVS520
SOMEONE hands the file to his daughter.
THE_VOW_DVS522
At dusk in the city, two elevated trains pass one another under the Chicago skyline.
THE_VOW_DVS523
In the apartment, SOMEONE drops a jacket on a chair and carries a stack of mail to a coffee table.
THE_VOW_DVS524
Sitting, he flips through the envelopes.
THE_VOW_DVS525
He pauses, then tosses them down.
THE_VOW_DVS527
a pink envelope bears a stamp reading Past Due.
THE_VOW_DVS528
SOMEONE wearily leans back on the sofa and stares at the ceiling.
THE_VOW_DVS529
Now, on a sunny day,
THE_VOW_DVS530
yellow rose petals arc through the air as wedding guests shower them on SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS531
In their tux and gown,
THE_VOW_DVS532
the newlyweds joyfully make their way up a narrow aisle between the well-wishers.
THE_VOW_DVS533
Later, the groom sweeps his bride up in his arms.
THE_VOW_DVS534
She laughs delightedly and he kisses her cheek.
THE_VOW_DVS535
Later still, SOMEONE steps toward SOMEONE, but then holds back as she joins her sister for a wedding photo.
THE_VOW_DVS537
the photographer takes a picture of the sisters, their parents, and SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS538
The bridal party moves on without SOMEONE, who stands among the guests.
THE_VOW_DVS539
He turns on the spot, watching SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS540
She smiles briefly at him, then turns away.
THE_VOW_DVS541
SOMEONE moves unhappily through the crowd.
THE_VOW_DVS542
Later, with his necktie loosened,
THE_VOW_DVS543
he strolls through a lavish outdoor reception
THE_VOW_DVS544
and spies SOMEONE dancing with her sister.
THE_VOW_DVS545
She fails to notice him and he moves on sullenly.
THE_VOW_DVS546
Reaching the edge of the party, he arrives at a crenelated terrace, overlooking the city’s distant gleaming skyline.
THE_VOW_DVS547
As he gazes off morosely,
THE_VOW_DVS548
SOMEONE approaches with a bottle of fine liquor.
THE_VOW_DVS549
He sets two glasses on the parapet.
THE_VOW_DVS550
SOMEONE pours the drinks.
THE_VOW_DVS551
They clink glasses.
THE_VOW_DVS552
The two men sip the amber liquor.
THE_VOW_DVS553
SOMEONE cocks his head and nods appreciatively.
THE_VOW_DVS554
SOMEONE puts down his glass, SOMEONE does the same.
THE_VOW_DVS555
SOMEONE takes another sip.
THE_VOW_DVS556
The young man turns away.
THE_VOW_DVS557
SOMEONE stares at him.
THE_VOW_DVS558
From the reception, Mrs. Thornton notices the exchange.
THE_VOW_DVS559
Moving past him, SOMEONE leaves the terrace.
THE_VOW_DVS560
The older man hesitantly takes a drink of his whiskey.
THE_VOW_DVS561
Behind him, SOMEONE goes inside.
THE_VOW_DVS562
Setting his drink on a coaster, he plunks onto an elegant leather sofa.
THE_VOW_DVS563
SOMEONE approaches, finishing off his own drink.
THE_VOW_DVS564
They stand toe to toe.
THE_VOW_DVS565
SOMEONE swallows and vaguely flashes a smile.
THE_VOW_DVS567
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE staring at him, stunned.
THE_VOW_DVS568
She marches off.
THE_VOW_DVS569
SOMEONE looks down at SOMEONE, who sprawls on the floor with a bleeding nose, then follows SOMEONE outside.
THE_VOW_DVS570
SOMEONE’s eyes glisten.
THE_VOW_DVS571
SOMEONE wears a bitter, tearful smile.
THE_VOW_DVS572
Blinking back tears, SOMEONE bravely meets her forgiving gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS573
He grows stoic.
THE_VOW_DVS574
SOMEONE averts her regretful gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS575
Bowing his head, SOMEONE shuffles back a few steps, then heads inside.
THE_VOW_DVS576
SOMEONE helplessly turns on the spot.
THE_VOW_DVS577
Pausing by the door he faces his wife.
THE_VOW_DVS578
SOMEONE regards her longingly, then turns away and walks back inside.
THE_VOW_DVS579
SOMEONE stares after her estranged husband, then takes a few deep steadying breaths and shuts her eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS580
Back in the city, SOMEONE lumbers down a sidewalk parallel to elevated train tracks.
THE_VOW_DVS581
His suit jacket dangling from one hand, and his tie hanging from the other.
THE_VOW_DVS582
His head droops forward and he transfers his coat to his other hand.
THE_VOW_DVS583
Now in his recording studio, SOMEONE sits playing an acoustic guitar.
THE_VOW_DVS584
The view drifts past stacked equipment and microphone stands as we watch the heartbroken young man play.
THE_VOW_DVS585
On the other side of the glass, two lamps turn on in the mixing room.
THE_VOW_DVS586
SOMEONE walks into view casually and peers at the soundboard.
THE_VOW_DVS587
In the recording room SOMEONE gently plucks the guitar strings.
THE_VOW_DVS588
His lips hold a pensive frown.
THE_VOW_DVS589
From the other side of the glass, SOMEONE stares at him, then leaves the room.
THE_VOW_DVS590
Unnoticing, SOMEONE’s eyes remain on the instrument in his hands.
THE_VOW_DVS591
His wedding ring gleams on his finger as his left hand sets up cords on the fret board.
THE_VOW_DVS592
SOMEONE walks up to him with folded arms.
THE_VOW_DVS593
SOMEONE gives a tearful sympathetic nod.
THE_VOW_DVS594
SOMEONE stares off, tears welling in his deep set eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS595
He wipes one away, sets his guitar down and faces his friend.
THE_VOW_DVS596
With a knowing shake of his head, he leaves his sorrowful friend stunned.
THE_VOW_DVS597
Out in the night, a gliding view of Chicago’s streets and high rises presents a vast expanse of speckled lights.
THE_VOW_DVS598
In SOMEONE’s now cleaned out studio,
THE_VOW_DVS599
SOMEONE finishes packing a box.
THE_VOW_DVS600
A half dozen empty worktables fill the room.
THE_VOW_DVS601
SOMEONE closes the box and carries it out.
THE_VOW_DVS602
Passing a trio of tall gracefully curved sculptures.
THE_VOW_DVS603
Outside, SOMEONE loads the box on top of another in the back of his Wagoneer, then shuts the rear gate.
THE_VOW_DVS604
As he goes back inside,
THE_VOW_DVS605
a few pots of leggy dying flowers come into view.
THE_VOW_DVS606
The plank mounded with SOMEONE’s clay scraps sits discarded beside them.
THE_VOW_DVS607
Now the bean shaped  cloud gate in Millennium Park reflects an overcast day.
THE_VOW_DVS608
Inside a high-rise building,
THE_VOW_DVS609
a woman at a conference table slides legal documents to SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS610
Next to a notary’s embossed stamp, he locates SOMEONE’s signature on a line labeled Plaintiff.
THE_VOW_DVS611
Above a phrase reads, Joint Petition for Simplified Dissolution of Marriage.
THE_VOW_DVS612
SOMEONE glances at the lawyer and signs his name on a line marked Defendant.
THE_VOW_DVS613
He twists the pen shut, drops it and leaves the table.
THE_VOW_DVS614
Now shirtless on a cloudy day,
THE_VOW_DVS615
the broad chested young man takes the garbage out
THE_VOW_DVS616
and finds the stray cat perched on the trash bin.
THE_VOW_DVS617
Munching a slice of pizza, he offers some to the cat.
THE_VOW_DVS618
The feline shows no interest in the food, but lets SOMEONE pick him up.
THE_VOW_DVS619
The cat’s paws rest on SOMEONE’s shoulder, as he carries the animal inside.
THE_VOW_DVS620
Now SOMEONE spots SOMEONE at a market and quickly turns tail.
THE_VOW_DVS621
SOMEONE grins at the apprehensive woman.
THE_VOW_DVS622
SOMEONE's words sink in hard.
THE_VOW_DVS623
SOMEONE approaches.
THE_VOW_DVS624
She sees SOMEONE hurrying out the door.
THE_VOW_DVS625
With a reluctant look, she faces her sister and meets her gaze.
THE_VOW_DVS626
SOMEONE shrugs her hands.
THE_VOW_DVS627
SOMEONE nods.
THE_VOW_DVS628
SOMEONE rushes away.
THE_VOW_DVS629
Now SOMEONE finds her mother gardening in front of the house.
THE_VOW_DVS630
SOMEONE shoves down her bicycle.
THE_VOW_DVS631
Her mother bows her head.
THE_VOW_DVS632
Shaking her head, her mother lowers her tearful eyes.
THE_VOW_DVS633
Smiling, she wipes away tears.
THE_VOW_DVS634
SOMEONE’s eyes brim with tears.
THE_VOW_DVS635
SOMEONE slouches and shakes her head to herself.
THE_VOW_DVS636
She shrugs.
THE_VOW_DVS637
Glaring, she walks away.
THE_VOW_DVS638
Her mother remains kneeling before the autumn flowerbed.
THE_VOW_DVS639
Now in the city, a water taxi glides under a bridge.
THE_VOW_DVS640
SOMEONE and a young woman follow the sidewalk in front of his apartment building.
THE_VOW_DVS641
As they stroll into the alley, SOMEONE’s grin fades.
THE_VOW_DVS642
His ex-wife sits on a stoop with her head rested on her hands. She awkwardly gets to her feet.
THE_VOW_DVS643
Closing her eyes for a moment, SOMEONE winces.
THE_VOW_DVS644
SOMEONE watches his female friend leave, then faces SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS645
He steps closer.
THE_VOW_DVS646
SOMEONE glances aside.
THE_VOW_DVS647
She sits back down on the stoop.
THE_VOW_DVS648
SOMEONE takes a seat beside her.
THE_VOW_DVS649
SOMEONE studies him, her expression growing tender.
THE_VOW_DVS650
As SOMEONE regards her, she sucks in a breath and gazes off thoughtfully.
THE_VOW_DVS651
SOMEONE shakes her head and drops her face in her hands.
THE_VOW_DVS652
Folding them she stares off.
THE_VOW_DVS653
Meeting SOMEONE’s gaze, she shrugs.
THE_VOW_DVS654
He returns a gentle look and she considers him.
THE_VOW_DVS655
Now at North Western Law,
THE_VOW_DVS656
SOMEONE sits in a lecture classroom with her notebook open.
THE_VOW_DVS657
As the other students around her diligently take notes and type on laptops,
THE_VOW_DVS658
SOMEONE draws in her notebook,
THE_VOW_DVS659
making sketches that resemble the treelike sculptures in her former studio.
THE_VOW_DVS660
Later, at a water taxi stop on the river, she walks with SOMEONE up a flight of stairs.
THE_VOW_DVS661
SOMEONE glances away.
THE_VOW_DVS662
She gazes at him with an apologetic look.
THE_VOW_DVS663
He forces a smile.
THE_VOW_DVS664
As they head up to the street, she takes his arm in a friendly gesture.
THE_VOW_DVS665
Now SOMEONE sits on a bench on the law school’s quad and stares into the distance.
THE_VOW_DVS666
Her father approaches.
THE_VOW_DVS667
He takes a seat beside her.
THE_VOW_DVS668
SOMEONE’s smile fades.
THE_VOW_DVS669
He stands.
THE_VOW_DVS670
Her gaze flickers over him.
THE_VOW_DVS671
He eyes her lovingly and gives a faint smile.
THE_VOW_DVS673
Seen in slow motion, SOMEONE hugs him, her chin pressing firmly to his shoulder.
THE_VOW_DVS674
Now in the alley by the flowerpot garden, fall turns to winter. Snow veils SOMEONE’s clay scrap pile.
THE_VOW_DVS675
Now Page paints animals on a nursery wall.
THE_VOW_DVS676
Her pregnant sister smiles, watching.
THE_VOW_DVS677
The sisters admire the mural which shows a giraffe, an elephant, and a lion balancing atop round trees.
THE_VOW_DVS678
SOMEONE listens as a band records in his studio.
THE_VOW_DVS679
In a new apartment, SOMEONE ladles her parents’ soup.
THE_VOW_DVS680
The cat lies on SOMEONE’s stomach.
THE_VOW_DVS681
SOMEONE sculpts in her apartment.
THE_VOW_DVS682
Rifling through an unpacked box, SOMEONE finds the SOMEONE Mnemonic menu with her vows written on it. She reads.
THE_VOW_DVS683
A factory style window shows a nighttime view of a light snowfall and a car traveling the warmly lit street.
THE_VOW_DVS684
SOMEONE looks away thoughtfully.
THE_VOW_DVS685
Now SOMEONE holds his coat, closed around his neck as he walks past a row of snow dusted Christmas trees for sale.
THE_VOW_DVS686
Striding down a sidewalk with hunched shoulders,
THE_VOW_DVS687
he blows on his cupped hands.
THE_VOW_DVS688
As he reaches the entrance to SOMEONE Mnemonic,
THE_VOW_DVS689
he finds a note written on a menu taped to the glass.
THE_VOW_DVS690
It reads, snow day.
THE_VOW_DVS691
He gives a disappointed look.
THE_VOW_DVS692
Meanwhile SOMEONE heads toward the SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS693
Turning from the entrance SOMEONE starts to walk off, but spots SOMEONE approaching.
THE_VOW_DVS694
She stops and puts her hands in her coat pockets.
THE_VOW_DVS695
Grinning, she steps closer.
THE_VOW_DVS696
He gazes tenderly at her, then glances at the SOMEONE.
THE_VOW_DVS697
He stares at her radiant smile.
THE_VOW_DVS698
He smiles.
THE_VOW_DVS699
His eyes shine with tears.
THE_VOW_DVS700
She nods then lifts her eyes to the falling snow.
THE_VOW_DVS701
He follows her gaze skyward.
THE_VOW_DVS702
The corners of SOMEONE’s mouth tug into a smile.
THE_VOW_DVS703
She shakes her head.
THE_VOW_DVS704
Stifling a grin, he gives a satisfied nod.
THE_VOW_DVS705
They head down the sidewalk.
THE_VOW_DVS706
She takes his arm as they head down the snowy street in the opposite direction.
THE_VOW_DVS707
An L train glides overhead.
THE_VOW_DVS708
Our view widens to show the glittering city scape.