In an office building,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS27
A receptionist shows SOMEONE into a conference room, where three executives wait around a large table.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS28
The executives stare at him blankly.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS29
From his briefcase, he pulls out a coconut,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS30
a potted plant,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS31
and soy sauce.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS32
He holds up a labeled spray bottle.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS33
SOMEONE hangs his head and repacks his briefcase.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS34
At dinner,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS36
she fills up a bottle with tap water.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS37
Grimacing, SOMEONE sets down his water.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS38
It's 11:30 and SOMEONE, a chubby man with curly dark hair, lies awake in bed.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS39
He goes to his mother's room to find her fast asleep, with her reading glasses still on.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS40
The home movie's playing on the television.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS41
Beside her bed is a framed photo of her and SOMEONE.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS42
After watching for a moment, SOMEONE switches off the TV and removes a packet of M&Ms from his mother's bed before leaving the room.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS44
they both arrive at the Montclair Mature Singles Club,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS45
where middle-aged men and women are mingling with each other and engaging in conversation.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS47
SOMEONE's mom takes her name tag.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS49
SOMEONE sits at a table sipping a drink. She looks around at the other guests,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS50
thoroughly unimpressed.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS51
Nearby, an older woman winks and smiles in SOMEONE's direction.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS52
Realizing her advances are directed at him, he hurries away.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS53
Later, a series of men try to approach SOMEONE.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS54
SOMEONE sighs as he sits at the bar, watching his mother turn down one man after another, until they stop approaching her altogether.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS55
Later, SOMEONE and his mom eat ice cream at the dining room table.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS56
SOMEONE stares at his mom for a moment, then squeezes his eyes shut.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS57
SOMEONE sits motionless at the table.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS58
In his room, SOMEONE opens his laptop and types "J&R Advertising" into a Bing search engine.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS59
Using a phone number off of an East Coast Offices search result,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS60
he places a call.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS61
SOMEONE hangs up and furrows his brow.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS62
SOMEONE avoids meeting SOMEONE's eyes.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS63
SOMEONE flicks her eyes from side to side.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS64
SOMEONE nods repeatedly, his lips pursed.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS66
SOMEONE stumbles over their luggage.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS67
SOMEONE smirks.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS68
They're driving a tiny red car. SOMEONE reaches in the backseat.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS69
He inserts an audio CD.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS70
SOMEONE smiles warmly.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS71
She shrugs.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS72
SOMEONE's expression softens, then turns thoughtful again.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS73
SOMEONE fidgets with her purse, as she waits with SOMEONE in an office lobby.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS74
She takes a small hook out of her purse and hangs the bag on the table.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS75
SOMEONE licks a few fingers, and attempts to reach over and smooth SOMEONE's hair.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS76
SOMEONE regains his composure.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS77
SOMEONE takes out her phone and puts on her glasses.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS78
SOMEONE frowns and raises an eyebrow at his mother.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS79
He throws his hands up.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS80
SOMEONE peeks around a corner at SOMEONE.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS81
SOMEONE leaves the conference room, downcast, and sees SOMEONE eagerly waiting for him at the front desk.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS82
Back in the car, SOMEONE plays her audio book.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS83
SOMEONE leaves another meeting,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS84
and once again faces his mother.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS85
They make a U-turn.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS86
SOMEONE waits in the car, outside a McDonald's.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS87
Back on the road, at an oncoming intersection, SOMEONE spots a hitchhiker signaling for a lift.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS88
SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS90
SOMEONE steps up to the hotel's front desk.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS91
The receptionist winks at SOMEONE.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS92
They both settle into their twin beds and SOMEONE turns out the light.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS93
She then reaches for the bedside table and picks up a small packet.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS94
SOMEONE looks over at his mother.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS95
SOMEONE scowls and closes his eyes.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS96
The next morning, SOMEONE wakes up and stretches his arms.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS97
Squinting in the bright daylight streaming in through the windows,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS98
he looks over to see SOMEONE, dressed in a plum-colored robe,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS99
smiling at him from her bed, flipping through a magazine.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS100
SOMEONE blinks, then stares up at the ceiling.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS101
Back on the road, they resume listening to Middlesex.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS102
SOMEONE turns it off.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS103
That night, they drive through a blizzard, the windshield wipers working through a layer of snow.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS104
He checks the tires in a strip-club parking lot.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS105
SOMEONE sits with his head down, ignoring the pole dancers in the dimly lit strip club.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS106
SOMEONE grimaces.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS107
Moonlight picks at the ice with her shoe.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS108
At Jessica and her husband's house,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS109
as SOMEONE looks away, SOMEONE slowly glances over at him.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS110
SOMEONE and SOMEONE drive on a bridge over the Mississippi River.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS111
SOMEONE, his brow furrowed,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS112
peers at his mother and scoffs as he shakes his head.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS113
SOMEONE bites her lower lip.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS114
SOMEONE keeps his eyes fixed on the road.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS115
SOMEONE shrugs hesitantly.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS116
SOMEONE opens her mouth as if to say something else, but stops herself.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS117
With a resigned expression, she leans on her hand and looks out the window beside her.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS118
SOMEONE drives up to a wide building.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS119
Inside, there's a large, open-seating area.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS120
Uniformed Costco employees approach people seated at scattered tables.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS121
SOMEONE sits at one of them, going over his notes, and muttering quietly to himself.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS122
He sees his mother taking a look around as she approaches his table.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS123
SOMEONE scowls.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS124
SOMEONE jots something down in a notepad.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS125
People at the other tables turn to look and SOMEONE's face falls.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS126
SOMEONE looks sternly at her son, her glasses sitting low on her nose.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS127
He sulks and avoids her gaze, shaking his head slightly. Back in the car,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS128
SOMEONE purses his lips.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS129
SOMEONE grits his teeth, as he continues driving off into the sunset.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS130
Later that night, they pull into a motel parking lot.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS131
A pale-blue neon sign reads "Abilene Motor Lodge Lounge. "
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS132
In their room, SOMEONE emerges from the bathroom, holding up a few small bottles.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS133
She places the bottles in her open suitcase lying on her twin bed.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS134
Sulking, SOMEONE sips a dark-colored drink from a plastic glass.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS135
SOMEONE ignores her and gazes at the floor.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS136
He takes another sip.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS137
SOMEONE taps her fingertips together, looking around the room.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS138
She edges past SOMEONE, and places the water bottle on a table beside him, then backs away.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS139
He holds up a hand.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS140
He goes back to his drink.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS141
SOMEONE, lost for words, sits down at the foot of her bed.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS142
SOMEONE shakes her head in disappointment and her expression hardens.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS143
She gestures at SOMEONE.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS144
SOMEONE breathes heavily as he watches SOMEONE storm out of the room.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS145
Later, he sits on the hotel bed, blankly watching the weather forecast.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS146
The bed opposite his remains empty.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS147
After a while, he looks at his wristwatch, then steps out onto the balcony, and leans on the railing, looking down around the parking lot.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS148
He spots someone entering the motel lounge.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS149
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE in the face, causing SOMEONE to black out.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS151
The next day, SOMEONE and her son are back in the car and on the road.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS152
SOMEONE, sporting a large mottled bruise on his upper cheek,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS153
casts furtive glances at his mother.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS154
SOMEONE looks to the ceiling, bites her lip,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS155
then goes back to staring listlessly out the window.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS156
He looks at her with a half-smile.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS157
SOMEONE nods and smiles.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS158
SOMEONE looks off into the distance.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS159
After a moment, a small smile forms on SOMEONE's lips, and she nods slightly to herself.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS160
Then they both notice a billboard, along the highway for a steak ranch located off the next exit.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS161
It reads "Steak Your Claim. Claim Your Steak. "
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS162
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS163
In a Western-style restaurant,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS164
a waitress hands them glasses of water.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS165
SOMEONE watches her walk away.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS166
SOMEONE looks down at the table, with a slight frown.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS167
SOMEONE takes a deep breath and lays her menu down on the table.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS168
She smiles.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS169
SOMEONE starts to fidget.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS171
He hands her an enormous charred steak.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS172
SOMEONE applauds from the nearby bar. SOMEONE holds up her hands, overwhelmed.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS173
SOMEONE readies a napkin and picks the greens off her plate.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS174
She holds up a morsel on her fork, then pops it into her mouth.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS175
A timer on the mantelpiece behind SOMEONE ticks down.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS176
There's around a quarter of her steak remaining, as she stuffs a forkful of potato and a piece of bread into her mouth and struggles to chew.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS177
SOMEONE winces as she pauses to remove her jacket.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS178
She sees him and whispers.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS179
SOMEONE forks in another mouthful and flutters her hands anxiously.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS180
A man in a blazer walks along the bar, smiling as he watches SOMEONE eat.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS181
He blocks SOMEONE's view, who strains to look around him.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS182
SOMEONE lulls back in her chair.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS183
SOMEONE approaches the stage and pulls up a chair beside SOMEONE, who is focused on eating.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS185
Three minutes left,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS186
SOMEONE leans forward on the table and shovels in the last of the steak.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS187
Lastly, she reaches for the shrimp cocktail.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS188
She stands and raises the glass.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS190
She downs the cocktail sauce in one swig.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS191
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the crowd throw their hands in the air, beaming.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS192
SOMEONE pats SOMEONE's shoulder and she pulls her son in for a hug.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS193
Later, outside,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS194
SOMEONE grins in response.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS195
SOMEONE reaches into his jacket
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS196
and hands her a card.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS197
SOMEONE nods.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS198
He smiles gently.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS199
SOMEONE touches the tip of his hat and walks to his truck.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS200
SOMEONE inserts another CD.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS201
Outside a convenience store, SOMEONE enters the wrong car, with a handful of candy.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS202
She sees SOMEONE and hurries towards him.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS203
SOMEONE sleeps while SOMEONE drives.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS205
They drive through New Mexico.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS206
Later, they stand facing a massive expanse of ridged rocky outcrops and cliffs.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS207
Their expressions soon turned bored and inattentive.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS208
SOMEONE shrugs.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS209
Against an indigo sunset, their tiny car heads toward the neon city lights of Las Vegas.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS210
They take in the bright lights and glittering signs of the Las Vegas Strip.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS211
They arrive at Caesars Palace.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS212
SOMEONE walks away, smiling.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS213
SOMEONE looks for her.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS214
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE at a slot machine.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS215
Later, SOMEONE enters their hotel room, holding a half-finished drink.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS216
She carefully closes the door and tiptoes in.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS217
SOMEONE lies in bed as daylight shines through the windows.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS218
SOMEONE rubs his eyes.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS219
SOMEONE's face falls and she looks down.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS220
SOMEONE nods slowly and closes her eyes.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS221
She joins her hands together and rests them against her forehead.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS222
SOMEONE regards her son, then fetches her handbag from the hallway.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS223
SOMEONE watches her leave the room,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS224
then drops his head and sighs.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS225
Later, SOMEONE waits in the hotel's convention hall.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS226
Other participants are seated or milling around preparing for their presentations.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS227
A man with a clipboard approaches.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS228
SOMEONE purses his lips.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS229
He picks up his briefcase and follows the man through the partition doors.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS230
A woman tries to apply makeup to SOMEONE.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS231
Back at the now empty casino, SOMEONE sits at her slot machine.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS232
She takes off her glasses and pinches the bridge of her nose before smiling to herself.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS233
Then she quietly enters the side of the convention hall,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS234
where SOMEONE is continuing his presentation.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS235
SOMEONE sees one executive texting on her cell phone and another absently taking a drink of water.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS236
He chuckles to himself.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS237
The executives smile.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS238
SOMEONE grins proudly.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS239
SOMEONE pours some ScioClean into a glass, holds it up towards SOMEONE, and drinks it.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS241
The executives whisper to each other.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS242
SOMEONE raises her eyebrows.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS243
The executives chuckle.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS244
SOMEONE leaves with SOMEONE.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS245
They drive along the San Francisco Oakland Bay Bridge.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS246
SOMEONE widens her eyes.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS247
SOMEONE smiles, but SOMEONE just gapes at her phone.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS248
She puts on some lipstick.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS249
They drive through a suburban neighborhood with wide green front lawns and large shady trees.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS250
SOMEONE parks by the side of the road and rolls down his window.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS251
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS252
A man in his thirties opens the door.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS253
Realization dawns on SOMEONE's face.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS254
SOMEONE's expression freezes and she looks to the floor.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS255
She turns aside and SOMEONE places a hand on her shoulder.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS256
SOMEONE furrows his brow.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS257
SOMEONE and her son glance at one another, smiling.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS258
Outside, SOMEONE holds on to her son's arm, as they cross the street and head toward their car.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS259
SOMEONE holds the door open for her and she gets in.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS260
SOMEONE rests her head back in the seat, as a warm grin forms on her face.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS261
She pulls SOMEONE close and kisses him.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS262
They both share a smile before driving off.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS263
Listening to SOMEONE's audio book, they arrive at the airport car rental and steer into the return lane.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS264
SOMEONE rolls down the window.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS265
He presses Play.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS266
SOMEONE and SOMEONE listen intently.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS267
Inside the airport, they walk up to the digital departure board.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS268
SOMEONE nods.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS269
SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE, holding on to him tightly.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS270
She kisses him on the cheek and smiles to herself, holding back tears.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS271
She finally lets go and holds him at arm's length.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS272
She holds a finger up to her face, as if just remembering something.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS273
SOMEONE smiles again, genuinely touched by SOMEONE's declaration.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS274
SOMEONE touches a finger to her lips and waves goodbye to SOMEONE.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS275
As he watches her walk away, she takes out her cell phone from her purse and dials a number.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS276
SOMEONE takes out his cell phone and stares at it, waiting.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS277
He looks from his mother to his phone and shrugs with a wry smile.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS278
SOMEONE picks up his briefcase and walks off into the bustling crowd.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS279
The end credits start to roll over the scene, as a man pushes his mother on a wheelchair, and a teenager offers his mom a sip from his juice box.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS280
Nearby, a middle-aged man talks to his mother over the phone.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS281
And a boy runs before his mom, guiding her as they both haul their luggage.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS282
A young boy sleeps, resting on a woman's shoulder. And a security guard guides another child to his mother,
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS283
who kneels on the floor to hug him.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS284
The scene fades to black and credits continue to scroll.
THE_GUILT_TRIP_DVS285
Various clips of SOMEONE and SOMEONE driving in their car appear beside the credits.