TV and watches James Franco on General Hospital.
THE_SITTER_DVS7
She blows him a kiss and pats his cheeks.
THE_SITTER_DVS8
She tilts her head staring meaningfully at SOMEONE.
THE_SITTER_DVS9
She lifts her brows.
THE_SITTER_DVS10
SOMEONE shakes his head.
THE_SITTER_DVS11
SOMEONE's mother sighs and heads up.
THE_SITTER_DVS12
Now he rings a doorbell outside.
THE_SITTER_DVS13
An elegant buxom brunette answers the door with a warm smile.
THE_SITTER_DVS14
Adolescent boy watches male gymnastics.
THE_SITTER_DVS15
In sunglasses the boy ignores.
THE_SITTER_DVS16
Answering a phone, she steps away.
THE_SITTER_DVS17
Upstairs the TV shows an
THE_SITTER_DVS18
She hides perfume behind her back.
THE_SITTER_DVS19
He points at SOMEONE as he goes.
THE_SITTER_DVS20
Facing it a boy plays with a sparkler.
THE_SITTER_DVS21
SOMEONE back upstairs. SOMEONE in pajamas Rodrigo lights another sparkler, leans back in his chair and watches it burn.
THE_SITTER_DVS23
The parents leave.
THE_SITTER_DVS25
Walks by a collection of liquors in decanters and stares at his baby sitter.
THE_SITTER_DVS26
He sweeps a folded
THE_SITTER_DVS27
Wearing cowboy boots, the boy walks over the mess.
THE_SITTER_DVS28
SOMEONE opens the door to a pair of redheaded twins.
THE_SITTER_DVS29
Holds his hand a foot apart.
THE_SITTER_DVS30
SOMEONE answers his cell.
THE_SITTER_DVS31
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE. Rodrigo's eyes widen.
THE_SITTER_DVS32
She sticks out her tongue.
THE_SITTER_DVS33
SOMEONE glances back.
THE_SITTER_DVS34
He turns to SOMEONE.
THE_SITTER_DVS35
On the GPS, a pulsing icon marks a location on a map.
THE_SITTER_DVS36
Approaches the Maitre d's post at an upscale restaurant.
THE_SITTER_DVS37
SOMEONE enters,
THE_SITTER_DVS38
He gets off the van and then heads to an alley way.
THE_SITTER_DVS39
Strapless T and short cut-offs, the
THE_SITTER_DVS40
He gazes into SOMEONE's eyes.
THE_SITTER_DVS41
They sit on white couches.
THE_SITTER_DVS42
He offers cocaine,
THE_SITTER_DVS43
spreads his arms.
THE_SITTER_DVS44
SOMEONE steps into SOMEONE's embrace.
THE_SITTER_DVS45
SOMEONE eyes it.
THE_SITTER_DVS46
He turns to the slick haired boy.
THE_SITTER_DVS47
Cocaine powder covers SOMEONE's face from the nose up.
THE_SITTER_DVS48
He blinks his enraged eyes.
THE_SITTER_DVS49
As the kids gawk at him, SOMEONE reaches into his pocket and takes out his cell. He checks its display, then answers with an uneasy look.
THE_SITTER_DVS50
He hangs up.
THE_SITTER_DVS51
SOMEONE looks up.
THE_SITTER_DVS52
SOMEONE winks, then approaches Rodrigo
THE_SITTER_DVS53
Casual look. SOMEONE strolls
THE_SITTER_DVS54
parts and pockets them. As he searches for more the server approaches.
THE_SITTER_DVS55
Sees Rodrigo peeing on the dance floor.
THE_SITTER_DVS56
Then she strides of leaving SOMEONE with SOMEONE.
THE_SITTER_DVS57
SOMEONE heads off.
THE_SITTER_DVS58
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE.
THE_SITTER_DVS59
As SOMEONE trudges off the valet approaches SOMEONE.
THE_SITTER_DVS60
The valet sobs.
THE_SITTER_DVS61
Now in a subway station, Rodrigo sighs. Farther down the platform SOMEONE counts money from the bar mitzvah cards.
THE_SITTER_DVS62
He smacks a pillar.
THE_SITTER_DVS63
Appears down the tracks.
THE_SITTER_DVS66
They approach a fishmonger.
THE_SITTER_DVS67
gives him a hug.
THE_SITTER_DVS68
Releases SOMEONE's cheeks.
THE_SITTER_DVS69
Woman answers the front door.
THE_SITTER_DVS70
In his study, SOMEONE's father paints a figurine.
THE_SITTER_DVS71
SOMEONE stands across the room.
THE_SITTER_DVS72
He crouches to his younger son.
THE_SITTER_DVS73
The bespectacled man faces his older son.
THE_SITTER_DVS74
He offers his hand. SOMEONE shakes it, then pulls him in for a hug.
THE_SITTER_DVS75
SOMEONE walks away.
THE_SITTER_DVS76
On his way out, SOMEONE stops short.
THE_SITTER_DVS77
A keychain of a hook.
THE_SITTER_DVS78
SOMEONE looks at a framed photo of his father, SOMEONE, and their young son, then punches in another four-digit code, followed by the pound key.
THE_SITTER_DVS79
The young man turns away from the alarm box.
THE_SITTER_DVS80
Biting his lip, SOMEONE nods.
THE_SITTER_DVS81
SOMEONE follows him back into the showroom.
THE_SITTER_DVS82
SOMEONE's view whirls to the bathroom, as the pajama-clad
THE_SITTER_DVS83
the car and runs away.
THE_SITTER_DVS84
SOMEONE runs to a railing and frantically peers over the edge.
THE_SITTER_DVS85
SOMEONE sits on a low wall. SOMEONE glances aside.
THE_SITTER_DVS86
SOMEONE takes a seat beside the boy.
THE_SITTER_DVS87
The boy gets up.
THE_SITTER_DVS88
They head back to the car.
THE_SITTER_DVS89
SOMEONE takes out the GPS.
THE_SITTER_DVS90
They get back in the Mercedes and peel out.
THE_SITTER_DVS91
Later, the silver sedan follows the minivan down.
THE_SITTER_DVS92
Vehicles round the corner, they briefly move in fast motion. SOMEONE blinks.
THE_SITTER_DVS93
the image jumps, the blurs.
THE_SITTER_DVS94
From an alley and creeps alongside a brick building. Up ahead SOMEONE's former schoolmate steps out of the minivan with a group of guys.
THE_SITTER_DVS95
She trades a look with her
THE_SITTER_DVS96
SOMEONE kneels at his side.
THE_SITTER_DVS97
Rolls over and drops the keys in his palms.
THE_SITTER_DVS98
SOMEONE mimes.
THE_SITTER_DVS99
The goateed man returns to his table.
THE_SITTER_DVS100
SOMEONE averts her bashful gaze.
THE_SITTER_DVS101
Picks out her cellphone and hands it to him.
THE_SITTER_DVS102
She heads off.
THE_SITTER_DVS103
the minivan parks along a curved
THE_SITTER_DVS104
Two officers approach.
THE_SITTER_DVS105
They Find the cocaine.
THE_SITTER_DVS106
SOMEONE unfolds a wanted poster.
THE_SITTER_DVS107
SOMEONE spots the name Huron on a street sign. He takes out a scrap of paper and reads an address. 37 Huron Street.
THE_SITTER_DVS108
drifts down a four-story apartment.
THE_SITTER_DVS109
Now SOMEONE stops Rodrigo.
THE_SITTER_DVS110
Clasps his middle finger down.
THE_SITTER_DVS111
Liquored boy sits on the steps.
THE_SITTER_DVS112
She walks away.
THE_SITTER_DVS113
Throws then waits for his reaction.
THE_SITTER_DVS114
He throws another punch, but Ricky blocks it and flips him on
THE_SITTER_DVS115
air and lands on its side in a
THE_SITTER_DVS116
van crashes into a sign for a carousel.
THE_SITTER_DVS117
SOMEONE holds a gun to SOMEONE's
THE_SITTER_DVS119
Parked. SOMEONE reaches a locked chain linked fence. She glances around, then kicks the chain link finding a section disconnected from
THE_SITTER_DVS121
Back on the street.
THE_SITTER_DVS122
SOMEONE approaches.
THE_SITTER_DVS123
Bucket off the ground.
THE_SITTER_DVS124
Holds it out in front of himself.
THE_SITTER_DVS125
Swings the bucket.
THE_SITTER_DVS126
Smoking crotch as he races.
THE_SITTER_DVS128
She wakes up and glances outside, avoiding SOMEONE's gaze.
THE_SITTER_DVS129
She averts her eyes as he watches her.
THE_SITTER_DVS130
She shakes her head.
THE_SITTER_DVS131
She turns to him tearfully and he nods. He gives her a kind look.
THE_SITTER_DVS132
She shifts her lips thoughtfully, then climbs out of the minivan. As SOMEONE watches her head up to the house
THE_SITTER_DVS133
unbuckles her seatbelt and climbs into the seat beside him.
THE_SITTER_DVS134
He pulls down SOMEONE's visor.
THE_SITTER_DVS135
She looks in the mirror.
THE_SITTER_DVS136
Shrugging a sad smile, she averts her gaze. He hands her some tissues.
THE_SITTER_DVS137
With a sheepish grin she takes the tissues and wipes her cheeks.
THE_SITTER_DVS138
SOMEONE blinks her thoughtful eyes. As SOMEONE pushes visor back up, SOMEONE stirs.
THE_SITTER_DVS140
They turn to him.
THE_SITTER_DVS141
They jump on the couch and turn on the TV.
THE_SITTER_DVS142
As she follows the kids upstairs, SOMEONE heads to the door.
THE_SITTER_DVS143
He hands SOMEONE a folded SOMEONE.
THE_SITTER_DVS144
He points at the doctor.
THE_SITTER_DVS145
He gets in his face as he heads out the door.
THE_SITTER_DVS146
Dr. SOMEONE glares as SOMEONE descends the steps.
THE_SITTER_DVS147
SOMEONE grabs his bike at the bottom and sets it upright.
THE_SITTER_DVS148
As he wheels it away, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and Rodrigo
THE_SITTER_DVS150
SOMEONE pulls up in the Mercedes. Letting his bike drop SOMEONE waves at the kids, then strides to the car.
THE_SITTER_DVS151
She holds the GPS.
THE_SITTER_DVS152
He takes out his cell.
THE_SITTER_DVS153
She looks away.
THE_SITTER_DVS154
He eyes the phone.
THE_SITTER_DVS155
He opens side door for her.
THE_SITTER_DVS156
As they walk side by side down the street, he gazes at SOMEONE.