Now, in reality.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS52
The rugged man descends courthouse stairs and encounters several journalists.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS53
They follow outside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS54
He walks off in the rain.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS55
Later he enters a coffee shop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS56
He takes a seat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS57
Dawning glasses he peruses a file as the news broadcasts behind him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS58
He whirls around to watch Wennerstrom's statement.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS59
The barista sets the items on the counter. Later SOMEONE stands outside in the shelter of the coffee shops entryway.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS60
He opens the Marlboros, puts one between his lips and throws the rest of the pack away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS61
SOMEONE lights the cigarette, then takes a deep satisfied drag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS64
The journalist runs across the street to a building. A sign near its entrance reads Millennium.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS65
Inside, he arrives at a suite door bearing the same title.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS66
As he enters, a staff of employees halt and face him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS67
He shrugs his brow grimly and goes upstairs to an office. Inside, a lovely blonde in her 40s steps away from her desk and regards him sympathetically.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS68
A staffer arrives, but the woman sends him away with a gesture.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS69
As SOMEONE steps further in, she shuts the door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS70
SOMEONE meets her gaze and his expression softens wearily.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS71
His colleague steps close and intimately nuzzles her forehead against his.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS72
Now a bespectacled old man waits in a conference room with a stylish businessman.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS73
Outside, a woman wearing a helmet arrives on a motorcycle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS74
Sporting a Mohawk, she rides an elevator.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS75
Spikes with spiraled ends impale her earlobes. Using keycards she passes purposefully through a series of doors.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS76
She hesitates seeing the two men in the glass walled room. She sports eyebrow, nose, and lip rings amid her delicate features. Her boss waves her in.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS77
Both men stand. Dressed in black with a matching leather jacket she enters avoiding their gaze and takes a seat at the far end of the conference table.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS78
She sits hunched, turned slightly away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS79
She faces SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS80
She turns away, giving him a full view of her black spikey Mohawk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS81
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE who wearily meets his gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS82
She stares through darkly lined eyes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS83
Now, in a working class high-rise she dumps packaged noodles into a bowl.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS84
A cigarette dangles from her lips. As she runs the bowl under a tap.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS85
She thrusts it into a microwave oven,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS86
then takes a can of coke from her fridge.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS87
Heading into the next room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS88
SOMEONE sits facing a laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS89
She goes to a Vanger Industries page profiling SOMEONE, then hacks into SOMEONE's email account.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS90
As SOMEONE goes back to the kitchen, a new email pops up.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS91
We glimpse its content.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS92
Dear Mr. SOMEONE, Are you available for an interview regarding the Wennerstrom verdict?
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS93
Returning with her steaming noodles, SOMEONE runs a Google search on Wennerstrom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS94
It leads her to a Wikipedia page. SOMEONE Googles Wennerstrom + Vanger Industries.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS95
A webpage mentions his previous work in the financial division.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS96
Now, at a Christmas gathering, SOMEONE faces his lover, her husband and a brunette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS97
SOMEONE notices a teen with dark hair watching him. He joins her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS98
SOMEONE takes an uneasy breath and sips red wine.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS100
Now, in a coat and knit hat, SOMEONE lights a cigarette as she walks down a sidewalk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS101
She pauses within earshot of a building entrance.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS102
Listening as a richly dressed older woman punches in an entry code.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS103
As the woman goes in, SOMEONE loiters briefly.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS104
The ends of her black hair stick out from under her hat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS105
Framing her jaw and chin.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS106
SOMEONE goes to the keypad, enters the code, and goes inside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS108
She pauses, looking around, then climbs a marble staircase to a posted directory.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS109
As the steps away we find Wennerstrom listed on the sixth level.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS110
Now, SOMEONE enters a basement area with rough stonewalls.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS111
She comes to the building's electrical center and photographs the circuit boxes, meters, and wiring.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS113
she takes a photo of an Ethernet hub.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS115
she steps back out onto the sidewalk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS116
She turns abruptly as a car pulls up.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS117
Looking over her shoulder, she spies Wennerstrom getting out.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS118
As he takes out a cellphone, SOMEONE continues down the sidewalk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS119
At the gathering, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE and her mother at a table.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS120
SOMEONE checks her cell phone then puts it down.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS121
Throughout the party, other guests do the same.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS122
SOMEONE checks his own phone then answers it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS123
Now, sleeping beneath a white comforter, SOMEONE's co-editor awakes alone in bed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS124
She lifts her head then gets up.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS125
Revealing an oversized shirt with a hem just below her hips.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS126
She finds SOMEONE at a laptop in the next room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS127
Sitting in his briefs, SOMEONE turns to face her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS128
She steps away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS129
SOMEONE slams his computer shut.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS130
Now in a blizzard, a train travels a mountainous snow dusted landscape.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS131
In a passenger car set with small tables, SOMEONE sits opposite two strangers. His gaze pensive.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS132
He rolls his head against his seatback.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS133
Watching trees pass the window.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS135
the train stops at a platform marked, SOMEONE disembarks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS138
Shivering, he walks to the edge of the platform.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS139
Waiting beside a nearby car, SOMEONE waves.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS141
Now, on a narrow snow smeared road, the car approaches a bridge with rainbow-shaped arches barely wide enough for two cars.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS142
The snow picks up again as the car turns down a road bordered with tall skeletal trees.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS143
As SOMEONE drives the journalist over the grounds of an estate.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS144
The blizzard drives a heavy snowfall almost sideways.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS145
SOMEONE leans forward peering through the windshield with narrowed eyes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS147
In the distance, twin lights barely pierce the storm on either side of the road.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS148
The car passes through a gate set with glowing lamps.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS149
Then approaches a sprawling elegant manor house with a circular driveway.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS150
As it pulls up next to a utilitarian pickup with a covered bed,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS151
the distinguished figure of SOMEONE Vanger comes outside to greet them.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS152
SOMEONE takes them into a cozy study and gestures SOMEONE to a leather armchair.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS153
The journalist sits facing his host.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS154
With a friendly pat, SOMEONE dismisses SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS155
Now, a heavyset techie in a Nine Inch Nails shirt lets SOMEONE into his apartment.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS156
She hands him some money and he examines it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS157
She holds out her hand to take it back but he instead gives her an electronic device with a screen, antenna, and attached wire.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS158
SOMEONE glances at the heavyset techie, then walks out the door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS159
She eyes him and shuts the door. A flashback shows a young woman on the beach.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS160
SOMEONE studies a photo.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS162
SOMEONE removes a school photo from an album.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS163
SOMEONE stares at the photo.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS164
In a flashback, children play outside the house.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS165
A young blonde woman follows Harriet upstairs.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS166
Outside, most of the adults all look in the same direction.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS167
A two-vehicle pileup blocks the island bridge.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS168
Fuel leaks from a tank.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS169
A maid sees Harriet step outside. Young SOMEONE sits the bloody driver back.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS170
Young SOMEONE puts on a prep school blazer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS171
The tycoon and journalist sip their drinks. Later, they walk a hall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS172
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE upstairs.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS173
They enter an attic.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS174
He switches on a shadeless lamp then gestures to a wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS175
SOMEONE views more than a dozen pressed and framed wildflowers, mounted meticulously on a wall in a tidy grid.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS176
A second grid of the artwork covers another wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS177
And several unmounted frames lean on the wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS178
SOMEONE returns his gaze to the wildflowers.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS179
A train leaves Hedestad station where a clock reads 4:30.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS180
Later, at dinner with SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS181
SOMEONE pours wine.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS182
He sips his wine. SOMEONE's jaw hangs slack.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS183
Now, pedestrians cross paths outside SOMEONE's apartment building.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS184
In the rough stone basement,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS185
holding a flashlight between her teeth,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS186
SOMEONE sets her handheld device on top of an electrical box.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS187
Then connects its wire to a circuit.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS188
She takes the flashlight out of her mouth and flips a switch. Then shoulders her bag and heads out.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS190
At the Millennium offices, SOMEONE's co-editor enters with a cup of coffee.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS191
She finds SOMEONE at his desk packing supplies.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS192
He meets her disapproving gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS193
He steps around her and she sets down her bag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS194
SOMEONE shoulders his bag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS195
He steps near to kiss her but she looks away. He kisses her cheek instead.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS196
He walks out the door. She watches him go with a disappointed gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS197
Now, at a coffee shop SOMEONE sits alone at a counter with a book decorated with a bow.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS198
SOMEONE Fischer: My 60 Memorable Games.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS199
She peels off a price tag, then checks her cell phone.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS200
She sets it down and glances around.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS201
Now, she marches across a street to a five-story brick facade with bay windows shaped like prisms.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS202
Inside, she approaches an apartment door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS203
She leans towards the door and listens.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS204
She opens the door and steps inside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS205
She walks deeper into the apartment and looks around. Then drops her bag,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS206
rushes to an elderly man on the floor and checks his pulse. She hurries out of the room as he remains motionless on his side.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS207
Now, at the Hedestad station, a thermometer nears negative 20 degrees Celsius.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS208
SOMEONE exits a train with his bags and reacts to the cold.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS209
He steps away from the train and waves to a driver waiting outside a taxi.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS210
Later, the taxi drives over the multispan rainbow arch bridge from the mainland to the island.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS211
At the guest cottage, SOMEONE pays the driver then slips on an icy stoop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS212
The driver gets back in his taxi.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS213
As he carries his luggage inside, The driver pulls out.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS214
Driving up a one-lane road made visible by two tire tracks in the snow,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS215
the taxi passes SOMEONE's house.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS216
Inside, as SOMEONE tries to make a call on his cell phone,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS217
he scans a toilet, tub, and table in a bathroom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS218
Attempting another call, he crosses to a bedroom where pillows and folded towels lie stacked at the foot of the bed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS219
SOMEONE looks over his shoulder then crosses to a window where a Tabby waits on the sill in the cold.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS220
He lets the cat inside and it jumps down to the floor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS221
He steps past the cat and opens a refrigerator but finds it empty.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS222
He shuts the fridge and shares a look with the hungry cat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS224
SOMEONE walks away from the cottage. Holding his cell phone at arm's length.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS225
He drops the phone to his side.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS227
Now, at a grocery store, SOMEONE adds two cans of cat food to his purchase.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS228
Later, he steps out front with a grocery bag and a cigarette hanging from his mouth.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS229
He attempts to make another call on his cell phone.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS230
At the cottage, while the cat eats, SOMEONE sits by a fireplace huddled in a blanket.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS231
He tears pages from a book and throws them in a meager fire.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS232
The frustrated man looks at the book's cover then tosses it on a few others.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS235
At a hospital SOMEONE sits on a hallway floor with her knees to her chest.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS236
A doctor enters and she rises to her feet.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS237
Now, she watches SOMEONE through a window.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS238
Riding a train, SOMEONE peers out a window.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS239
Morning on SOMEONE's island.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS240
A balding man tows a cart to the cottage. SOMEONE sleeps in bed beside the cat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS241
The cat sits up, SOMEONE stirs, wrapped in a few blankets.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS242
He sits up and looks at his watch on a nightstand.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS243
Wrapping himself in one of the blankets he pulls it out from under the cat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS244
SOMEONE opens the front door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS245
Gunnar grabs one of many file boxes from his cart then steps inside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS246
SOMEONE quickly shuts the door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS247
Later, as Gunnar works on the fireplace, SOMEONE brings him coffee.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS248
He puts on glasses and crouches over the files.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS249
Gunnar lights a fire.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS250
SOMEONE frowns to himself.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS251
Gunnar raises his mug.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS252
Now, outside SOMEONE's mansion.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS253
Under falling snow they cross the front yard.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS254
SOMEONE takes notes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS255
A tiny house in the distance.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS256
SOMEONE stares across the property.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS257
SOMEONE glances at his white mansion.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS258
Now in the cottage, SOMEONE crosses the living room to a family tree he's created on a wall, and attaches current photos of SOMEONE and SOMEONE besides various sticky notes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS259
He crosses to a map on another wall
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS260
and attaches sticky notes indicating the homes of the other Vanger residents.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS261
Studying the map he deflates.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS262
Later, sitting at a table SOMEONE studies a file.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS263
He picks up a marker and highlights a line on SOMEONE's notes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS264
Officer SOMEONE informed by telephone of situation.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS268
a young Officer SOMEONE rides a patrol boat passing under the commotion on the bridge.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS269
The patrol boat cruises along the coast.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS270
SOMEONE highlights another line.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS271
Officer SOMEONE traveled to site in patrol boat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS273
SOMEONE meets with the family members who gather in a sitting room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS274
SOMEONE gestures to SOMEONE. We glimpse the words the mother was inebriated. SOMEONE highlights another line.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS275
SOMEONE inspected missing girl's bedroom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS276
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE into the room where the officer opens a purse.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS278
Personal belongings including comb,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS279
pocket mirror, a handkerchief, wallet, and address book.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS280
SOMEONE flips through a datebook.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS281
SOMEONE notices the young blonde woman gazing at him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS283
SOMEONE began interviews with the Vanger family members. Sitting with the family the officer jots notes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS284
SOMEONE meets SOMEONE's concerned gaze. SOMEONE rises from his chair.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS288
As the boats sale around the island our roving view finds SOMEONE on the shore.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS291
Led by dogs a search party comes afforest.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS292
Two men search a dilapidated house.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS293
In the forest, a man inspects a rusted bin.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS294
The search party members leave the rundown house behind.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS295
The young officer lights a cigarette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS296
In the present, in SOMEONE's living room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS297
He takes out of the datebook and slides it toward the older man.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS298
SOMEONE leans toward the datebook.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS299
He slides it back to his visitor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS300
SOMEONE gets up and grabs their mugs.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS301
He heads for the kitchen.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS302
Riding a train, SOMEONE pages to the list in Harriet's book.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS303
Now in an office with SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS304
A bearded man reads paperwork.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS305
From her seat across his desk, SOMEONE shoots the portly bearded man a weary look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS306
He glances haughtily at the heavily pierced woman as he reviews her file.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS307
Avoiding his gaze, SOMEONE clenches her jaw.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS308
He folds his hands.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS309
He consults her file.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS310
She stares off.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS311
Lowering her steely eyes, SOMEONE sucks in a breath.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS312
Under her new guardian's menacing gaze she works her lips, struggling to remain composed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS313
Now, SOMEONE hurries out of the office and steps into an elevator. As the door slides shut a view through its window shows her enraged face.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS314
In Hedestad a Volvo stops beside SOMEONE as he trudges up a hill.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS315
Now the car glides up a long driveway to a sleek glass-walled home.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS316
A middle-aged man with thinning hair steps outside and smiles.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS317
They cross the chic and minimalist home.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS318
After dinner.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS319
He and SOMEONE glance around.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS321
SOMEONE refills his guest's glass then disappears down a hallway off the dining area.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS322
She eyes him thoughtfully.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS323
He averts his gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS324
SOMEONE heads back to them.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS325
He pours more wine.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS326
SOMEONE looks away thoughtfully. SOMEONE sits.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS327
SOMEONE rubs his shoulder.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS328
He broods.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS329
SOMEONE nods.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS330
He, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE clink wine glasses. Their reflections visible in the pristine full-length windows.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS331
Now, at SOMEONE's.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS332
A caretaker removes a tray from the table in front of the blank faced man.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS333
Sitting diagonally beside her former guardian, SOMEONE wipes drool from his mouth with her sleeve.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS334
As she watches him, SOMEONE's absent stare remains ahead.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS335
The young woman looks away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS336
Later, she rides an escalator down into a subway station. A train glides up.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS337
As she approaches the platform a guy snatches her backpack off her shoulder.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS338
She sees him racing to the escalator.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS340
As he rides up, SOMEONE sprints after him and grabs her bag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS341
She and the thief tug it back and forth
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS342
fighting for control, and she punches him in the face.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS343
He falls to the escalator's gliding steps.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS344
Grabbing him by the lapels she leans over him, her face contorted with rage.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS345
The thief grabs the bag again and she kicks him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS346
As he reaches for her she rolls onto the inclined metal barrier between the ascending and descending escalators.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS347
Letting her pack slide down the ramp she jumps onto the descending escalator.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS348
At the bottom she grabs the bag and races on to a train.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS349
Its doors close behind her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS351
SOMEONE finds a blonde with aristocratic features at his door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS352
He stares.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS353
She steps into the cottage and he closes the door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS354
Her gaze fixes on the family tree in the living room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS355
SOMEONE watches as she moves closer, her shrewd eyes scanning the photos and facts on each family member.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS356
She heads off.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS357
SOMEONE watches her leave then gives a frustrated look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS358
Now, SSOMEONE's laptop sits on a tech support counter.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS359
Its shattered screen shows a blinking question SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS360
She takes the computer back.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS361
Now, an office building's windows glow below a darkening sky.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS362
Inside, SOMEONE passes a janitor waxing the floor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS363
She strides through a vacant reception area.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS364
She peers into an office.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS365
Sitting across from her new guardian, she gives an affronted look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS366
A picture of the guardian's family rests on his desk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS367
He rises and moves to the front of his desk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS368
As he sits on the edge facing her, SOMEONE anxiously shifts in her seat and avoids looking at him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS369
As he stares down at her she continues to avoid his gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS370
He reaches toward her backpack, which sits in her lap.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS371
As she withdraws her hands from it
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS372
he lifts the bag away and then lets it drop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS373
SOMEONE flinches as it hits the floor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS374
Under his intent gaze, SOMEONE clenches her jaw.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS375
Her guardian holds out his hand.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS376
Her resigned eyes remain averted as she places her hand in his.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS377
He strokes the top of it with his thumb,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS378
then pulls her closer and sets her hand against his crotch.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS379
He makes her rub him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS380
He stares down at her, his expression hardening.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS381
As he moves her hand against the front of his pants,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS382
his lips twitch in a sadistic frown.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS383
SOMEONE straightens in her chair her gaze still averted, and lowers his zipper.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS384
He rolls his exasperated eyes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS385
She shoots him a repulsed look then reaches into his pants.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS386
His lips part in an ecstatic expression.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS387
Trembling slightly he gently cups a hand to her check.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS388
She juts out her chin.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS389
His fingers wrap around the back of her head
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS390
clutching it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS391
And he forces her to bend forward putting her face in his lap.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS392
Her shoulders and head SOMEONE
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS393
as she performs fellatio on him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS394
He closes his eyes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS395
He leans his head back.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS396
Now, in a bathroom, SOMEONE rinses her mouth out at a sink.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS397
Bending over a toilet she shoves a finger down her throat then vomits.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS398
She wipes her mouth as she exits into her guardian's office.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS399
He gives her a friendly smile then moves out from behind his desk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS400
Holding a check in one hand
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS401
he picks up her bag and hands it to her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS402
She slings it over her shoulder then takes the check.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS404
On her way out the janitor waxing the floor glances at her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS405
Later seen from behind.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS406
She sits cross-legged by a space heater on her apartment floor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS407
A close drifting bird's eye view passes over her head.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS408
She smokes a cigarette and listens to ear buds.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS409
As the view descends, showing her upside down, she stares vacantly.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS410
Now on a plane, a flight attendant serves SOMEONE then continues down the aisle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS411
The rugged writer glances out his window at the bright sky,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS412
then empties two nips of liquor into a plastic cup.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS413
Later, in London, a cab pulls to a curb and SOMEONE climbs out.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS414
He spritzes his mouth with breath freshener as he strides across the street to a stately stone building.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS416
he heads down a marble corridor bustling with business people and stops at a reception desk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS417
In an office he finds an elegant blonde woman at a desk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS419
They’re in a cafe.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS420
She gives an unnerved look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS421
SOMEONE gazes off.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS422
She shrugs her lips.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS423
She sips from her coffee cup.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS424
Now with SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS425
She walks outside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS426
SOMEONE's pierced lip curls aggressively as she listens. She ends the call and marches down a bustling sidewalk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS427
At dusk SOMEONE takes a drag off a cigarette as she arrives outside an apartment building.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS428
She mounts the front stoop
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS429
She eyes a directory and punches a code into an intercom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS430
She enters and climbs a stairwell that wraps an old-fashioned wrought iron elevator shaft.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS432
On a landing SOMEONE opens a door and steps into the hall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS433
Clutching the strap of her shoulder bag in her fists
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS434
she enters a tastefully decorated apartment.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS435
SOMEONE shuts the door and positions himself in front of it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS436
He smiles. SOMEONE lowers her gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS437
SOMEONE starts to move past his ward then stops in front of her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS438
SOMEONE avoids his gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS439
Proceeding past her he leads her down a hallway.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS440
He ushers her through a doorway.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS441
It leads to a room with a bed set against the far wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS442
SOMEONE sets her bag in a chair facing it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS444
She removes her jacket. SOMEONE starts to take it from her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS445
She goes to the bed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS446
SOMEONE steps closer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS447
Perched on the bed's footboard, SOMEONE avoids his gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS448
SOMEONE takes her hand.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS449
He slaps handcuffs on her wrist.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS451
Looking up, SOMEONE bolts for the door. Her hand bumps it shut as SOMEONE drags her back.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS453
We drift back down the hall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS454
In the bedroom a mirror reflects Berman wrestling SOMEONE to the floor in a chokehold. Her flailing leg kicks a chair.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS456
We drift further down the hall, our gaze locked on the door. Fade to black.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS457
Now, SOMEONE wakes face down on the bed with a thick black gag separating her upper and lower teeth.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS458
Her widely spread arms are chained to the headboard.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS459
Looking over her shoulder, she finds SOMEONE chaining her ankles to the footboard.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS460
SOMEONE wrenches against her bonds but they give no sign of budging.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS461
As SOMEONE moves up beside her she flails and kicks desperately. The welfare guardian grabs SOMEONE by the waistband and yanks her hips up off the mattress. Jamming a pillow under her hips, he drops her upon it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS462
SOMEONE lifts the back of her shirt over her head and lets it fall under her chin.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS465
Kneeling beside her, he pulls her pants down around her ankles. He twists a fist into the fabric of her black panties and rips them off.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS466
SOMEONE now lies fully exposed from her shoulder blades to her ankles.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS467
She writhes miserably in her bonds.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS468
Looking over her shoulder, she finds SOMEONE unfastening his pants and gives her restraints a desperate tug.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS469
As her captor drops his pants, she thrashes wrathfully.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS470
SOMEONE takes hold of her hips and buries his face between her butt cheeks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS471
He positions himself directly over her, sweeps his bathrobe back like a cape and takes out a condom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS472
He opens the wrapper.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS473
SOMEONE slams her upper body against the mattress. Looming over her SOMEONE puts on the condom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS474
His gaze hungry and remorseless, SOMEONE leans down, planting his fists on either side of his victim.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS475
His bearded jaw works rhythmically as he thrusts himself into her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS476
SOMEONE sobs beneath him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS477
Her black chin length hair obscuring her face.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS478
Our gaze drifts to her bag sitting on the chair. A snap gleams on its fabric.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS479
In Hedestad, as it snows, outdoor lamps gleam along the island bridges crossbeams.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS480
Outside the guest cottage, the tabby paws at a window then walks out of view.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS481
SOMEONE stands with his glasses drooped down to his chin.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS482
He reaches in his pocket and switches off music playing in his earbuds. A few Vanger family keepsakes lie on a table before him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS483
Four wallet size photos show the young Vanger women.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS484
SOMEONE reads handwritten notes in SOMEONE's white leather Bible.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS485
SOMEONE flips through the Bible's pages then snaps it closed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS486
He lies back on a sofa.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS487
His head and feet propped up on its armrests.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS488
The journalist moves his reading glasses to his brow
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS489
then turns on his music and settles in.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS490
A slow gliding view behind him drifts toward the top of his head.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS491
Out view sinks down, moving closer to the side of the sofa until darkness fills our view.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS492
Now, beside SOMEONE's ravaged bed,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS493
SOMEONE finishes dressing and hobbles painfully to her bag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS494
She keeps her head bowed, her hair masking her face from view.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS496
At a dining table, SOMEONE glances at her as he writes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS497
As his victim shuffles into the hallway with her things, he meets her with a check.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS498
SOMEONE takes it without looking at him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS499
As she leaves we spot a swollen goose egg at the corner of her mouth.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS500
He rapist gazes after her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS501
SOMEONE reaches the staircase and SOMEONE steps back inside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS503
bundled up with her hood over her head
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS504
SOMEONE's hunched figure shuffles up a brick walkway illuminated with street lamps.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS506
She lumbers up a flight of outdoor stairs.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS507
Now, SOMEONE arrives at her door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS508
Unlocking it she drops her keys.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS509
She hesitates, then braces a hand against the wall and bends down for them. her bag drops onto the floor and her keys and the check plunk onto a table.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS517
Later, she takes off her shirt. In the shower, water pours down an exquisite tattoo of a winged dragon that forms a reverse S curve from her left shoulder down along the side of her ribcage.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS518
As she crouches, water washes away at her feet.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS521
Now, on the Vanger estate SOMEONE smiles at the sight of a parked car.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS523
The driver's window lowers, revealing his lover's face.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS524
Now they visit SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS526
In the cottage, SOMEONE pours two drinks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS527
She steps through the French doors into the bedroom. The blinds show her silhouette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS528
SOMEONE leaves his drink.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS529
Now at a tattoo shop an artist with round 2-inch earlobe plugs readies his electric needle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS530
SOMEONE eyes the tool.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS531
SOMEONE gives an undaunted shrug.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS532
She looks away as he tattoo's her ankle. Now a TV news report.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS533
SOMEONE spots a news van. Now in SOMEONE's study.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS535
In a store, SOMEONE spies Wennerstrom on TV.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS536
A cashier faces SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS537
Now at home. She unpacks hardware supplies from her shopping bag as she eats a Happy Meal.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS538
On her laptop, an email types out before her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS539
From Wennerstrom, it reads, Can somebody please explain to me what the fuck is going on with these two assholes?
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS540
Now, at the cottage.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS541
Moving a box of research materials SOMEONE drops some folders and envelopes. He sets down the box.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS543
As he picks up the materials he notices a stack of 8 x 10 photos sticking out of an envelope.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS544
He flips through them and finds distant shots of SOMEONE's manor house.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS545
One shows the blurred figure of a young woman at a window. SOMEONE goes to his posted photographs of the Vanger family members.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS546
He compares the woman in the window to SOMEONE's picture, then SOMEONE's.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS547
He posts the newly found photo beneath SOMEONE's picture.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS548
Next, SOMEONE takes a stack of snapshots from a wax paper envelope and looks through them.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS549
He halts at a shot of the parade.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS550
He finds another parade photo beneath it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS551
SOMEONE hurries to his desk and uses a magnifying glass to study the snapshots.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS552
Amid the parade spectators SOMEONE smiles with a few girlfriends.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS554
Turning the photo over, he finds a stamp reading, HEDESTADS KURIREN.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS555
SOMEONE scratches the stubble on his cheek and eyes the photo again.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS556
Now, he walks down the parade route with the snapshot in his hand.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS557
He wears his reading glasses around his chin as he studies the abutting city blocks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS558
Stopping, he puts on his glasses and consults the photo.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS559
SOMEONE turns and eyes the windows of a building.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS560
He spots a likely match to the photographer's vantage of SOMEONE's position in the 1960s.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS561
He enters the building and looks around as he climbs a flight of stairs.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS564
Later, he steps out onto a balcony overlooking the historic parade route.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS566
he enters a building.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS567
Now, he consults with an archivist. The archivist takes two large binders from a shelf.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS568
SOMEONE opens the first and leafs through pages of plastic sleeved contact sheets. He starts on the next binder.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS569
SOMEONE finds a collection of parade shots.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS570
Now, SOMEONE opens his apartment door to find SOMEONE in the hallway with her head bowed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS571
She lifts her miserable gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS572
SOMEONE allows a brief eager smirk as she enters his apartment. He shuts the door and lingers in front of it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS573
She tases him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS574
SOMEONE topples falling face first on the floor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS575
At the cottage, SOMEONE stands over a scanner, a pencil in his mouth.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS576
Removing a strip of negatives he sets them back in the binder and lays both aside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS577
The journalist sits at his laptop and scrolls through uploaded parade images.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS578
He leans forward making note of SOMEONE's orientation on the sidewalk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS579
SOMEONE brings up a grid of thumbnail images.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS580
In SOMEONE's apartment, a trail of fluid and crumpled clothes lead down the hall to his open bedroom door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS581
On the floor,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS582
the rapist wakes to find himself naked, bound, and gagged. SOMEONE uses a drill gun to screw the zip ties around his ankles to the floor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS583
Black makeup rings her eyes like a mask.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS584
She wears a tasseled leather whip at her hip.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS585
She shows her bag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS586
SOMEONE strains against his bonds. SOMEONE goes to a TV and clicks a remote.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS587
The screen shows a video of SOMEONE raping her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS588
Now helpless, he raises his head and sees himself unfastening his pants on screen.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS589
Sitting partially hidden in a chair on the other side of a bureau, SOMEONE huddles up and lights a cigarette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS590
Clicking the remote, she mutes the video.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS591
SOMEONE chucks her cigarette away then rummages in her bag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS592
She pulls out a large metal dildo with a slight curve and a sizeable head.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS593
Her gaze cold and business like, SOMEONE takes it to SOMEONE
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS594
crouches and rolls his bent knees over exposing his anus to her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS595
She thrusts the dildo out of view.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS596
She stands and steps away shakily wiping her gloves on her pants.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS597
SOMEONE turns back to face her rapist.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS598
He avoids her gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS599
She tases him and he faces her with wide eyes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS600
He obeys.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS601
SOMEONE vigorously nods his head.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS602
He obeys.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS603
Going to the bedroom door, SOMEONE picks up his pants.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS604
She pulls out keys.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS605
SOMEONE looks past her to the rape video.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS606
SOMEONE swings her foot.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS607
She works her boot out of view and SOMEONE writhes painfully. SOMEONE crouches, leaning over him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS608
SOMEONE shakes his head.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS609
With an icy stare, she leans in close.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS610
As he obeys, she stands and steps over him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS611
She throws down a pillow and then dawns a clear face shield.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS612
Crouching, she turns on an electric tattoo needle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS613
SOMEONE uncaps a jar of ink then dips the needle in it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS614
She crouches astride SOMEONE who struggles beneath her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS615
SOMEONE leans forward, her eyes wide.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS616
She braces herself against the bed's footboard as she brings the tattoo needle to his chest. Outside the room
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS617
the floating view withdraws at the littered hall away from the open bedroom door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS618
In the cottage, SOMEONE initiates a slideshow of the parade photos.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS619
The images crossfade as they change, creating a disjointed animated effect.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS620
SOMEONE's brow creases as the images show SOMEONE smiling among her girlfriends.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS621
She turns, her gaze following something in the parade.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS622
She lays a hand on a friend's shoulder and backs away from the group.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS623
SOMEONE leans back in his chair, his gaze chilled.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS624
The computer replays the ghostly sequence of SOMEONE reacting and her smile becoming a frightened stare.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS626
Watching the slideshow SOMEONE slowly removes his glasses.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS627
He looks over his shoulder with a troubled gaze as the cat lounges comfortably nearby.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS629
Back in SOMEONE's apartment, SOMEONE finishes a drink of water and sets the cup in the bathroom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS630
She goes to a chair, gathers up her things and stands over an unconscious SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS631
Tattooed words cover his torso in a bloody scrawl.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS632
I am a rapist pig.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS633
On her way out, SOMEONE tosses wire cutters down beside him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS634
She leaves the apartment without looking back.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS635
Now SOMEONE walks the grounds of the Vanger estate.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS636
He slows to a stop then smiles.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS637
SOMEONE waits for him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS638
SOMEONE gives her a big hug and kisses her cheek.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS639
He picks up her suitcase.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS640
Inside, SOMEONE studies SOMEONE's list on the wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS641
SOMEONE sets two plates on the table and they each take a seat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS642
He starts to cut into his sandwich before noticing his daughter's head bowed in prayer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS643
Setting down his knife
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS644
he sits back and wipes his hands.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS645
His daughter finishes her silent prayer and gives him a look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS646
She takes a bite of her sandwich and he pours them each some coffee.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS647
At the train station.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS648
They embrace.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS649
He hands over her bag and she boards her train.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS650
A door slides shut and she mouths I love you through its window.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS651
Slack-jawed SOMEONE pivots away pensively.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS652
He glances back at the departing train then heads off.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS653
At the cottage he marches past his desk then stops and grabs the copy of SOMEONE's list of names, initials, and numbers from the wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS654
He crosses to a windowsill as the cat watches him from a chair.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS655
Then puts on his reading glasses, picks up SOMEONE's Bible and flips to Leviticus Chapters 3-4.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS656
He thumbs the corner of the page then sits on the couch, puts his feet up
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS657
and matches the other numbers from the list with Bible verses.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS658
Now in a phone booth.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS659
An ambulance races across the bridge.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS660
SOMEONE exits the phone booth and heads for the bridge.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS661
Later, the ambulance speeds back followed by cars.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS662
SOMEONE runs to the tree-lined road and an SUV slows to a stop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS663
He speaks to SOMEONE through the passenger window.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS664
SOMEONE speeds off.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS665
Later, in the cottage SOMEONE reads Bible verses on his laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS666
He sets down a drink then answers the door to SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS667
The bespectacled man steps inside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS668
SOMEONE closes the page of Bible verses on his laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS669
He sets his glass and a dish in the sink.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS670
He pours SOMEONE a glass of scotch then doffs his glasses and pours one for himself.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS671
In Stockholm
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS672
he points to the report.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS673
He writes on a card.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS674
The image quickly fades to black.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS675
Now at a nightclub, SOMEONE sits alone sipping a drink as she watches a crowded dance floor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS676
The pictures pulses in and out of view, offering us fleeting glimpses of the establishment's trendy young patrons.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS677
SOMEONE ashes her cigarette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS678
An exotic beauty approaches.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS679
She sets her beer on SOMEONE's table.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS680
The hacker purses her lips then glances aside bashfully.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS681
The exotic beauty smiles.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS682
Later, holding a vial she doses SOMEONE then kisses her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS683
The pierced hacker turns the woman's back to a wall,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS684
feels up her bare thigh to her crotch and kisses her cheek.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS685
As the exotic young beauty grins in ecstasy, the image fades to black.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS686
The next morning the two lie in bed together, both of them half-naked.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS687
SOMEONE wakes with a start.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS688
Her lover stirs as she climbs out of bed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS690
SOMEONE carries a takeout bag and two coffees up a stairwell.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS691
In her bedroom SOMEONE puts on an oversized T-shirt.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS692
SOMEONE approaches the door to her apartment.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS693
SOMEONE heads for her bathroom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS694
She pauses eyeing the door, then glances back at her sleeping lover in the bedroom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS695
She pivots away from the door, her panicked eyes glancing about.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS696
She opens the door a crack and peeks out, but SOMEONE yanks it wide open. SOMEONE recoils as he barges in.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS697
He eyes the bedroom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS698
He enters the kitchen.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS699
SOMEONE's gaze lingers on him as she returns to her bedroom and pushes the door most of the way shut.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS700
She wakes her lover.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS701
The exotic beauty gets out of bed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS702
In the kitchen, SOMEONE takes off his scarf then sets two plates on the table.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS703
Meanwhile, SOMEONE opens a dresser drawer, takes out her taser and stuffs it in her back pocket. Her lover notices.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS704
In the kitchen.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS705
SOMEONE pauses and watches the two young women head to the front door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS706
SOMEONE opens the door. Her exotic lover steps out, then turns back and gives her a kiss.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS707
SOMEONE ambles toward the kitchen
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS708
then stops and switches on her taser.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS710
She grabs a cigarette from an ashtray and a lighter. SOMEONE takes a seat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS711
He slides a plate toward her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS713
SOMEONE stubs out her cigarette and starts to walk away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS714
She points to her head but SOMEONE insistently holds out his notes. Taking them, she curtly drops them on the table as she heads out of the room. Now a taxi crosses the bridge back to the island.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS715
In her apartment, SOMEONE enters keywords into her laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS716
Rape, decapitation, dismemberment, fire, altar, priest, prostitute.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS717
The taxi parks and SOMEONE steps out.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS718
Meanwhile, SOMEONE packs a bag with soda and snacks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS721
At her laptop she stuffs junk food in her mouth then types, Magda, underneath a line reading status equals unsolved.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS723
the taxi departs as SOMEONE marches back to the cottage.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS724
Now, SOMEONE reads the repeated line, full police report not digitized.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS725
She shuts her laptop then packs it up.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS726
At the cottage, SOMEONE picks up the cat's bowl from outside the front door and looks out over the yard.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS727
Shutting the door behind him,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS728
He enters the kitchen. He sets his leather bag on the floor and the bowl on the counter.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS729
Grabbing a can from the top of the refrigerator he accidentally knocks over a bottled water.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS730
It rolls off the side but he catches it and puts it back.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS731
As he digs through a drawer, our view shifts to find the cat on his desk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS732
SOMEONE notices the tabby licking itself and sets down the can.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS733
He heads over and pets the cat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS734
Now, SOMEONE rides to a police station. A detective checks her ID card and a letter of recommendation signed Dragan Armanski, CEO Milton Security.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS735
Meanwhile, SOMEONE checks his things as a locksmith changes his lock.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS736
That night at a hostel SOMEONE reads by flashlight.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS737
In a hospital waiting area, SOMEONE meets SOMEONE and several members of the SOMEONE family.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS738
SOMEONE gives her a glower then turns to SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS739
Now SOMEONE rides her motorcycle over a bridge as a train passes underneath.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS740
At another police station.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS741
A detective hangs up his phone.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS742
SOMEONE follows him into a file room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS743
Later outside a dilapidated building on some farm land.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS744
SOMEONE watches a train whiz by.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS745
At the cottage, SOMEONE attaches a newspaper clipping about Birger Vanger to the family tree above a sticky note reading Son of Harold.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS747
SOMEONE lights a cigarette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS748
SOMEONE takes a drag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS750
SOMEONE arrives on her motorcycle. SOMEONE takes another drag from his cigarette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS751
As his research assistant parks, he takes a couple of steps forward.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS752
SOMEONE climbs off her bike and removes her helmet.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS753
She grabs her bag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS754
SOMEONE offers his hand but she heads inside ignoring him. He turns to SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS755
As SOMEONE walks away, SOMEONE tosses his cigarette and joins SOMEONE in the kitchen.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS756
She takes off two layers of leather jackets.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS757
She offers police reports.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS758
She lights a cigarette ignoring him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS759
Now, they sit outside smoking.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS760
He takes a drag and points out Harold's house.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS761
He looks back at his assistant.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS762
Later, in the living room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS763
She grabs a stack of sheets.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS764
SOMEONE pauses on his way into the bedroom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS765
He shifts his contemplative gaze and shuts the door. SOMEONE bites her bottom lip.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS766
The next morning.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS767
A printer ejects images of crime scene photos. SOMEONE smokes as she skims the personal photo library on SOMEONE's laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS768
Stopping on one of him and his co-editor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS769
As the report awakes to cigarette smoke, SOMEONE hurriedly closes the photo library in the adjoining room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS770
SOMEONE emerges.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS771
He pours himself coffee.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS772
He joins her at the laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS773
A photo shows a woman near SOMEONE snapping a picture. SOMEONE reaches around SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS774
She flinches. He shares the laptop with her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS775
SOMEONE gives an exasperated look as he clicks incorrect icons.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS776
He finds a photo with the same woman climbing into a car. He points to a decal on it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS777
With a cigarette between his lips he steps outside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS778
SOMEONE hurries over. Following his gaze she finds the cat lying just outside the door with its head cut off.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS779
A pool of blood glistens under its lifeless body. And it's crookedly bent limbs form the shape of a swastika.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS780
As SOMEONE grabs a camera and snaps photos of the mutilated tabby
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS781
SOMEONE presses his lips together stifling a wretch.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS782
They both glance over at Harold's house, then exchange a look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS783
Now SOMEONE stops her motorcycle in a rental car company's parking lot.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS784
Standing at the open door of a Volvo sedan
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS785
SOMEONE meets her gaze and nods.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS786
She flips down her helmet's visor and speeds off.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS787
SOMEONE climbs into his vehicle and backs it out of its spot.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS788
Later, in a small hardware store.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS789
He shows a middle-aged clerk the photos of the woman from the parade
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS790
getting into a car with a young man.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS791
He turns away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS792
Now, SOMEONE speeds between cars in a tunnel.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS793
At a retirement home SOMEONE sits with an elderly man.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS794
The man points to the photo.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS795
Meanwhile, SOMEONE exits a freeway in Stockholm.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS796
Now, SOMEONE consults a GPS as he approaches a modest house on a country road.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS798
She views his photos.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS799
He shows a photo.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS800
The woman gives a startled look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS801
As she strides into an adjacent dining room and disappears from view
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS802
SOMEONE leans forward to stare after her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS803
She returns with a photo album and hands it to him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS804
She sits beside him on the couch as he puts on his glasses and opens the album.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS805
Flipping through its pages he skims over photos of parade goers. The white haired widow leans closer and examines the images with him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS806
His gaze stops on a picture showing the back of SOMEONE's head and the people across the street from her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS808
A tech clerk gives an exasperated look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS809
Under SOMEONE's steady gaze he resignedly scans her ID.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS810
She leaves with a case of equipment.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS811
Back at the guest cottage
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS812
SOMEONE places the borrowed photo on a scanner then watches his laptop screen as the image uploads.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS813
Leaning closer to the monitor, he enlarges the picture.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS814
He pans over the blurry faces of people standing across the street from SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS815
Then thoughtfully shifts his gaze away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS816
Now, SOMEONE glances at another passenger as he boards the elevator outside his office.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS817
The door slides shut.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS818
Standing in a corner the passenger faces away from him. Obscured by a sweatshirt's pulled up hood.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS819
SOMEONE stops the elevator.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS820
She grabs his throat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS821
He flinches from her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS822
She points to his brow then hits a button on the elevator's control panel. SOMEONE averts his gaze as they resume their descent.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS823
The doors open.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS824
SOMEONE exits, SOMEONE shuts his eyes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS825
At the cottage SOMEONE tucks the borrowed photo in an envelope.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS826
Then stares at the now extensive family tree on the wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS827
As he scratches the back of his head, his hand freezes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS828
Stepping closer to the postings he examines a photograph in a newspaper article about Gottfried's death.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS829
The image of the drowning site shows a dock on the Vanger estate.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS831
SOMEONE overlooks the water and the present day dock.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS832
He stands by studiously, a rustic cabin at his back.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS833
He consults the newspaper photo then heads over to the cabin. He jiggles a doorknob. He Finds it locked.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS834
He moves to a window and peers inside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS836
Entering through a different door, he glances around the abandoned cabin lit meagerly by daylight.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS838
His foot kicks an empty bottle on the floor as he moves into a neglected room scattered with papers, books, and trash.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS839
His gaze rose past the paperbacks,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS841
Moving to a box of books he picks up a children's paperback and flips through it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS842
Inside, he finds a name written in a child's shaky cursive.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS845
SOMEONE climbs a hill away from the cabin.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS846
Standing at the top, he scans the area contemplatively.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS848
A bullet hits the utility pole behind him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS849
He ducks, glances at the pole's chipped wood
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS850
and notes a bleeding cut just above his right eyebrow. He bolts.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS851
He races through the woods pushing tree branches aside as he goes.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS852
Meanwhile, at the cottage, SOMEONE removes surveillance cameras from the equipment case.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS855
She drags a chair to the corner of the room climbs on top and mounts one camera from the ceiling.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS856
Its black and white view shows the young woman staring up at it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS858
She mounts a camera on an eve of the roof.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS859
Its view shows a blurry image of her face washed out by light.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS860
She steps away to reveal the camera's aim at the door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS861
Elsewhere on the cottage's exterior she places another hidden camera.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS864
SOMEONE stumbles as he sprints past SOMEONE's mansion. I
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS865
She sees a figure racing into the house then turns as SOMEONE enters. n the cottage SOMEONE watches the three surveillance feeds on a portable monitor split screen.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS867
Later, he sits shirtless in a tub with his legs hanging over its side as water showers onto his head. Blood streams down his face and chest.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS868
His hand trembles as he wipes his eyes. SOMEONE threads a needle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS869
She bites a strand off with her teeth and approaches him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS870
She glances around the bathroom then strides into the kitchen.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS871
She grabs a vodka bottle from the freezer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS872
Returning, she pours alcohol on the needle and his cut.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS873
As he swigs from the bottle she moves closer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS874
She pierces his skin on one side of the cut.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS875
She pulls the needle through to the other side then sews another stitch.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS876
Later, SOMEONE enters his bedroom still holding the vodka bottle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS877
SOMEONE follows.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS878
She takes the bottle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS879
Exiting the room she sets it on a table.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS880
A view through the glass panes of his bedroom doors show him stripping off his pants. Meanwhile, SOMEONE peers outside then locks the doors and windows and turns off the light.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS881
SOMEONE in only his briefs, SOMEONE sits on the edge of his bed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS882
He bows his head.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS883
In the living room SOMEONE takes off her pants. SOMEONE touches his cut.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS884
SOMEONE glances around then enters SOMEONE's bedroom in only her panties and tank top.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS885
Standing in front of him she slides down her panties. His jaw drops.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS886
She pulls off her shirt.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS887
Pushing him back onto the bed she straddles him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS888
They kiss and then she moves her mouth lower and bites his nipple.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS889
She straightens to a kneeling position and slides his briefs off his waist.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS890
As he works them down the rest of the way she lowers herself back on top of him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS891
Rocking her hips, she hovers her mouth mere inches above his.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS892
He reaches between their legs and pulls her into a kiss.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS893
She thrusts against him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS894
He sits up with her straddling his lap and gently flips her, lowering himself on top.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS895
He kisses her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS896
Later SOMEONE lies on her back still naked, and takes a drag off a cigarette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS897
Beside her, propped on his elbows, belly down, SOMEONE watches.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS898
Without looking at him she offers her lit smoke.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS899
He accepts and she folds her arm behind her head.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS900
SOMEONE drags off the cigarette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS901
Then props his head on his hand. His puzzled eyes fixed on his enigmatic partner.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS903
Sitting on the counter by the kitchen sink, her hair mussed, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE emerge from the bedroom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS904
He spots two breakfast settings arranged on a small table, then approaches.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS905
She bites a piece of toast.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS906
She considers him briefly, then bites her toast again.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS907
Now they talk with SOMEONE and SOMEONE in SOMEONE's living room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS908
SOMEONE and SOMEONE move aside to a corner.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS909
SOMEONE walks away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS910
Now SOMEONE arrives at an industrial complex on her motorcycle and turns through a gate marked with a stately letter V.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS911
Later, a security guard leads SOMEONE into an archive facility.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS912
Facing a matronly manager through a window
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS913
the guard gestures at the visitor whose bag and helmet land on a reading table.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS914
Now a file folder opens on a laptop screen.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS915
A series of photos shows the parade then the Hedestad bridge.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS916
Scrolling through the images in his cottage, SOMEONE comes to snapshots of the accident.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS917
In a couple of them he notices the blurred figure of a man holding a camera.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS918
SOMEONE hurries to his posted photo of Harold Vanger on the family tree.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS919
Our view drops to SOMEONE's information right below it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS920
SOMEONE prints out some photos and leaves with them.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS922
As SOMEONE studies documents at the archive,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS923
Her partner visits SOMEONE. She slides the printed photos across a table to SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS924
Picking them up, he gives an imploring stare.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS925
Back at the Vanger Industries archives.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS926
With a prim glare, the corporate archives manager makes a phone call.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS927
Later, she coldly escorts SOMEONE into an elevator.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS928
As its gate lowers the manager puts on white cotton gloves.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS929
Now on a ladder she takes two heavy volumes from a high shelf.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS930
She looks to SOMEONE who makes no move to assist her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS931
The archives manager climbs down and adds the books to a fully stacked cart.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS932
As she wheels it out of view SOMEONE follows.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS933
Now in a dimly lit foyer SOMEONE turns.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS935
From an upper landing a hunched old man smokes a cigar as he rides a motorized chair down a staircase.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS936
SOMEONE's brow furrows and he swallows nervously.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS937
Harold climbs out of the chair.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS938
He leads SOMEONE into a den.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS939
Three rifles hang on a rack by the door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS940
As the old man settles into a chair among stacks of books
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS941
SOMEONE studies photos of Nazis on a wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS942
He gestures to a drawer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS943
Back at the archives SOMEONE spreads out a map of Sweden.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS944
Circular V emblems SOMEONE Vanger Holdings all over the country.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS945
SOMEONE shifts her gaze then goes to another table.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS946
She comes back with the list of the murders, which gives their dates and locations.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS947
For each location she finds a corresponding Vanger property on the map.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS948
Now, Harold pours tea as SOMEONE looks through his personal photos.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS949
He offers a cigarette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS950
SOMEONE lights it and takes a drag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS951
The journalist looks up at Harold's earnest scowl.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS952
SOMEONE sets down a stack of photos and moves on to some others.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS953
One features a search party in the woods.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS954
The blurry teen wears a prep school blazer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS956
At the archives, photos of the murder victims now lie on their corresponding locations.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS957
The manager finds SOMEONE at a card catalog.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS958
The matronly woman stays put staring at her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS959
As the manager steps away the visitor selects a catalog card.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS960
Later SOMEONE flips through a book.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS961
The manager locks up her office then tosses keys on a nearby table.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS962
As the manager marches out haughtily SOMEONE finishes flipping through the pages of a binder then shuts it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS963
She opens another labeled 1957.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS964
Each page boasts a single news clipping pasted at its center.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS965
SOMEONE pauses at an article with a photo headlined Carlin and Vanger rebuilt local port.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS967
She brings the binder to her laptop and calls up a casefile on one of the murders.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS971
SOMEONE looks down at a photo in the newspaper article captioned Gottfried Vanger and Carlin Shaking Hands.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS972
She brings up a digital copy of the photo of Gottfried from SOMEONE's wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS973
Then opens a spreadsheet charting the serial murder details.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS974
Searching another binder
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS975
she stops at an article featuring Gottfried.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS976
A typed heading above reads, Palmar, 28th of October
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS978
On the spreadsheet a row detailing SOMEONE Homburg's Palmar murder ends with a blank field.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS981
SOMEONE flips through another binder stopping at the typed heading. A newspaper photo shows Gottfried at a podium.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS985
SOMEONE enters his name with a question SOMEONE into a row detailing SOMEONE murder.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS986
Meanwhile, SOMEONE returns to the cottage and brings up the honeymooner's parade photos.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS987
One shows a partially obscured figure wearing a prep school blazer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS988
SOMEONE notes the time on a clock positioned above him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS989
At the archives SOMEONE finds a newspaper featuring a Vanger Industries investment and SOMEONE's murder on the same page.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS990
As she reads, a figure passes in the next room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS991
She turns, finding herself alone among the cold metallic book stacks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS993
Now on the spreadsheet, Gottfried's name types out with a question SOMEONE in the row detailing SOMEONE's murder.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS995
In the cottage SOMEONE takes the photo of SOMEONE with the search party to a table bearing stacks of case files.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS997
Selecting the file for Lena Anderson, he flips through its pages and finds a portrait of the girl in a shirt bearing her school crest.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS998
He holds it up with the search party photo comparing it with the identical crest on SOMEONE's blazer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1001
SOMEONE looks up, shifting his jaw.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1002
At the archives, SOMEONE flips through a binder and finds an obituary reading. In memoriam, Gottfried Vanger 1927-1965.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1003
Now SOMEONE leaves the cottage holding up his cell phone for a signal as he dials a call.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1004
He glares at his phone then looks up.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1005
SOMEONE's house glows from its steep hilltop perch.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1006
Staring grimly at it SOMEONE backtracks towards the cottage.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1009
At the archives SOMEONE takes Gottfried's obituary to her laptop. She marks the date of death.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1010
Then notices a murder listed as two years later
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1012
In its blank suspect field she types a row of question marks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1013
She wearily rolls her neck then leaves with the keys.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1014
Our view closes in on her open laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1015
On the spreadsheet the cursor blinks at the end of the long row of question marks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1017
In the cottage SOMEONE removes his reading glasses and shifts his thoughtful gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1018
He marches back out leaving the photos of SOMEONE and Lena on his laptop keyboard.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1019
At Vanger Industries SOMEONE gets on the elevator, stretches her neck and shoulders and zips up her hoodie.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1020
The gate lowers beside her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1021
Now SOMEONE climbs a steeply ascending walkway overlooking the water.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1022
He stops facing SOMEONE's now dimly lit home.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1023
Meanwhile, SOMEONE trails her fingertips along the volumes of archives as she walks through the stacks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1024
Coming to an intersection, she turns out of view.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1025
Now SOMEONE moves around the perimeter of SOMEONE's house. Peering inside through the floor to ceiling windows.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1026
He makes his way to a bedroom door, tries the handle, and finds it locked.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1027
Continuing around the house he comes to the kitchen and living room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1028
He tries another door and it slides open.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1030
He leans in cautiously.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1031
Elsewhere a Range Rover turns into view. It crosses the bridge into Hedestad.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1032
Meanwhile SOMEONE slips inside the house. As he creeps past an island counter he pauses at a set of knives.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1033
He takes one from the knife block revealing its long smooth edged blade.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1034
Now, SOMEONE's SUV reaches the island.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1035
Back at his house SOMEONE ventures down a brief corridor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1036
He tries the door at the far end but it doesn't budge.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1037
We watch from outside as he goes to the bedroom and peeks through a partially opened door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1038
At the archives SOMEONE pushes through heavy doors and approaches some vending machines.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1039
A security guard sits in a windowed booth beside them.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1040
As he watches SOMEONE through the glass
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1041
she instinctively jerks her hood up over her head
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1042
then punches in her selections.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1044
the Range Rover pulls up behind SOMEONE's mansion and cuts its headlights.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1045
SOMEONE gets out and gazes toward the cottage.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1046
Meanwhile, SOMEONE continues to explore his sleek modern home.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1047
At the Vanger Industries vending machines
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1048
SOMEONE takes a sandwich from a compartment and collects a paper cup of coffee.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1049
As she leaves the room, the guard makes a note on a clipboard.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1050
From outside SOMEONE's home we watch SOMEONE striding more boldly through the living room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1051
Reaching the dining area he pauses to face a dark corridor beside him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1052
He ventures down it wearily.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1053
It turns at a right angle leading him to a study with a gun case on the wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1054
He cautiously approaches the room, opens its glass door and enters.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1055
Stepping into the center of the study
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1056
he peers through another door into the darkness outside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1058
he notices the gun case.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1059
Its glass door shows a rack built for four rifles. It contains only three.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1061
SOMEONE turns on the spot. His lips pressed together tightly.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1062
Later, arriving in another room he pauses and stares past a glass cabinet displaying an impressive wine collection.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1063
Stepping forward he tries a door at the other end of the room and finds it locked.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1064
At the archives SOMEONE munches on her sandwich as she walks among the towering stacks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1065
She sips her coffee then wipes her mouth with her hand.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1067
Back in Hedestad, SOMEONE stands and faces him with a nonchalant wave. SOMEONE's SUV travels down a curving path.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1068
Back in Hedestad, SOMEONE's SUV travels down a curving path.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1069
As SOMEONE explores his house light sweeps across a nearby wall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1070
Turning, he spots the SUV arriving outside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1072
He scrambles to a recess and puts his back to a pair of doors.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1073
SOMEONE gets out of his SUV and opens one of its back doors.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1074
In the house, SOMEONE lunges sideways and pulls a door closed. Outside,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1076
SOMEONE heads for the house with a vertical four-foot long bag slung over his shoulder.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1077
SOMEONE darts out of the corridor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1078
Reaching the dining area he finds himself fully exposed by its floor to ceiling windows. He looks over his shoulder then darts out of view as SOMEONE enters the house.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1079
SOMEONE dashes from the living room just before the owner comes in.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1080
SOMEONE pauses, shifting his weary gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1082
From outside, we watch SOMEONE backing across the bedroom.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1083
Reaching a door in the corner he turns the handle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1084
In the living room SOMEONE sets his bag down and approaches the kitchen.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1085
SOMEONE opens the bedroom door and slips out.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1086
Meanwhile, SOMEONE finds the backdoor from the kitchen slightly ajar.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1087
SOMEONE peeks in through a window then makes a run for it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1088
SOMEONE slides the kitchen door open, gazing out.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1089
Running toward the steps, SOMEONE loses his footing and falls.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1090
SOMEONE turns and spots him. SOMEONE stands and faces him with a nonchalant wave.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1091
Smiling calmly, SOMEONE heads into the house.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1092
SOMEONE stares after him with a furrowed brow then reluctantly follows with a slight limp.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1093
At the archives, photos of the murder victims sprawl across various locations on the Swedish map.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1094
Sitting by her laptop SOMEONE flips through magazine-like company newsletters.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1095
She pauses at a photo of a dinner.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1098
SOMEONE locates the teen boy wearing his school blazer. She rubs the crest with her finger.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1101
Sweeping her sandwich wrapper off the keyboard she brings up the parade photos. She finds the one with SOMEONE, recognizable by his blazer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1106
In the house. Coming inside, SOMEONE complies. SOMEONE takes off his jacket and drapes it over a low cabinet.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1107
SOMEONE crosses to the island counter. He takes a small flashlight from a drawer and tosses it to SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1108
Pouring two drinks SOMEONE notices the empty slot in his knife block.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1109
SOMEONE pockets the flashlight.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1110
SOMEONE adds a little tap water to the drinks then gives one to his guest.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1111
SOMEONE's gaze falls on a rifle bag standing propped up near SOMEONE's jacket.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1112
His host notices then gives a shrewd smile.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1113
SOMEONE avoids his gaze. SOMEONE sips his drink.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1114
Setting his glass down, SOMEONE circles back around the island.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1115
He takes a gun from a drawer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1116
He cocks it and gestures at his knife block.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1117
He steps out from behind the island.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1118
SOMEONE shifts his defeated gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1119
Under SOMEONE's cold stare he takes the knife from his coat and drops it on the counter.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1120
Meanwhile, hurrying from the archives SOMEONE drops off the keys at the empty security booth.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1122
Now, SOMEONE ushers SOMEONE through his house at gunpoint.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1123
Outside Vanger Industries SOMEONE walks briskly with her phone to her ear.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1124
At the house.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1125
They stop at the wine case.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1126
SOMEONE touches a keycard to a panel and the door behind SOMEONE opens.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1127
Outside Vanger Industries SOMEONE races off on her motorcycle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1128
In the house SOMEONE keeps his gun trained on SOMEONE as he ushers him down a dark narrow stairway.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1129
His drink in hand,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1130
the journalist takes in his surroundings as they pass through an electrical room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1131
Behind him SOMEONE glowers darkly at his captive.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1132
SOMEONE reaches a steel door and halts. He faces SOMEONE who scans his key card on a panel.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1133
The door swings open into a dark space.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1134
The journalist steps through. SOMEONE follows and turns on a light revealing a torture chamber with a white tiled center.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1135
Turning, SOMEONE finds him covering his own face with an oxygen mask as he flips a switch.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1136
Gas plumes from ceiling pipes. SOMEONE collapses, his drink shattering beside him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1137
The fumes fill our view.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1138
Meanwhile, SOMEONE speeds across the bridge. Now, SOMEONE uses a cable and harness with armpit straps and a neck brace to hoist up his captive in the white tiled area.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1139
A video camera stands on a tripod facing SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1140
Handcuffs and chains prevent him from lifting his hands any higher than his abdomen. SOMEONE brings a fresh drink.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1141
He holds it out insistently.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1142
SOMEONE grasps it in his tightly restrained hand and stares down at it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1143
SOMEONE steps away setting his gun on a monitor displaying a feed from the video camera.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1144
SOMEONE makes adjustments to the video camera. SOMEONE surveys his surroundings.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1145
SOMEONE sits on a sofa. SOMEONE arches his back then slumps.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1146
At the cottage SOMEONE drops her helmet and bag then looks around for SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1147
She crosses to his laptop and finds the photograph of young SOMEONE among the search party,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1148
wearing his prep school blazer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1149
She switches on the laptop
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1150
which shows the photo of young SOMEONE at the parade.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1151
She looks up from the laptop then crosses the room,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1152
picks up a duffle bag and takes out the portable monitor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1153
Meanwhile, in the torture chamber.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1154
SOMEONE stares at him. SOMEONE glances back at the camera. A monitor shows the prisoner.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1155
SOMEONE eyes him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1156
SOMEONE gets up scratching his hand.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1157
He uses hand sanitizer.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1158
He returns to his seat.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1159
SOMEONE sneers.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1160
In the cottage SOMEONE studies surveillance feeds on the portable monitor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1161
She holds its screen up close viewing SOMEONE at the front door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1162
Two of the three angles show the SOMEONE entering the cottage through a wooden side door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1163
SOMEONE puts the monitor down and heads off.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1164
In the basement, SOMEONE switches on a reel-to-reel tape player.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1165
His helpless prisoner grimaces in pain.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1166
He clutches the neck brace, lifting SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1167
SOMEONE lets him go.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1168
While SOMEONE catches his breath SOMEONE ties a plastic bag over his head.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1169
SOMEONE flips a switch and a cable lifts SOMEONE a few feet off the floor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1170
As his captor casually taps his fingers on a counter,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1171
SOMEONE glances at him through the bag. His mouth open wide.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1172
SOMEONE returns with a utility knife.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1173
The clear plastic sticks to SOMEONE's face as he inhales, and puffs out as he exhales.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1174
SOMEONE studies his prisoner, cracking a subtle smile.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1175
He rips open SOMEONE's button over shirt
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1176
then uses the utility knife to tear open his undershirt, exposing the helpless man's chest.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1177
SOMEONE unbuttons SOMEONE's pants then stands upright and steps back, gazing thoughtfully.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1178
SOMEONE's eyes bulge. SOMEONE meets his terrified gaze then ambles back to the counter.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1179
He returns with a kitchen knife.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1180
As his prisoner continues to gasp for air, he presses on his midsection with his fingertips.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1181
Meanwhile, SOMEONE enters the basement wielding a golf club.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1182
She approaches SOMEONE from behind.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1183
He turns and she strikes him in the face knocking him to the tile floor.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1184
She lowers SOMEONE then rips the plastic bag off his face and unshackles his ankles.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1185
His jaw misaligned, SOMEONE struggles to his feet and runs out.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1186
SOMEONE sees him go.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1187
SOMEONE runs through a corridor. SOMEONE grabs the gun.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1188
SOMEONE runs upstairs.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1189
SOMEONE crouches over SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1190
Leaving him behind, she runs out the door through the corridor and up the darkened steps.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1191
With her gun at the ready, SOMEONE crosses the kitchen in search of the SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1192
She looks in a study then heads through a hallway past a modern painting
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1193
and approaches the dining table.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1194
She turns a corner, peers down another hallway,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1195
then scans the living room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1196
Outside, SOMEONE's Range Rover backs out. SOMEONE breaks into a run.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1197
The SUV climbs the gravel driveway.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1198
Stepping outside SOMEONE spots its headlights over a ridge. She tucks the gun behind her back and climbs on her bike.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1199
The SUV cruises a forest road.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1200
Pulling out, the motorcycle kicks up gravel.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1201
As SOMEONE struggles to drive, the SUV swerves.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1202
SOMEONE catches air then races down the forest road and rounds a bend.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1203
Her lone headlight shines through SOMEONE's back window.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1204
Her view finds the SUV rounding a bend.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1205
SOMEONE checks his rearview mirror. SOMEONE hunches over her bikes handle bars. The vehicles race along the forest road flanked by tall thin trees.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1206
Now the motorcycle gains on the SUV jouncing in the cold rushing air.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1207
SOMEONE checks his rearview again. She follows him down a hill peering ahead with a determined gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1208
As they reach the bridge SOMEONE rides up close.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1209
SOMEONE spots her in his side mirror then cuts her off before she can pass.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1210
She tries the other side but he blocks her way.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1211
Nearing the end of the bridge she fakes him out and as his SUV grazes the right hand railing, SOMEONE races ahead on his left.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1212
She veers across his path.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1213
He swerves through a wooden fence, banks off a low stonewall and goes airborne.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1214
As SOMEONE skids off her bike, SOMEONE's SUV grinds on its side into a fuel tank outside the grocery store. SOMEONE approaches.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1215
Thick smoke rises from the wreck.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1216
Approaching the vehicle SOMEONE removes the gun from her waistband and holds it at her side.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1217
Inside the SUV SOMEONE watches through the windshield.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1218
Still about 50 yards away, SOMEONE continues her march towards the wreck through a gentle snowfall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1219
SOMEONE watches her. His face bloody.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1220
The pale woman's gaze remains fixed on him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1221
He sees a spark.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1222
A fiery explosion erupts, rising over 50 feet high.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1223
SOMEONE steps back and watches the SUV burn.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1224
The flames reach into the night sky.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1225
Our view swings around behind the young woman. The burning wreck now visible over her shoulder.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1226
She looks at the gun, releases its trigger, then turns away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1227
She marches back to her motorcycle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1231
A hearse drives off, leaving behind the charred SUV, which still lies on its side.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1232
A flatbed tow truck pulls around the wreck.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1233
A hovering view from the middle of the bridge draws back from the scene.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1234
The image dissolves to SOMEONE who lies on his back in bed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1235
He rolls on his side and faces SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1236
She gazes at him, lying on her side.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1237
The petite young woman wears a black tank top. The head of her dragon tattoo visible on her bare shoulder.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1238
She lowers her gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1239
She looks at him directly.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1240
She leaves him lying on the bed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1241
In the kitchen she sets down a coffee mug then produces two photos of a nude teenage girl.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1242
SOMEONE glances aside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1243
She follows him into the living room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1244
SOMEONE stands behind SOMEONE as he faces the family tree.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1245
Peering at a photo of SOMEONE Vanger.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1246
The images dissolves to the cabin of an airplane
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1247
where the heavy set techie sleeps with his mouth hanging open.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1249
Across the aisle, SOMEONE sits beside SOMEONE who wakes from a nap.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1250
At night, in a pleasant upscale neighborhood of row houses
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1251
a car pulls into a narrow drive.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1253
In a van parked across the street, SOMEONE sees the arrival and talks into a walkie-talkie.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1254
He eyes a basement access stair rail under a bay window.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1255
The heavyset techie and SOMEONE come up the steps
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1256
followed by a tall young man who shuts the railing gate.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1257
They cross the street with their hands in their pockets and climb into the van.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1258
The door startles SOMEONE. SOMEONE sits beside him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1259
He nods.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1260
He steps out.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1261
In the back the techie lights a cigarette and blows smoke at the tall young man.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1262
SOMEONE crosses the street and walks up to the front door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1263
SOMEONE peers out the passenger window.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1264
As an anxious SOMEONE gazes in the van's direction, SOMEONE answers the front door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1265
She shuts the door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1266
An antenna protrudes from the van's roof.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1267
SOMEONE returns to the vehicle and gets behind the wheel.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1268
SOMEONE and SOMEONE peer over their seats at the techie's laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1269
It shows SOMEONE's internet activity as she checks her email
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1270
and navigates a shopping site.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1271
The techie takes a drag.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1272
SOMEONE and SOMEONE trade a look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1273
Now in a hotel, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE on a bed where she uses her laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1274
He rubs her back under her T-shirt.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1275
She taps a popup view on screen.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1276
SOMEONE rubs her back again.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1277
Later, they have sex.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1278
Her naked upper body exposed, SOMEONE straddles SOMEONE posting her arm on a headboard.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1279
Her black hair dangles over the top of his head.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1280
She collapses over his right side.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1281
She notices his distant gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1282
The next day SOMEONE enters the investment bank and marches upstairs.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1283
He peeks around a corner then approaches SOMEONE who hangs up her desk phone.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1284
Her jaw goes slack.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1285
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in a park.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1286
SOMEONE shifts his gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1287
He takes out one of the photos of the nude teenage girl.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1288
She looks at the photo.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1289
She averts her gaze and he puts it away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1290
In a flashback.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1291
Gottfried strangles her as young SOMEONE looks on.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1292
Young SOMEONE ducks behind a boatshed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1293
She strikes him with an oar and he falls off the docks.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1294
SOMEONE nods. SOMEONE recalls the parade.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1295
Bystanders snap photos.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1296
SOMEONE sets down a purse.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1297
SOMEONE hides in a storage tunnel.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1298
The teen hides in the trunk of a car.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1299
SOMEONE drives past a police car.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1300
She wipes her nose.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1301
They look at SOMEONE who leans against a brick wall across the park.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1302
SOMEONE returns her gaze to SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1303
Now, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE wait in SOMEONE's study.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1304
SOMEONE wheels SOMEONE into the room.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1305
He picks up a thick file.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1306
He drops it on his desk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1307
SOMEONE turns the Wennerstrom file his way. SOMEONE peeks at it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1308
SOMEONE meets SOMEONE's misty gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1309
The older man wears a nasal breathing tube.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1310
SOMEONE meets SOMEONE at the front door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1312
As SOMEONE wheels SOMEONE into the hall SOMEONE steps inside,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1313
looks around, and spots her uncle.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1314
SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE who wheels himself toward her, his lips curled downward.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1315
Behind him, SOMEONE and SOMEONE step into the hall.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1316
Holding her uncle's gaze, SOMEONE caresses the lapel of her coat self-soothingly.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1317
He peers back. His gaze crestfallen and disbelieving.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1318
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look on solemnly.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1319
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1320
He begins to cry as they embrace.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1321
SOMEONE heads out a back door and SOMEONE follows.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1324
Now SOMEONE dismantles the family tree.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1326
He puffs on a cigarette.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1327
In Stockholm.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1328
SOMEONE enters his apartment with a bag of groceries and gives her a terse nod.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1329
Entering the kitchen she heads right past the two publishers to a counter.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1330
SOMEONE shoots a look to SOMEONE who shrugs.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1331
Now a TV shows a news report.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1332
SOMEONE watches from his bed.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1333
SOMEONE finds a large envelope under his front door.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1334
He enters the bedroom and tosses a copy of the new issue to SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1335
Later, at a SOMEONE, a monitor shows a news headline. Financial Mafia?
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1336
Wennerstrom accused of wide-ranging crimes. Financial markets rocked by news.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1337
Sitting with SOMEONE, SOMEONE wears a gloomy look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1338
He reaches for his wallet.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1339
His lips stutter.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1340
He casually sips from a mug.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1341
Now, news reports play in various high-end stores.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1342
SOMEONE buys designer clothes and expensive luggage.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1343
She peruses wigs.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1344
From a display rack she grabs a package labeled, Shape Inserts.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1345
In her bathroom she covers the tattoo on her neck with makeup.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1346
She snaps a photo of herself in a wig with long blonde hair.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1347
The heavyset techie gives her fake credit cards and a counterfeit passport.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1348
Now disguised in her wig and designer clothes, she hands the passport to a custom's official at the Zurich airport.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1349
He stamps it and hands it back.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1350
Later an SUV glides up a long driveway to a luxury hotel on a mountain.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1351
Inside, SOMEONE approaches the front desk.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1352
She hands it over then eyes a surveillance camera on the ceiling through her chunky sunglasses.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1353
As the desk clerk scans the passport its image appears on a monitor under the fake name SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1355
Now, stripped down to her underwear and leather gloves in her hotel bathroom,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1356
SOMEONE removes the padded inserts from her bra.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1357
Entering a sitting room with a cigarette between her lips she sits down at her laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1358
As she accesses SOMEONE's account information a news report plays on a nearby TV.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1359
Later, in her posh disguise SOMEONE steps out of a Rolls Royce. As a businessman escorts her through a building
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1360
she tilts her face away from a security camera. They reach a man's office.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1361
SOMEONE sits across from him.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1362
She opens her purse.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1363
The banker checks his watch.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1364
He takes her list of codes. Later, in her hotel suite.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1365
Sitting on her bed SOMEONE listens to the report as she counts stacks of bonds.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1366
Now, a man totes two bags for her as he leads her into a building.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1367
In an office, the disguised woman reveals the bonds inside one of the bags.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1368
She sips from a teacup as the bespectacled banker punches numbers into a calculator.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1369
Noticing a lipstick smear near the cups rim, SOMEONE wipes it away with a gloved finger.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1370
The bank official shows her the calculator.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1371
The total is $3,212,655,732.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1372
In her hotel suite SOMEONE dials a cell phone hooked into her laptop.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1374
Then initiates a transaction on the website for Dorfman Bank.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1375
Grabbing a cigarette
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1376
she moves to a balcony's open door and lights up.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1377
In disguise, SOMEONE walks an airport's bustling skyway.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1379
she removes her earrings and lets them drop down a sink's drain.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1380
She takes off her necklace, wraps it in a paper towel and shoves it in the trash.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1381
Later, she rides an escalator down from the terminal to a train platform.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1382
Arriving just as a sleek bullet train glides up.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1392
Now, at the Millennium offices SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and their colleagues watch a news report.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1393
SOMEONE looks out a window then exits.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1394
SOMEONE joins her outside.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1395
She gives him a check.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1396
She offers him her cigarette. He notices SOMEONE watching them from the window.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1397
She glances away with a faint smile.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1398
Puffing on her cigarette she glances over her shoulder as she walks away.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1399
SOMEONE stares after her.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1400
In the Millennium offices a goateed man approaches SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1401
She turns from the window.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1402
Now, in his apartment, SOMEONE sits across a chessboard from SOMEONE. As he feebly inches a pawn forward she helps him, then lowers her gaze and bites her thumb.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1403
He crooks his eyebrow in an intrigued look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1404
Now SOMEONE enters a SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1405
Turning his back to the TV he opens a newspaper.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1406
Now, a tailor unzips a garment bag and shows SOMEONE a black leather jacket.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1407
She compares it to SOMEONE's jacket in the photo of him and SOMEONE.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1408
Zips the bag back up. SOMEONE gives a wistful look.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1409
Now, at her apartment she intently writes a message inside a card then slides it into an envelope.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1410
The card's cover shows a horse bending its neck down as a child bundled against the cold pats its head.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1411
SOMEONE writes an M on the front of the envelope then underlines it.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1412
She stares off.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1413
Snow drifts to the ground as SOMEONE glides her motorcycle down a hill and parks across the street from SOMEONE's apartment building.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1415
Dismounting, she removes her helmet.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1416
Then takes the garment bag with her gift off the bike's rear cargo rack.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1417
She sees SOMEONE and SOMEONE leaving the building and watches unnoticed as he drapes an arm over her shoulders.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1418
The couple heads down a walkway to a waiting taxi at the top of a hill.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1419
SOMEONE watches woundedly as they climb into the cab, then lowers her heartbroken gaze.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1420
Turning away, she tosses SOMEONE's gift into a dumpster against the side of a building.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1421
She glances at the cab as it drives off,
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1422
then dawns her helmet and mounts her bike.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1423
She speeds off down the cobblestone street, her figure disappearing from view as she rounds a corner.
THE_GIRL_WITH_THE_DRAGON_TATTOO_DVS1424
Exterior lamps on buildings catch falling flakes of snow in their pale shafts of light as they drift to the ground.