In the high-ceilinged modern facility, a slender woman with short, curly hair swivels in her chair.
THE_CALL_DVS68
She raises her arms as a message flashes on her screen. Call disconnected.
THE_CALL_DVS69
The 911 operator locks her hands behind her head and leans back in her chair.
THE_CALL_DVS70
Looking at her computer, she exhales deeply and sets her arms down.
THE_CALL_DVS71
She types Unit on scene 13:48 hours, then answers an incoming call.
THE_CALL_DVS72
She tilts her head and smiles.
THE_CALL_DVS73
She trades a smile with an older woman.
THE_CALL_DVS74
A cop enters and gives the operator a kiss.
THE_CALL_DVS75
She leaves with the policeman.
THE_CALL_DVS76
Now outside, he sits on a table and she stands between his knees in an embrace.
THE_CALL_DVS77
Her arms around his neck, she shrugs coyly.
THE_CALL_DVS78
He gives her a sly smile.
THE_CALL_DVS83
Now, the woman returns to her desk.
THE_CALL_DVS84
SOMEONE smiles and accepts an incoming call.
THE_CALL_DVS93
A man reaches into the broken window as SOMEONE goes to the stairs. SOMEONE rapidly types on her computer.
THE_CALL_DVS109
The intruder walks down the upstairs hall and opens one of the doors. As it swings shut behind him, the dark ominous figure stands frozen in a vestibule with an arched entry.
THE_CALL_DVS110
He goes to the archway and briefly surveys the room before kneeling at the foot of the bed.
THE_CALL_DVS112
Catching sight of his reflection in a mirror,
THE_CALL_DVS113
the prowler walks up to an open closet door.
THE_CALL_DVS114
He slowly pulls it closed as he checks behind it.
THE_CALL_DVS116
His face obscured by a ball cap, the menacing man turns. He heads toward a beaded curtain and parts it.
THE_CALL_DVS117
He returns to the vestibule and closes the door to the hall.
THE_CALL_DVS118
Pausing, he slowly goes back into the room.
THE_CALL_DVS119
From the archway, he spies a French window that stands ajar.
THE_CALL_DVS120
The intruder rushes to it and steps onto a small balcony.
THE_CALL_DVS121
A pair of flip flops lies on the ground below.
THE_CALL_DVS122
He rushes inside and leaves the bedroom as our view shifts to SOMEONE, who lies under the bed behind a large box.
THE_CALL_DVS123
SOMEONE exhales deeply.
THE_CALL_DVS124
The phone disconnects.
THE_CALL_DVS125
SOMEONE hits the redial button.
THE_CALL_DVS127
He looks up toward the second floor.
THE_CALL_DVS128
SOMEONE lies still under the bed.
THE_CALL_DVS129
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
THE_CALL_DVS130
In the bedroom, SOMEONE holds the phone to her ear and quivers in the darkness.
THE_CALL_DVS135
SOMEONE's glistening eyes dart. She brings a hand to her headset.
THE_CALL_DVS136
SOMEONE's boss watches her from across the room.
THE_CALL_DVS137
At the house, the man holds SOMEONE down with a latex-gloved hand.
THE_CALL_DVS140
SOMEONE's eyes dart about frantically. She turns to her coworker.
THE_CALL_DVS141
A message on her screen flashes. Call disconnected.
THE_CALL_DVS142
She rises and rushes out.
THE_CALL_DVS144
She opens a door marked Quiet Room and bursts in on a lounging coworker.
THE_CALL_DVS145
Blurry-eyed, she puts a hand on her temple and looks away from him.
THE_CALL_DVS146
The man leaves and shuts the door. SOMEONE grips her head with both hands, pacing.
THE_CALL_DVS147
Her boss enters the room and she turns to face her.
THE_CALL_DVS148
SOMEONE shrugs and shakes her head.
THE_CALL_DVS149
She steps past her boss and leaves the room.
THE_CALL_DVS150
The stern-faced woman stares at the door and takes a heavy breath.
THE_CALL_DVS151
Now, SOMEONE lies on her back. A bare hand caresses a lock of hair pressed against her neck.
THE_CALL_DVS152
The hand grips her chin and a finger passes over her mouth.
THE_CALL_DVS153
A bloody mouth fills our view.
THE_CALL_DVS154
SOMEONE wakes with a start.
THE_CALL_DVS155
A shadowy figure stands at a window in her door.
THE_CALL_DVS156
She puts her face in her hands.
THE_CALL_DVS157
SOMEONE stands outside.
THE_CALL_DVS158
She slowly gets out of bed.
THE_CALL_DVS159
She passes a framed photo of a police officer.
THE_CALL_DVS163
SOMEONE drives.
THE_CALL_DVS164
She reaches for the radio dial.
THE_CALL_DVS165
Now on the main floor of the call center, SOMEONE's boss stands behind a bank of monitors with her hands on her hips.
THE_CALL_DVS166
The young operator walks by SOMEONE, who looks up from his desk.
THE_CALL_DVS167
SOMEONE gazes listlessly around the busy room and makes her way to her workstation.
THE_CALL_DVS168
Her chest heaves as she looks over the cluster of monitors, keyboard, and audio controls before her.
THE_CALL_DVS169
She slowly sits and rests a hand next to her keyboard.
THE_CALL_DVS171
SOMEONE turns to her coworker.
THE_CALL_DVS172
She nods to her friend and they both face their terminals.
THE_CALL_DVS174
Facing the screens, she relaxes her shoulders. She stares at the main display and the green Ready icon in the center of the interface.
THE_CALL_DVS175
The green icon changes color.
THE_CALL_DVS176
SOMEONE stares at the now red Not Ready icon.
THE_CALL_DVS177
Her hand hovers over the space bar on her keyboard.
THE_CALL_DVS178
She looks down at it.
THE_CALL_DVS184
The icon turns green.
THE_CALL_DVS185
She shuts her eyes.
THE_CALL_DVS186
She opens them and exhales.
THE_CALL_DVS187
Another call comes in and she hits the space bar.
THE_CALL_DVS188
SOMEONE looks back.
THE_CALL_DVS189
Her coworker stands and stares with her gaze fixed ahead.
THE_CALL_DVS190
The young operator bolts out of her chair.
THE_CALL_DVS191
On a large monitor, she watches aerial news footage of investigators unearthing a corpse.
THE_CALL_DVS193
Kidnap victim's body found in Lancaster.
THE_CALL_DVS194
SOMEONE looks at the pixelated form lying on a black tarp.
THE_CALL_DVS195
Now on the sunlit roof of the call center.
THE_CALL_DVS196
She leans on a cement ledge.
THE_CALL_DVS197
Officer SOMEONE goes to her.
THE_CALL_DVS198
He joins her at the edge of the building and looks at her tenderly.
THE_CALL_DVS199
Resting her chin in her hand and keeping her eyes on the city, she nods.
THE_CALL_DVS200
She tilts her head toward her boyfriend and looks at him with glistening eyes.
THE_CALL_DVS203
She nods.
THE_CALL_DVS204
SOMEONE looks into her eyes, then steps back and leaves SOMEONE by the edge of the roof.
THE_CALL_DVS205
She rubs her face and sets her chin between her hands.
THE_CALL_DVS211
Words appear. Six months later.
THE_CALL_DVS213
Now, patrons ride an escalator in the center of an indoor sunlit mall.
THE_CALL_DVS214
On the lower level, children ride a miniature train around a display of oversized lollipops.
THE_CALL_DVS215
Amid the shoppers, two teenage girls ride up the escalator.
THE_CALL_DVS216
Autumn pulls out a second phone.
THE_CALL_DVS217
Smiling, Autumn's blond friend shakes her head.
THE_CALL_DVS218
Meanwhile, SOMEONE dumps a prescription pill into her hand by a running bathroom faucet.
THE_CALL_DVS219
She sips water from a clear plastic cup and thrusts back her head as she swallows.
THE_CALL_DVS220
With her eyes closed, she leans on the sink.
THE_CALL_DVS221
The words Training Unit stand out on her button up shirt.
THE_CALL_DVS223
SOMEONE gazes at herself.
THE_CALL_DVS224
Later, she places the pill bottle beside several others at a locker.
THE_CALL_DVS225
She eyes a newspaper clipping for Leah Templeton's memorial taped inside the door.
THE_CALL_DVS226
Now in a conference room, SOMEONE faces a table of trainees.
THE_CALL_DVS228
Now, she leads them through the facility.
THE_CALL_DVS241
SOMEONE stops and turns.
THE_CALL_DVS252
They gaze down at the bustling main floor.
THE_CALL_DVS255
Stopping, Autumn points at her friend.
THE_CALL_DVS256
She smiles and shakes her head as Autumn hurries off.
THE_CALL_DVS257
Sitting alone, the young blond sips her fountain drink and gazes across the court.
THE_CALL_DVS259
From behind a pillar, we watch her put her purse on her shoulder and collect a few shopping bags.
THE_CALL_DVS260
The blond sips her drink, then finds Autumn's prepaid track phone on the table.
THE_CALL_DVS261
She grabs the phone and stands, looking after Autumn.
THE_CALL_DVS262
Smiling, the blond shakes her head and slides the phone into her back pocket.
THE_CALL_DVS263
Now she strolls through a quiet parking garage.
THE_CALL_DVS264
She keeps her eyes on the phone. A sedan almost backs into her.
THE_CALL_DVS270
Her body falls limp and he drags her to the sedan.
THE_CALL_DVS271
In the hive, SOMEONE leads her trainees to a young woman's workstation.
THE_CALL_DVS272
SOMEONE glances at his trainer.
THE_CALL_DVS273
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
THE_CALL_DVS275
Now, a bit of light sneaks through a round car speaker and lands on the blonde's face.
THE_CALL_DVS276
Her closed eyelids quiver as her head slightly jolts about.
THE_CALL_DVS277
Opening her eyes, the dazed teen faces the interior of a car's trunk.
THE_CALL_DVS278
Her eyes shift about.
THE_CALL_DVS279
Slowly blinking, the blond rolls her head to the side.
THE_CALL_DVS280
A soft red light glows on her cheek from one of the tail lights.
THE_CALL_DVS281
The young blond quickly glances around.
THE_CALL_DVS282
Realizing her location, she presses her hands to the roof,
THE_CALL_DVS288
then frantically bangs on the pulsating speaker.
THE_CALL_DVS291
The kidnapper casually taps the wheel as he drives.
THE_CALL_DVS295
As she hits a button, light shines on her face. She sees a new voice mail from Raul and immediately dials 911.
THE_CALL_DVS299
In the hive, SOMEONE faces her trainees.
THE_CALL_DVS302
SOMEONE stops her trainees behind Brooke's station.
THE_CALL_DVS303
The trainees observe as SOMEONE puts on a headset.
THE_CALL_DVS308
SOMEONE searches the room for her boss and spots her on a phone call.
THE_CALL_DVS316
SOMEONE waves Brooke up and takes her place, putting on the headset.
THE_CALL_DVS323
SOMEONE looks to her boss.
THE_CALL_DVS326
The boss faces Brooke.
THE_CALL_DVS371
SOMEONE shifts her gaze.
THE_CALL_DVS384
On a mountain, a red and white cell tower overlooks the sprawling valley. Congested traffic flows along a wide freeway below.
THE_CALL_DVS385
The maroon sedan speeds beneath an overpass, moving easily with other cars in light traffic.
THE_CALL_DVS401
SOMEONE's boss approaches.
THE_CALL_DVS407
From overhead, the maroon sedan speeds along the freeway. The kidnapper reaches for the radio. He cranks the volume as SOMEONE struggles in the trunk. She pries off the tail light's back cover, then grabs a short-handled paint roller.
THE_CALL_DVS426
Now, a call comes in to SOMEONE's station.
THE_CALL_DVS433
SOMEONE enters the plate in their system.
THE_CALL_DVS463
Moving a tarp, her eyes widen.
THE_CALL_DVS465
Slowly closing her eyes, the scared teen presses her lips tight.
THE_CALL_DVS466
An industrial rail yard full of motionless freight trains rests beside the large boulevard. The kidnapper drives along as SOMEONE pries open a paint can with a screw driver.
THE_CALL_DVS478
A search chopper soars overhead.
THE_CALL_DVS479
Approaching a large intersection, the kidnapper slows to a stop in the left turn lane. A thick patch of white paint beneath the right tail light hole drips onto the street.
THE_CALL_DVS480
The kidnapper stretches his neck.
THE_CALL_DVS481
The man stopped next to him lowers his window.
THE_CALL_DVS482
With his shaggy hair slicked back, the suited driver points toward the rear tail light. The kidnapper rolls down his passenger window.
THE_CALL_DVS484
The kidnapper stares at the driver, then glances back.
THE_CALL_DVS485
He peers into the side mirror, then gives the good Samaritan a thumbs up.
THE_CALL_DVS487
Facing forward, the kidnapper's jaw trembles. His teeth clink together as he fixates on the red stop light.
THE_CALL_DVS490
His large sunglasses rest on the center of his nose, exposing his dark, narrow eyes.
THE_CALL_DVS491
SOMEONE uncaps the other paint can and moves it to the hole.
THE_CALL_DVS492
She carefully tilts the can with both hands.
THE_CALL_DVS493
Glancing over, the suited driver watches the mysterious man as the light turns.
THE_CALL_DVS500
She desperately wipes the phone. The kidnapper screeches to a halt in an empty parking lot and marches to the trunk. He glares down at the busted tail light and patch of white paint. SOMEONE's mouth hangs open as she eyes the hole. Lowering the phone, she slips it into her back pocket. The kidnapper chuckles. The frightened teen arms herself with the screw driver.
THE_CALL_DVS508
He aims the screw driver at her eye then runs his fingers along her paint-stained hair.
THE_CALL_DVS509
Clenching his teeth, the kidnapper slams the trunk.
THE_CALL_DVS518
Turning, he sees the suited driver beside his town car and tucks the bottle into his back pocket.
THE_CALL_DVS519
He presses the screw driver to SOMEONE's cheek.
THE_CALL_DVS520
Leaning over the trunk, the kidnapper smiles at the driver.
THE_CALL_DVS521
A tear slides down SOMEONE's cheek.
THE_CALL_DVS522
Turning, the driver heads to his car.
THE_CALL_DVS523
He stops and glances back, then continues forward as the kidnapper looks up from the trunk.
THE_CALL_DVS524
He gives the driver a friendly wave.
THE_CALL_DVS525
The driver puts his hands on the wheel and turns his head.
THE_CALL_DVS526
Adjusting the side mirror, he watches the kidnapper aggressively dig at something in the trunk.
THE_CALL_DVS527
With his brow tensed, the suited driver retrieves his cellphone.
THE_CALL_DVS528
He dials 911, keeping his gaze straight ahead.
THE_CALL_DVS529
The kidnapper shatters the window with a shovel.
THE_CALL_DVS533
The kidnapper bashes the driver's head and stands glaring at the motionless body.
THE_CALL_DVS535
The enraged man starts off, then turns as the helpless driver crawls away.
THE_CALL_DVS539
Backing away, he drops the shovel and turns.
THE_CALL_DVS541
The kidnapper removes a handful of glass shards from his back pocket.
THE_CALL_DVS542
They fall from his trembling hand.
THE_CALL_DVS543
He shifts an anxious gaze between his trunk and the body.
THE_CALL_DVS546
Ripping off his blood-stained shirt, he wipes blood from his undershirt and tosses it down.
THE_CALL_DVS547
The killer faces the sedan with his mouth hanging open.
THE_CALL_DVS548
The terrified teen keeps her eyes on the roof.
THE_CALL_DVS549
Frozen in place, his frenzied gaze softens on the trunk.
THE_CALL_DVS555
Holding her headset, SOMEONE shifts her wide, frantic eyes to the GPS locator screen.
THE_CALL_DVS558
From overhead, we narrow in on the parking lot.
THE_CALL_DVS560
Now, two squad cars speed toward the abandoned sedan and screech to a halt.
THE_CALL_DVS562
With their guns aimed, the officers rush toward the sedan.
THE_CALL_DVS564
Moving to the trunk, SOMEONE nods to SOMEONE and he swings it open.
THE_CALL_DVS565
Only paint supplies remain.
THE_CALL_DVS567
Phillips' eyes shift from the glass shards to a large blood stain.
THE_CALL_DVS571
The kidnapper's face calms as he stares straight ahead.
THE_CALL_DVS572
SOMEONE lies inside the trunk with the driver's body pressed against her back.
THE_CALL_DVS573
Turning her head, she pushes his face off her shoulder and moves an arm from her torso then quickly retrieves the phone.
THE_CALL_DVS580
The driver ignites a lighter.
THE_CALL_DVS588
With his mouth hanging open, the killer lowers the body onto SOMEONE and leans over the trunk.
THE_CALL_DVS590
He places a hand on the driver's face and yanks the screw driver from his flesh.
THE_CALL_DVS591
Clenching his jaw, the killer rips off the release lever and grabs the frightened teen.
THE_CALL_DVS595
SOMEONE's eyes widen.
THE_CALL_DVS599
A female agent dusts for prints.
THE_CALL_DVS602
SOMEONE shares a look with his partner. Nodding, he turns away and notices something on the ground.
THE_CALL_DVS603
The officer removes his sunglasses and takes a few steps forward.
THE_CALL_DVS605
Crouching down, SOMEONE eyes the broken chloroform bottle.
THE_CALL_DVS609
From overhead, cars move along a curvy freeway cutting through mountains.
THE_CALL_DVS610
The kidnapper speeds down the adjacent two-lane surface street.
THE_CALL_DVS611
In the hive, SOMEONE stares at the GPS locator screen with no coordinates found. SOMEONE approaches.
THE_CALL_DVS615
SOMEONE's eyes glisten.
THE_CALL_DVS633
She reaches into his breast pocket and removes a wallet.
THE_CALL_DVS652
Now, the kidnapper pulls into an empty gas station with old style pumps.
THE_CALL_DVS653
Hopping out, he approaches a chubby service attendant with some cash in hand.
THE_CALL_DVS654
He rushes back around the car and opens the gas cap.
THE_CALL_DVS655
Large sweat stains SOMEONE his chest and back.
THE_CALL_DVS656
The cell battery flashes red.
THE_CALL_DVS657
She aims the phone's light around the trunk and spots something.
THE_CALL_DVS658
SOMEONE shifts her anxious gaze.
THE_CALL_DVS660
The attendant shrugs and moves away. Sliding the phone into her pocket, SOMEONE peels back a velcro flap.
THE_CALL_DVS661
The kidnapper anxiously eyes the pump's counters.
THE_CALL_DVS664
In the back seat, the center arm rest flops down.
THE_CALL_DVS665
Sticking her arms out first, SOMEONE crawls through the small opening.
THE_CALL_DVS666
She squeezes her shoulders through and sees the kidnapper with his back turned.
THE_CALL_DVS667
To the right of the hood, the attendant opens boxes of motor oil with a box cutter.
THE_CALL_DVS671
The kidnapper keeps his eyes on the pump as SOMEONE spots the man and desperately waves her arms.
THE_CALL_DVS673
Turning around, the murderer leans on the roof.
THE_CALL_DVS674
SOMEONE grips the front seats and tries pulling her hips through the opening.
THE_CALL_DVS676
It cuts to the picture of SOMEONE with descriptive features and details of the abduction.
THE_CALL_DVS678
The kidnapper's mouth falls open.
THE_CALL_DVS687
Glancing between them, the attendant whips out the box cutter.
THE_CALL_DVS692
The kidnapper glares through the window. SOMEONE glances between them as the attendant reaches for the handle.
THE_CALL_DVS697
Flames instantly consume the attendant.
THE_CALL_DVS698
The kidnapper watches as the burning man flails about. Breaking his stare, the killer rushes to the trunk.
THE_CALL_DVS707
With her jaw trembling, SOMEONE shifts her desperate eyes.
THE_CALL_DVS708
Elsewhere, the police database finds a match for the kidnapper's print.
THE_CALL_DVS712
SOMEONE receives the call.
THE_CALL_DVS715
Her database searches briefly, then loads a smiling photo of the kidnapper.
THE_CALL_DVS716
SOMEONE glares at the image.
THE_CALL_DVS721
Three squad cars arrive at the target home. SOMEONE and his fellow officer hop out with their side arms drawn, rushing past toys in the front lawn.
THE_CALL_DVS722
SOMEONE goes in the front door. SOMEONE finds SOMEONE's wife and kids in the kitchen.
THE_CALL_DVS733
He follows an officer.
THE_CALL_DVS734
SOMEONE eyes the young children.
THE_CALL_DVS735
At the hive.
THE_CALL_DVS740
At SOMEONE's house, the officer leads SOMEONE upstairs.
THE_CALL_DVS742
He points to a wall of framed photos.
THE_CALL_DVS744
SOMEONE eyes photos of a beautiful, lively, blond teen. Several depict her and a smiling young boy.
THE_CALL_DVS745
In a glass display case, a light illuminates a portrait of the blond. He spots a poem titled My Sister.
THE_CALL_DVS750
SOMEONE closely examines a twirling ballerina inside a pink jewelry box.
THE_CALL_DVS751
On a secluded road, the town car rolls through a field.
THE_CALL_DVS752
From the other side of a grimy window lined with figurines, we watch the car slow to a stop.
THE_CALL_DVS753
SOMEONE emerges from the car and pops the trunk. Through the window, we watch the killer pull SOMEONE out.
THE_CALL_DVS754
Hefting her over one shoulder, SOMEONE notices the cellphone in her back pocket.
THE_CALL_DVS755
He sees it's been connected for an hour and 28 minutes.
THE_CALL_DVS756
He lowers her to the ground, covers her mouth, and puts the phone to his ear.
THE_CALL_DVS757
SOMEONE stares wide-eyed at her computer screen.
THE_CALL_DVS758
SOMEONE's smiling DMV photo stares back.
THE_CALL_DVS759
Behind the car, he crouches over his victim with his mouth ajar.
THE_CALL_DVS761
SOMEONE's mouth tenses and she wets her lips.
THE_CALL_DVS766
At the hive, SOMEONE listens to another phone and watches SOMEONE.
THE_CALL_DVS771
The trembling killer stares at the ground.
THE_CALL_DVS772
SOMEONE's GPS locator still reads No location information.
THE_CALL_DVS776
SOMEONE remembers SOMEONE's phone call.
THE_CALL_DVS778
The call disconnects as a flashback shows SOMEONE bringing a fist down toward SOMEONE.
THE_CALL_DVS779
The GPS graphic disappears from SOMEONE's screen.
THE_CALL_DVS780
She blinks her glistening eyes and takes a few ragged breaths.
THE_CALL_DVS781
SOMEONE tears off her headset, catching the attention of her coworker.
THE_CALL_DVS783
At SOMEONE's home, SOMEONE looks over a collection of photos on the wall. In one, a young SOMEONE poses with his sister in front of a truck outside a house.
THE_CALL_DVS784
SOMEONE removes the photo from the wall.
THE_CALL_DVS785
In the kitchen, SOMEONE interviews SOMEONE's wife.
THE_CALL_DVS795
She keeps her hand over her mouth.
THE_CALL_DVS796
SOMEONE reaches for his walkie.
THE_CALL_DVS797
SOMEONE runs a search.
THE_CALL_DVS798
An officer approaches SOMEONE as he leaves with SOMEONE.
THE_CALL_DVS806
With a concerned gaze, he stares off and lowers his walkie.
THE_CALL_DVS808
At the hive, SOMEONE reads articles on the SOMEONE Templeton murder.
THE_CALL_DVS809
An aerial photo shows the blond teen's body stripped down in the desert with blood around her head.
THE_CALL_DVS813
A pair of lights illuminate the doorway of SOMEONE's childhood cottage.
THE_CALL_DVS814
One behind the other, several groups of officers stealthily approach from all sides, weapons drawn.
THE_CALL_DVS815
A SWAT team takes the lead and smashes the front door in with a battering ram.
THE_CALL_DVS818
In the hive, SOMEONE and her coworkers listen as the office ers move through the dark cottage.
THE_CALL_DVS824
As SOMEONE leaves her workstation, SOMEONE watches her go.
THE_CALL_DVS825
The frustrated operator walks into the break room with a hand on her forehead.
THE_CALL_DVS826
SOMEONE enters.
THE_CALL_DVS827
SOMEONE rolls her head, then gives SOMEONE a look and leaves.
THE_CALL_DVS828
Now darkness obscures our view.
THE_CALL_DVS829
Now, four wheels, the front two large and the back two tiny, roll across a dingy concrete floor.
THE_CALL_DVS830
SOMEONE sits upright in a wheelchair, her left eye nearly swollen shut.
THE_CALL_DVS831
Her right eye shifts as SOMEONE lowers the high chair back, creating a gurney.
THE_CALL_DVS832
He fills an old white sink with water,
THE_CALL_DVS833
then aligns a pair of metal scissors on a tray beside two combs.
THE_CALL_DVS834
SOMEONE turns on a tank of nitric oxide.
THE_CALL_DVS837
Gripping the top of her head, he roughly keeps the mask in place.
THE_CALL_DVS839
Her resistance subsides.
THE_CALL_DVS840
Now, SOMEONE cuts off her shirt, stripping her down to her bra. He removes her sandals and grips her ankles as she pulls away. Now, SOMEONE lowers her head back over the lip of the sink and sprays down her hair.
THE_CALL_DVS841
As he massages her scalp with shampoo, he keeps his face close to hers.
THE_CALL_DVS842
Later, he holds his hand over her mouth,
THE_CALL_DVS843
then replaces it with a gas mask.
THE_CALL_DVS844
SOMEONE presses it against her until she calms.
THE_CALL_DVS845
Now, the killer slides a cassette tape into an old boom box.
THE_CALL_DVS846
SOMEONE springs SOMEONE's chair into the upright position and circles her with his hand on her head.
THE_CALL_DVS849
Sitting beside her, she looks away as he takes a comb off the tray.
THE_CALL_DVS850
The disturbed man gently combs her hair in front of her face.
THE_CALL_DVS851
SOMEONE tries squeezing her left hand out from the thick restraint strap as SOMEONE trims a little of her hair.
THE_CALL_DVS852
Her hair still in her face, SOMEONE cringes as SOMEONE strokes her cheeks.
THE_CALL_DVS853
He brushes the hair away from her right eye.
THE_CALL_DVS854
SOMEONE flashes a tight smile as SOMEONE stares with a horrified gaze.
THE_CALL_DVS856
The killer turns away and SOMEONE squeezes her left hand free from the wrist restraint.
THE_CALL_DVS859
He falls back and she frees her other hand.
THE_CALL_DVS860
The teen hurries into a narrow dark hallway.
THE_CALL_DVS862
In the hall, SOMEONE reaches a dead end and backtracks.
THE_CALL_DVS865
She turns the lock and rests her head, then spots something across the room.
THE_CALL_DVS866
SOMEONE trudges toward the door.
THE_CALL_DVS867
She steps forward, her jaw hanging slack.
THE_CALL_DVS869
SOMEONE breaks through the door and grabs her, covering her mouth.
THE_CALL_DVS872
Now, an officer patrols the hive as several workstations lie quiet and vacant.
THE_CALL_DVS873
SOMEONE sits at her desk working a recorder's controls.
THE_CALL_DVS875
She lifts her head from her hand and her eyes widen.
THE_CALL_DVS876
She rewinds the recording.
THE_CALL_DVS877
She stops the track and adjusts the audio levels, then replays the recording with her eyes closed.
THE_CALL_DVS878
SOMEONE tosses off her headset and covers her eyes. At a road block, SOMEONE instructs officers.
THE_CALL_DVS880
SOMEONE looks around the hive.
THE_CALL_DVS882
He hangs up and approaches a line of cars.
THE_CALL_DVS883
At her desk, SOMEONE removes her cell from her ear and lowers her thoughtful gaze.
THE_CALL_DVS884
Holding the phone against her chin,
THE_CALL_DVS885
she chews her fingertip and looks at a map of the Santa Clarita hills.
THE_CALL_DVS886
She glances over her shoulder.
THE_CALL_DVS887
She looks down at her watch. SOMEONE taps her thumbnail against the watch face.
THE_CALL_DVS888
Glancing back up to her monitor, she finds SOMEONE's profile with a smiling photo.
THE_CALL_DVS889
Her eyes dart and she rises from her chair.
THE_CALL_DVS891
A single car's headlights cut through the darkness.
THE_CALL_DVS892
SOMEONE drives.
THE_CALL_DVS893
A police cruiser passes in the opposite direction.
THE_CALL_DVS894
Another follows, coming down the mountain road.
THE_CALL_DVS897
Later, she parks her car on a dirt road.
THE_CALL_DVS898
SOMEONE shuts off her car and stays seated.
THE_CALL_DVS899
The car faces SOMEONE's childhood cottage.
THE_CALL_DVS900
Three porch lights illuminate the exterior.
THE_CALL_DVS901
Now, SOMEONE slowly pushes the front door open and shines a flashlight inside.
THE_CALL_DVS902
She hits a light switch, which turns on a single lamp that barely sheds light on the room.
THE_CALL_DVS904
Our view spies on her through an inner door opened a crack.
THE_CALL_DVS905
SOMEONE's flashlight beam finds a couch and settles briefly on a big wheel tricycle.
THE_CALL_DVS907
On the fireplace mantle, she finds family photographs, including ones of SOMEONE and his kids.
THE_CALL_DVS910
From behind the door, we watch as she moves the flashlight across the mantle.
THE_CALL_DVS911
Our view lingers on the operator, then ducks back as she turns toward us.
THE_CALL_DVS912
SOMEONE spots an open doorway and moves into the next room.
THE_CALL_DVS914
In the corner, plastic sheets cover old furniture.
THE_CALL_DVS915
She finds a step ladder with three paint cans at its base.
THE_CALL_DVS916
Moving through the space, she enters another room filled with boxed belongings.
THE_CALL_DVS917
SOMEONE aims her flashlight at the boxes and singles one out.
THE_CALL_DVS919
She pulls the flaps open and finds it packed with medical equipment.
THE_CALL_DVS920
SOMEONE picks up a green rubber glove, then drops it disgustedly.
THE_CALL_DVS921
Looking away, she finds another box filled with trophies and photos.
THE_CALL_DVS922
SOMEONE removes a framed picture of SOMEONE's beautiful blond sister.
THE_CALL_DVS923
In it, the lively teen poses on her belly, chin in her hands and ankles crossed up behind her.
THE_CALL_DVS924
SOMEONE digs deeper into the box.
THE_CALL_DVS926
The operator pulls out a photo album.
THE_CALL_DVS927
Flipping through it, she finds photos of the young loving siblings.
THE_CALL_DVS928
She studies another portrait of the grinning blond, then finds an envelope with more pictures.
THE_CALL_DVS929
In the first photo, the teen girl sits in the wheelchair gurney wearing a hospital gown.
THE_CALL_DVS930
Only the slightest remnants of hair remain on her head.
THE_CALL_DVS931
SOMEONE compares the picture to SOMEONE's sister's portrait,
THE_CALL_DVS932
which shows off her thick blond hair.
THE_CALL_DVS933
SOMEONE shuffles through more photos showing the sickly girl with her brother at her bedside.
THE_CALL_DVS934
At the end of the stack, she finds a photo of the boy kissing his sister.
THE_CALL_DVS935
Her lips parted, SOMEONE looks away.
THE_CALL_DVS936
Now, SOMEONE exits the cottage and stares out into the darkness with the flashlight at her side.
THE_CALL_DVS937
She turns her head, then steps off the low wooden front porch and heads for her car.
THE_CALL_DVS938
She stops and furrows her brow.
THE_CALL_DVS939
She turns alertly, listening.
THE_CALL_DVS940
Now, SOMEONE shines her flashlight as she traverses a path through a small field.
THE_CALL_DVS941
She walks astride a row of bushes and approaches a flag pole.
THE_CALL_DVS942
The snap hooks at the end of the cable sway against the pole.
THE_CALL_DVS944
the flag flapping in the breeze.
THE_CALL_DVS946
Lowering the flashlight, she looks at the snap hooks then surveys the surrounding area.
THE_CALL_DVS947
SOMEONE turns away from the underbrush and goes deeper into the field.
THE_CALL_DVS948
She carefully sidesteps as she lowers the flashlight and discovers a small black object in the dirt.
THE_CALL_DVS949
Bending over, she picks up a piece of SOMEONE's disposable phone.
THE_CALL_DVS950
SOMEONE glances up thoughtfully.
THE_CALL_DVS951
She rubs the broken face of the phone and drops it back on the ground.
THE_CALL_DVS952
Catching sight of something, she digs around in the dirt and dry grass.
THE_CALL_DVS954
Brushing away, she peels back a flap of material to reveal an inset handle.
THE_CALL_DVS955
She shines her light over it and examines the small grip.
THE_CALL_DVS956
With her free hand, she grabs the handle and yanks on it,
THE_CALL_DVS957
lifting a wide hatch.
THE_CALL_DVS959
SOMEONE shines her flashlight into the hole and sees a metal ladder leading down several feet.
THE_CALL_DVS960
Looking up, she scans the field.
THE_CALL_DVS961
She switches the light to her other hand and reaches into her back pocket.
THE_CALL_DVS962
Taking out her phone, she fumbles with it over the hole and drops it.
THE_CALL_DVS963
The phone lands face up at the foot of the ladder.
THE_CALL_DVS964
The screen displays a flashing message.
THE_CALL_DVS965
SOMEONE stares down at it,
THE_CALL_DVS966
then slowly lifts her head and looks toward the dimly lit cabin.
THE_CALL_DVS967
She turns her gaze back to the opening.
THE_CALL_DVS968
She leans forward and sets her hand on the open hatch.
THE_CALL_DVS970
Putting a foot on the ladder, SOMEONE descends into the underground chamber.
THE_CALL_DVS971
As she lowers herself, she hesitantly lets go of the hatch.
THE_CALL_DVS972
The operator carefully climbs down the ladder to the floor and looks at her phone.
THE_CALL_DVS973
An icon flashes with the words No signal.
THE_CALL_DVS974
She looks deeper into the chamber as she picks up her phone and swings her flashlight around to survey a narrow hallway.
THE_CALL_DVS975
SOMEONE hesitantly steps down the hall and inspects the underground structure.
THE_CALL_DVS976
Rounding a corner, she faces a wall with an exposed wooden frame.
THE_CALL_DVS977
Turning left, she spies a white door with a deadbolt.
THE_CALL_DVS978
She moves to her right and sees a white plastic lawn chair with a work light hung above it.
THE_CALL_DVS979
Shutting her flashlight off,
THE_CALL_DVS981
Haphazardly nailed slats of wood crisscross the openings between support beams.
THE_CALL_DVS983
She passes into a low-ceilinged room bisected by the crumbling wooden skeleton of a wall.
THE_CALL_DVS985
As she steps forward, the woman cautiously puts out a hand and lightly leans on a dingy wooden partition.
THE_CALL_DVS986
She looks at a light shining through a half open door.
THE_CALL_DVS988
She retreats as SOMEONE appears in the door crack and heads in her direction.
THE_CALL_DVS989
He holds a torn shirt and cloth and tosses them down.
THE_CALL_DVS990
Now, SOMEONE scurries back through the white door and shuts it, pressing herself against it.
THE_CALL_DVS993
SOMEONE stares off, then picks up a large bucket and goes back to the well-lit room.
THE_CALL_DVS994
SOMEONE hunches against the door in the darkness, then looks around.
THE_CALL_DVS995
She turns on her flashlight and peers at the wall to her right.
THE_CALL_DVS996
A small green chair sits next to an open wardrobe and a small crystal chandelier hangs over the room.
THE_CALL_DVS997
SOMEONE steps farther into the space and fixes her gaze.
THE_CALL_DVS998
Her eyes widening, the 911 operator stands frozen.
THE_CALL_DVS999
She hides as SOMEONE enters.
THE_CALL_DVS1000
He flips on a light and paces tensely around the space.
THE_CALL_DVS1001
The sweaty killer's gaze darts wildly about.
THE_CALL_DVS1002
He stares downward by the door and stills himself.
THE_CALL_DVS1003
SOMEONE glances up and across the room.
THE_CALL_DVS1004
As he walks away from the door, our view shifts to reveal a pink twin bed covered in blood.
THE_CALL_DVS1006
SOMEONE looks at the grim sight and softly smiles.
THE_CALL_DVS1007
He goes to a mirrored vanity.
THE_CALL_DVS1008
On it, a wig form wears straight, flaxen hair.
THE_CALL_DVS1009
On the other side of the room,
THE_CALL_DVS1010
SOMEONE hides behind the open door of the wardrobe.
THE_CALL_DVS1011
She watches SOMEONE tensely through the thin crack between the hinges.
THE_CALL_DVS1013
Leaning forward, she sees him with his ring finger in his mouth.
THE_CALL_DVS1015
He slides his finger from his lips, leaving his wedding ring between his teeth.
THE_CALL_DVS1016
SOMEONE takes it out of his mouth and places it on the finger of a white mannequin hand sitting on the vanity.
THE_CALL_DVS1018
He stares at the wig form.
THE_CALL_DVS1019
Behind it sits a childhood photo of SOMEONE and his sister.
THE_CALL_DVS1021
His mouth quivering, the killer gazes at the mannequin's impassive face.
THE_CALL_DVS1022
SOMEONE spies him through the crack as he picks up the mannequin head.
THE_CALL_DVS1023
SOMEONE holds it close to his face with one hand and sits on the bed with his back to SOMEONE.
THE_CALL_DVS1024
He caresses the hair tenderly, then pulls it off of the head.
THE_CALL_DVS1025
A dried red drip of blood remains on the mannequin forehead.
THE_CALL_DVS1026
SOMEONE examines the interior of the wig.
THE_CALL_DVS1027
SOMEONE's mouth falls open as she sees the gory scalp underneath the long blond hair in his hands.
THE_CALL_DVS1028
She watches him press his face into the hair and inhale deeply.
THE_CALL_DVS1029
SOMEONE falls back on the bed with the scalp on top of his face.
THE_CALL_DVS1030
SOMEONE's eye stares fixedly from the narrow space behind the door.
THE_CALL_DVS1031
SOMEONE lifts the hair and inspects it.
THE_CALL_DVS1033
Turning it over, he pulls out a thin purple extension.
THE_CALL_DVS1034
SOMEONE balks. He tosses it aside.
THE_CALL_DVS1041
He throws the hair into a mini fridge with several other bagged scalps.
THE_CALL_DVS1042
SOMEONE shifts her gaze and discovers SOMEONE absent from her view.
THE_CALL_DVS1043
She turns slightly and the agitated killer appears.
THE_CALL_DVS1044
He stares intently in her direction.
THE_CALL_DVS1045
SOMEONE takes a few measured steps towards the wardrobe, his shirt soaked with sweat.
THE_CALL_DVS1046
Coming within inches of the hidden woman,
THE_CALL_DVS1047
he turns to face the hanging clothes and sets his hand on top of the open door.
THE_CALL_DVS1048
SOMEONE shuts her mouth in a tight SOMEONE while SOMEONE closes his eyes and smells the contents of the wardrobe.
THE_CALL_DVS1055
His fingers hang over the thin door above SOMEONE. She eyes them while SOMEONE buries his face in his shirt sleeve. SOMEONE abruptly turns away and looks at the wig form on the bed.
THE_CALL_DVS1057
The lights in the room go out. SOMEONE puts her hand over her mouth.
THE_CALL_DVS1066
SOMEONE hangs up and faces the officers leaning over SOMEONE's body.
THE_CALL_DVS1068
SOMEONE's upside down face peers down beside it.
THE_CALL_DVS1069
His image blurs then refocuses.
THE_CALL_DVS1072
Standing behind the wheelchair, SOMEONE leans over SOMEONE, who wears a shower cap on her head and the gas mask over her mouth and nose.
THE_CALL_DVS1073
He adjusts the chair into its reclined position.
THE_CALL_DVS1074
A tube from SOMEONE's mask leads to the nitric oxide tank.
THE_CALL_DVS1075
SOMEONE grabs a large black bucket and sets it down next to SOMEONE.
THE_CALL_DVS1076
He carefully stuffs loose locks of her flaxen hair into the clear plastic shower cap.
THE_CALL_DVS1078
He places his hands on either side of SOMEONE's head.
THE_CALL_DVS1079
The teen shuts her eyes.
THE_CALL_DVS1080
SOMEONE goes across the room and retrieves a pair of latex gloves.
THE_CALL_DVS1083
He removes the sheath from a scalpel.
THE_CALL_DVS1084
The killer pulls back SOMEONE's shower cap, revealing a dotted marker line on her forehead.
THE_CALL_DVS1091
He cuts into her forehead.
THE_CALL_DVS1095
SOMEONE collapses as SOMEONE whacks his head with the wig form. He turns to her and she bashes him again. She stands over him and breaks the ceramic head over his.
THE_CALL_DVS1096
SOMEONE runs to SOMEONE and looks over the shirtless and bruised captive.
THE_CALL_DVS1097
She removes her mask and shower cap and holds her face.
THE_CALL_DVS1100
SOMEONE turns to see SOMEONE behind her. He charges and tackles her to the ground. With his gloved hands, he picks her up by the collar and slams her into the wall. He drags the struggling woman across the room. She pulls away with all her might and SOMEONE takes her head and shoves it into the utility sink full of water.
THE_CALL_DVS1101
He holds her down as her body tenses and bucks. SOMEONE fights for her life and briefly comes up for air before SOMEONE submerges her head again.
THE_CALL_DVS1102
She screams underwater.
THE_CALL_DVS1103
SOMEONE looks at her wrists, then at SOMEONE, his back turned to the wakening girl.
THE_CALL_DVS1104
SOMEONE's face slackens and her body begins to relax.
THE_CALL_DVS1105
SOMEONE stoops over her as her struggling weakens.
THE_CALL_DVS1108
SOMEONE stands pointing a pair of surgical scissors at her kidnapper.
THE_CALL_DVS1110
SOMEONE takes a step back as SOMEONE rises to face them.
THE_CALL_DVS1111
She sees a deep gash running from between his eyebrows down his right cheek.
THE_CALL_DVS1118
Pulling herself out of the hole, she staggers away from it with SOMEONE close behind.
THE_CALL_DVS1119
He stands up, his eyes locking on the escaping woman before him.
THE_CALL_DVS1120
He arches his back and winces.
THE_CALL_DVS1121
SOMEONE slows her pace and turns around.
THE_CALL_DVS1122
SOMEONE looks behind him, facing SOMEONE.
THE_CALL_DVS1123
Our view shifts down behind SOMEONE to the surgical scissors protruding from his lower back.
THE_CALL_DVS1124
SOMEONE watches nervously as he grips the scissor handle and slowly yanks the instrument out of his body.
THE_CALL_DVS1125
He raises the bloody blades to eye level.
THE_CALL_DVS1127
He looks at SOMEONE.
THE_CALL_DVS1128
SOMEONE delivers a high kick to his back and he falls halfway through the hatch. The killer desperately fights to find perches on the ground as he dangles over the hole.
THE_CALL_DVS1132
She and SOMEONE peer down at the unconscious man.
THE_CALL_DVS1133
SOMEONE looks over the hole at SOMEONE, who stands shivering.
THE_CALL_DVS1134
She stares wide-eyes at her rescuer.
THE_CALL_DVS1135
The operator searches her pockets and pulls her phone out of her jeans.
THE_CALL_DVS1136
She activates the screen and dials 911.
THE_CALL_DVS1137
She looks up at the young girl, who shifts her eyes down to the open hatch.
THE_CALL_DVS1138
SOMEONE follows SOMEONE's gaze.
THE_CALL_DVS1139
SOMEONE looks up again, her bruised left eye almost swollen shut,
THE_CALL_DVS1140
a deep laceration marring her forehead.
THE_CALL_DVS1141
The two survivors exchange a knowing look.
THE_CALL_DVS1143
His sweaty head sags against his chest.
THE_CALL_DVS1144
He sits up and blinks several times.
THE_CALL_DVS1146
He catches sight of duct tape binding his wrists to the wheelchair.
THE_CALL_DVS1147
A thick chain circles his torso.
THE_CALL_DVS1148
SOMEONE fights to free himself from the chair in his own makeshift operating room.
THE_CALL_DVS1152
He turns as SOMEONE and SOMEONE come into view.
THE_CALL_DVS1154
He squints slightly and scrutinizes SOMEONE's face.
THE_CALL_DVS1157
She stares him down and nods.
THE_CALL_DVS1164
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
THE_CALL_DVS1170
She leans in close to the killer's face.
THE_CALL_DVS1178
He looks at her pleadingly.