In a classroom the teenage boy draws in his textbook, sketching a mustached man with a worried face.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS19
As a matronly teacher makes her way down an aisle other students hand her their assignments.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS20
The young artist sits concentrating, shading a shirt collar under the worried face.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS21
SOMEONE collects his things and heads out. Now outside, he cuts across a grove of leafless trees beside a river. He stops and gazes ahead. He stands alone in his dark coat before a backdrop of buildings and a stonewall. Now he enters the school office where an assistant does paperwork.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS22
A man behind a window beckons SOMEONE sternly.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS23
In the Principal's office the young man slings his backpack to the floor.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS24
SOMEONE drops his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS25
SOMEONE gazes a scant at the departing student.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS26
Collecting his book bag, SOMEONE heads off. Now he emerges from a stairwell unto the school roof. With parted lips he stares through the chain linked fence toward a highway and a distant bridge spanning the nearby river. Glancing over his shoulder, he spots an onlooker across the rooftop.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS27
One of the three students from the lunchroom, a blond girl, exhales smoke and meets his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS28
As SOMEONE faintly smiles, the stairwell door opens.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS29
The blond tosses her cigarette through the fence.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS30
SOMEONE quickly takes out a cigarette.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS31
A dark haired faculty member arrives.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS32
The blond mouths thank you as she leaves.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS33
Later. Entering a stylish apartment, SOMEONE walks a hall to a spacious living room with a comfy sitting area and a baby grand piano. In the kitchen he pours a bowl of cereal. A middle-aged woman enters and sets a briefcase on the table. SOMEONE averts his gaze from hers as he gets milk from the fridge.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS34
He takes his leave. Now seated at a white canvas in school he draws in pencil. Charcoal portraits decorate the walls.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS35
A gray haired bearded instructor approaches glowering.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS36
His drawing shows a fist punching the teeth out of the bearded teacher's grotesque caricature. SOMEONE punches him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS38
Other art students glance up from their work. Now, SOMEONE exits the building. As the blond girl tries to walk abreast of him, SOMEONE ignores her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS39
She catches up on the sidewalk.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS40
On a nearby court boys shoot baskets.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS41
SOMEONE bites her lip thoughtfully.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS42
SOMEONE glares as she spots
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS43
a couple canoodling on a brown stone stairway.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS44
SOMEONE in a negligee and robe, the woman kisses a younger man, then flirtatiously touches his coat lapel. Her gaze follows as he makes his way past SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS45
SOMEONE's mother heads indoors. SOMEONE stares, transfixed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS46
The kids enter a well-appointed dining area where SOMEONE's mom holds a drink.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS47
Now, the three share drinks on a patio.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS48
Mrs. SOMEONE touches SOMEONE's leg. He jolts spilling his beer.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS49
SOMEONE rolls her eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS50
Mrs. SOMEONE steps away.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS51
SOMEONE grins, his eyes darting.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS52
SOMEONE rises, smiling. SOMEONE's gaze meet his expectantly
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS53
and she offers a demure smile. SOMEONE returns a winsome shrug.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS54
He lingers a moment then heads inside.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS55
SOMEONE leans forward, resting her head on her hand.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS56
Now, leafless trees silhouette the dusky horizon where SOMEONE stops and gazes off.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS57
He opens the door to his dimly lit apartment.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS58
He flicks a light switch, then another with no effect. Candles illuminate the living room and dining area.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS59
At the table, SOMEONE's mother shares a meal with a middle aged man.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS61
Later on a balcony, he gazes toward the twinkling Manhattan skyline.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS62
At school a pretty teacher in bookish glasses leads a class.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS63
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE in the desk to his right.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS64
SOMEONE adds detail to a doodle die ball.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS65
He looks up.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS66
SOMEONE absent-mindedly thumbs the pages of a book.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS67
SOMEONE grins.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS68
Under the teacher's beaming gaze he fidgets.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS69
He shoots a glance at SOMEONE. Now he crosses the lunchroom where SOMEONE sits with her two friends, a dark haired girl and a preppy guy. SOMEONE catches his eye as SOMEONE starts to take a seat at an empty table.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS70
He approaches, tray in hand.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS71
SOMEONE hands him a textbook.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS72
SOMEONE scans the pages revealing severe black and white renderings of faces, eyes and mouths. Some punctuated with red.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS73
SOMEONE nods tentatively.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS74
Now in his bedroom, SOMEONE sits at a desk. He leans over a sketchbook with a pen and adds to a drawing which includes a horned Cyclops wearing a party hat.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS75
SOMEONE covers his sketch with homework as SOMEONE enters.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS76
As SOMEONE pretends to resume his homework, a pleased SOMEONE steps out. The teen sticks the assignment into a textbook, then returns to his drawing.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS77
He adds shoulders to a grimacing demon within a starburst design.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS78
The next day he arrives at school and opens the doors which have been decorated with paper snowflakes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS79
At lunch. His drawing shows the demon punching through the page.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS80
He cracks a smile. Now Asian lettering adorns shops in Chinatown. SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk up from a Subway station.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS81
Later they eat from takeout containers. Now a film shows a man and boy descending a spiral staircase on the Eiffel Tower.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS82
Subtitles. Tell me why aren't you married? I haven't found my dream girl. In the movie theater, SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE who wears glasses.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS83
Do you like me? Of course not. A Marquee reads Zazie Dans le Metro.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS84
Across the street SOMEONE walks alone.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS86
SOMEONE and SOMEONE round a corner and spy on him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS87
Wearing his trench coat SOMEONE slowly ambles along with a briefcase in hand. SOMEONE and SOMEONE peer around the nose of a truck and watch him enter a coffee shop called, The Cup & Saucer.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS88
SOMEONE takes a seat at a window.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS89
SOMEONE watches his stepfather do paperwork.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS90
Now at school, as the teen heads up a stairwell the Principal blocks his path.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS91
He sips from a mug.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS92
The principal heads off. Now a banner hangs over the school entrance, Career Fair. SOMEONE steps outside with his shirt tucked in and a nametag on his chest. He looks around.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS93
He spots a scruffy looking guy standing across the street then heads in his direction. With his back turned to the approaching student the unshaven man hunches over to light a cigarette.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS95
A monitor shows an abstract painting.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS96
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit on a boulder.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS97
SOMEONE musses up his own hair. SOMEONE sits back and folds his arms.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS98
Holding a coffee with both hands, SOMEONE stares at him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS99
SOMEONE glances at his coffee. Now, he and SOMEONE stroll along a sidewalk.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS100
SOMEONE smirks, then shakes her head and continues on alone.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS101
Watching her go, SOMEONE smiles to himself. About 50 yards away SOMEONE glances back.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS102
Now traffic passes several evergreens adorned with lights. The image dissolves to the trees at night as more traffic crawls by. On another day, a taxi drives over the Manhattan Bridge. Riding in the back seat, SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE who sits beside him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS103
She glances out his window.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS104
SOMEONE sits up following her gaze past a railing to a cluster of industrial brick buildings.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS105
An American flag waves atop a pillar on the distant Brooklyn Bridge. SOMEONE smiles to himself.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS106
Now he presses a doorbell.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS107
The teens wait outside a blue building. SOMEONE shoves the door open.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS108
Seeing SOMEONE with SOMEONE, he giggles.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS109
He gestures inside.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS110
SOMEONE and SOMEONE enter. SOMEONE yanks the door shut behind them.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS111
Inside his studio they look over various paintings.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS112
He points to one.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS113
SOMEONE wanders off alone.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS114
Later, SOMEONE looks over SOMEONE's sketchbook.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS115
He glances at SOMEONE who sits in the next room.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS116
SOMEONE looks at her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS117
He peers out the window.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS118
He returns his attention to the sketchbook. SOMEONE shifts his gaze. That night he and SOMEONE ride back in a cab.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS119
SOMEONE rolls her eyes curiously then folds her legs. She and SOMEONE each look out their windows. Traffic drives past the median lined with Christmas trees.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS120
Now at dinner.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS121
SOMEONE text messages.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS122
Later in his room, he lies on his bed with an art book. He flips back several pages and studies a red hued painting of a figure standing under bare trees before a distant building.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS123
Turning to the next page he studies an oil painting of a woman in a ruffled dress facing a mirror.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS124
He turns the page again and studies a portrait of a sickly somber faced boy. The transfixed teen focuses on the boy's dark eyes,
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS125
which seem to stair back at him. Shades of peach represent the subject's
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS126
fair skin. Now in a gallery, patrons gather around SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS127
He notices SOMEONE approaching. A photographer snaps a picture.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS128
SOMEONE stares past SOMEONE and frowns.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS129
He turns around and sees only blank canvases adorning the walls.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS130
Now he awakes in bed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS131
On a busy city street, traffic lights turn from green to red. In the kitchen SOMEONE fills a bowl with cereal, then glances around.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS132
He pours in the last few drops of milk from a carton.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS133
Stepping into a doorway, he sees SOMEONE hunched over paperwork in an office across the hall.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS134
SOMEONE watches his frustrated stepfather set one page aside and grab another.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS135
The teen takes out his cellphone and reads a text message from SOMEONE, Happy New Year. Meet me at SOMEONE's. 6 SOMEONE Circle. 20th floor. SOMEONE walks off. Now he knocks on a door.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS136
SOMEONE answers it wearing a shiny Lamé dress.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS137
SOMEONE gawks at her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS138
He follows her inside.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS139
She leads him downstairs to a chic living room where they join SOMEONE and a girlfriend.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS140
A blond guy sits across from them. His friend sits beside SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS141
SOMEONE arrives.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS142
SOMEONE picks up a card reading, New Year's Eve Party. Then flips it over to find his drawing.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS143
He smiles at his work.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS144
Later on a quiet street SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk together following the others.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS145
Now in a trendy nightclub, she leads him through the crowd.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS146
She leads him across the dance floor.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS147
SOMEONE hands him a bottle of champagne. SOMEONE leads SOMEONE to the middle of the dance floor. A strobe light flashes on the anxious teen. Facing him, SOMEONE brushes back her hair.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS148
SOMEONE tries to dance, awkwardly swaying to the music.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS149
SOMEONE grins as she watches him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS150
SOMEONE smiles and watches her dance ecstatically with her eyes closed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS151
SOMEONE and SOMEONE hug. As he dances close to her she looks at SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS152
He pleasantly raises his bottle of champagne then backs away disappearing within the crowd.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS153
SOMEONE watches him go, then turns her attention back to SOMEONE as she dances with him joyfully.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS154
Now, SOMEONE walks through the crowd.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS155
He approaches SOMEONE's friends at the bar. SOMEONE turns to him, holding a shot.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS156
They all raise shots.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS157
SOMEONE studies SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS158
A blond girl whispers in SOMEONE's ear then leads her off.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS159
SOMEONE watches her go.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS161
Wandering through the crowded dance floor SOMEONE glimpses SOMEONE still dancing with SOMEONE. As SOMEONE moves on someone hands him a shot.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS162
He toasts with the group.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS163
A brilliant disco lights swings by overhead as he shifts his dull gaze. Strobe-like flashes of the tightly packed club goers go in and out of focus.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS164
SOMEONE stumbles through the crowd.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS165
Outside, he shuffles across the street and vomits, catching the attention of two bystanders.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS166
He sits back against a wall.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS167
He spits.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS168
A string of saliva falls from his mouth as he sits up and catches his breath.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS169
He undoes a button of his shirt, then hangs his head with his eyes half closed. Down the block, a group of pedestrians walks by.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS170
Later, SOMEONE lies alone, passed out against the wall.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS171
Crossing the street, SOMEONE picks up her pace as she finds her lost friend.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS172
She crouches at SOMEONE's side and helps him sit up against the graffitied wall.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS173
Now, with SOMEONE's arm draped over her shoulders, SOMEONE helps him into her bedroom. Leaning him against the door jam, she doffs her coat.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS174
She rolls out the lower level of a trundle bed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS175
She grabs a pillow and a comforter.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS176
She twitches a smile then straightens SOMEONE's overcoat.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS177
SOMEONE blinks over her smile and averts her gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS178
With a kind look she reaches for him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS179
She slides his coat off then steadies him as he staggers to the bed. Holding his side, she guides him to the lower bed beside her own. He flops back on it, then watches as she spreads the comforter over him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS180
SOMEONE turns her back to him and switches off a lamp on a dresser.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS181
As SOMEONE's eyelids open and close between wakefulness and sleep, he glimpses her intermittently.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS182
With her back to him, SOMEONE slides out a dresser drawer.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS183
She pulls her dress up over her head, revealing her bra.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS184
She puts on a three quarter sleeve baseball T.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS185
As she dons pajama pants, she glances over her shoulder at SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS186
He sees her just before his eyes fall shut.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS187
One last glimpse shows the dresser without SOMEONE in front of it.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS188
Now, pale light glows on SOMEONE's sleeping face.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS189
His eyelids flutter and he wakes up.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS190
Shifting his head on the pillow, he turns to SOMEONE and watches her sleep.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS191
He props himself up on his elbows and sweeps his gaze up SOMEONE's face, taking in her rosy lips, smooth cheeks, and closed eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS193
Still studying her beauty, he lies back.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS194
With his thoughtful gaze fixed on the sleeping girl, SOMEONE lets his eyelids shut.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS195
Morning. Propped on one elbow, SOMEONE sits awake in bed, her eyes darting to the lower regions of SOMEONE's blanket. She presses her lips together to stifle a smile, then shifts her gaze to SOMEONE who blinks awake and looks up at her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS196
He smiles. Following SOMEONE's gaze, he sees his morning wood jetting up under the blanket. He rolls off the bed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS197
He glances at SOMEONE, then drops his head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS198
Later in the dining room, Mrs. SOMEONE brings SOMEONE a Bloody SOMEONE garnished with a celery stalk and bendy straw.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS199
Sitting kitty corner to SOMEONE's mom SOMEONE nods, then sips the drink.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS200
He shoots her an alarmed look.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS201
She pushes her chair out and strides away. Her mother glances after her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS202
SOMEONE smiles.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS203
He lifts the straw to his lips and drinks. Now he follows SOMEONE down a sidewalk. Slowing his pace, he watches his stepfather grab a newspaper off the top of a trash can then cross the street. With his eyes fixed on the man, SOMEONE remains on the opposite sidewalk.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS204
He pauses behind a pair of pay phones then takes a few steps and sees
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS205
SOMEONE sitting on a bench in a crowded bus shelter.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS206
The people waiting around him stir as a bus pulls up.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS207
The bus glides away to reveal SOMEONE alone on the shelter bench.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS208
He reads the newspaper. Later SOMEONE exits an elevator in an office building. He walks down a barren corridor and stops in front of a door. His jaw drops as he spots an eviction notice taped to it. The door's shiny nameplate reads, SOMEONE Sargent. Marketing Research Incorporated.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS209
Nighttime. Wearing dark framed glasses, SOMEONE sits on her bed and reads. Her mother joins her as she folds her daughter's clothes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS210
SOMEONE gives her mother a pointed look. With a faint smile, Charlotte glances away. Now in a gallery at the Whitney Museum, SOMEONE and SOMEONE face a gray canvas covered with chalky scribbles.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS211
Wearing a coiled white scarf, SOMEONE moves to a painting of two red rectangles below a white one.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS212
SOMEONE nods uncertainly.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS213
He glances at SOMEONE then returns his gaze to the paintings.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS214
SOMEONE shrugs, then moves to another painting. SOMEONE joins him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS215
SOMEONE gazes at the piece of art.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS216
SOMEONE eyes him thoughtfully, then steps in front of the next piece.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS217
The sharp perspective canvas shows six rows of plates each holding a slice of cake or pie identical to the others in its row.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS219
He gives an embarrassed shrug.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS220
SOMEONE eyes the plates.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS221
With a knowing smile, SOMEONE leaves SOMEONE staring at the image. SOMEONE leaves.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS222
Now SOMEONE sits across from SOMEONE at a restaurant.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS223
A plastic table stand between them reads, Valentine's Day menu.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS224
SOMEONE nods and smiles.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS225
Nodding, SOMEONE stares down at the table.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS226
He folds his hands on the table.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS228
Staring at SOMEONE, he gives a faint sad smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS229
SOMEONE shoots him a thoughtful look, then lowers her eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS230
She meets his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS231
Starring into SOMEONE's eyes, SOMEONE gives a tiny nod.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS232
She twitches a smile then brushes hair away from her face.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS233
He grins. SOMEONE rumples her lips.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS234
SOMEONE stares at her with hard eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS235
SOMEONE presses his lips into a tight line. He averts his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS236
As she peers directly at SOMEONE his eyes widen. His lips part fumbling.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS237
SOMEONE bows her head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS238
She averts her gaze as SOMEONE stares crestfallen, SOMEONE leans toward him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS239
As she sits back and sips her drink SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS240
Later, heading down a sidewalk with SOMEONE, SOMEONE stares straight ahead. His hands in his pockets and his face sullen.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS241
SOMEONE glances at him but he avoids her gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS242
He looks down thoughtfully.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS243
He stops walking.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS244
SOMEONE blinks her confused eyes. SOMEONE stares back angrily.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS245
He turns on his heels and strides away.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS246
Staring after him she shakes her head then storms off in the opposite direction.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS247
Now, SOMEONE lies on his bed with his hands folded under his head. His iPod plays beside him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS248
His phone display flashes. SOMEONE calling. With a sour look, he rejects the calls then smooths the front of his shirt and folds his hands behind his head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS249
SOMEONE shoots his cell a brooding glance, then reaches for his iPod and hits play.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS250
Now he wears a different but similar outfit as he lies on his bed with his eyes closed.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS251
His mother raps on the door. She opens it and looks in.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS252
His mother stares at him, her brow creased.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS253
Slack jawed, she closes the door as she leaves. SOMEONE lies with his arms folded over his stomach and his eyes shut.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS254
He presses play on his iPod and lies back.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS255
Now at school SOMEONE sits in the lunchroom with SOMEONE and SOMEONE. She glances back at SOMEONE reading alone one table away. SOMEONE scrutinizes him curiously, and SOMEONE wears a wounded expression.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS256
Later, SOMEONE lies on his bed gazing dourly at the ceiling. SOMEONE opens the door and gawks.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS257
SOMEONE stares at him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS258
Rolling his eyes, SOMEONE returns his gaze to the ceiling. SOMEONE stares at him for a moment then backs out of the room and closes the door.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS259
SOMEONE shuts his eyes. Meanwhile SOMEONE listens on her phone.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS260
She ends the call then hits redial.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS261
With a frustrated look she hangs up. Striding down a waterfront walkway she pauses as she notices someone up ahead. She smiles faintly then heads over to SOMEONE who sits on a low stonewall sketching on a pad. Later, SOMEONE strides down a sidewalk. SOMEONE approaches from the opposite direction. His hands in his coat pockets and his gaze fixed on the ground. The two teens walk right past each other offering no sign of acknowledgment.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS262
Evening. Pale sunlight gleams off cars parked on both sides of a city.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS263
White letters on a red sign outside of a bar read, SOMEONE's. Sitting alone inside SOMEONE brushes her bangs out of her face, then glances at the door as it opens. SOMEONE joins her at the bar.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS264
Shifting uneasily, SOMEONE tucks some hair behind one ear.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS265
One elbow on the bar, SOMEONE runs a hand through his wavy hair. He props his head on it and gazes at SOMEONE with wistful eyes. He offers a restrained smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS266
She gives him an annoyed look.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS267
As she gently sways back and forth in her seat, SOMEONE turns away.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS268
SOMEONE slides out of her chair.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS269
She offers her hand.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS270
SOMEONE accepts, then rises from his chair. Gazing into his eyes, she lifts his hand and spins under his arm. As she pulls him in and starts to dance he sits again.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS271
SOMEONE nods then breaks into a flirtatious smile. Closing her eyes, she begins to dance in front of SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS272
She sways sensually and the artist gives a longing look. Daytime. In class, SOMEONE stares out a window at a neighboring building. A bird flies past.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS273
As his English teacher collects the students’ papers, she stops at his desk and touches his shoulder.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS274
She notes his distant expression.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS275
His teacher frowns.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS276
SOMEONE averts his head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS277
Now, SOMEONE arrives at the school office.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS278
The assistant sheepishly meets his gaze. SOMEONE proceeds to the Principal's office. Later he sits wringing his hands.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS279
Three of SOMEONE's teachers sit in the room.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS280
The English teacher purses her lip.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS281
With glistening eyes, SOMEONE looks up at SOMEONE who avoids his gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS282
The math teacher gives him a harsh look.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS283
He rubs tears from his eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS284
The sober faced teachers stay put as SOMEONE gets up from the couch and exits. He turns back at the open door.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS285
He continues out with a numb expression.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS286
Now Vivian and SOMEONE sit waiting for him at home.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS287
The distraught mother dabs at the corners of her eyes with her pinkie.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS288
SOMEONE steps into the room.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS289
SOMEONE grabs him roughly and they wrestle to the floor.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS290
As SOMEONE gets back up his stepfather restrains him from behind.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS291
He backs SOMEONE into the doorframe and the older man slumps to the floor clutching his shoulder.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS292
The troubled teen runs out.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS293
Later, our view chases after him as he races through the park.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS294
Night falls as he bolts down SOMEONE's street and into her apartment building.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS295
He catches his breath as she answers.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS296
She slips out shutting the door behind her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS297
He presses her up against the door and kisses her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS298
She pushes him back and frowns uncomfortably.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS299
With a heavy blink, she lifts her brown eyes to meet his.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS300
SOMEONE twists the doorknob behind her back. She pushes the door open a crack and SOMEONE takes a look inside.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS301
Charlotte sits on the sofa near SOMEONE who guiltily leans forward in an armchair.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS302
Later, SOMEONE marches away from the apartment building.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS303
SOMEONE runs out after him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS304
The boy turns around with a wounded glare.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS305
SOMEONE pouts, his eyes glistening.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS306
Tears stream down SOMEONE's cheek.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS307
The boy dries his face
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS308
with his sleeve, then glances off pensively.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS309
He flashes a wry dimpled smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS310
Dusting contritely shifts his arms at his sides.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS311
SOMEONE's chin furrows sadly as he stares at his mentor.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS312
SOMEONE returns a solemn, remorseful look.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS313
SOMEONE turns around and mopes off down the block of brown stone buildings. Later he sulks at a bar while SOMEONE, SOMEONE and others have a good time all around him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS314
Someone passes in front of our view as the picture fades to black.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS315
In the early morning under a gray sky SOMEONE walks down the middle of a street.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS316
Later he strolls through a park on a pathway between tall leafy trees and approaches Vivian sitting on a bench. His shoulders sag as he lets out a sigh.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS317
His mother smiles at him and lifts her eyebrows.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS318
SOMEONE tightens his lips and takes a seat beside her on the bench. He folds his overcoat closed as a strong breeze blows through some trees and bushes at a wall behind them.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS319
Smiling gently she closes her eyes and lets out a breath.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS320
She closes her hands over her nose and mouth as she sobs. SOMEONE puts his arm around her and kisses her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS321
He rests his cheek against her honey blond hair.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS322
Later, SOMEONE strides into the Principal's office.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS323
SOMEONE hurries out.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS324
Now in the art room.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS325
Later, SOMEONE leaves the school with a tall stack of assignments.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS326
SOMEONE falls into step with him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS327
SOMEONE stops and faces her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS328
SOMEONE's mouth creases as she stares at him remorsefully.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS329
He walks off leaving her behind.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS330
Later at home.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS332
As he heads off, Vivian watches him fondly. In his bedroom SOMEONE plops the thick stack of assignments down on his desk. He removes his coat. Rolling up his sleeves he takes a seat at his desk and straightens the pile of homework. He stares at the daunting stack of folders and assignment books for a moment then turns on a lamp and opens up his laptop.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS333
On another day, our view travels across his bedroom to find him hard at work at his desk.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS334
He works out a trigonometry equation. Vivian shows in another couple.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS335
Later, SOMEONE sets up a blank canvas on an easel and stares at it. In the kitchen Vivian wraps up pieces of pottery in newspaper and boxes them.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS336
SOMEONE writes an essay on ruled notebook paper.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS337
He now takes a brush to his canvas and starts his painting.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS338
He mixes shades of emerald and white to form a pale green. Later on the canvas, he uses thick brush strokes to apply streaks of white over the green. He paints a purple vertical line, then shadows it in burnt sienna. Now at school he writes an essay for his English final. Later he uses a calculator to work out a problem for his trig final. Back at home, he solves another long equation, types on his laptop and fills in answers on some French homework.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS339
He types up a paper citing the Thoreau's Civil Disobedience. Taking an essay test he begins an answer with a mention of SOMEONE Bacon and SOMEONE Hockney. For a multiple-choice question he circles the answer, Renaissance. Back at home he rubs his eye then places a completed assignment atop a stack and grabs the next piece of homework. Now in his loft, SOMEONE works on a painting as dawn breaks outside his windows. SOMEONE wakes up in his bed and watches him deliberately stub out a lit cigarette near the bottom corner of the canvas. Her eyes lower pensively.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS340
Meanwhile, SOMEONE works on his own painting in a white T-shirt.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS341
Vivian smiles in his doorway drying her hands on a towel. SOMEONE grins.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS342
Vivian looks around the bare walls.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS343
He eyes his canvas. Later.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS344
Vivian admires her son as she shakes her head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS345
Later, SOMEONE strolls into his room where only his twin size bed remains.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS346
He gets a text from SOMEONE, I need to see you.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS347
Now an illuminated awning over an entry way reads, Lou's. Inside the softly lit bar, SOMEONE and SOMEONE share a booth, each with a bottle of beer on the table.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS348
Her friend musters a tight smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS349
SOMEONE responds with a forgiving nod.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS350
SOMEONE's eyes glisten and he presses his lip.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS351
SOMEONE gives him a grave nod. He bravely looks her in the eye.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS352
SOMEONE lowers her gaze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS353
She rubs her neck then rests her head in her hand and allows a brief sad smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS354
SOMEONE looks down and bites her lips.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS355
With a faint smile, she reaches out and takes his hand in hers stroking his fingers with her thumb.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS356
Later as they follow the sidewalk, the young beauty casually bumps against SOMEONE, then tucks her hair behind her ear.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS357
Their interlocked hands sway gently with their
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS358
Now they arrive at her deserted apartment.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS359
They sit before laced curtained windows filled with soft golden light and kiss tenderly.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS360
Pulling back SOMEONE beams at SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS361
He invitingly brushes the tip of her nose with his.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS362
Her smile grows and she brings her lips to his again.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS363
As they share a series of soft gentle kisses, her hand moves up to his shoulder.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS364
Now in the soft predawn light, street lamps twinkle beyond a weathered wooden bench. SOMEONE strolls into view and takes a seat.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS365
He stares off, his lips pursed in a thoughtful pout.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS366
Back in Charlotte's empty apartment SOMEONE pulls away abruptly and looks up at SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS367
SOMEONE gives her an eager kiss.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS368
SOMEONE kisses him and drapes her arms around his shoulders.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS369
He smiles down at her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS370
On the bench SOMEONE gives a hopeful smile.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS371
He lowers his gaze and licks his lips
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS372
Now, verdant tree branches dapple our view of a bright blue sky patched
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS373
with wispy clouds.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS375
She sets a heavy backpack at her feet.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS376
Then slips her hands in her pockets and cranes her neck for a view up the street.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS377
Elsewhere, SOMEONE leaves his building with his now draped canvas tucked under one arm. His other arm curls around the massive stack of completed homework assignments as he heads down the sidewalk at a brisk pace.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS378
Now, cars line up outside an international terminal at an airport.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS379
A black luxury car with tinted windows pulls into view and parks at the curb. SOMEONE and SOMEONE get out.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS380
The trunk pops open and they reach in for their bags. In the Principal's office SOMEONE's hands set the massive stack of assignments down on the desk. Working facing the wall, the administrator turns and looks up at SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS381
He eyes the stack.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS382
At the airport, SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive at the boarding area where other passengers file through a gate.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS383
The teen girl hesitates and looks around. In the art room, SOMEONE sets SOMEONE's canvas on an easel.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS384
He steps back, his hands on his hips and regards it shrewdly as his troubled student stands nearby.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS385
The art teacher faces SOMEONE with a cocked eyebrow.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS386
He shoves the boy, then envelops him in a proud embrace. The teen gives a dimpled smile as he returns the hug, then faces his work with gleaming eyes. SOMEONE puts an arm around his shoulder and looks at the painting with an appreciative scowl.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS387
At the boarding gate, SOMEONE lingers by a window. Now a banner over the school entrance reads, Morgan. Congratulations, Seniors.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS388
SOMEONE sits by SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS389
He shakes his head.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS390
On her other side SOMEONE stands, goes to the stage and shakes the Principal's hand.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS391
The teen takes his diploma and executes a groovy spin.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS392
SOMEONE chuckles fondly and SOMEONE laughs into her hand. They briefly share a smile. At the boarding gate, SOMEONE checks with a ticket agent then joins SOMEONE at the sun lit window.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS393
With a fond smirk SOMEONE steps closer, cradles her head in his hands and gives her a tender kiss.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS394
SOMEONE briefly averts her gaze then flashes a wan smile. SOMEONE kisses her again. At graduation, SOMEONE's expression grows pensive. At the airport SOMEONE lowers her gaze then smiles at SOMEONE again. At school, SOMEONE notices SOMEONE's tense demeanor.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS395
SOMEONE beams warmly at him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS396
The principal leans over the podium looking straight at him. SOMEONE lifts his gaze, his hazel eyes gleaming. In slow motion he stands and makes his way to the stage. SOMEONE and SOMEONE grin after him. His mother beams happily. As he reaches the stage SOMEONE winks at him. SOMEONE regards him proudly. His math teacher gives a delighted round of applause and his English teacher nods approvingly. The Principal meets him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS397
Smiling faintly he shakes SOMEONE's hand then leans in.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS398
He holds out SOMEONE's diploma. As the teen accepts it the Principal pats him on the arm and steps away. SOMEONE smiles after him appreciatively.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS399
As he faces the audience, sunlight flares in brightly through a window behind him. His mother beams proudly, her eyes glistening. The teen scans the room. Elsewhere SOMEONE turns, her surroundings washed out by sunlight. At graduation, SOMEONE's eyes shine as he lingers on the stage. Outside, tree branches bordering the streets sway gently in a breeze.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS400
At the school a teen girl comes outside in her cap and gown and joins two fellow graduates.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS401
In the art room, SOMEONE stands with his graduation robe slung over one arm. On the easel, his painting offers a portrait of SOMEONE in
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS402
tints of green and purple.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS403
The subject gazes off with a stoic expression hinting at wisdom beyond her years. Turning away, SOMEONE sets his diploma and graduation robes on a chair.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS404
As he turns back he halts and stares. In the doorway SOMEONE stands with her hands clasped before her. She offers a little smile and he regards her with shining eyes.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS405
The teen girl enters the room holding SOMEONE in a solemn gaze. SOMEONE's eyes follow her.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS406
As she passes obliviously behind her own portrait, moving with slow deliberate steps,
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS407
she keeps her gaze on him.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS408
Approaching the young artist, she regards the portrait appraisingly then tilts her head and smiles.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS409
SOMEONE glances at the painting then eyes SOMEONE anxiously.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS411
SOMEONE's gaze cools and his smile vanishes. She joins him at his side then faces the portrait again.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS412
She looks up at him with a teasing smirk. SOMEONE beams understandingly.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS413
His hand reaches out taking a gentle hold of SOMEONE.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS414
As they linger facing the painting together she glances at him fondly.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS415
SOMEONE heaves a grave sigh. She faces SOMEONE intently then looks back at the painting.
THE_ART_OF_GETTING_BY_DVS416
The two teens hesitantly met each other's gaze. SOMEONE yields a coy smile and turns toward the painting. SOMEONE follows her example with a hopeful gaze.