Heading toward glass doors onto the helipad, the rugged brother spots SOMEONE's reflection. He turns and shoots into the air.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS17
Using the captured guard as a shield, SOMEONE advances.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS18
As enemy fire, takes his captive out, SOMEONE dives behind the fallen body and shoots.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS20
SOMEONE hands one off as he raise his pass.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS21
He slides on his knees into a guard, knocking him over.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS22
SOMEONE shoots three guards as he runs to the helipad. At the chopper, SOMEONE passes his brother a backpack. Leaping in from the opposite side, SOMEONE swings from the door and kicks SOMEONE back. The briefcase of money opens as it hits the ground. The rugged brother slams Tucks against the chopper. But SOMEONE blocks his strikes and punches him in the face. As SOMEONE throws SOMEONE down, the older brother kicks him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS23
SOMEONE catches himself on the roof's edge as he tumbles off.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS26
SOMEONE, his older brother hands him a gun then leaps off the building. A parachute releases from his backpack. Leaping onto the helipad, SOMEONE shoots a bald guard.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS27
SOMEONE aims the gun at SOMEONE. A dark-haired guard attacks SOMEONE who blocks him then knees him. Winding up, he punches the guy out.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS29
He grabs SOMEONE who drops the case with the device over the roof. SOMEONE catches it. SOMEONE snatches SOMEONE's backpack. SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE's sleeve for balance but it rips and he plummets off the roof.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS30
Drifting to the ground, the older brother watches SOMEONE crash into a car on the street below.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS31
The vehicle careens into another car.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS32
As SOMEONE climbs back onto the helipad, SOMEONE stares down at the destruction.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS33
The surviving Heinrich brother lands safely and slides his parachute off his back.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS34
He glances up at the skyscraper then moves to SOMEONE's body which lies sprawled on the car's crushed roof. The rugged Heinrich finds the patch of fabric torn from SOMEONE's suit, still in his brother's clinched hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS35
He takes it then lifts his gaze to the helipad.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS36
An aerial view shows him moving away from the crash as bystander’s crowd closer.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS37
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from the helipad.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS38
Hundred dollar bills flutter all around them.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS39
An all caps title appears, word by word filling the screen. THIS MEANS WAR. The word war is in red. Now a blonde with pixie-like features fires a blowtorch at frying pans. A location types out, Smart Consumer, Inc. Los Angeles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS40
She inspects the pans.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS41
They leave the testing room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS42
Her smile fades as her assistant heads off.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS43
Now a location types out, CIA Field Office.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS44
Standing on a mezzanine, overlooking an atrium, their boss jerks her thumb.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS45
Later in her office.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS46
Later a desks facing each other, SOMEONE watches his gun spin as he reclines with his feet up while SOMEONE sits face down at his desk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS47
Drumming a pen at each hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS48
Now in workout clothes, SOMEONE listens to headphones as she walks down a sidewalk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS49
A bicycling couple stops in front of her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS50
She spots SOMEONE's ring.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS51
She watches them kiss.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS52
SOMEONE lovingly eyes SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS53
SOMEONE heads away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS54
Later, she enters a sushi restaurant. The chefs behind the bar cheer.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS55
She gives a dispirited look then heads over.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS56
One of the chef hands her a warm towel as she sits.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS57
She drops her face in the towel.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS58
Ken grins at the new arrivals.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS59
Lifting her face from the towel, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS60
SOMEONE glares. Now she shops with her friend.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS61
She nudges SOMEONE's butt.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS62
Her blonde friend narrows an eye at her. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE attend an elegant lawn party.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS63
He tries some cake.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS64
An older gentleman kisses her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS65
As he leads her off, SOMEONE gazes at his grandparents.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS66
The elderly couple dances on the lawn. A boy with a bucket over his head spins in circles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS67
He falls over. SOMEONE gazes at the dancing couple.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS68
SOMEONE gawks at his friend. Later a woman in a bikini swims the breaststroke in a glass bottom pool, which serves as a foyer ceiling.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS69
Entering his bachelor pad, SOMEONE lifts his gaze to the swimmer.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS70
He removes his sunglasses and stares. Sliding off his jacket, he smirks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS71
Now at a Karate Dojo.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS72
Two boys face each other.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS73
A burly father watches his son square off with SOMEONE's smaller one.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS74
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE face.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS76
SOMEONE gives his son two thumbs up.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS77
SOMEONE trudges over and sits.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS78
SOMEONE's dad smacks his rear. As SOMEONE faces him, the aggressive father stares into his eyes.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS79
Smirking, he slaps SOMEONE's face then leaves. SOMEONE stares after him. SOMEONE shoulders his bag and heads off.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS80
As they exit the dojo together, an SUV pulls up and a pretty brunette waves from the driver seat.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS81
SOMEONE climbs in back.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS82
SOMEONE closes the door behind him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS83
He steps away from the SUV.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS84
His ex drives off.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS85
Now at his bachelor pad, SOMEONE wears a robe, boxers, and slippers.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS86
Turning on a flat screen TV, he sits on a couch with a bowl of cereal.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS87
Meanwhile, the same program plays on SOMEONE's swanky loft as he spars with a beefy opponent.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS89
Bending his opponent over, SOMEONE eyes the TV ad.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS90
SOMEONE watches with the bored look. SOMEONE holds his opponent in a choke hold.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS91
His opponent flips him to a mat.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS92
SOMEONE shakes his head as the ad shows an embracing couple.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS93
The burly man picks SOMEONE up.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS94
He throws him down again.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS95
With SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS96
Now at Smart Consumer, a receptionist peeks over her computer monitor.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS97
SOMEONE notices her whispering colleagues.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS98
Crossing the office, he glances over her outfit.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS99
Looking back, she heads across the testing area.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS100
SOMEONE steps around her computer and finds in itsfate. net profile with her picture and the headline, Come and Get It Boys.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS101
At a Gymboree Play Center, SOMEONE's friend answers her cellphone.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS102
SOMEONE finds SOMEONE's profile.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS104
Now at bustling pub - The Blarney Stone, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE sitting at a table outside.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS105
He takes off his sunglasses and she does the same.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS106
They sit across from each other.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS107
A movie plays on a TV at a video store. SOMEONE takes an escalator down to a lower floor, observing a variety of single women.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS108
He smiles at a dark-haired woman strolling by.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS109
He checks out a short-haired woman then takes out his cellphone and reads a text message.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS111
SOMEONE nods emphatically.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS112
Later at the video store, SOMEONE smiles to herself as she takes the escalator downstairs.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS113
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE grab the same movie.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS114
He smiles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS116
She struts pass him and he follows. Later.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS117
She heads off with another movie.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS118
SOMEONE watches her go then shakes his head and leaves as well.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS119
Now at the field office with the tech.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS120
The tech scrolls through customer profiles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS121
SOMEONE points.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS122
They view a DMV cross-reference and a tax return.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS124
SOMEONE sits near the back.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS125
He approaches her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS127
She rolls her eyes and he walks off with a grin.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS128
Now an aerial view, roves pass downtown Los Angeles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS129
At the CIA Field Office, SOMEONE and SOMEONE work at their opposing desks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS130
Each man turns his laptop to reveal a photo of the same woman.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS131
SOMEONE shuts his laptop. SOMEONE does the same. Then resumes work at his desktop computer.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS133
Now a satellite view zooms out from the CIA Field Office locates London, England and zooms in on Saville Row.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS134
In the dimly lit backroom of a tailor shop, a tailor lays out a work in progress over a table then stands upright and finds Heinrich facing him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS136
Cut to black.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS137
At SOMEONE's pad.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS142
SOMEONE carries a huge stuffed pig, SOMEONE notices her taking hold of his hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS143
In a darkened corridor.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS144
SOMEONE covers SOMEONE's eyes.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS145
He reveals a trapeze structure adorned with lights in the middle of a circus ring.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS146
He takes her hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS147
As SOMEONE swings, SOMEONE stands on a platform.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS148
He swings under a domed ceiling.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS149
SOMEONE grabs hold of her trapeze.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS150
She jumps from the platform and swings out over the net.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS151
Hanging on by their legs, they grab each other's wrists. SOMEONE lets go and swings with SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS152
He lets her fall and she lands on the net, bouncing high into the air.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS153
He lets himself fall and bounce as well. Then they roll into the middle and lie side by side.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS154
As SOMEONE lies on his back, SOMEONE kisses him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS155
He wraps his arms around her and draws her near.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS156
We glimpse the couple from across the ring as they embrace, surrounded by the several strands of lights adorning the trapeze structure.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS158
At home by a fireplace, SOMEONE kisses a half-naked man lying on his back near an open bottle of red wine. She smacks him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS160
Now at work, SOMEONE sits alone at his desk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS161
As his colleagues move on, SOMEONE shifts his gaze. Now with the tech.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS163
He steps aside with his hands in his pockets.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS164
A satellite view zooms in on a street, tracking an Audi convertible which loops around and parks outside a busy nightclub.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS165
SOMEONE hops out of the sports car and joins SOMEONE who stands in a long line to get in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS166
He leads her to the entrance.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS168
SOMEONE shakes hands with the bouncer on the way in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS169
He chats with the coat check girl.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS170
To a bartender.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS175
They enter a VIP section.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS177
A bartender hands him a bottle of wine.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS178
SOMEONE turns to find SOMEONE missing from her chair. He peers across the dance floor then heads after her. Outside, as SOMEONE crosses the street, SOMEONE catches up.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS179
She spots SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS180
She grabs SOMEONE as he walks away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS181
She pulls him into a passionate kiss as the happy couple arrives.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS182
SOMEONE glares at her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS183
She glances at SOMEONE. He finally turns to SOMEONE and offers his hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS185
She smacks him playfully.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS186
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch them kiss again.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS187
Later at Pizzeria.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS188
He smiles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS189
He taps his temple and she brightens.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS190
An aerial view shows the city at dawn. At the field office.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS191
SOMEONE strolls cheerfully through a bullpen.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS192
Turning, he finds a bald agent grinning at him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS193
SOMEONE's smile fades to a comprehending scowl.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS194
He marches into the work area he shares with SOMEONE and finds him sitting casually at his desk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS196
He drops the file in front of SOMEONE. It contains a photo of the blunt-featured SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS197
SOMEONE sits at his own desk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS198
SOMEONE gestures bashfully.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS199
SOMEONE looks up from a file.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS200
Now they hold separate briefings.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS201
Now in a stylish home, SOMEONE dances in a kitchen as she makes microwave popcorn.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS202
A window behind her shows SOMEONE lowering to the ground on a cable.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS204
Wearing shorts, a big comfy shirt, and a ponytail, she struts into the living room and turns on a flat screen TV.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS205
Behind her, SOMEONE creeps in and ducks behind a couch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS206
SOMEONE returns to the kitchen obliviously.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS207
Getting to his feet, SOMEONE peers at her bookshelf and notices models of vintage sports cars.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS208
In the kitchen, she swivels her hips as she wipes out her popcorn bowl. As she leaves the kitchen, he darts out.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS209
She passes stairs, steps through a doorway, and shuts it behind her. SOMEONE darts down the stairs.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS210
He glides over to a lamp and sticks a tiny device under the shade's cross-beamed frame.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS211
Noticing a framed poster for a Gustav Klimt Exhibit, he studies it closely.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS212
SOMEONE ducks around a doorway and hides as SOMEONE comes out and eyes an open laptop.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS213
SOMEONE notices a website for a pet shelter on her browser.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS214
SOMEONE waves her hands in the air as she dances to her microwave.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS215
SOMEONE ducks behind the kitchen island then darts around a corner as she takes out her popcorn.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS216
Behind her, SOMEONE dashes off outside.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS218
Now at his desk, SOMEONE throws a crumpled paper ball at a waste basket and misses.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS219
A paper ball flying from another direction goes in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS220
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE who blows on his fingers like a gun barrel and flashes a cocky smile.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS221
SOMEONE tries again and his paper ball goes in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS222
Their feet on their desks, they take turns throwing.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS223
Now a marquee reads, The Penthouse - Beautiful Girls Nightly.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS224
As a bouncer moves aside, SOMEONE faces his partner.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS225
He sniffs SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS226
Leaning on SOMEONE, SOMEONE staggers drunkenly into a backroom where men play cards.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS227
SOMEONE glares at him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS228
SOMEONE stands revealing his powerful build.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS229
SOMEONE's poker buddies draw guns and fires as he flees.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS230
Dropping to the floor, the agent shoot their assailants.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS232
As he runs through a doorway, a bald man tosses SOMEONE a shotgun then attacks SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS233
The agent fights back, wrapping a payphone cord around his neck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS234
SOMEONE drops to the floor as SOMEONE shoots. The blast misses him and SOMEONE flees. SOMEONE and SOMEONE give chase, dropping the bald man.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS235
Reaching the main floor, SOMEONE trips then draws an ankle pistol and aims.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS237
SOMEONE forces a patron down and SOMEONE shot misses again. SOMEONE dashes over the bar then somersaults across the table. As SOMEONE reaches the dancer stage, SOMEONE knocks him down and falls away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS238
Arriving, SOMEONE disarms SOMEONE and slams him against the pole. SOMEONE charges but SOMEONE kicks him away. SOMEONE forces SOMEONE down and SOMEONE punches him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS239
While his partner straps SOMEONE's neck and cuffs him to the pole, SOMEONE holds him at gun point.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS241
Later, they haul SOMEONE into the field office.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS242
I'm not saying anything.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS243
SOMEONE eyes his cell. It reads, Boyles - urgent check in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS244
SOMEONE gets a text from SOMEONE reading, mission alert.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS247
Now at SOMEONE's house.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS248
She shows the photo of SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS249
As SOMEONE spies on the women from a surveillance truck, SOMEONE burst in on him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS250
Both men listen worriedly.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS251
SOMEONE faces his cackling friend.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS252
His smile vanishes.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS253
The men meet separately with their team leaders.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS255
SOMEONE rides in the Camaro with her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS256
A spy drone flies into view behind them. Tilting his side mirror, SOMEONE spots it.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS257
From a surveillance room, SOMEONE watches footage from its camera. SOMEONE sticks up his middle finger.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS258
Behind his back, he discreetly draws a gun then makes a show of resting his hand behind SOMEONE's seat back.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS259
He shoots the drone, destroying it.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS260
SOMEONE raises both hands, SOMEONE grabs the wheel. The briefings continue.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS261
Now SOMEONE takes SOMEONE to an enormous art vault.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS262
In an alcove, several paintings by Klimt stand propped against crates.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS263
At a remote location, SOMEONE speaks into a headset.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS265
SOMEONE frowns.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS266
With SOMEONE, SOMEONE giggles mischievously.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS268
Elsewhere, SOMEONE laughs.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS269
He takes her to a draped painting.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS270
He unveils it, revealing Klimt's romantic masterpiece, The Kiss.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS271
It depicts a man kissing a woman's face.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS272
She takes SOMEONE's arm as she gazes wistfully at the stylized yet tender image.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS273
The agent's expression softens affectionately and he faces the painting.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS274
They share a smile. Later, a phone call.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS275
In surveillance.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS276
SOMEONE brings up a video feed from SOMEONE's house.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS277
SOMEONE's smile fades.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS278
Now he takes SOMEONE to a dog shelter.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS279
He high fives a boy.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS280
She faces a tiny mutt's cage.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS281
SOMEONE starts to open it.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS282
As SOMEONE moves on to the terrier's cage, the tiny mutt springs out and attacks SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS283
The terrier jumps up and down in front of SOMEONE. With great effort, SOMEONE wrestles the mutt into submission.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS284
Turning, SOMEONE smiles fondly at them.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS285
He puts the dog back in its cage.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS286
SOMEONE brushes more hair off his shirt.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS288
Later, SOMEONE spies on SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS289
SOMEONE frowns. Now at a paintball park.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS290
SOMEONE sweeps curtains of netting apart revealing men and boys on a paintball field.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS292
He swings out from a rail, kicking a man down.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS293
He disarms another.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS294
Crouching on a deck, he shoots the players hiding beneath then beacons SOMEONE with the wave.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS295
She fumbles with goggles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS296
Now they peek out from behind a partition.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS297
SOMEONE whips around and shoots players surrounding him. He hits two in their helmets.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS298
In a bunker.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS299
SOMEONE drops onto the roof and throws in a canister.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS300
He swings away, leaving the kids staring from the bunker windows. Blue paint sprays out from inside. SOMEONE leaps from post to post up to a tower with a flag.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS301
He yanks a man from the tower, grabs the flag and proudly shows it to SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS302
He nimbly climbs down to her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS303
Her gun shoots him in the crouch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS304
He straightens his face flushed.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS305
At the gymboree.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS306
SOMEONE shakes his hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS307
SOMEONE checks his watch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS308
Later, with Agent SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS309
Now candles filled SOMEONE's loft.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS310
As they kiss, a monitor in the CIA surveillance room shows their glowing heat signature. SOMEONE scowls.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS311
A tech wearing glasses stands behind him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS312
SOMEONE presses a remote.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS313
In the loft, the overhead fires sprinklers go off, extinguishing the candles and drenching SOMEONE and SOMEONE. SOMEONE smirks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS314
On another day, SOMEONE walks with Agent SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS315
At SOMEONE's pad.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS316
An old dog wheezes on his couch as they stop and kiss. SOMEONE pulls away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS317
She exists. SOMEONE watches her go then excitedly grabs a wine bottle and two glasses and hurries over to the coffee table.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS318
He sets them down then presses the remote.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS319
He quickly lights a candle then almost sits down on his new pet.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS320
He shoos the dog off the couch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS322
He pulls a dart from his neck. Looking out the window, he sees SOMEONE on the next roof.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS323
Holding a tranquilizer rifle, his partner communicates with him using military hand signals then disappears. SOMEONE's knees slowly buckle and he collapses to the couch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS324
As he falls unconscious, SOMEONE returns.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS325
The next day, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand in an elevator.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS326
As they both try to exit at the same time, they get log-jammed.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS327
They enter an interrogation room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS328
He brandish his pliers.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS329
Sitting handcuffed in a chair, SOMEONE chuckles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS330
SOMEONE glares at SOMEONE
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS331
who turns to their prisoner.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS333
Sooner or later he'll be coming for you.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS335
He glowers at SOMEONE's poker face.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS336
He turns his harsh eyes on SOMEONE who gives a cool smirk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS337
Now a satellite view zooms out from the CIA Field Office rapidly relocates the Los Angeles harbor and zooms in. At a dock, a henchman clasps hands with Heinrich and helps him disembark off a fishing boat.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS338
I'm sorry about SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS339
They get in one of two black Chevy Suburban’s waiting at a curb.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS340
As the cars pull out, the picture fades to black.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS341
Now SOMEONE brings SOMEONE to his grandparents' estate.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS342
His little nephew spins around with a bucket on his head then collapses.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS344
She pulls SOMEONE away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS345
Left behind with a pie in his hand, SOMEONE lets out a sigh.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS346
Nana walks SOMEONE out to a stable where photographs clutter a wall.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS347
At a family dinner.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS348
SOMEONE raises her glass of white wine.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS349
Everyone toasts.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS350
That night, SOMEONE walks SOMEONE to her house.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS351
They both glance away shyly then look each other in the eyes.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS352
SOMEONE chuckles nervously.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS353
The two surveillance teams watch from the CIA.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS354
SOMEONE and SOMEONE burst into her house. Kissing hungrily as they remove their coats. They start tearing off each other's clothes. She straddles his thighs as he lifts her onto the kitchen island. He whips off his blue button down shirt. Agent SOMEONE watches the video feed.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS355
SOMEONE lifts SOMEONE's dress off over her head. She reclines with a sultry smile.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS356
Back at the CIA Field Office, SOMEONE's three colleagues crane their necks to watch. As SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie kissing on the kitchen island, the picture fades to black.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS357
The next morning, he lies asleep in her bed.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS358
Dressed for work, SOMEONE tiptoes out from her bathroom and gathers her things.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS359
He winces. SOMEONE makes a call as she heads out.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS360
At the CIA.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS361
Agent SOMEONE reluctantly takes it out of his breast pocket.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS363
Avoiding eye contact, SOMEONE nods tensely.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS364
He chucks the disk in the trash and storms off. Now SOMEONE watches Titanic.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS365
Standing at the prow of the ship, SOMEONE Winslet looks out over the water. SOMEONE smiles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS366
He goes to an elevator door and answers it to reveal a sexy woman in a flight attendant's uniform.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS367
SOMEONE gives a shock gape then nods and smiles politely.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS368
The elevator doors slide shut.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS369
SOMEONE closes his eyes and lifts his brow then returns to the living room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS370
Pausing in tracks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS371
He looks back over his shoulder toward the elevator.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS373
The satellite view zooms out from the CIA Field Office.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS374
It shifts to James Monroe Elementary. SOMEONE comes out from the school.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS375
SOMEONE stands by smiling as SOMEONE gives his son a hug.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS376
SOMEONE monitors the conversation.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS377
At the Smart Consumer offices, SOMEONE sits before a toy fire truck. SOMEONE gives him a hammer and lets him smash it to pieces.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS378
Later, the three spray water at some test windows.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS380
They spray him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS381
A water fight ensues between all three of them.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS382
Back in the surveillance room, SOMEONE paces as he monitors the scene.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS384
She waves from his truck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS385
SOMEONE's ex comes out of her and watches him give SOMEONE a hug.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS386
SOMEONE smiles as he returns to his truck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS387
Back in the surveillance room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS388
On screen, a satellite zooms in on SOMEONE's vehicle as it pulls over to the side of the road.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS389
SOMEONE sits and watches SOMEONE and SOMEONE's heat signatures in the front seat.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS391
As SOMEONE pulls away, their noses graze and their lips linger an inch apart.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS392
They meet in a tender kiss.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS393
SOMEONE shuts his eyes and bows his head.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS394
Now the couple barges into SOMEONE's house locked in a passionate embrace.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS395
As SOMEONE lifts SOMEONE up onto a console table, he discreetly removes the bug from the lamp and throws it on the floor.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS396
As SOMEONE crashes it under his shoe, the surveillance team loses one of their angles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS397
SOMEONE leans SOMEONE over a dining table and reaches into a center piece.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS401
SOMEONE throws down a pair of headphones.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS402
Now SOMEONE lays SOMEONE down on the couch. He kisses her neck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS403
SOMEONE listens in.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS404
SOMEONE tenderly strokes his cheek. In the surveillance room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS405
SOMEONE's head sinks and he covers his eyes. Daytime, at SOMEONE's house.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS407
She lifts her son onto her lap.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS408
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE stand at their desks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS409
As SOMEONE takes a clip from his gun, SOMEONE packs up his belongings in a file box.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS411
SOMEONE takes his cellphone from his pocket.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS412
Keeping his stare on SOMEONE, SOMEONE ends the call.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS413
SOMEONE shuts his laptop. Pockets his phone and grabs his jacket.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS414
As SOMEONE strides out of the room, SOMEONE stands motionless at his box of belongings.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS415
Later, SOMEONE enters the surveillance area with the box under his arm.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS416
He sets it down next to SOMEONE watching surveillance footage.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS418
SOMEONE glances back at the footage and stops.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS419
The camera zooms in from a wide view to a close up of the truck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS420
SOMEONE's eyes narrow.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS421
They see a car parked behind the truck.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS422
The tech complies. A zoomed in image clarifies, revealing the shadowy face of the driver.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS423
SOMEONE rushes out of the room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS424
SOMEONE approaches.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS425
She heads up some stairs.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS426
SOMEONE waves. Now SOMEONE is bare feet, move up and down.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS427
She rests from using her fitness ball.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS429
As SOMEONE nods and complies, SOMEONE gives him a slap on the cheek.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS430
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE then delivers a fast right hook.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS431
In a posh ladies room, SOMEONE controls her breath.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS432
In the chic restaurant, customers clear out as the two men brawl. SOMEONE sends SOMEONE rolling over a table then throws a knife into a leather chair by SOMEONE's head.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS433
She sees food on her gum line.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS435
SOMEONE stuns SOMEONE with a throat punch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS436
SOMEONE wheels a coat rack like a quarterstaff.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS437
SOMEONE uses the pole to ram SOMEONE backward through a glass partition.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS439
She mops her cleavage. Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE scrap right over a balcony. They plummet 20 feet onto a table below.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS440
In the ladies room.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS441
Now bloody face then lying on glass shards, SOMEONE feebly throws a fork at SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS442
SOMEONE comes down the stairs.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS443
With disappointment in her eyes, SOMEONE turns away.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS444
As she clears out, the two battered man wilt.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS445
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in her convertible bug.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS446
SOMEONE hands her a sippy cup.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS447
An SUV bumps them from behind. A second bumps them from the front. Trapping the car. Two men approach, one is Heinrich.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS448
Heinrich signals an accomplice. In the trashed restaurant, the guys stand up.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS449
Now they exit to the sidewalk.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS450
It's SOMEONE's cell calling.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS451
Three SUVs escort SOMEONE's VW.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS452
SOMEONE manipulates his handheld.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS454
SOMEONE flings the valet from the car.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS456
SOMEONE takes the mic.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS457
On the freeway, SOMEONE's convertible is escorted on three sides. The passenger side is unguarded.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS458
As the Jeep comes up fast on the VW's unguarded side, SOMEONE grips the roll bar and leans out. He leaps aboard the convertible and punches a thug in back, sending him tumbling. SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS461
SOMEONE shoots the tire on SOMEONE's car which veers off the road and catches air over a decorative man-made lake.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS462
The huge splash blocks everything from view except a free flying license plate.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS463
The water calms. SOMEONE sits safely in the buoyant bobbing bug.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS464
On the road, a gunman in one SUV fires on the jeep which evades to the right. Heinrich fires from another SUV. A return shot from SOMEONE tags Heinrich's shoulder. His car halts and he scolds, Drive you idiot. His driver slumps dead. Heinrich shoves the body out and drives on.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS466
In a parking garage, two SUVs race their way. SOMEONE reverses as they advance head on. He beckons SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS468
The Jeep does a tight skidding 180, SOMEONE nearly falls out but SOMEONE pulls him back in. As one SUV gunman aims at them, SOMEONE pulls his trigger and pegs the guy.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS469
With a lug wrench, SOMEONE smashes the window of an enemy driver beside them. Hooks the stirring wheel and yanks. The SUV hits a column and explodes. Meanwhile, SOMEONE's son watches TV.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS472
Chased by another SUV, SOMEONE throws a gas jug from the Jeep. As it bounces under the pursuer's bumper, the agents shoot it and it explodes. The SUV gets thrown upside down. Seeing the road's end, SOMEONE breaks. The Jeep spins to a sidelong halt within inches of the sheer drop.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS473
SOMEONE sways outward precariously.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS474
Two traffic cones plunge to the highway below.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS475
SOMEONE looks from SOMEONE to SOMEONE. His gaze intense and thoughtful.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS476
He addresses SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS477
Heinrich's SUV speeds toward them. Standing on the road, SOMEONE and SOMEONE both fire at it.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS478
SOMEONE stands back by the Jeep, visible between the two agents.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS481
The agents kneel. As the SUV rounds closer, they fire.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS482
A deploying airbag wallops Heinrich's face and he careens into a mobile construction light.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS483
The blast sends the SUV rolling sideways toward the road's unfinished end.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS484
In slow motion, SOMEONE and SOMEONE each race to one side. They both beacon SOMEONE, urging her to clear out of the way. But the tumbling SUV bares down swiftly.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS485
Scene from the ground, the SUV and Jeep barrel over the edge and explode on impact.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS486
A bird's-eye-view shows the black smoke hiding the end of the unfinished roadway.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS487
The smoke thins and SOMEONE becomes visible, semi-reclined on the road.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS488
Opposite him, SOMEONE holds SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS489
SOMEONE's squints at them, stunned and knowing.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS490
SOMEONE tenderly caresses her hair and SOMEONE peers longingly at him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS491
As SOMEONE looks on, they both turn their attention to him.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS492
He resiliently straightens his posture and gives a few curt nods of his head.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS493
All three notice the news chopper. Meanwhile, SOMEONE's son and ex-wife gawk at the TV.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS494
Later, a paramedic faces SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS495
Wrapped in a blanket, SOMEONE goes to SOMEONE who sits at the rear of an ambulance. He stands and they kiss each other's cheeks.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS496
He looks to his friend.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS498
SOMEONE gives him a warm smile.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS499
SOMEONE lowers his gaze and nods shyly.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS500
Heading off, he pauses and turns back to face his approaching friend.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS501
SOMEONE adjusts his wrist watch.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS502
SOMEONE regards his friend with a concerned frown.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS503
They hug.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS504
They part and SOMEONE heads off.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS505
Rejoining SOMEONE, SOMEONE wraps his arms around her.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS506
His lips meet hers in a smoldering kiss.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS507
They rock back and forth lingering in the embrace.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS508
Looking up at SOMEONE, SOMEONE shakes her head knowingly and smiles.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS509
As they enjoy another kiss, we drift up and away from the unfinished overpass and gaze out over the city.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS510
Now in the SOMEONE Arts Dojo, SOMEONE and SOMEONE face off again as both of their fathers look on.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS511
As SOMEONE charges, SOMEONE swings his leg over the bigger boy's arm and flips him to the mat. He runs proudly to SOMEONE.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS513
Leaning on SOMEONE, the man obeys with effort.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS514
SOMEONE pats his back.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS515
As SOMEONE steps away, SOMEONE shyly approaches his ex who waits for him in a doorway.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS516
She smiles and glances away. Her wide eyes glistening.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS517
He presents himself to her humbly.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS518
Leaning against the door frame, she steps forward and extends a hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS519
SOMEONE's brow lifts in a delighted smile, he shakes her hand.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS520
With a tearful smile, she gestures SOMEONE to follow her as she goes over to her son.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS521
In slow motion, the reunited family walks down a hallway together.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS522
SOMEONE lays a hand on SOMEONE's back, gently ushering her through a doorway.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS523
He follows with a hopeful gaze. Fade to black.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS524
Now a military grade helicopter flies out at a night time mission.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS525
Inside, SOMEONE answers his cell.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS526
In a sporty convertible.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS527
In the helicopter.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS528
They jump up and down, a hatch lowers.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS529
SOMEONE checks SOMEONE's chute.
THIS_MEANS_WAR_DVS530
SOMEONE stares at him.