He lowers his hand from his heart.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS23
SOMEONE enters the penalty box, where he sits on a waiting recliner, puts his feet up, and rests his hands behind his head.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS24
Fans bang on the glass.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS25
Now, in the locker room, reporters gather around a young man. The muscle-bound SOMEONE steps out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS26
SOMEONE stares at the trendy kid.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS27
He watches SOMEONE return to the reporters,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS28
then glances around with a troubled expression.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS29
Later, in the rink,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS30
he approaches a group of fans.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS31
As a zamboni passes, a grinning SOMEONE accepts a pen from a curly-haired boy.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS32
SOMEONE eyes the boy.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS33
SOMEONE frowns.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS34
The children's parents glare.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS35
The boy lowers his gaze.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS36
SOMEONE winks.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS37
Now, in a suburban neighborhood, a Corvette's license
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS39
Indoors, SOMEONE clowns, wearing French fries like fangs.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS40
A girl and mother smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS41
A pre-teen boy glowers.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS42
The moppy-haired boy goes to the fridge. SOMEONE pretends to perish.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS43
The girl makes fangs.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS44
Her brunette mother crouches beside her.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS45
She checks the new gap.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS46
SOMEONE shifts uncomfortably.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS47
His mother reluctant.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS49
SOMEONE watches.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS51
SOMEONE brings dinner plates to a counter.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS52
She shoots him a look.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS53
She caresses his cheek with her thumb.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS54
He smiles and they kiss.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS55
He chases the girl through the house.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS56
SOMEONE and four buddies play cards at the kitchen table.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS57
SOMEONE makes a face.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS58
The guys stare and he gets up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS59
SOMEONE glances through a doorway.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS60
Now, the girl sleeps soundly in her bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS61
SOMEONE reaches under her pillow and pulls out a dollar SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS63
Grinning at the money, he tiptoes out of her room.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS64
Later in the kitchen, SOMEONE holds a wad of cash.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS65
The couple share a smile
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS66
and SOMEONE follows the guys.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS68
SOMEONE's playful grin evaporates. His girlfriend searches the floor.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS69
SOMEONE shows his winning.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS71
She mouths the word "Stop", then secretly goes through her purse behind the bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS72
Her mom holds up a dollar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS73
SOMEONE smiles and hugs her mother.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS74
The woman kisses her cheek, then glares at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS76
She hands him his jacket.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS77
She starts off.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS78
She goes upstairs.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS79
SOMEONE rattles a fist.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS81
Now, his Corvette sits outside an apartment complex, where a second story light goes out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS83
In a darkened bedroom, SOMEONE lies on his side and rubs his shoulder.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS84
He rolls onto his back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS85
He stirs under the covers and rolls onto his stomach.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS86
Two bulges form under SOMEONE's shirt on his upper back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS87
SOMEONE wiggles his shoulder.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS88
As he lies still, his hands find a glowing document under the pillow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS89
Its heading reads "Department of Dissemination of Disbelief"
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS90
and demands his appearance at the Grand Hall of Tooth Fairy Land.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS92
SOMEONE sits up on the edge of his bed, flips on a lamp, and reads the summons.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS93
As he chuckles, a pair of fluffy-edged wings spread open on his back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS94
Wide-eyed, SOMEONE swallows, then glances nervously.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS95
He approaches a mirror.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS96
He stumbles back on the bed, then gets up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS97
SOMEONE looks down.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS98
Magical smoke envelops his feet and rises up his entire body,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS99
leaving behind a fairy's pretty tights, tutu, and satiny bodice. As SOMEONE grimaces, the magical smoke swirls overhead.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS100
Loose papers fly and a wind blows blankets off the bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS101
SOMEONE looks up, peering through a seemingly endless funnel of energy.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS102
SOMEONE blinks helplessly as lights glimmer on his frightened face.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS104
Now, in his pretty dress, SOMEONE stands in a grand hall.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS105
Male and female fairies pass by. Some with wings, some without.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS106
A female fairy flies overhead.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS107
A male fairy's wing brushes SOMEONE's face and he bats at it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS108
Another male sneers at him. A female smiles. On a wall, a mechanical information board updates.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS109
Name, tooth, location, and status. A listing about a canine in a tin can updates to a molar on a window sill.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS110
SOMEONE watches a flying female collect files from office worker fairies. She flies up to a map of the world and touches her wand to a location over Eastern Europe.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS111
SOMEONE gapes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS112
A gangly geeky man faces him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS113
SOMEONE grimaces.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS114
SOMEONE sneers at SOMEONE's tutu.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS115
Bald fairies pass with pamphlets.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS116
A stocky male fairy walks up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS117
SOMEONE puts on a beaming smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS118
SOMEONE grins. The stocky fairy pantomimes flying.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS119
SOMEONE bolts, knocking other fairies down on his way.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS120
Fairies point magic wands and drag him back to SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS121
He stands up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS122
The wingless case worker pushes him, then smirks.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS123
SOMEONE pushes him back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS124
He rolls his shoulders and SOMEONE glances at the crowd.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS125
SOMEONE takes off his glasses.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS126
SOMEONE shoves him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS127
SOMEONE grabs the stocky fairy's magic wand.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS128
Someone throws SOMEONE a wand.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS129
As he flexes his arms, his wand shoots fairy dust in his eyes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS130
SOMEONE pokes him with his wand. SOMEONE grabs it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS131
He snaps it in two.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS132
Everyone turns. A matronly four-winged fairy gracefully descends through sunbeams to the floor.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS133
The captivated younger fairies gape.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS134
SOMEONE grins.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS135
SOMEONE shakes his head, then furrows his brow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS137
She grins, then starts off.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS138
She studies his dress.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS139
She leans and SOMEONE mimes cracking an egg.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS140
Now, SOMEONE waits among tall supply shelves. SOMEONE arrives in a blue satin tunic and tights.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS146
He tosses SOMEONE's clipboard.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS147
As SOMEONE fetches it, SOMEONE finds an elderly fairy in a cardigan descending a ladder.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS148
He hangs up a cellphone.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS150
He glances aside, then gestures for SOMEONE to crouch to his eye level.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS151
His wing hits SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS152
His wing brushes SOMEONE's face again.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS153
SOMEONE accepts the wand and avoids SOMEONE's wing.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS154
SOMEONE shows SOMEONE a spray canister.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS155
He grabs a tube of paste.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS156
A tiny bone shape decorates each mint.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS157
SOMEONE takes one.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS158
SOMEONE's eyes widen and SOMEONE nod.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS159
The new fairy glances around.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS160
He grabs a tiny canister.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS161
He hurries off.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS163
He holds up a little pouch.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS164
He sprinkles it in SOMEONE's face.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS165
Later, in utter whiteness,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS166
a male fairy stands at a control station.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS167
They pound fists.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS168
Duke pulls a lever and SOMEONE takes off.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS169
He pushes another lever and a squirming SOMEONE flies higher.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS171
The case worker grabs a tennis ball from a bin.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS172
He throws the ball, then grabs a racket.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS173
A pitching machine fires ball after ball.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS174
One nails SOMEONE's groin. Now, SOMEONE stands at a check-in window.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS175
SOMEONE reluctantly raises his hand and glares at the winged clerk.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS176
SOMEONE balks.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS178
The clerk glares. SOMEONE sheepishly glances around, then gives in.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS179
She eyes him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS180
Now in an office.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS181
He notices her tapping finger, then shakes his head.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS182
She sprinkles fairy dust.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS183
The screen goes white,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS184
then SOMEONE wakes up in bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS185
He glances at his surroundings.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS186
He crosses his arms and feels his back for wings.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS187
Finding nothing, he relaxes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS188
Now, SOMEONE answers her door to find SOMEONE holding a bouquet of roses.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS189
She holds a few of Tess' dolls.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS190
SOMEONE eyes her steadily.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS191
She barely smiles.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS192
SOMEONE raises her brow thoughtfully and nods.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS194
With a playful look, SOMEONE shifts his eyes to the bouquet of flowers then gives his girlfriend a winning grin.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS195
She half stifles her smile as she accepts the bouquet.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS196
SOMEONE's grin stays plastered on his face as he gives a few wobbling nods.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS198
He turns away. SOMEONE grins.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS199
In his room, SOMEONE plays guitar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS200
SOMEONE enters with a hockey stick half wrapped in paper.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS201
SOMEONE keeps playing on his loft bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS202
He autographs it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS203
SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS204
SOMEONE glares at the stick then at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS205
SOMEONE leans the stick against the bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS206
He grins widely at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS207
SOMEONE looks away.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS208
He holds out his fist.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS209
SOMEONE ignores it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS211
Later at SOMEONE's. SOMEONE grins.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS212
She leans in and they kiss.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS213
SOMEONE's phone lights up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS214
He grabs it from a nearby table and reads a text message.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS217
He heads to the kitchen.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS218
SOMEONE gets whipped cream and strawberries from the fridge.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS219
As he returns to the living room,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS220
his fairy wings sprout from his back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS221
SOMEONE paws at the air, her eyes still shut.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS222
SOMEONE grabs his phone.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS223
As he turns away, he knocks over a lamp.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS224
In the kitchen, light flashes and SOMEONE finds himself in his tooth fairy uniform.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS225
SOMEONE rushes outside and answers his phone.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS226
SOMEONE stands in the doorway.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS227
She leaves.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS228
SOMEONE creeps off.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS229
Now, his wing sticks out of the driver's window of his Corvette as he pulls up in front of a house.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS230
Waiting on the sidewalk, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE climb out of the vehicle.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS231
SOMEONE swats a bent wing into place as he stands.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS232
He approaches his case worker.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS233
At the front door, SOMEONE takes out his tube of shrinking paste.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS235
Shaking his head skeptically, SOMEONE twists the cap off the tube.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS236
He lifts the tube to his lips.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS237
SOMEONE grimaces as he sucks on the tube.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS238
He smacks his lips thoughtfully as he lowers
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS239
He flicks his tongue.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS240
He shrinks to only a few inches.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS241
SOMEONE raises his foot at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS242
SOMEONE sets his foot down.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS243
He drops a rolled up dollar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS244
In SOMEONE's hands, the dollar is the size of a rolled up poster.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS245
SOMEONE glares sourly as SOMEONE lies on his stomach and wriggles under the door.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS246
He drops the rolled up dollar and slides back to retrieve it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS247
Now, he straightens on the other side of the door and looks around.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS248
With the dollar strapped to his back, he cautiously tiptoes across a hardwood floor, making his way past a looming dining table.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS249
He peers around a corner.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS250
He pulls back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS252
With a frightened look, he steps out and stares at a sleeping cat.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS253
SOMEONE carefully sidesteps past the head of the sleeping tabby.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS254
The cat's ear twitches as he passes in front of its face.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS255
SOMEONE stumbles as the tabby stretches. Its eyes remain closed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS256
As SOMEONE hurriedly tiptoes by, the cat shifts in its sleep.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS257
Now, SOMEONE slides under a bedroom door.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS258
SOMEONE emerges on the other side of a door
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS259
and spots a sleeping boy across the room.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS260
A few toys show in silhouette underneath his bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS261
SOMEONE dashes to a night stand,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS263
then frowns uncertainly at the towering bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS264
He grabs hold of a knob on the night stand and hoists himself up to the drawer above.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS265
On the nearby bed, the blanket hangs over the side.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS266
SOMEONE leaps for it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS267
Clinging to the blanket, he climbs up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS268
He reaches the top and peeks over at the boy, whose chest rises rhythmically.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS270
SOMEONE glances around, then swings his legs up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS271
He stumbles slightly as the stands on the bed's plush surface.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS273
With his gaze fixed on the boy's closed eyes, SOMEONE creeps toward the headboard.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS274
He takes a cautious step toward the boy's pillow,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS277
He lifts it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS278
He crawls underneath the pillow. Using the lit tip of his wand, he searches under the pillow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS279
Creeping further under the pillow, he finds a tooth.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS280
He grabs it and starts to wriggle back out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS281
With a quick glance over his shoulder, he leaves the rolled up dollar SOMEONE in its place.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS283
SOMEONE cautiously crawls out from under the pillow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS284
As he straightens, he looks at the boy, then turns to the edge of the bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS285
The boy rolls in his sleep, knocking SOMEONE off the bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS286
SOMEONE lands safely on the back of a plush alligator.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS287
He rolls off and shakes out his arms.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS288
The boy peers down at him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS289
SOMEONE jumps.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS291
SOMEONE scurries away. As he flattens himself against the wall, the boy's parents rush in. The flung open door whacks him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS292
SOMEONE peeks out from behind the door.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS293
As SOMEONE heads out, he comes face to face with the cat.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS294
He scampers behind a miniature skateboard half pipe.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS295
The tabby glares.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS296
SOMEONE reaches out from behind the half pipe and retrieves a tiny skateboard.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS297
As the tabby stalks closer, SOMEONE rides the skateboard up the half pipe and soars into the air. He winks at the cat as he passes over its head.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS298
As he escapes down the hallway, the tabby bounds after him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS299
SOMEONE jumps off the skateboard. The tabby gains on him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS300
He points his wand.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS301
He races into the kitchen and skids to a stop.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS302
Pressing his back against a wall, he swallows hard.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS303
With a SOMEONE, he peeks around the corner into the hallway and sees the tabby closing in.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS304
He notices a cat door on the other side of the kitchen.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS305
He reaches into his pouch, pulls out his cat away canister, and presses the nozzle button.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS306
The tabby shoots upward then runs off.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS307
SOMEONE scurries across the kitchen and launches himself against the plastic cat door flap.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS308
He tumbles outside then hurries away.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS309
At home, SOMEONE's barely taller than his sofa.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS310
She lies on the sofa. He sneaks by.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS312
Now, at the rink.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS323
SOMEONE walks with SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS324
SOMEONE grins as he leaves SOMEONE and joins his teammates on the ice. SOMEONE eyes the crowd.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS326
He steps out of the gangway and stares disbelievingly. Words on the scoreboard flash "Mick the Stick" in sync with the crowd's chanting.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS327
In the center of the rink, SOMEONE raises his arms to the crowd and lifts a gloved hand to his ear. He pumps his arms to the beat of the cheers, then skates over to SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS330
As SOMEONE glides away, SOMEONE uneasily glances around the arena. Later.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS340
SOMEONE deftly dribbles the puck toward the opposing team's goal.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS344
He works the puck between his skates.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS348
A roughneck checks SOMEONE. Behind him, SOMEONE checks a roughneck.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS353
As a player charges SOMEONE, SOMEONE starts over, then reads a message on the scoreboard.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS354
"Kids asleep at 2631 Castle Heights. "
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS356
He trips and falls face first. The charging roughneck mows SOMEONE down.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS359
SOMEONE frowns at SOMEONE, who smiles meagerly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS360
A bulge sprouts at his shoulder under his jersey.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS361
SOMEONE hides it. Now in the locker room.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS363
SOMEONE hurries by.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS364
He rushes into the bathroom and locks himself in a stall.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS365
His wings burst out of his jersey. He ducks.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS367
More teammates enter.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS368
They look under SOMEONE's stall.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS369
They glimpse the powder blue tights on his toes. SOMEONE squeezes his eyes shut and pushes the magic generator button on his wand.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS370
Glancing at the toilet, SOMEONE takes out his shrinking paste.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS371
He eats some paste.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS372
The players burst into the stall and find it empty.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS373
They see only water swirling down the flushed toilet.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS374
Now, SOMEONE waits on a sidewalk as SOMEONE slams his Corvette door.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS375
SOMEONE storms up to a house.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS376
And old man opens the front door.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS377
He throws amnesia dust then steps inside.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS378
He throws dust in the faces of all the family members.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS379
Dust falls on a dog, whose eyes go goofy.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS381
Now, SOMEONE lifts a pillow and the head of the child sleeping on it, takes the tooth, and tosses down a dollar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS383
She shows the disoriented family members wandering around.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS384
SOMEONE smacks SOMEONE's chest.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS385
SOMEONE smacks him back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS386
They spot the googly-eyed dog.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS387
Now, letters on double doors read "Break Room".
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS390
a young fairy reads, while another peruses food in a display case at a counter.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS391
SOMEONE flips through a magazine.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS392
He scowls at SOMEONE, who sits by him drinking.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS393
The case worker freezes and stares dreamily at the gossamer wings of two fairies across the room,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS394
the fluffy edges agleam in the sunlight.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS395
SOMEONE's lips part longingly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS396
SOMEONE notices his odd expression
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS397
and follows his gaze to the wing.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS398
He watches the wide-eyed case worker.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS399
SOMEONE blinks out of the moment.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS400
He meets SOMEONE's gaze, then sheepishly sips from his cup
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS401
As time passes, the break room grows emptier and emptier until only SOMEONE remains.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS402
His mouth hangs open as he lies across two chairs and sleeps.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS403
His head rests on a third chair's arm.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS404
He picks up his phone and reads a text "Assignment cancelled. "
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS407
SOMEONE honks her horn.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS408
SOMEONE steps onto his balcony.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS409
SOMEONE lifts his brow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS410
As SOMEONE gets out with a scowl,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS411
his mother sweetly mouths the word "Please".
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS412
SOMEONE forces a delighted crinkle of his nose.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS413
SOMEONE trudges toward the apartment.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS414
With a sarcastic smile, SOMEONE heads inside.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS415
SOMEONE wears his earphones as he steps into the living room,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS416
his hands shoved in his pockets.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS417
SOMEONE faces.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS419
Shaking his head, SOMEONE takes out his earphones.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS420
He scans the room, noting SOMEONE's hockey paraphernalia and average apartment, then sneers.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS423
Looking away impatiently, SOMEONE sets his hands on his hips. He turns back to SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS424
Later, he and SOMEONE stroll through the guitar section of a music store.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS425
SOMEONE picks up a guitar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS426
He plugs it into an amp.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS427
He thrusts the electric guitar into SOMEONE's hands.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS428
The boy grudgingly plops down on a stool and glowers up at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS429
He rolls his eyes as he leaves SOMEONE by himself. The boy watches SOMEONE walk away.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS431
He adjusts the guitar in his hands.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS432
A dark-haired girl rounds a corner and spots SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS433
As he continues to riff, his head down, she approaches.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS434
A boy walks over.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS435
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS436
He waves bashfully.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS437
As she leaves, SOMEONE steps closer.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS438
SOMEONE grabs the guitar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS439
SOMEONE arrives and taps SOMEONE's head with drumsticks.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS440
SOMEONE fearfully hands the guitar back to SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS441
SOMEONE watches as SOMEONE scurries away.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS442
SOMEONE grins and SOMEONE does too.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS443
Later, in SOMEONE's living room, they play cards and use cheese puffs as betting chips.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS444
SOMEONE bets.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS445
SOMEONE sets down his hand. SOMEONE collects his winnings.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS446
He tilts his head at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS447
SOMEONE stops organizing the cards and meets SOMEONE's gaze.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS448
The boy lifts his brow expectantly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS449
SOMEONE holds out his fist.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS451
SOMEONE eyes it, then pounds his fist to SOMEONE's.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS452
He and SOMEONE share a grin.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS453
SOMEONE's phone vibrates.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS456
He escorts them outside.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS457
Later, with SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS458
SOMEONE closes his eyes as he sprays.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS459
Mist shoots away from him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS460
SOMEONE turns the nozzle to face SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS461
SOMEONE opens his eyes and glares at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS462
He closes them again and sprays.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS463
A could of mist wafts over him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS464
SOMEONE inspects himself.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS465
He disappears.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS466
Now, SOMEONE's footprints appear on a carpet as he steps into a den.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS467
A couple reads on a couch.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS468
The woman looks up as a rocking seems
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS469
to move by itself and a lamp tips.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS470
SOMEONE steps on a plush toy.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS471
Amnesia dust whirls in the air.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS472
SOMEONE fumbles the powder onto the coffee table. The woman faints.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS473
At the front door, SOMEONE faces a small dog.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS474
At headquarters, the dog dangles from SOMEONE's wing by its teeth.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS475
Two fairy assistant go to grab the dog.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS476
His wing freed, SOMEONE gives his boss the tooth.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS477
He offers a sarcastic salute, then heads out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS478
Fairy Godmother's jaw hangs slack.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS479
SOMEONE grins.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS480
He storms out into a corridor.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS481
A cagey fairy waits for him as he passes through a doorway.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS482
The cagey fairy waves him over.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS483
SOMEONE points quizzically at himself and the fairy nods.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS484
He opens a display pouch and shows magic supplies.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS485
SOMEONE knits his brow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS486
He glances toward his boss.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS487
He leans toward Ziggy.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS488
SOMEONE frowns and glances back at Fairy Godmother's office.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS490
In front of a house, SOMEONE sprays himself down.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS491
He turns see through but doesn't disappear.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS492
A woman sees his ghostly form on her way out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS493
SOMEONE examines his transparent hands.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS494
The terrified woman gapes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS495
SOMEONE eats some shrinking paste.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS496
Smacking his lips, he goes back to normal.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS497
The woman's chin trembles fearfully. Instead of shrinking, SOMEONE's head stretches like a balloon. His ears spring out as his head grows too big for his body.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS498
The fairy's head returns to the right size.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS499
The woman uses her phone.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS500
Later, police cruisers surround the house. Now, SOMEONE sits in a police department holding cell with four other detainees.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS501
SOMEONE appears in front of him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS502
The others can't see SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS503
SOMEONE frowns.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS504
SOMEONE frowns. The others stare.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS505
Later, SOMEONE walks SOMEONE out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS506
They halt near the front desk.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS507
SOMEONE winces helplessly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS508
SOMEONE narrows her eye.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS509
The clerk at the desk watches as SOMEONE tosses a pinch of amnesia dust in SOMEONE's face.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS510
He throws more dust at her.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS511
SOMEONE dashes her with more dust and the clerk gawks.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS512
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE, then gives him a hug.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS513
The clerk scoffs.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS514
In SOMEONE's apartment.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS515
SOMEONE wears his helmet and hockey pads over his tooth fairy uniform.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS516
SOMEONE arches his brows doubtfully.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS517
Later outside, SOMEONE runs up to a tall concrete fence, hooks his hockey stick over the top, and vaults over it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS518
Now, the door to a young boy's room swings open
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS519
and a shadowy figure strides in.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS520
It's a mousy-looking father in a sweater vest.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS521
He moseys over to the bed and reaches under his son's pillow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS522
As he extracts a tooth,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS523
SOMEONE treads up behind him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS524
The father turns and his jaw drops. SOMEONE covers his face with his gloved hand.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS525
He lowers his glove from the man's gaping mouth.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS526
He turns his hand palm up demandingly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS527
The father moves his hand toward SOMEONE's.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS529
SOMEONE nods.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS530
The dumbfounded father blinks his wide eyes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS532
SOMEONE grins and strides onto a balcony.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS533
He halts just outside and the father steps closer.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS534
SOMEONE props his hands on his hips.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS535
The father gawks disbelievingly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS536
SOMEONE climbs over the railing and jumps off the balcony.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS540
SOMEONE looks on.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS541
During a game. A fight breaks out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS543
Alone in the locker room, SOMEONE douses himself with invisibility spray and grins.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS544
He fades completely from view.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS545
Later, a door to the rink opens. Two lines carve onto the ice as the invisible SOMEONE skates out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS546
The lines stop right behind SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS547
The ref drops the puck.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS548
SOMEONE pumps with his skates but stays in place.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS549
Finally free, SOMEONE chases after the puck.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS550
Without warning, SOMEONE gets thrown backward.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS552
Now, the star player's jersey stirs under his arms as he's tickled.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS553
A peppermint embossed with a dog bone floats through midair and flies into SOMEONE's mouth. As he gulps it down, a ref skates up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS554
SOMEONE grabs his throat.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS555
SOMEONE snarls.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS556
The visible SOMEONE exits
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS557
the locker room.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS558
SOMEONE returns to the bench and takes a seat,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS559
taps his throat and shudders, then shrugs. A teammate elbows him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS560
SOMEONE bumps him angrily and strokes his throat, then hunches over and pants.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS561
SOMEONE beams.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS563
As SOMEONE plays drums, SOMEONE plays his guitar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS564
SOMEONE's stunned lips part as SOMEONE sneers expectantly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS565
The hockey player locks eyes with him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS566
The burly man swallows and shakes his head.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS567
SOMEONE blinks thoughtfully.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS568
SOMEONE points at him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS569
The player eyes the boy sheepishly, then smiles.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS572
SOMEONE drops his gaze and works his lips. He nods. They share a chuckle.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS574
Now, at tooth fairy headquarters,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS575
SOMEONE saunters into SOMEONE's office. He wears his hockey pads and fairy uniform.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS576
He presents her with a tooth box and leaves. SOMEONE smiles. As SOMEONE gives a stunned look, he shrugs modestly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS578
In the grand hall.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS579
Outside, SOMEONE sprints.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS580
He weaves through an obstacle course.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS581
In the empty ice rink, SOMEONE practices but falls. Now, he and SOMEONE play music.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS582
Outside, SOMEONE runs away from the obstacle course.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS583
On the ice, SOMEONE wipes out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS584
Back at the obstacle course.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS585
At the rink, SOMEONE shoots pucks at the net.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS586
At the obstacle course, a flat cutout of a cartoony bulldog pops up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS587
Another cutout shows a child.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS588
Now, SOMEONE skates, then plays music with SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS589
At the obstacle course, SOMEONE hurdles a fence. His ankles graze the top and he falls.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS591
Later, SOMEONE skates nimbly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS592
At the obstacle course, cutouts showing a family pop up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS593
SOMEONE beheads one.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS594
He smacks into an arch holding up a fake bedroom window.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS595
Later, he climbs up SOMEONE to reach it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS596
He pokes partway through.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS597
With a shove from SOMEONE, he flops through and hits the ground.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS598
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE dance as SOMEONE and SOMEONE play their instruments.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS599
Now, SOMEONE minces around traffic cones.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS600
Later, SOMEONE demonstrates invisibility spray.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS601
They face the parent cutouts.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS602
At the rink, SOMEONE works a puck around a simple dummy consisting of two feet and a stick.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS603
Observing, SOMEONE beams. Now, SOMEONE fires puck after puck into the net.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS604
An awed SOMEONE watches from the bench. SOMEONE shoots the last puck and pumps a fist.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS605
At the obstacle course, SOMEONE mimes using invisibility spray then amnesia dust. He climbs up the staged window and shows a prop tooth.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS606
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE finish music practice.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS607
They share a smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS608
SOMEONE shows a flyer for the talent show.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS609
It lists the performers names with SOMEONE's at the bottom.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS610
SOMEONE folds the flyer and sets it aside.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS611
SOMEONE nods, stifling an eager smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS612
SOMEONE's mouth stutters, then relaxes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS613
SOMEONE grins.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS614
SOMEONE gives an encouraging smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS615
Now, at a hockey game.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS616
On the bench.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS617
As SOMEONE skates out, SOMEONE checks the scoreboard.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS618
A teammate returns to the bench and SOMEONE skates out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS619
He ducks down and checks an arrow then hurls the player on his back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS620
The arrow crashes down onto the ice.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS621
SOMEONE hesitates, his stick raised and the puck at his feet.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS622
An arrow bashes him away from the puck, knocking him down.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS623
As SOMEONE irritably shakes his head, SOMEONE pushes himself onto his hands and knees.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS624
SOMEONE hangs his head.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS625
Behind the Ice Wolves bench, the coach angrily chews his gum and glares at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS626
The burly player returns to the bench and takes a seat, his gaze downcast.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS627
His coach swaggers closer and averts his eyes, then whirls to face SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS628
SOMEONE shakes his head.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS630
Later, SOMEONE drives home.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS631
He finds SOMEONE and the kids waiting in the parking lot.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS632
He musters a curt wave and pulls into a parking space.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS633
SOMEONE and SOMEONE tango toward his bumper.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS634
SOMEONE totes his guitar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS635
SOMEONE gets out with his duffel.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS636
Cringing tearfully, SOMEONE smashes his guitar on the pavement.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS637
SOMEONE and SOMEONE clutch their hands to their mouths.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS638
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE and shakes his head, then collects the pieces of his guitar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS639
SOMEONE storms to her car.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS640
SOMEONE stands frozen.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS641
SOMEONE stifles tears.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS642
She tugs open her car door and gets behind the wheel.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS643
SOMEONE jerks her head and drives off.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS644
SOMEONE squeezes his eyes shut,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS645
then regretfully shakes his head and summons a sorrowful breath.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS646
Fade to black.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS647
Now in bed, he wakes up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS648
He staggers to his front door.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS649
Opening up, he finds SOMEONE outside.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS650
Later, upstairs.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS651
SOMEONE shows a fairy learner's permit with his photo on it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS652
SOMEONE shifts uncomfortably.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS653
SOMEONE throws a hand toward the floor in a falling motion.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS654
SOMEONE eyes the spot sadly,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS655
then purses his lips.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS656
He and SOMEONE lock gazes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS657
The case worker gives a mocking sneer and disappears in thin air.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS659
At a game, a ref drops the puck.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS660
Two players crash into each other.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS661
An opposing player blocks SOMEONE as he tries to weave around.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS662
The puck bounces off the net's frame.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS663
An opponent bashes SOMEONE in the back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS664
SOMEONE writhes face down on the ice. A SOMEONE skates out.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS665
Behind the bench, the Ice Wolves' coach scowls, then sidles over to SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS666
SOMEONE eyes him quizzically.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS667
The coach glares, then stalks away.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS668
Straightening out of a slouch, SOMEONE grabs his helmet.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS669
In the stands, the NHL hopeful, SOMEONE, watches anxiously as SOMEONE heads onto the ice.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS670
SOMEONE lumbers onto the ice.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS671
An opposing team member knocks him down.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS672
SOMEONE slides into the rink wall under the opposing team's box. His rivals bang their sticks.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS673
SOMEONE wearily pushes himself up onto all fours.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS674
As he sits back, he sees two opposing players skate past with smug stares.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS675
Their teammates on the bench jeer at SOMEONE as he gets to his feet.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS676
At the Ice Wolves' bench, the coach shouts impatiently. His teammates pound the wall with their gloved hands.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS677
SOMEONE's hopeless gaze sweeps over the ice rink.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS678
He spots SOMEONE perched on a goal's crossbar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS680
Unseen by the rival goalie, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE steadily.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS681
As the discouraged athlete meets his gaze,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS682
the case worker jerks his head toward the rink.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS683
SOMEONE's eyes narrow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS685
SOMEONE repeats the encouraging gesture and gives a nod.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS686
The athlete looks away, his chest heaving.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS689
SOMEONE brightly lifts his brow and cocks his head.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS691
His gaze growing determined,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS692
SOMEONE heaves a resolute sigh and bravely leaves the wall. SOMEONE's smile grows as the athlete skates out with an invigorated stride.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS693
He rushes an opponent.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS694
Stopping short, he intercepts the puck.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS695
SOMEONE stares slack-jawed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS696
The defender smacks him with his stick.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS697
Leaping, SOMEONE flings the puck with his stick.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS698
He lands on his stomach and slides. The puck flies into the net.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS699
His teammates cheer and SOMEONE's dad lifts the boy in his arms.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS700
As the fans whoop, SOMEONE and another teammate shout joyfully. Their coach folds his arms, shakes his head, and allows a smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS701
SOMEONE stands and raises his arms. His teammates join him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS702
SOMEONE and his teammates skate across the ice.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS703
He faces SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS704
SOMEONE gives a crooked smile and pumps his fist. With a warm smirk, SOMEONE sits back on the bench.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS705
SOMEONE reaches the center line with his teammates and exhales through pursed lips.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS706
SOMEONE spots SOMEONE by the bench tapping his watch. As the athlete stares, the case worker stubbornly points at his timepiece.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS707
He shifts his conflicted gaze and crouches slightly, his stick ready.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS708
The play begins.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS709
He faces SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS710
The scoreboard LED screens flash an address.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS711
2122 Pine Street.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS712
SOMEONE soberly faces SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS713
SOMEONE gives a patient shrug.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS714
The case worker's lips curl upward in a smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS715
SOMEONE's wings sprout from his back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS716
His coach and teammates stare wide-eyed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS717
In the stands, SOMEONE blinks at his favorite player.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS718
SOMEONE drops his stick, shakes off his gloves, and removes his helmet.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS719
His brow lifted, he eyes the people filling the stands all around him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS720
SOMEONE yields a stoic shrug and faces his case worker.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS722
With a brilliant flash of light, SOMEONE's hockey uniform vanishes, leaving him clad in his satiny tunic and tights. His coach and teammates gape. SOMEONE flashes a self-conscious smirk.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS724
He skates a broad, graceful arc around the rink as the crowd watches breathlessly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS725
SOMEONE makes another turn and gathers speed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS726
He smiles at his benched teammates as he passes and they respond with slack-jawed stares.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS727
Beside them, SOMEONE looks on proudly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS728
In slow motion, SOMEONE's wings give a powerful flap and his skates lift off the ice.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS729
The winged man extends his arms straight by his sides and flies over us.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS730
SOMEONE grins, tilting his head back to watch.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS731
SOMEONE's teammates and fans get to their feet.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS732
The coach's chewing gum balances on his slack lip.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS733
In the stands, SOMEONE stands on his chair.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS734
From overhead, we watch SOMEONE ascend toward us with a wide-eyed smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS735
As SOMEONE watches soberly, a sparkling swirling vortex opens just beneath the ceiling.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS736
The announcers gawk as SOMEONE flies toward the vortex then vanishes inside it with a flash of light.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS737
Below, his teammates and fans stare after him and the players on the ice stand motionless.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS738
SOMEONE rides out atop a zamboni mounted with a sleek gleaming cannon.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS739
SOMEONE swivels the gun as it shoots a thick jet of amnesia dust.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS741
As SOMEONE sleeps soundly in her bed, SOMEONE's hand reaches under her pillow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS742
He removes a tiny envelope sealed with a smiley face sticker.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS743
SOMEONE beams fondly at it,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS745
then slides a rolled up SOMEONE under the pillow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS746
The winged man leans forward, resting his elbows the side of Tess' bed as he gazes tenderly at her.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS747
She awakens and smiles.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS748
She sits up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS749
She notices his broad wing.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS750
SOMEONE pats his cheek.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS751
SOMEONE blinks sweetly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS753
SOMEONE smiles gently, then sprinkles a ring of glowing sparkly dust between them.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS754
SOMEONE looks up at the hovering wreath
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS755
and SOMEONE grins at her.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS756
Meeting his gaze, she beams joyfully.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS757
They share a smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS758
The little girl gazes up at the shimmering dust.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS761
SOMEONE creeps downstairs and ducks around a corner, leaving SOMEONE undisturbed on the sofa, sound asleep.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS762
She doses under an afghan, a work document by her side.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS764
In his room, SOMEONE lies on his loft bed, his back to the door and his eyes closed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS768
An ear bud wire trails from SOMEONE starts to approach, then pauses. The boy's hand rhythmically.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS769
Taking a breath, SOMEONE tucks his wings out of sight.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS775
and crosses to the bed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS778
He exhales bracing, then taps the boy's elbow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS779
Rolling over, SOMEONE scowls and removes his ear buds. He turns away from his visitor.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS781
SOMEONE shakes his head
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS782
His back still to SOMEONE's remorseful gaze, SOMEONE shuts his eyes and bites his lip.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS785
Blinking tearfully, he rolls over and props himself up on his elbows.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS787
SOMEONE shifts his sober gaze, nods, then raises a finger.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS789
Crouching beneath the bed, he takes out his wand.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS790
SOMEONE shuts his eyes, shakes his head, and mutters a silent wish.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS792
Opening his eyes, he flourishes the wand and sparkling light trails from its tip. SOMEONE eyes his handiwork and grins.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS796
he presents SOMEONE with a shiny new guitar.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS798
SOMEONE sizes up SOMEONE's outfit.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS799
SOMEONE smiles and nods.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS800
Leaving the room, SOMEONE spreads his wings.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS801
The boy's smile vanishes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS802
Now, by the stairs.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS803
Turning, he finds SOMEONE gawking.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS804
SOMEONE hurries downstairs and joins the winged man at his side.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS805
SOMEONE takes in the situation, then tilts her head.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS806
As SOMEONE grins, SOMEONE joins them.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS807
Passing SOMEONE, SOMEONE pauses and gives him a kiss.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS809
Holding SOMEONE close, SOMEONE takes to the air.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS810
City lights twinkle below.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS811
They land in the school's parking lot.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS812
As SOMEONE grins at him, SOMEONE lets out a breath and soberly holds the boy's gaze.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS813
SOMEONE's smile fades.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS814
SOMEONE produces his pouch of amnesia dust.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS815
The boy's lip curls questioningly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS816
SOMEONE takes out a pinch of dust,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS817
casts it at SOMEONE's face, and vanishes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS818
A school faculty member comes out and spots the
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS819
Now, in SOMEONE's office.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS820
SOMEONE looks on.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS821
As SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE expectantly,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS822
the case worker leans closer.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS823
SOMEONE gapes proudly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS824
SOMEONE offers a warm smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS828
She sprinkles an arc of sparkling dust before him and his wings vanish.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS829
She extends a hand.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS830
SOMEONE points at it.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS831
Grinning, he spreads his arms and envelops her in a hug.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS832
SOMEONE winces.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS833
He hugs her again and kisses her cheek.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS834
SOMEONE shifts anxiously.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS835
SOMEONE bestows a badge upon him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS836
It's shaped like a tooth with a pair of fairy wings.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS837
SOMEONE beams as she pins it on SOMEONE's vest.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS838
The case worker gawks.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS839
SOMEONE hands over his supply bag.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS840
He leans toward SOMEONE with puckered lips but she gracefully recoils.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS841
He offers an awkward bow.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS842
She holds a small box.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS843
SOMEONE's smile fades.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS844
SOMEONE smiles.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS845
SOMEONE shakes his head and shrugs his hand.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS846
He grins.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS847
SOMEONE's expression grows serious and earnest.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS848
The human nods.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS849
The new tooth fairy gives a sad smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS850
SOMEONE whops him.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS851
SOMEONE punches SOMEONE's shoulder twice.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS852
He flings his arms around SOMEONE, who returns the brotherly hug.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS853
SOMEONE rolls her eyes, then sprinkles SOMEONE with amnesia dust.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS854
In the talent show's packed audience, SOMEONE anxiously looks around.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS855
Seated beside her, SOMEONE contentedly bops her shoulders to the music.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS856
SOMEONE arrives and scans the crowd.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS857
Moving down the aisle, he sits beside SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS858
He gazes off with a puzzled frown.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS859
SOMEONE winks at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS860
The three companions face the stage.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS861
Young members of a band wave and take their bows.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS862
In a white shirt and black vest, SOMEONE comes out with his new guitar and gives a shy wave.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS864
The boy arrives at center stage and raises his strumming hand to the guitar strings.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS866
He pauses, facing the large packed house, and gives a modest smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS869
Swaying on his feet, he looks down at his instrument.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS870
The boy rhythmically bobs his knees and wags his head.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS871
As the audience listens appreciatively, the band members peek out from backstage.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS872
SOMEONE grins broadly.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS873
On stage, her son's playing grows bolder and more relaxed.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS874
The band members exchange nods, then join SOMEONE on stage. He glances up from his guitar, confidently facing the audience between phrases.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS875
As he notices the other musicians, the audience members leap to their feet and the bass player smiles.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS876
Dancing with SOMEONE, SOMEONE raises her hand high and SOMEONE beams.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS877
SOMEONE faces the crowd with a joyful smile.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS878
SOMEONE draws SOMEONE close and she blinks back proud tears.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS879
Elsewhere in the crowd, SOMEONE smiles up at the guitarist.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS880
Grinning, SOMEONE points rhythmically at the boy while SOMEONE bounces SOMEONE in her arms.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS881
SOMEONE bites his lip in blissful concentration. As the audience grins and pumps their fists,
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS882
he bounces smoothly, leaning back.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS883
He wags his head, swishing his moppy hair, and his little sister beams.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS884
SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE. Her boyfriend points at SOMEONE, smiling warmly. The boy takes a bow and SOMEONE gives a thumbs up.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS885
SOMEONE blows him a kiss.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS886
SOMEONE returns the gesture, then swaps friendly nods with his fellow musicians.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS887
SOMEONE grins up at him while SOMEONE lovingly watches SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS889
She shares an elated smile with him, then faces the stage.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS890
She stares, then rolls her head in a double take.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS891
SOMEONE gazes into her eyes.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS892
Smiling tearfully, she nods.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS893
They share a passionate kiss and hold each other tight.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS894
Swaying with SOMEONE in his arms, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE watching them.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS895
Beaming, she claps her hands.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS896
As SOMEONE grins on stage, SOMEONE draws SOMEONE and SOMEONE close, kisses the little girl's head, and points at SOMEONE.
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS897
The boy nods and SOMEONE mouths "Getting married. "
TOOTH_FAIRY_DVS898
He kisses SOMEONE.