SOMEONE peers out of the window at a sprawling western town.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS25
Black smoke billows as the train rolls to a stop at the end of the line.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS26
SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb down from the train.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS27
The train reverses away.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS30
SOMEONE and her companion walk down the busy main street.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS31
At the undertakers, Lying in an open coffin, SOMEONE's bearded father looks serene as if he's sleeping.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS32
a craggy gray bearded man holds a lantern above SOMEONE's father.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS34
SOMEONE looks around.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS35
A crowd watches three men get hanged. The man who spoke has a black bag placed over his head.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS37
SOMEONE watches, captivated man.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS38
A bag's placed over his head. A Native American.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS39
A bag's put over his head.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS40
The trap door opens. The men dangle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS41
SOMEONE is watching. SOMEONE walks off with the old sheriff.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS43
In an outhouse, SOMEONE stands facing the small wooden building.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS44
A coffin is slid onto a rail wagon. Written on the lid is CL County, Hold at station.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS46
At the undertakers, SOMEONE walk into the gloomy lamp lit room clutching a bedroll.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS47
A body lies on a small wagon covered in sacking.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS48
SOMEONE stares at a dark exposed hand.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS50
Wearing her long dark dress, SOMEONE walks along the main street.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS51
She passes a hardware store and heads for Colonel G. Stonehill's sales table.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS53
SOMEONE walks into an office where elderly white-haired SOMEONE sits at a desk writing.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS54
She sits.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS55
He smiles and raises his eyebrows.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS56
SOMEONE goes to the boarding house where a jolly round lady greets her with a big hug.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS57
In a bedroom, SOMEONE stares at a small collection of her father's things.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS59
She picks up a shiny revolver and cradles it in both hands.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS60
SOMEONE looks thoughtful.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS61
That night she lies wide awake in bed.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS62
Snoring beside her is Grandma SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS63
She turns over, taking the covers with her.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS64
SOMEONE tries to retrieve them with little success.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS65
Next day, SOMEONE walks up the stairs in the courthouse.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS66
SOMEONE stands watching and listening.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS67
A thin man with dark eyes and black hair.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS68
Black suited SOMEONE Cogburn sits in a wooden chair. In his 60s, he has a gnarled old face with a black patch over his right eye.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS69
His ratty gray hair is slicked over in a side parting
TRUE_GRIT_DVS70
and white stubble covers his chin.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS71
SOMEONE waits for SOMEONE at the bottom of the stairs.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS72
She smiles.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS73
He takes out tobacco.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS74
She rolls a cigarette.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS75
He takes out her father's revolver.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS76
He regards her through his one narrowed eye.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS77
He touches the brim of his hat, with a cigarette in his mouth. He turns and goes.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS79
That evening, SOMEONE walks along the street to the boarding house.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS80
She slows up and stares at a man sitting in the shadows on the porch.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS81
He rests his boots on the wooden rail.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS82
He wears jeans, a thick suede jacket, and a Stetson
TRUE_GRIT_DVS83
and has a bullet belt around his waist.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS84
He lights a pipe and the flame illuminates his beady eyes which are fixed on SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS86
She walks up to the front door.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS87
She goes inside.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS88
Another night in bed with Grandma SOMEONE who turns over and steals the bed clothes.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS89
SOMEONE lies in her long white nightgown shivering
TRUE_GRIT_DVS90
with her arms folded over her chest.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS92
SOMEONE lies in bed alone with a blanket over her side.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS93
She frowns restlessly and wakes.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS94
She sits up and her eyes widen.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS95
Sweat glows on her brow.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS96
The man from the porch sits by the window smoking his pipe.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS97
He has messy brown hair and a mustache.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS98
SOMEONE stares at him as he takes a puff.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS100
He puts his pipe on a side table.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS101
He stands and walks over.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS102
SOMEONE peers at the large star-shaped spurs on his brown boots.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS103
He hands her a photograph of a man in a dark suit.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS104
He smiles cockily and shows his badge.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS105
He stands sharply.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS106
SOMEONE reads a letter. Colonel Stonehill.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS108
SOMEONE smiles.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS110
In Stonehill's stables, a boy carries SOMEONE's saddle and shows her a fine young black horse.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS111
Smiling, she goes and strokes its nose.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS112
SOMEONE sits in the saddle
TRUE_GRIT_DVS113
and the boy leads the horse into a yard.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS114
The boy lets go of the reigns
TRUE_GRIT_DVS115
and the horse bucks his head and rears up.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS117
SOMEONE clings onto the reigns as the horse jumps about.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS118
In a storeroom.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS119
SOMEONE lies in a small bed.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS120
She shakes his shoulder.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS121
She rolls him a cigarette.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS122
He stares at her.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS123
Wearing dirty combinations, SOMEONE lies on the scruffy bed staring at SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS124
SOMEONE lets a smile slip.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS125
She drops the money on a table and leaves.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS126
At the boarding house, she puts on her father's coat and rolls up the sleeves.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS127
She saddles up and rides off on Little Blackie.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS128
SOMEONE goes to SOMEONE’s bed.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS129
She finds the Chinese grocery store owner lying in bed.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS131
He holds a pipe and a letter, which she reads.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS132
SOMEONE rides along a track to a wide river with a wooden ferry.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS133
The ferryman walks up and SOMEONE looks at two figures on the opposite bank.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS134
He leads Little Blackie away.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS135
She takes an apple from her bag and hurls it at the man's head.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS136
Stunned, he lets go of the reigns.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS137
SOMEONE rides back to the river.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS141
SOMEONE rides Little Blackie into the muddy river and they swim across, their heads just above the fast flowing water.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS142
On the other side, SOMEONE is with SOMEONE,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS143
both astride their horses.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS144
They causally watch as SOMEONE approaches.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS146
SOMEONE and Little Blackie struggle on determinedly.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS147
SOMEONE puts a cigarette in his mouth and lights it.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS148
As they approach the riverbank, SOMEONE remounts Little Blackie.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS149
Little Blackie snorts and wallops up the steep muddy bank,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS150
then trots onto the parched matted grass in front of SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS151
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare at SOMEONE impassively.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS152
She returns their gaze, breathing heavily from her exertion.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS153
Her long neat pigtails hang down over the front of her dark sodden brown coat.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS154
On her head, she wears her father's wide-brimmed hat which she packed with paper to make it fit.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS157
SOMEONE gets down from his horse and marches over to SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS160
He grabs her coat, pulls her to the ground.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS162
He slaps her behind. He gets a stick.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS163
SOMEONE blows out cigarette smoke as he observes, He whips her.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS166
SOMEONE pulls out his pistol, cocks it.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS167
He aims at SOMEONE and stares at him fiercely.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS168
SOMEONE stands and throws the stick away.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS169
He walks towards SOMEONE who uncocks his weapon and holsters it.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS170
In the pitch black night, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit by a campfire.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS171
SOMEONE stares at the flames
TRUE_GRIT_DVS172
and SOMEONE puffs on his pipe.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS173
SOMEONE wanders over, stares at SOMEONE for a moment,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS174
then drops a pile of logs on the fire.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS175
SOMEONE unreels some rope.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS179
SOMEONE lies down staring at SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS182
SOMEONE sips booze from a bottle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS183
SOMEONE frowns indignantly.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS184
SOMEONE smiles at them both.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS186
SOMEONE looks bewildered.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS187
SOMEONE clasps both hands around his booze bottle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS189
SOMEONE lies under a blanket with her head against her saddle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS190
She wakes and sits up.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS191
A breeze ruffles loose strands of her hair.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS192
She walks over to SOMEONE who's by some bare trees tying leather bags to his horse’s saddle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS193
SOMEONE points at SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS194
SOMEONE watches, frowning as SOMEONE rides off across the plains.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS197
SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride side by side along by some rocks.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS198
They head towards a wooden shack.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS199
Two Native American kids sit on the porch tormenting a tied up donkey,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS200
poking it with a broom and a stick.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS201
SOMEONE dismounts and hands his reigns to SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS202
He stomps over to the kids, holding a big knife.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS203
He cuts the donkey's rope and sets it
TRUE_GRIT_DVS205
He grabs the kid with the broom, throws him to the ground,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS206
and whacks him with the broom.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS207
SOMEONE boots the kid with the stick off the porch and goes into the shack.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS208
A bell hands from the porch roof.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS209
It has the letter B in relief on it.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS210
The two kids sit staring at SOMEONE through narrowed eyes.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS212
SOMEONE comes out of the shack and shoves one of the kids to the ground.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS213
He flips a square of gold to SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS214
Surrounded by bare twisted trees, they stop.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS215
Dangling from one of the upper most branches of a tree is a hanged man. A large bird pecks at the corpse’s flesh.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS217
SOMEONE shoots his pistol in the air and the bird flies off.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS218
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk over and stand beneath the hanged man.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS219
They look up.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS220
High up in the tree, SOMEONE looks down indignantly.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS221
SOMEONE smokes a cigarette.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS222
SOMEONE cuts through the rope with a knife.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS223
The corpse drops.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS225
SOMEONE pushes the body onto its back with his boot.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS226
He stares at the dark, deathly face framed by matted hair.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS228
They both look round.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS229
A man slowly approaches on horseback.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS230
SOMEONE opens his coat revealing his pistol holstered at his side.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS231
He rests his hand on it and watches the man approach.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS233
SOMEONE looks down from high above.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS234
The man stops with the body on the ground between him and SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS235
SOMEONE climbs down from the tree.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS236
The man rides away with the body.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS237
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stay put, sitting on their horses by some trees.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS239
Snowflakes flutter around them.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS240
The snow falls heavier, swirling through the air. As they continue to sit and wait,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS241
staring at dense tangled bushes
TRUE_GRIT_DVS242
and gnarled tree branches,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS243
a rider and two horses slowly approaches.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS244
SOMEONE cocks his head, curiously.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS246
The rider appears to be a black bear and the second horse has a dead body draped over it.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS247
The rider stops facing SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS248
It is in fact a grizzled old man wearing a bear skin with the head still attached.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS249
The man has a thick scraggy gray beard.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS250
SOMEONE stares at him.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS251
SOMEONE peers at the corpse.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS252
That night, SOMEONE and SOMEONE look down at a cabin lodged into a muddy hillside.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS253
Smoke wafts from a brick chimney.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS254
Holding SOMEONE's coat, SOMEONE carefully walks onto the roof
TRUE_GRIT_DVS255
and over to the chimney.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS256
Holding his rifle, SOMEONE makes his way to the front of the cabin.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS257
All is dark apart from a slit of yellow light at a window.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS258
The door opens.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS259
They shut the door.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS260
SOMEONE raises his hand to SOMEONE who puts SOMEONE's coat over the chimney top, stifling the smoke.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS261
SOMEONE squats down by some tree branches and aims at the dark cabin with his rifle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS262
Smoke seeps under the front door. SOMEONE carefully treads across the rooftop.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS263
The men start shooting from the cabin and SOMEONE returns fire.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS264
Inside, SOMEONE stares at the two scruffy, dirty men, now handcuffed.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS265
The younger, Moon, has lank straggly hair and his face is covered in sweat. He holds a bloody cloth over a wound on his leg.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS266
SOMEONE has a round jowly face
TRUE_GRIT_DVS267
set in a frown. SOMEONE stirs a pan of stew.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS269
SOMEONE sits with a bowl of stew and smiles at SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS270
She looks at Moon.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS271
SOMEONE plunges a knife into Moon's chest. SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE in the face.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS273
SOMEONE lies dead.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS274
Blood speckles cover SOMEONE's cheek.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS275
He looks down at Moon with a knife sticking out of his chest.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS276
SOMEONE watches Moon lying on the floor shaking and grimaces.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS280
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch the cabin from high up on the hill above it.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS281
SOMEONE readies his rifle and pistol.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS283
SOMEONE eyes him nervously.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS284
He gets comfy.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS285
SOMEONE picks up his rifle and looks down into the gloom.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS286
A lone rider approaches the cabin.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS287
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch the rider head along a track towards the cabin then stop.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS288
Smoke billows from the cabin’s chimney.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS289
The rider dismounts and walks his horse toward the cabin.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS290
As SOMEONE enters the cabin, several more riders approach.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS291
SOMEONE cocks his rifle and takes aim. SOMEONE looks nervously between the cabin and the approaching posse.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS292
SOMEONE and SOMEONE keep watching from the hill.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS293
SOMEONE walks out of the cabin and steps up to the four riders who sit side by side on their horses facing him.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS294
Two of the riders move closer to SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS297
One of them lassoes him with a rope, pulls him over, He drags him along the ground.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS298
The other man gets off his horse and walks toward the cabin. SOMEONE shoots him.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS299
The man flops to the ground in the doorway.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS300
The three men still on horseback shoot up towards the hill.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS301
SOMEONE methodically shoots back with his rifle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS302
SOMEONE gets dragged around in the dirt.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS303
A horse and rider collapses.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS305
The rider springs up and jumps on the back of one of the other horses as it gallops away.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS306
SOMEONE takes aim.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS307
SOMEONE shoots and the man in the saddle falls.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS308
The guy who jumped on the back takes the saddle and escapes.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS309
SOMEONE holds his rifle upright.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS310
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk past the dead man to SOMEONE, who's mouth is covered in blood.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS311
SOMEONE looks him over.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS312
He pulls SOMEONE's tongue.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS314
Snowflakes gently drift through the darkness.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS315
The dead men are propped up outside the cabin.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS316
Inside, SOMEONE sits with a bandage over his shoulder.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS317
SOMEONE lies on a bunk.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS318
SOMEONE goes in.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS319
SOMEONE drinks whiskey from a bottle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS320
They slowly ride across the SOMEONE plains.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS321
He throws his bottle in the air.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS322
He misses and the bottle lands on the grass.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS323
On the fourth shot, the bottle breaks.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS324
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE who dismounts and tumbles to the ground.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS325
He keeps hold of his horse's reigns and drunkenly struggles to his feet.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS326
SOMEONE twirls his gun in his hand and goes to his saddle bag.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS327
He digs around and some bits of yellow cornbread fall out.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS328
He takes a piece and stands with his legs apart.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS329
He throws the cornbread in the air
TRUE_GRIT_DVS330
and shoots it to bits.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS332
SOMEONE just stares at SOMEONE who goes to get more cornbread from his saddle bag.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS333
He throws two pieces in the air.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS334
And before he can shoot, SOMEONE takes a shot.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS335
SOMEONE misses and stares at his gun frowning.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS336
SOMEONE goes to his saddle bag.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS337
SOMEONE hurls yet another piece.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS338
Both he and SOMEONE shoot
TRUE_GRIT_DVS339
and the cornbread explodes.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS341
SOMEONE holsters his gun and SOMEONE hurls another piece.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS342
He shoots wildly.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS343
Under a pale sky SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE ride across a vast prairie of short patchy grass.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS344
Behind them, in the distance, is a mountain range.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS346
Fluffy white clouds hang in a blue sky above the trio as their horses plod on across a largely featureless landscape.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS348
They ride through longer grass beside a river. Another empty whiskey bottle hits the water.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS350
The three riders meander through tangled pale bare trees.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS351
They cross a river.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS352
Under a canopy of swollen dark gray clouds, they head across a plain of straw-like grass.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS353
As they head through a pine forest, SOMEONE sticks another empty bottle over the end of a thin stubby branch.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS354
SOMEONE stands framed by the square entrance to a dark mine.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS355
He shoots into the darkness.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS356
SOMEONE looks in.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS357
The entrance is surrounded by craggy stone cliffs.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS358
A rainy night.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS359
By a campfire, SOMEONE mashes some cornbread and water and holds it out to SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS360
SOMEONE brings wood.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS361
SOMEONE stands.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS362
SOMEONE sits staring at him.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS363
SOMEONE looks shocked.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS364
SOMEONE stares intensely at SOMEONE who sits beneath a hide canopy strung up between two trees.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS365
She goes to see SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS366
He looks earnest.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS367
He mounts his horse.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS368
He looks down at her from his horse.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS369
He holds out his gloved hand.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS370
SOMEONE's brow is pinched
TRUE_GRIT_DVS371
and tears glisten in her eyes.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS372
She takes SOMEONE's hand and they hold each other's gaze for a moment.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS373
He leans down to her.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS374
He touches his hat, turns his horse, and rides off through the trees.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS375
SOMEONE watches him go.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS377
She goes back to the camp.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS378
The fire glows gold on her young face.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS379
She looks down at SOMEONE sleeping on animal hides.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS380
She picks up a reel of rope lying beside him
TRUE_GRIT_DVS381
And lays it on the ground surrounding her bedding.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS382
Later, SOMEONE sleeps soundly wrapped in a blanket.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS384
SOMEONE slumbers, a disheveled heap.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS385
SOMEONE watches him for a moment.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS387
She pulls back her blanket and gets up. She picks up a wooden bucket by its rope handle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS388
SOMEONE carries the wooden bucket through the wintry brush, her oversized coat belted up tightly around her waist.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS389
She passes between slender leafless trees crossing the snow dappled ground to the edge of a shallow, fast moving river.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS390
She takes a few uninhibited steps into the water and dips the bucket.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS391
She looks up to see three or four horses drinking from the water on the opposite side.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS392
A figure steps out from behind a thicket with his back to her.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS393
SOMEONE stares at him as he tends to the horses.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS394
The man turns to look at her.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS395
He has a black SOMEONE on his left cheek.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS396
It's SOMEONE. They lock eyes.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS397
They lock eyes.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS398
SOMEONE drops the bucket and it floats away on the water.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS399
SOMEONE takes a rifle from over his shoulder and advances a few steps with the gun leveled at her.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS402
SOMEONE fumbles in her coat pocket.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS403
SOMEONE shakes his head.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS404
Having slung the rifle back over his shoulder, SOMEONE watches SOMEONE wrest her pistol from the potato sack.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS405
SOMEONE narrows his eyes incredulously. He looks away, then raises his eyebrows.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS408
She shoots him as he starts towards her and the recoil puts her on her backside in the water.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS409
SOMEONE doubles in pain.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS410
SOMEONE picks herself up again.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS411
An indignant SOMEONE stalks toward her. She pulls the trigger but the gun doesn't fire. SOMEONE snatches it and strikes her.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS412
SOMEONE marches her across the river.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS414
Two men open fire on SOMEONE from the other side of the river and he takes cover behind a tree.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS416
SOMEONE trade shots with the men who then disappear into the woods
TRUE_GRIT_DVS417
with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS418
An ugly rat faced man has SOMEONE by the wrist.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS419
The man, Lucky Ned, throws her to the ground. He draws a revolver and stamps a boot against her cheek.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS420
He sneers and lifts his gaze.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS421
He keeps his gun pointed at SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS423
Out of sight in the trees, he drags her to her feet and they continue.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS424
A simpleton springs out. The man waggles his elbows like a chicken.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS425
Reconvened, they climb a steep track.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS426
They approach a camp.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS427
SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit by the fire.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS428
SOMEONE smirks.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS429
A distant SOMEONE fires his pistol at the sky.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS430
SOMEONE responds in kind then watches through a telescope as SOMEONE heads off on his horse with Little Blackie close behind.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS431
SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS432
and twirling the slender telescope between his fingers,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS433
he sits down opposite her by the campfire.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS435
The men ride off on horseback leaving SOMEONE alone with SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS437
Clutching his rifle like a walking stick and holding a gloved hand to his injured chest,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS438
SOMEONE sits down on a box by the flickering campfire.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS440
He hangs his head and stares at the ground. SOMEONE looks somewhat disgusted by his self-pity.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS441
SOMEONE's eyes are closed.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS443
SOMEONE wears a brooding expression.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS444
SOMEONE stares at him expectantly.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS445
He looks at her.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS446
SOMEONE swallows. Smoke rises from the fire between them as SOMEONE rises.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS447
He pounces, pinning her to the ground and putting a knife to her throat.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS448
Clobbered with a rifle butt, SOMEONE hits the ground. SOMEONE looks up to see SOMEONE. SOMEONE's unconscious.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS449
They look down at the plain.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS450
On the dusty scrub land below, SOMEONE rides back towards SOMEONE and his three gang members,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS451
one of whom is the blithering simpleton.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS452
They bring their horses to a halt as SOMEONE draws near. Gaunt, whiskered SOMEONE peers out at SOMEONE from beneath a broad-rimmed hat.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS453
SOMEONE flashes a yellow grin.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS454
SOMEONE draws a rifle and SOMEONE two pistols, gripping the reigns between his teeth
TRUE_GRIT_DVS455
as he gallops toward his four foes.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS457
Charging, SOMEONE's men fan out. SOMEONE shoots the simpleton. SOMEONE aims his rifle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS460
SOMEONE shoots and one of SOMEONE's men slumps down the side of his saddle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS461
Another puts a bullet through SOMEONE's shoulder.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS462
SOMEONE blasts him through the chest.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS463
The man tumbles from his horse, cracking his head against a rock in a shower of blood.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS464
SOMEONE and SOMEONE each fire as they cross paths.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS465
SOMEONE buckles and SOMEONE's horse goes down.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS466
SOMEONE stands sharply and gasps.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS467
A dust cloud rises from the ground where SOMEONE's horse has fallen.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS468
His leg is trapped beneath it
TRUE_GRIT_DVS469
and he struggles in vain to free himself.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS470
SOMEONE approaches, sitting slumped on his horse.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS471
SOMEONE squints down the barrel of his rifle as he takes aim.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS472
SOMEONE pants.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS473
SOMEONE limply points and cocks his pistol.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS474
SOMEONE takes a breath.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS475
SOMEONE is but a tiny speck far below on the plain.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS477
Still astride his horse, SOMEONE doesn't move a muscle.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS478
SOMEONE looks up from his gun and frowns.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS479
SOMEONE topples over.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS481
SOMEONE bashes SOMEONE on the head with a boulder, knocking him unconscious.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS482
SOMEONE quickly grabs his rifle but SOMEONE gets hold of the barrel.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS483
SOMEONE rests it free of his grasp
TRUE_GRIT_DVS484
and traps him in her sights.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS485
She makes sure the gun is cocked.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS486
Scowling, he does as he's told.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS488
She blasts him off the cliff edge. Thrown off balance by the recoil, SOMEONE trips over a log and tumbles backwards through a crevice into a subterranean cave.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS489
Bouncing down a steep rocky slope, she lands on her back and snags her foot on a tree root. Light pours in through the dust shrouded mouth of the cave.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS490
SOMEONE grimaces in pain and sits up slightly.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS491
She tries to free her foot but cannot.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS492
Breathless, she stares up through the narrow cave mouth.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS493
She collapses back despairingly.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS494
then sits up again.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS496
She glances about the cave and frowns as her eyes alight on a dead body lying just a few feet away.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS497
She slowly looks the dead man over
TRUE_GRIT_DVS498
and spots a knife ina belt around his waist.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS499
SOMEONE reaches out and grasps one of the man’s boots,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS500
dragging him closer with surprising ease.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS501
As she does so, his leg comes apart at the knee.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS502
She instead pulls his thigh and then his shirt
TRUE_GRIT_DVS503
which rips as she does so.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS505
SOMEONE stares in horror.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS506
In the hollow where the corpse’s viscera should be is a coiled and glistening rattlesnake.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS507
It starts to move.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS508
SOMEONE pulls away but the corpse slides closer. She panics.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS509
She turns to look at the corpse, her head now level with its fleshless skull.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS511
The snake slithers closer.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS512
She sits up and fumbles with the tree root.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS514
SOMEONE throws a rope into the cave and starts down the slope.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS515
A snake glides onto SOMEONE's shoulder and she flings it aside. As SOMEONE descends clutching the rope,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS516
another snake sinks its teeth into her left hand.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS518
SOMEONE shoots his pistol at the ground.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS519
He reaches SOMEONE who grimaces in pain.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS521
She nods at her hand which he grasps.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS523
There are two puncture marks in her flesh.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS524
SOMEONE closes her eyes and SOMEONE scores an X between the fang marks with his large hunting knife.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS525
He sucks poison from the wound and spits it out.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS526
He cuts her foot free of the tree root and returns the knife to his back pocket.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS528
Wrapping the rope around them both, he then takes SOMEONE in his arms.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS529
SOMEONE walks Little Blackie away from the cave, pulling SOMEONE and SOMEONE up on the rope.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS531
SOMEONE gallops off with SOMEONE through trees.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS532
They continues along the plain passing the slain bodies of SOMEONE's gang.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS533
SOMEONE looks down at the simpleton lying sprawled on the dry earth.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS534
SOMEONE's horse lies dead beside SOMEONE, Who’s own horse stands over him.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS537
Silhouetted against the pale sky, SOMEONE gallops on across the dusty plain.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS538
SOMEONE glances at the setting sun, her face cast in its golden glow.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS539
Sets in and soon gives way to night.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS540
But Little Blackie keeps going.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS541
SOMEONE and SOMEONE ride on through trees and tall grass.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS542
The sky is black.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS543
The horse begins to tire.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS544
SOMEONE stabs Little Blackie.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS546
Little Blackie forages onward, kicking up dust in his wake.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS547
Little Blackie's breath clouds in front of him. His neck glistening with sweat in the moonlight.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS548
SOMEONE sways back and forth along with the horses labored gait.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS549
She sees a silhouetted horseman up ahead.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS550
Little Blackie hobbles to a standstill.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS551
Little Blackie sinks to his knees and topples over, spilling SOMEONE and SOMEONE from the saddle. Little Blackie's head hits the ground with a thud.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS552
SOMEONE drags SOMEONE away from him.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS557
SOMEONE looks at the exhausted horse and put his hand on his pistol.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS558
SOMEONE bends down to scoop SOMEONE up in his arms.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS560
She resists, pushing him away bitterly, and beating at his chest with balled fists.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS562
SOMEONE picks her up and her aggression subsides.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS563
SOMEONE gazes back tearfully at Little Blackie
TRUE_GRIT_DVS564
as SOMEONE carries her away across the plain.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS565
SOMEONE lulls her head back and SOMEONE picks up his pace, trotting briskly on as fast as his legs.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS566
SOMEONE carry him.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS567
SOMEONE stares ahead with a look of determination, his grizzled countenance picked out by the pale moonlight.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS568
SOMEONE has a pained and weary face, her hair damp with sweat and her brow deeply furrowed.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS572
SOMEONE staggers to a halt and drops to his knees.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS575
He takes out his pistol and points it in the air.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS576
Cradling SOMEONE in his arms, SOMEONE hangs his head.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS577
A light comes on in a house a short distance away.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS578
A figure dressed in white long-johns steps out onto the front porch with a lantern.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS579
SOMEONE looks down at SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS580
The image of the figure on the porch fades to black.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS581
SOMEONE stares out of a train window.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS582
Now a grown woman with slim features and a severe expression, she wears her dark hair up beneath a flat-brimmed hat.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS584
The train stops and she steps down onto a railway platform,
TRUE_GRIT_DVS587
her left arm now ends at the elbow.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS588
It reads. "For a wild-west show".
TRUE_GRIT_DVS589
She approaches two seated men on the show site.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS590
SOMEONE stands.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS591
SOMEONE nods.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS592
She glares at seated Mr. SOMEONE.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS593
She walks away.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS594
SOMEONE's coffin is loaded onto a train. Ashen faced, SOMEONE stands at his grave.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS595
His headstone reads Ruben Cogburn.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS597
Snow drifts down on the plot where a small number of gravestones are clustered.
TRUE_GRIT_DVS598
SOMEONE cuts a lonely figure as she walks away.