They arrive at school.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS21
As SOMEONE's son slings his backpack over his shoulder, a strap breaks.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS22
His books fall out.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS23
He takes his daughter's hand.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS24
His son grabs his lunch and hurries off.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS25
A blonde woman holds out a casserole dish.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS26
SOMEONE accepts it.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS27
Still holding onto the dish, she draws him closer.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS28
She gives a sultry look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS29
Smiling politely, he heads away.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS30
As he returns to his car, a group of chatting mothers gazes after him. Later, he strolls a neighborhood with a rugged-	faced man.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS31
They glance at a diner.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS32
SOMEONE spots a restaurant ahead and his face falls.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS33
He turns away.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS34
He drapes an arm around SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS35
SOMEONE blinks his contemplative eyes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS36
The two men bow to each other.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS37
They hug.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS38
They part ways.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS39
SOMEONE bows to him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS40
His brother spreads his arms.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS41
Now, in an office.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS42
The silver-haired editor lifts his brow.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS43
SOMEONE turns away.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS44
He slings his bag onto his shoulder.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS45
Later in a principal's office.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS46
his son sits beside him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS47
He strides to an open awning window which jiggles in the wind. Steadying it, he takes out a tool on his keychain.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS48
Entering the office, the principal furrows his brow as he sees SOMEONE fiddling with his window.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS49
He beckons SOMEONE into the hall and leads him past artwork posted above the lockers.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS50
A drawing shows a man with his head flying off his sliced neck.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS51
He holds SOMEONE's gaze. With concerned looks, both men shift their eyes back to SOMEONE's drawing, where the bald 	decapitated man's tongue juts from his mouth in agony, as his head flies away from his body.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS52
Blood spurts from his sliced neck and drips from slashes along his jawline.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS53
The principal shoots the father a horrified glance, then heads off.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS54
Turning thoughtfully to his son, SOMEONE sees him leaning against the bank of lockers with his arms crossed. The 	teen stares back at him broodingly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS55
As his father approaches, SOMEONE hoists his backpack onto his shoulder.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS56
SOMEONE strides out of the school with his son right behind him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS57
At home, SOMEONE opens the fridge to reveal stacks of plastic containers with notes on them.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS58
His daughter watches as he fits the new casserole dish inside.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS59
Sitting at a table in a breakfast nook, he smiles. He watches his daughter spread peanut butter and jelly on slices of 	bread in the adjoining kitchen.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS60
She combines the slices to make two sandwiches, then grabs storage bags.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS61
She bags the sandwiches.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS62
Holding a marker, SOMEONE draws a check SOMEONE in the air.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS63
She smiles as she resumes her work.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS64
SOMEONE watches her with an amused loving stare.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS65
On the storage bag's white label, SOMEONE writes PB and a backwards J.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS66
Now, SOMEONE pushes open SOMEONE's bedroom door and finds his son asleep on top of the covers.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS67
The teen's hand rests on a leather-bound book resembling a journal.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS68
Entering the room, SOMEONE gently lifts his son's hand and takes the book.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS69
He sits on the edge of the bed and shoots SOMEONE a perplexed glance.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS70
Furrowing his brow, he opens the book to a pair of skillfully drawn sketches.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS71
One shows a bald burly man with a menacing look
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS72
and the other depicts a hollow-cheeked face
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS73
with a grim expression.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS74
Dark-smudged pencil work creates gloomy shading around both figures.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS76
Nodding, SOMEONE turns the page. In the next sketch, a boy sits with his elbows on a table, his face buried in his hands.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS77
At the center of the table, tiny people stand around a gaping chasm.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS78
The sketch on the opposite page shows a woman cradling a baby while a figure watches from a doorway.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS79
Flipping to the next two pages,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS80
SOMEONE finds a drawing filling up both sides.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS81
In it, an anguished three-eyed face lets out a scream, its red uvula visible through its gaping mouth. SOMEONE sets 	the sketchbook aside and caresses his son's shaggy brown bangs.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS82
Later in a bathroom, he dabs his mouth with a towel and wipes his hands, then lifts his eyes to a mirror above the 	sink.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS83
He stares at his weary defeated reflection.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS84
He shifts his gaze to a cluster of pill bottles filling a shelf.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS85
The shelf below contains jewelry, knick-knacks, and a framed photo of him and SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS86
SOMEONE lowers his heartbroken eyes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS87
SOMEONE stands in the doorway.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS88
Picking her up, SOMEONE carries her into her bedroom.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS89
Reaching a bed piled high with stuffed animals, he sits on its edge and sets SOMEONE on his lap.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS90
He gazes out a window at a party in the yard next door.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS91
She watches them with a doleful look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS92
Turning from the window, SOMEONE holds her tighter.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS93
She rests her head against his shoulder and closes her eyes. As he returns his attention to the young partygoers 	next door, a blonde woman holding a beer spots him and gives a friendly wave.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS94
He smiles wistfully.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS95
Daytime. In a car, SOMEONE flips through a binder of property listings as he rides besides a dimple-chinned man in 	glasses.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS96
In the back seat, SOMEONE plays with a digital camera.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS97
SOMEONE nods.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS98
SOMEONE eyes the real estate agent thoughtfully, then shrugs his lips in an accepting look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS99
Now, SOMEONE lifts the camera as they cruise past a Tudor-style house.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS100
SOMEONE flips to another listing in the binder. They drive past a plain-gray, two-story home with red trim.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS101
They pass a cozy-looking white house with an ivy-covered chimney.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS102
Flipping through the binder, SOMEONE furrows his brow. They pull up in front of a ranch-style house with a yard 	covered in native-California plants.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS103
SOMEONE holds out a listing.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS104
They drive up a rustic tree-lined road.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS105
Gazing out her window, SOMEONE smiles. Up ahead, the house lies shrouded behind a cluster of mature trees. A slack-	jawed SOMEONE eyes the large property.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS106
The car parks alongside an old wooden fence. We glimpse the sun through a canopy of tree branches,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS107
then find SOMEONE riding on her father's shoulders, aiming her camera at the quaint two-story Colonial house.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS108
SOMEONE heads inside.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS109
He looks around the spacious, mostly empty rooms.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS110
He follows SOMEONE upstairs.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS111
From a window, she overlooks the countryside.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS112
Startled by the sound, SOMEONE and SOMEONE look around.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS113
Outside, a male lion walks up to a chain-link fence.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS114
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the real estate agent watch him from the other side.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS115
SOMEONE looks up at her dad.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS117
He looks at his daughter, who lowers her saddened gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS118
They leave the enclosure.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS119
He looks back, but finds no sign of his daughter.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS120
The real estate agent follows him up a set of stairs set into a hillside.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS121
They find SOMEONE feeding crackers to peacocks.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS122
The agent pats him on the shoulder, then walks off.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS123
SOMEONE takes a seat on a rock and watches his daughter sprinkle her crackers on the ground.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS124
As he glances aside and smiles, a ray of sunlight haloes his hair and shoulders.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS125
SOMEONE meets her father's gaze and smiles.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS126
Welling with emotion, SOMEONE beams.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS127
He chuckles to himself, then licks his wide lips.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS128
Glancing back at the lion enclosure, he locks eyes with the big cat. Sunlight glares behind SOMEONE's joyful face. The 	lion's soulful eyes watch him through the chain links. Now, at SOMEONE's Restaurant.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS129
A waitress brings their food.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS131
He storms off, leaving his father and sister at the dinner table.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS132
They tap forks. Now they pack.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS133
He holds up a sweatshirt.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS134
SOMEONE shifts her jaw and gives a nod.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS135
SOMEONE puts it in a donations box.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS136
He holds out a monkey puppet.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS137
Now the family's SUV drives through the neighborhood, followed by a Mayflower Moving truck.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS138
SOMEONE eyes his rear view mirror, then glances back at SOMEONE, who wears earbuds.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS139
The concerned father returns his attention to the road ahead and notices Little Dom's.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS140
Patrons eat at sidewalk tables outside the corner cafe.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS141
As he drives by, SOMEONE stares at a bank of windows.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS142
We glimpse SOMEONE sitting alone at a booth inside. Her brown eyes find us and she gives a pretty smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS143
The SUV now leads the moving truck onto the zoo property. In the back seat, SOMEONE sighs and shifts his unhappy 	gaze. Indoors, a blonde teenage girl attaches light-up letters to a metal frame, which she displays in a window.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS144
SOMEONE halts their vehicle.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS145
The sign reads, Welcome, Brave New Owners.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS146
SOMEONE waves to the blonde girl, who smiles and waves back.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS147
From the back seat, SOMEONE waves as well.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS148
SOMEONE stares curiously at the welcoming stranger inside the restaurant. She moves along the dingy windows, continuing to wave as she watches them drive on.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS149
SOMEONE keeps his eyes on her until a tree finally blocks his view.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS150
Now in a downpour, a burly bearded man in a raincoat pushes a wheelbarrow full of mulch.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS151
A sultry woman stands in an old barn.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS152
She watches the Mees move in.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS153
She trades a look with her bearded colleague. SOMEONE leads the kids to a door.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS154
He opens it and their beagle darts in past the cluttered counters.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS155
The boy sulks off.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS156
Now on a dry day, the Mees meet the zoo staff outside.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS157
The monkey waves to SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS158
He glances at SOMEONE. SOMEONE shifts her skeptical gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS159
He rubs SOMEONE's shoulder, causing him to turn away in embarrassment.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS160
Sitting on SOMEONE's shoulder, Crystal slaps a hand over her head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS161
He marches off, but the staff heads in the opposite direction.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS162
An entry gate sign reads, Rosemoor Wildlife Park.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS163
SOMEONE walks with SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS164
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS165
We glimpse a binturong crossing a branch, a fox lying in tall grass, one parrot grooming another, a camel licking its 	mouth, and a grizzly bear.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS166
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE an embarrassed look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS167
The frizzy-haired man heads off.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS168
SOMEONE shyly averts his gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS169
He moves off.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS170
SOMEONE hurries after him. SOMEONE leads the group down a trail lined with tall bushes. As they reach the low wall of a tiger 	enclosure, SOMEONE halts upon seeing the big cats and holds them in his attentive gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS171
One of the tigers steps past two others lounging in the grass.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS172
SOMEONE watches admiringly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS173
She leans on the wall.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS174
A tiger perks up.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS175
SOMEONE smiles a bit.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS176
SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS177
SOMEONE studies the old tiger. Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk ahead of the kids.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS178
He takes notes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS179
SOMEONE slows her pace and stuffs her hands in her pockets.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS180
SOMEONE frowns pensively.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS181
He lowers his thoughtful gaze and purses his lips.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS182
SOMEONE waits for his reply.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS183
He lifts his eyes and earnestly meets her gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS184
The zookeeper's jaw goes slack.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS185
SOMEONE smiles, then continues up the trail. He looks back with a grin.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS186
SOMEONE stares after him with a pinched brow, then allows a faint smile as she jogs forward to catch up with him on a 	hill.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS187
At night, SOMEONE studies invoices.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS188
Wearing reading glasses, he sits alone, at the end of the dining room table, in front of a laptop, and surrounded by 	bills. He touches his brow as he continues to review the expenses.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS189
His attention drifts to a window.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS190
He goes out onto the porch,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS191
ambles to the railing with his hands stuffed in his pockets, and listens.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS192
He watches the wispy branches of a tree sway in the gentle breeze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS193
He looks to his left.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS195
He looks to the right, then back at the tree.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS196
Soft moonlight shines on his curious face.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS197
He steps down from the porch.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS198
Meanwhile, SOMEONE lies in bed staring at a framed photo of himself with his mother.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS199
He presses the picture to his chest, and wraps his arms around it, with tears in his eyes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS200
Now, SOMEONE enters the dim restaurant.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS201
He finds the staff in a dining room, adorned with a framed photo of SOMEONE Warhol, as well as memorabilia of 	MacCready's daredevil past,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS202
including a photo of him giving a lion a ride in a vintage race car.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS203
Noticing SOMEONE, SOMEONE opens his arms.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS204
He throws darts at a man's photo attached to a dartboard.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS205
He pulls out a chair for SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS206
SOMEONE brings him a beer. SOMEONE and SOMEONE play chess at the bar.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS207
The next day, SOMEONE marches up a hill wearing a black skull cap, a tool belt, and brown work boots. He pauses to 	scan his surroundings, then continues on his way. As SOMEONE works on a porcupine enclosure, Crystal hands him a 	tool. SOMEONE interrupts to show him a ledger. SOMEONE enters the enclosure with an armful of posts.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS208
SOMEONE notices.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS209
An approaching porcupine startles the rookie and he backs away, fumbling a few posts.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS210
It flares its quills. SOMEONE drops his posts, hurdles the fence, and lands in a thicket of nettles.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS211
SOMEONE hurries over to help him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS212
SOMEONE hops up in pain.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS213
He yanks a nettle from SOMEONE's back. Now in a zebra enclosure.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS214
SOMEONE works on an overhang.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS215
An ostrich pesters him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS216
In a barn loft, SOMEONE sketches in his pad. From a ladder, SOMEONE climbs into view.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS217
She greets SOMEONE with a sunny smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS218
He lowers his shy gaze as she approaches with a basket draped with a napkin.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS219
SOMEONE kneels beside him and sets a sandwich on his other side.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS220
SOMEONE glances at her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS221
Dried blood rims one of his nostrils.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS222
In black ink, he sketches a shriveled ghoulish face with stringy hair and black eye sockets.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS223
SOMEONE moves in close beside him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS224
He timidly edges away a few inches.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS225
Her cheery smile fades as she studies the picture.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS226
SOMEONE bites his lip and shyly glances away. SOMEONE's smile briefly returns.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS228
The boy presses his lips together.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS229
Amused, SOMEONE's rosy lips turn up at the corners.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS230
SOMEONE steals a curious glance. SOMEONE grins to herself.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS231
She beams,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS232
rattling her fist.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS233
As she climbs down, he cranes his neck to peer after her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS234
In an office.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS235
With a smarmy smile, SOMEONE wags a finger.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS236
She drops a stack of invoices in front of him and saunters off in her puppy-appliqued sweatshirt.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS237
SOMEONE studies the bills.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS238
As he writes one check after another, we glimpse an ocelot living in the zoo, then two curious ostriches.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS239
SOMEONE doffs his reading glasses and rests his head in his hands.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS240
Now outside, SOMEONE draws a sneering creature with no eyes or nose. He checks his watch.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS242
He looks around, then resumes drawing.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS243
SOMEONE steps into view with her basket.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS244
SOMEONE allows a brief smile as she cheerfully trots over and holds out a sandwich.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS245
Accepting, he eyes its tidy paper wrapping and smiles up at her. SOMEONE beams and prances away.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS246
SOMEONE removes the seal decorated with Magic Marker then unwraps the sandwich.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS247
Tucked inside the brown paper, he finds a cheerful drawing of a smiling sun wearing shades.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS248
Big loopy letters spell, Hey SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS249
SOMEONE smiles.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS250
In the office.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS251
Nighttime. In the farmhouse, SOMEONE and SOMEONE husk corn.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS252
The kids stare up dolefully.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS253
Later, SOMEONE's car returns to the house. As he gets out with a grocery bag, SOMEONE passes by.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS254
She rummages through supplies.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS255
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE a bucket.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS256
SOMEONE steps closer, a scolding smile on his face.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS257
Smirking, SOMEONE swivels away and walks toward an old pickup parked nearby.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS258
SOMEONE gazes after the young woman as she hefts up a few supply bags slung around her shoulders.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS259
Peering back, she catches him watching.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS260
A smile just dawns on her face and she turns away.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS261
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE, who waits on the porch.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS262
He lumbers wearily with the bucket and butter.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS263
They head indoors.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS265
SOMEONE halts on the footpath.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS266
He watches his father and sister approach a barn, hand in hand.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS267
He begrudgingly complies. Now at Spar's indoor cage.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS268
Spar lies on his side.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS269
Spar nudges his head closer to SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS270
The little girl regards her father tenderly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS271
SOMEONE's gaze softens appreciatively.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS272
They view each other through the cage wire.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS273
SOMEONE gives an understanding nod.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS274
SOMEONE screws her mouth to one side, lifts her brow, and tilts her head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS275
Her father looks to Spar, then nods resolutely.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS276
In the garage, SOMEONE peers into an open bin filled with wriggling mealworms.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS277
The boy takes a recoiling step back, then looks around uneasily as he advances.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS278
Ahead, a long flat crate lies on a steel table.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS279
Stickers and stamps on every side read, Caution: Live Snakes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS280
SOMEONE's hand hovers over its metal latch.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS281
He lifts the lid to reveal a writhing tangle of intertwined snakes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS282
SOMEONE lowers the lid and flees. He neglects to latch it. On his way out, he switches off the lights.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS283
Unsupervised, two snakes slither from the crate.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS284
A third pokes its head out. Now SOMEONE draws the curtains in SOMEONE's bedroom. She lies buried in stuffed animals.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS285
He takes a few toys off of her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS286
SOMEONE comes out of his room.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS287
He looks in, but remains unseen.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS288
Tickling SOMEONE, SOMEONE finds the old sweatshirt under the covers.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS289
SOMEONE's smile fades.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS290
His bewildered gaze shifts between SOMEONE and the shirt.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS291
Clutching her monkey puppet, SOMEONE nods.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS292
SOMEONE points in the air, then claps her hands together.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS293
He places SOMEONE's hand over her heart.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS294
SOMEONE makes a heart shape with her hands.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS295
She presses it to SOMEONE's shoulder.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS296
Apart from them, SOMEONE wipes a tear.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS297
SOMEONE shows the sweatshirt and SOMEONE nods.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS298
She gently takes it from her father's grip.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS299
SOMEONE returns to his room. Morning. As llamas, a hawk, and oxen stir, SOMEONE works in the kitchen.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS300
SOMEONE opens the front door.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS301
Snakes infest the driveway. SOMEONE runs out, turns tail, and runs back in.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS302
Later, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE collect the escaped snakes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS303
SOMEONE watches from the porch. SOMEONE laughs at SOMEONE gripping a handful of snakes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS304
SOMEONE tries to put one in a bucket.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS305
SOMEONE throws the bucket and drop kicks a snake.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS306
SOMEONE storms inside. SOMEONE stares after him, then glares at SOMEONE. A snake slithers at SOMEONE's feet.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS307
Later with SOMEONE, SOMEONE threads a chunk of raw animal flesh.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS308
She picks up a hawk.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS309
She chucks it into a refrigerated locker.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS310
Later, SOMEONE pushes a wheelbarrow. SOMEONE escorts him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS311
Elsewhere on the property, SOMEONE rakes leaves. As a flashy black pickup passes on a nearby road, she uses a walkie-	talkie.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS312
In the restaurant.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS313
SOMEONE and another staffer hold the door shut. Outside, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE and SOMEONE as they wait to greet the 	arriving pickup.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS314
The driver side door swings open and a pair of simple black boots step out. As the visitor turns, we recognize Ferris' 	features from the photo on the dartboard. Wearing a suit beneath a rugged parka, he approaches with a cocky 	disdainful smirk.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS315
Both men whip out notepads in unison.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS316
SOMEONE steps in close.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS317
SOMEONE looks her up and down.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS318
She glowers at his sly smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS319
SOMEONE lifts his brow.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS320
He eyes SOMEONE with mock surprise.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS321
He dramatically makes a fist.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS322
SOMEONE stares at his hand, which he wags slowly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS323
As SOMEONE moves off, SOMEONE faces his colleagues and emphatically mouths, Wow.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS324
They follow SOMEONE across the property. Later, as they hike up a grassy sun-kissed slope, SOMEONE snidely takes in his 	surroundings through sunglasses.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS325
Now at SOMEONE's enclosure, he scrutinizes a railing.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS326
From a hip holster, SOMEONE whips out an electric tape measure. As he activates the device, its tape extends over a 	moat separating SOMEONE's enclosure from the guard railing.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS327
Cocking an eyebrow, SOMEONE faces SOMEONE, who cocks his head and gives a few perfunctory nods.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS328
The inspector shifts his gaze to SOMEONE and wiggles his eyebrows.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS329
He reads the measurement.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS330
SOMEONE makes a note.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS331
Now at the tiger habitat.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS332
SOMEONE pauses just long enough to give a derisive sneer.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS333
In the restaurant, SOMEONE fights his way out of the restroom and stares at SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS334
Outside, the flashy black pickup speeds away, kicking up a trail of dust.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS335
SOMEONE runs after the truck.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS336
SOMEONE eyes the notepad grimly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS337
SOMEONE zips off.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS338
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch him go. Behind them, SOMEONE shakes her head and makes notes. SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS339
Crystal the Capuchin turns on SOMEONE's shoulder.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS340
SOMEONE points. About 50 yards away, SOMEONE stands doubled over, catching his breath.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS341
Oblivious to his observers, he straightens and fires a series of furious punches and kicks at the air.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS342
SOMEONE gives a pitying frown.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS343
SOMEONE paces, hands on his hips.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS344
He kicks over a large wooden barrel.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS345
SOMEONE's brow knits as she looks on, and SOMEONE shakes her head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS346
SOMEONE remorsefully rights the barrel, then continues pacing.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS347
Pressing her lips together, SOMEONE allows a warm amused smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS348
Noticing the others watching, SOMEONE affects a stoic demeanor and holds his hand up in a wave.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS349
SOMEONE beams fondly at him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS350
Now, SOMEONE's SUV travels a winding road among verdant hills. At the wheel, the father glances at SOMEONE, who 	rides shotgun.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS351
SOMEONE blinks at his son, his mouth agape.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS352
As they stop at an intersection, SOMEONE frowns.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS353
Buster casually lopes across the street in front of the SUV. With their jaws hanging open, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stare 	at the lumbering grizzly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS354
SOMEONE bars an arm across SOMEONE's chest as though protecting him from hitting the brakes hard. The bear moves 	to the driver side window.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS355
The grizzly smells the window, then rises onto his hind legs and presses a paw to the glass. He drops back down to 	all fours and sniffs the side mirror.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS356
With his eyes fixed on the escaped bear, SOMEONE takes the phone from his son. A string of drool hangs from 	Buster's lips. As the bear trudges away, SOMEONE makes a call.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS357
SOMEONE pulls three tranquilizer rifles from a cabinet.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS358
SOMEONE searches with SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE, who carry tranquilizer guns. Meanwhile, Buster roams a sunny 	woodland path.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS359
Tranquilizer gun in hand, SOMEONE freezes as he spots the grizzly on a hill.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS360
Buster bounces on his forepaws and tosses his head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS361
SOMEONE steps closer.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS363
The bear looks up at him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS364
SOMEONE squints apprehensively as Buster lumbers toward him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS365
The grizzly keeps approaching.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS366
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS367
A swat from Buster sends the gun flying.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS368
SOMEONE leans away from Buster's wide-open jaws. Air and saliva hit his face.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS370
SOMEONE flinches, then watches as Buster lies down on the grass. SOMEONE and SOMEONE close in with their guns 	ready. The others join them.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS371
SOMEONE makes a call.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS372
SOMEONE gazes down at the bear.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS373
Later, Buster lies in a shelter in his enclosure. Its door drops shut.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS374
Now with SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS375
SOMEONE gives an unhappy look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS376
The vet swipes his credit card through a portable card reader and types in an amount.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS377
SOMEONE peers at the screen.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS379
At the restaurant, SOMEONE selects a song on the jukebox. Sitting at the bar, SOMEONE stares off with a troubled look,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS380
then lifts his eyes to the tables where his staff members drink and chat.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS381
SOMEONE meets SOMEONE's gaze and jerks her head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS382
He follows her outside. As SOMEONE watches his son leave, SOMEONE looks over at him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS383
Her lips twitch in a thoughtful expression. The zoo owner clenches his jaw, then sucks in a breath.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS384
SOMEONE raises her glass.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS385
He raises his beer bottle in a toast, then shakes his head. Meanwhile, a flashlight's beam moves back and forth in 	the sky as SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie side by side on the roof. SOMEONE holds the light on her stomach.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS386
She grins at him. He smiles back, then returns his gaze to the sky.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS387
Lifting his head, he looks over and finds her swirling her fingers over the flashlight, as she stares at the sky with a 	dreamy expression.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS388
A wide view shows the high-reaching beam, its glow shifting with SOMEONE's hand movements.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS389
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE stroll from the restaurant.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS390
SOMEONE gives him a mildly intrigued look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS391
They stop walking. SOMEONE smiles.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS392
She half subdues her smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS393
SOMEONE shifts his gaze to the zoo's grounds.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS394
She eyes him sympathetically.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS395
SOMEONE meets her friendly gaze and gives a thoughtful look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS396
Now in his bedroom, he wears an undershirt and sweatpants as he stands at his dresser, his hair damp.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS397
He finds the old faded sweatshirt in the top drawer and takes it out.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS398
He examines it.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS399
Pulling it on, he lifts his eyes to a framed black-and-white photo of his wife on the dresser.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS400
As he grabs a book and flops onto the bed,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS401
his hand brushes against the sweatshirt's front-pouch pocket.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS402
Reaching inside, he finds a receipt for a safe deposit box bearing SOMEONE's name.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS403
He looks at the framed photo of her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS404
Shot from the waist up during one of her pregnancies, she stands nude with one arm across her chest.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS405
Daytime. At the Jaguar.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS406
SOMEONE faces the staff.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS407
Now, SOMEONE hurries into an open office of cubicles, past employees consulting clients.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS408
He arrives at his brother's desk.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS409
He hands SOMEONE an envelope.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS410
SOMEONE grabs his coat. Later at a restaurant, SOMEONE sits across a table from his brother and reads bank statements.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS411
His jaw drops as he examines some pie charts, and he gives SOMEONE an amazed look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS412
He slides a letter from an envelope.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS413
SOMEONE leafs through a lengthy handwritten letter. His gaze falls on two words in quotation marks.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS414
Now at the zoo.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS415
SOMEONE brings a sandwich to SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS416
He continues to sketch as she sits beside him at a picnic table.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS417
With a sad smile, she gazes at the oblivious boy.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS418
He looks at her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS419
SOMEONE resumes drawing.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS420
He lifts his excited gaze to SOMEONE. Struggling to remain composed, she nods.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS421
He returns to his sketch.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS422
As SOMEONE focuses on his drawing, SOMEONE watches with heartbroken eyes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS423
She gets up.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS424
He gazes after her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS425
Blinking back tears, SOMEONE strides away.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS426
SOMEONE shakes his head disbelievingly and smiles to himself.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS428
they walk to the restaurant.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS429
Inside, SOMEONE gives a snide look as SOMEONE faces the staff.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS430
SOMEONE drops his knife.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS431
SOMEONE glowers.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS432
SOMEONE scoffs.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS433
He looks at SOMEONE, who sits at the bar and gives an encouraging nod.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS434
SOMEONE expectantly takes a steadying breath.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS435
SOMEONE shifts her weight, her gaze intent.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS436
SOMEONE nods.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS437
SOMEONE shares a quizzical glance with her cousin.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS438
SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS439
As he stares at the bank statements in his hands, SOMEONE bridles.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS440
SOMEONE wears a puzzled frown.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS441
SOMEONE holds up the bank statements.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS442
SOMEONE looks on, dazed.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS443
SOMEONE gestures for a timeout.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS444
SOMEONE tears up and SOMEONE grins from ear to ear.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS445
Clapping, SOMEONE stands. Next to SOMEONE, SOMEONE applauds.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS446
Smiling, she bows.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS447
SOMEONE stifles a laugh. SOMEONE grins at her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS448
Pointing two fingers like a gun, SOMEONE mimes aiming it into his own mouth and pulling the trigger.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS449
Now, SOMEONE and SOMEONE set towering posts near Buster's enclosure. On a monthly calendar, a hand checks off 	the 1st of June. SOMEONE mounts a sign in front of a capuchin enclosure. Later, the hand crosses off June 10th.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS450
As a circular saw cuts a pole, otters watch from a rock.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS451
On the calendar, the hand Xs out the 19th, then adds to a doodle at the bottom. Now, SOMEONE cuts through bars 	on Buster's enclosure.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS454
Sitting outside, SOMEONE draws in his sketchbook. He glances around, then checks his watch and gazes down a path for 	Lily. Seeing no one, he gives a disappointed look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS455
Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE assemble wrought-iron fencing around SOMEONE's enclosure. She eyes his knit cap.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS456
She lifts her brow high.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS457
A hand checks off June 28th. Now at Home Depot with SOMEONE, SOMEONE grabs an item.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS458
SOMEONE grabs onto the back of his belt and he puts an arm around her. Later, they check out.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS459
She eyes his weathered credit card.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS460
SOMEONE signs his receipt.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS461
He starts to leave.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS462
He takes her hand as she offers his bag.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS463
At the zoo.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS464
He replaces a bulb over Spar's cage. The tiger hangs his head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS465
SOMEONE enters the cage area, unnoticed by SOMEONE. The owner climbs down from his ladder and faces Spar.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS466
Spar bares his teeth.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS467
He glances away, then opens his mouth wide.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS468
As he gazes sadly at the tiger,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS469
SOMEONE observes from the end of the cage row.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS470
Spar meets his pleading gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS471
Spar looks away.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS472
As SOMEONE tries to hold the tiger's gaze, he notices SOMEONE watching them.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS473
Standing, he grabs his tool bag and strides past her to the door.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS474
SOMEONE stares after him as he hurries out.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS475
Now, SOMEONE sits at the kitchen island with a laptop in front of him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS476
Opening it, he puts on his glasses.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS477
He moves the cursor down the desktop photo of SOMEONE and SOMEONE to a row of icons at the bottom.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS478
The cursor moves along the monitor's dock to the iPhoto application.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS480
Clicking it, SOMEONE opens an album displaying thumbnail images of family photos.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS481
He opens the first one, then selects Full Screen.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS482
He glides the cursor across a smiling photo of SOMEONE with trees behind her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS483
A lens flare obscures her angelic face with brilliant sunlight.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS484
SOMEONE hovers the cursor over an arrow icon to continue to the next image.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS485
His cursor remains on the icon as he gazes at the sun-blanched photo of his wife.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS486
He blinks his languishing eyes and his lips tighten into a frown.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS487
He removes his glasses and pulls the laptop shut.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS488
Now SOMEONE runs to Spar's enclosure, joining SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS489
He heads to the gate.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS490
SOMEONE halts and faces the others.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS491
Catching his breath, SOMEONE looks in at Spar.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS492
The aging tiger wearily meets his gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS493
SOMEONE turns back to the others.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS494
SOMEONE and SOMEONE are taken aback.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS495
As SOMEONE regards Spar uncertainly, SOMEONE arrives.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS496
SOMEONE uses his radio.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS497
Later, the zoo staffers bang on buckets, pots, and pans.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS498
Spar stays up on his boulder.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS499
SOMEONE joins in on the yelling.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS500
Spar lazily looks over from his boulder.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS501
Spar gets to his feet.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS502
He carefully makes his way down.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS503
SOMEONE lowers his cupped hands from his mouth.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS504
SOMEONE lifts her brow.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS505
SOMEONE and a tall zoo worker swap concerned looks.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS506
SOMEONE leans heavily on a guard rail.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS507
As he glances toward SOMEONE, she looks away.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS508
He abruptly turns and walks off.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS509
SOMEONE hurries after him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS510
She storms up the footpath.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS511
She halts and wheels back on SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS512
She marches off, leaving SOMEONE with his mouth agape.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS513
Now, SOMEONE looks down at a peahen.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS514
The penned bird sits on a nest.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS515
SOMEONE arrives.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS516
SOMEONE sketches on the porch.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS517
Now at dusk, light shines softly from the house. SOMEONE brings a pizza box into the dining room.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS518
SOMEONE brings plates and placemats.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS519
At the table, SOMEONE closes his sketchbook.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS520
SOMEONE sets the table.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS521
She pats his hand and steps away.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS522
SOMEONE brings napkins and a plate of utensils.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS523
Later, SOMEONE takes the little girl upstairs, followed by SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS524
We watch through a window as SOMEONE ushers the zookeeper into her room.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS525
SOMEONE follows at a leisurely swagger, his sketchbook in hand.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS526
Later, SOMEONE sits on the porch, sipping peacefully from a mug.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS527
SOMEONE's SUV pulls up.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS528
The grieving widower climbs the porch steps and takes a seat in a chair beside SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS529
SOMEONE lies near her feet, watching them placidly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS530
SOMEONE takes SOMEONE's hand in his. She studies his distant ponderous expression, glances away for a moment, then 	gives him a warm smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS531
Looking down, she watches him adjust his grip on her hand.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS532
She glances at his face again, then gazes off with a gentle smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS533
He releases her hand and they both sit quietly, staring into the darkness.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS534
SOMEONE faces him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS535
SOMEONE meets her attentive gaze, then shakes his head wistfully.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS536
SOMEONE gives an understanding nod.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS537
She offers a gentle sympathetic smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS539
SOMEONE listens in.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS540
Frowning, SOMEONE releases a deep breath and leans forward in her seat.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS541
A brief wistful smile flits across SOMEONE's features.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS542
SOMEONE gives a stoic shrug.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS543
He mimics Ferris' gesture, causing SOMEONE to chuckle.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS544
She regards him compassionately, then gets up, pats his leg, and looks him in the eye.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS545
She moves past him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS546
He gazes after her gratefully.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS547
Going into the house, he finds SOMEONE sitting at the foot of the stairs, in tears.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS548
SOMEONE follows him upstairs.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS549
His father stares at his tearful savage glare.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS550
SOMEONE's shoulders sag in a weary sigh.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS551
Pressing his lips together, he leans against the banister railing.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS552
Under his father's imploring gaze, SOMEONE swallows.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS553
He shuts himself in his room.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS554
SOMEONE knocks on the door.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS555
He turns to find SOMEONE coming out of her room.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS556
Now, the sun peeks over distant trees.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS557
A vulture's sharp-beaked face and white fluffy collar fill our view as it shifts its keen gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS558
A kangaroo hops gracefully around its grassy enclosure.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS559
Near a watchtower, SOMEONE rests his arms on a fence and gazes off pensively.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS560
Now, Spar lies in his backroom cage.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS561
He stares out at SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS562
The zoo owner takes a seat on the floor, leaning back against the wall.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS563
Spar relaxes onto his side in a shaft of sunlight.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS564
SOMEONE holds the animal in his melancholy gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS565
At the far end of the room, a windowed door opens.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS566
Turning, SOMEONE finds his son staring in at him timidly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS567
Clad in a red hooded sweatshirt and jeans, SOMEONE comes in and shuts the door.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS569
The young teen moves through shafts of sunlight
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS570
pouring in from the high windows as he approaches SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS571
Sitting beside him on the floor, he glances at his father's grief-stricken expression, then looks to the cage.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS572
On the other side of the grating, Spar lies with his eyes half-closed.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS574
Beneath his striped pelt, his rib cage rises and falls, slowly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS575
SOMEONE gives his son a loving sidelong stare.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS576
SOMEONE gives a receptive nod and SOMEONE returns his gaze to Spar.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS578
The teen releases a deep pent-up breath, then swallows.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS580
Blinking thoughtfully, SOMEONE purses his lips tightly and nods.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS581
SOMEONE regards his father with a faint understanding smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS582
Spar slumbers peacefully in his shaft of sunlight.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS583
SOMEONE faces his father earnestly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS584
SOMEONE faces his son with a furrowed brow.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS585
The boy gazes solemnly into the cage.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS586
Spar opens his eyes a slit and blinks heavily.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS587
Later, SOMEONE bites his lip as he walks outside with SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS588
He approaches SOMEONE and gives a resigned nod.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS589
She watches them walk off together down the sun-dabbled footpath.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS590
Seeing SOMEONE throw an arm around his son's shoulder, she takes a deep warm-hearted breath.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS591
As they near a bend in the path, SOMEONE's father gives him a playful shove.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS592
The boy staggers sideways, then shoves him back good-naturedly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS593
At night, SOMEONE tucks a blanket around his sleeping son. He strokes the teen's smooth hair, then notices a stack 	of drawings on a bedside table and picks them up.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS594
The top sketch depicts a human figure with taloned hands and a spiraling worm-like head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS595
Flipping through the drawings, SOMEONE next finds a detailed illustration of a fly with pincers and a toothy maniacal 	grin.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS596
The father's brow knits and he glances at his son.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS597
Continuing to the next drawing, he finds a portrait of Spar's face.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS598
The minimalistic rendering captures the tiger's characteristically warm, intelligent gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS599
SOMEONE's lips part as he takes in the evocative image.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS600
He looks back at his sleeping son and beams proudly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS601
Taking a deep breath, SOMEONE returns his gaze to the portrait, and blinks back tears.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS602
Now at his laptop, he clicks an arrow on his iPhoto application.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS603
The image of a sun-haloed SOMEONE changes to a picture of her smiling in the bright daylight.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS604
SOMEONE sits cross-legged on the kitchen floor with the computer on his lap.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS605
He clicks to the next image, which shows him and SOMEONE sharing a kiss.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS606
The widower smiles wistfully.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS607
More images follow.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS608
SOMEONE facing a sunny window.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS609
She and SOMEONE standing in their wedding clothes beside a single-propeller airplane,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS610
SOMEONE lying on a bed with a newborn infant.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS611
SOMEONE's breath grows ragged and his chin quivers.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS612
The next picture shows a black-and-white-photo print lying on a table.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS613
It features SOMEONE holding a glass of red wine.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS614
In the next photo, the smiling beauty stands in the snow in an ankle-length coat.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS615
More images follow.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS616
SOMEONE grinning in a tutu.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS617
SOMEONE making a goofy face behind a seated SOMEONE. A younger SOMEONE giving a thumbs-up on the beach.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS618
SOMEONE by a lake,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS619
her hair tumbling around her shoulders.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS620
SOMEONE stares tearfully at the photo.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS621
The next shows SOMEONE kissing his cheek.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS622
In another, she lies asleep in bed, her shoulders bare.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS623
SOMEONE imagines her opening her eyes, her chest rises and falls beneath the sheet.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS624
A tear escapes SOMEONE's eye and he gives a brief smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS625
In another picture, SOMEONE plays with SOMEONE as a puppy. In a field, SOMEONE stands on one leg, with her arms spread, 	as her children look on. Another tear rolls down SOMEONE's cheek.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS626
Looking up from the computer, he remembers taking photos in the field as his wife and children frolic around him. 	Later, they play a game of tag. SOMEONE grins at the memory. In the field, SOMEONE and SOMEONE spread their arms 	like wings as they run circles around him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS627
Back in the present, SOMEONE beams joyfully as he visualizes his wife and children playing before him in the dimly lit 	kitchen.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS628
Back in the field, SOMEONE's white spotted sundress flutters as she leads her children in tighter circles around her 	husband. In the kitchen, SOMEONE's glasses show their dancing reflections.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS629
He wets his lips as he stares longingly at the passing vision of his wife.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS630
In the field, the family gathers in a group embrace around him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS631
Later, SOMEONE reclines across his lap and SOMEONE leans against his side.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS632
Later still, SOMEONE holds his wife in his arms as she reaches out to scratch SOMEONE's back.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS633
In the kitchen, the widower lowers his overwhelmed gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS634
He removes his reading glasses,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS635
the skin around his eyes glistening with traces of tears
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS636
Now, a blurred image sharpens into focus to reveal the gnarled branches of a California oak.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS637
At the tiger's outdoor enclosure, SOMEONE finishes posting a memorial plaque.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS639
It reads, Spar, 1993 to 2010, Our Unforgettable Friend and features a photo illustration of the Bengal tiger.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS640
As SOMEONE steps away, our view drifts closer to the touching memorial
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS641
passing through patches of flared sunlight.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS642
Elsewhere in the zoo, two wolves forage within their enclosure.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS643
A horned owl turns its head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS644
Two black boars trot around in their pen.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS645
Grass sticks out from a tortoise's mouth as it crawls over the ground. A peahen turns her head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS646
SOMEONE kneels at the edge of SOMEONE's pen in front of the house.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS647
A chick hatches from an egg.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS648
Inside, SOMEONE intercepts SOMEONE as he comes downstairs.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS649
He unrolls a poster.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS650
An advertisement for the zoo features SOMEONE's portrait of Spar at its center.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS651
The teen's eyes light up.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS652
SOMEONE chuckles, overcome with SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS653
They share a smile. SOMEONE comes running in.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS654
A boxy older-style Mercedes pulls up nearby. SOMEONE gets out, wearing sunglasses.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS655
He takes off his shades.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS656
He clicks a remote, popping his trunk.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS657
Now in his enclosure, Buster paws at a tray of SOMEONE curiously. Outside the Jaguar, SOMEONE squeegees a window.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS658
SOMEONE strides past and takes a screwdriver to a water fountain. It squirts him in the face. SOMEONE uses a leaf 	blower.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS659
Crystal paints with SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS660
SOMEONE gazes longingly at SOMEONE. Now at the park entrance, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE lift a sign to an entryway frame.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS661
Bearing SOMEONE's portrait of Spar as its central logo, it reads Rosemoor Animal Park Adventure. SOMEONE and SOMEONE 	hold it in place while SOMEONE attaches it.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS662
Now, a spotless sweatless SOMEONE strides past SOMEONE and SOMEONE, with an ax and an overly confident air.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS663
Now, everyone assembles.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS665
Ferris' truck pulls up nearby. Beaming, SOMEONE pats SOMEONE's back.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS666
As the pretty girl grins, SOMEONE sneaks a look at her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS667
SOMEONE wears a khaki safari-style vest over his suit.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS668
His long hair in a ponytail, SOMEONE shakes his hand.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS669
They grip each other's hands.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS670
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE and nods. The zoo owner gives a bewildered shake of his head. Now, SOMEONE faces a 	schedule on a whiteboard.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS671
Later, as SOMEONE and SOMEONE look on, SOMEONE picks up a single piece of straw. Scrutinizing it, he turns it in the light, 	then gives it a sniff.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS672
He eyes his host disapprovingly, flicks the straw away, and moves on.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS673
SOMEONE and SOMEONE follow worriedly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS674
Now, SOMEONE extends his electric measuring tape along a railing.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS675
Later, he stands on a building's corrugated metal roof. He bounces lightly, then tries another spot.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS676
Now, he peers closely at a surface and sets a miniature level on it.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS677
In its clear tube of fluid, a bubble hovers in the center.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS678
Later, as SOMEONE pushes a measuring wheel over the footpath, a camel walks beside him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS679
Now, he stands at an ankle-deep pool as otters swim around him. Later, he taps on the enclosure's glass.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS680
Now, SOMEONE arrives at SOMEONE's enclosure and opens the gate.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS681
She pauses and frowns. Glancing around, she pulls the gate shut and hurriedly takes a key from a ring on her belt.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS682
Opening the gate again, she turns the key extending a deadbolt.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS683
SOMEONE turns the key back, and tries closing the gate, but the extended deadbolt prevents it from latching shut.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS684
SOMEONE turns the key persistently, but finds the deadbolt stuck.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS686
Lying on a rock, SOMEONE stands and faces her. She takes out her walkie. At Buster's enclosure, SOMEONE makes notes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS687
SOMEONE turns off his walkie-talkie.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS688
SOMEONE leads him off. At the malfunctioning gate, SOMEONE struggles with the key and the lock.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS689
The lion gets down off his rock and takes a few steps towards SOMEONE, holding the gate shut from the outside.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS690
Meanwhile, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE and his kids through a grove.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS691
SOMEONE dashes off to the far side of the enclosure.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS692
SOMEONE takes off his jacket and points.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS693
The lion turns. As he takes a step toward SOMEONE, SOMEONE enters the enclosure behind him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS694
He takes out his tools.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS695
With SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS696
In the lion enclosure, SOMEONE shakily removes the gate's knob-shaped handle. Safely outside it, SOMEONE jumps up 	and down.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS697
SOMEONE peeks over his shoulder.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS698
He slams the gate on his fingers.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS699
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE and stalks toward him. His back to the lion, the Scotsman reassembles the lock.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS700
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE and points.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS701
The lion licks his chops.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS702
SOMEONE finishes the lock, slips out, and bolts the gate.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS703
SOMEONE primps her hair, then wheels around to meet SOMEONE with a big smile. SOMEONE joins her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS704
SOMEONE peers into the enclosure, then turns his suspicious gaze on the others.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS705
He takes out his electric measuring tape.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS706
With a scowl at SOMEONE and SOMEONE, he extends it over the moat.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS707
Now, a clipboard bears a document headed,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS708
Final Inspection Report.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS709
SOMEONE holds a pen between two checkboxes labeled, Denied and Approved.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS710
SOMEONE, his kids, and the zoo staff stand before him as he considers.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS711
A smirk plays on Ferris' lips as he regards the staff.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS712
He shakes his head and aims his pen.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS713
SOMEONE stares at his daughter, who looks up sweetly at the inspector. SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE sheepishly.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS714
Facing SOMEONE, the inspector lifts his brow, smirks, and marks the report.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS715
SOMEONE resignedly approaches SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS716
SOMEONE blinks and lowers her forlorn gaze. As SOMEONE holds out the report,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS717
SOMEONE hangs her head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS718
SOMEONE looks down at the report, then holds it up to the others.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS719
SOMEONE shakes SOMEONE's hand. As SOMEONE starts to go, SOMEONE stops him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS720
SOMEONE's smile fades. He offers a terse professional nod to the inspector, who reciprocates.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS721
SOMEONE heads off, then stops to look back at the jubilant group.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS722
Among them, SOMEONE embraces SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS723
SOMEONE scoops up SOMEONE and hugs SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS724
SOMEONE shakes his head and leaves.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS725
Now, at the Jaguar Restaurant, SOMEONE joins his brother at the bar.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS726
SOMEONE spits out his scotch bottle's cork and holds up a glass.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS727
He fills SOMEONE's and SOMEONE's whisky glasses, then steps away.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS728
He jerks his thumb at the zoo staff.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS729
SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS730
SOMEONE turns and SOMEONE looks up.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS731
Outside, raindrops land in Buster's enormous footprint. The storm quickly picks up, turning the dirt into mud.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS732
Water drips off a leafy branch. At the ground's entrance, an archway reading Rosemoor Wildlife Park stands in the 	heavy downpour.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS733
Now wearing a hooded raincoat, SOMEONE walks on the dirt road.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS734
Passing the restaurant, he doubles back and reads a new illuminated sign in the window.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS735
If you love me, let me know.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS736
SOMEONE smiles wistfully at the words, nods, and dashes off.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS737
Now a rain-drenched window shows SOMEONE working leather in her room.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS738
SOMEONE approaches.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS739
The pretty teen puts down her work, kneels at the window, and lifts the sash.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS740
SOMEONE solemnly shakes her head, then yields a smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS741
SOMEONE's mirthful grin vanishes and she stares at SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS742
Panting, he stares back, then cracks an undaunted smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS743
SOMEONE's large blue eyes fill with tears and she beams back at him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS744
SOMEONE wraps his arms around her and they share a warm heartfelt embrace. The teen boy leans diagonally into SOMEONE's 	window, his feet planted in a flowerbed as he holds her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS745
Now, a TV weather report.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS746
Now, rain drips from a sign reading Zookeepers Only. Water streams from the barn roof.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS747
By a fence, raindrops pelt two full water bowls. In Buster's enclosure, his enormous footprint is now a paw-shaped 	puddle. In another enclosure, monkeys gather on a branch.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS748
In his living room, SOMEONE reads in an armchair while SOMEONE sketches nearby.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS749
Seated at the coffee table, SOMEONE colors. A glass of milk stands within her reach.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS750
SOMEONE eyes the unrelenting rainfall outside.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS751
Elsewhere, SOMEONE opens a flask in his living quarters and finds the vessel empty.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS752
SOMEONE leaves a building and uses her walkie-talkie.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS753
The bearcat eats from SOMEONE's hand.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS754
A zebra hoofs through mud.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS755
Two tigers gaze out from windows in the big-cat house.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS756
Crystal licks rain from her fur.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS757
In an open-air shelter, SOMEONE cuts potatoes into chunks, and then puts them in a scale's bowl, and reads the 	measurement.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS758
In town, in spite of the downpour, SOMEONE holds a zoo poster up to a bulletin board.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS759
SOMEONE staples it in place with clownish aggression.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS760
On the calendar, a young hand marks an X through July 6th.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS761
Now, SOMEONE watches a TV weather report.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS762
Now, a digital alarm clock on a nightstand reads 6:43 AM. In bed beside it, SOMEONE wakes and slaps it. He frowns 	and pushes himself up a little.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS763
The zoo owner rolls over and finds sunlight peeking in between his curtains.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS764
SOMEONE climbs out of bed and draws the curtains apart.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS765
Outside, the sun shines brightly through a row of tall leafy trees.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS766
SOMEONE gives a satisfied smirk and dashes from the window. He hurries through the house.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS767
The calendar's on SOMEONE's door. Now, as SOMEONE dons a zookeeper uniform, SOMEONE enters in one of her own.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS768
Now, at the zoo entrance.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS769
The uniformed staffers listen with fond respectful gazes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS770
SOMEONE cuts a red ribbon stretching across the entryway.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS771
SOMEONE checks his watch. SOMEONE peers down the dirt road, but finds no sign of visitors.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS772
SOMEONE runs down the road.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS773
The others follow him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS774
He finds a massive tree blocking the road.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS775
SOMEONE joins his son as he climbs onto the toppled tree.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS776
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE follow suit.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS777
On the other side, they find a crowd waiting by a line of cars.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS778
As SOMEONE stares with astonished eyes, the zoo's patrons give excited looks. He snaps out of his daze.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS779
SOMEONE helps people climb over the tree.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS780
SOMEONE takes a woman's hand as she climbs up.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS781
SOMEONE and SOMEONE help the guests as they climb down on the other side.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS782
With Crystal perched on his shoulder, SOMEONE lifts a boy off the tree and sets him on the ground.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS783
Beaming, the zoo staffers assist their eager guests.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS784
SOMEONE holds out her hand for a descending woman.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS785
Gazing down the road, SOMEONE sees long lines of people surging forward around the parked cars.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS786
SOMEONE looks out at the crowd, then glances at SOMEONE, and gives an overjoyed laugh.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS787
Later in the bustling zoo, a staffer hands out brochures, an old woman gives away balloons, and SOMEONE distributes 	packaged kites. In front of the tiger enclosure, SOMEONE gives a talk.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS788
SOMEONE gives a talk to guests.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS789
Mr. SOMEONE stands with two boys.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS790
Crystal smacks SOMEONE's head.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS791
A guest pats SOMEONE's arm.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS792
As he smiles at passing patrons, his gaze finds the Home Depot cashier in the crowd.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS793
She gives an impressed smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS794
She pats his shoulder.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS795
In a small office, SOMEONE checks inside an empty ticket box. SOMEONE enters as she searches under a table.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS796
Turning, he finds himself face to face with SOMEONE.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS797
She closes her eyes and presses her lips to his.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS798
As she draws back, her uncertain gaze flickers over his face.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS799
She smiles nervously.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS800
He kisses her and she closes her eyes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS801
As he pulls away slightly, SOMEONE leans closer, her eyes still closed, and lets her lips graze his.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS802
She twitches a smile and her eyelids flutter open.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS803
She nods. He gazes at her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS804
He gives a tender look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS805
Standing hastily, she leaves.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS806
He glances after her, then shifts his thoughtful eyes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS807
Later, SOMEONE aims a camera.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS808
SOMEONE and SOMEONE pose.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS809
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from a bench.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS810
SOMEONE pretends to toss SOMEONE into the tiger enclosure. SOMEONE stares at them.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS811
She turns to her older cousin. SOMEONE looks at SOMEONE and SOMEONE, who pose with their arms draped over each other's 	shoulders.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS812
She smiles.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS813
SOMEONE notes her cousin's expression.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS814
She grins.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS815
She watches as SOMEONE and SOMEONE pretend to flex their biceps for a photo.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS816
Now, kites float high in the sky. A girl with glasses holds her spool above her head. And a boy winds the string of his. 	Another kid holds his red kite up as he runs. And a woman a launches her own identical one.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS817
SOMEONE stands with SOMEONE, who glances up at her as she flies her red kite.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS818
Smiling, the zookeeper crouches behind her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS819
As SOMEONE strolls through the crowd, he spots the kites.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS820
Gazing up at the kite-filled sky, SOMEONE smiles lovingly. With her eyes on him, SOMEONE straightens.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS821
SOMEONE meets her gaze with a grateful look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS822
She beams. His eyes crinkle at the corners as he smiles at her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS823
He shrugs a shoulder.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS824
SOMEONE nods at SOMEONE and she glances at the crowd. She lifts her brow in an impressed look.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS825
We see animals in their respective enclosures. A tiger strides across grass. A capuchin sticks out its tongue. Buster 	lifts his face to the sunlight. Flamingos drink from a pond. And SOMEONE opens his mouth.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS826
Now, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE in a lookout tower.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS827
They gaze out at departing guest.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS828
Now, the Mee family enters a restaurant. Its sign reads Little Dom's.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS829
As they gaze at an empty table, SOMEONE smiles.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS830
His kids watch as he hurries out the door.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS831
He reappears at a window beside them.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS832
Reenacting, he halts in his tracks.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS834
He checks his watch.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS835
He enters through a side door and stops a few feet from the table where SOMEONE had been.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS836
He gives a nod.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS837
He strides up to the table, faces a seat, then stares wistfully. SOMEONE lifts her brow in an expectant look and SOMEONE 	smiles.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS838
He sees SOMEONE seating at the table.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS839
As the pretty brunette lifts her gaze to his, he watches with longing eyes.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS840
She grins at him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS841
With a smile, he turns to his kids. SOMEONE looks up at SOMEONE, who smiles.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS842
SOMEONE gestures at SOMEONE, and SOMEONE's eyes fill with tears as he sees her sitting there.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS843
Shifting his gaze from his kids,
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS844
SOMEONE turns to the pretty brunette.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS845
She smiles tenderly at him.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS846
He stares down at her.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS847
As she gazes up at him, her lips spread into a faint smile.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS848
SOMEONE sucks in a breath and she grins.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS851
Now, words appear. The Dartmoor Animal Park on which this story is based is an acclaimed zoo whose methods are studied worldwide. 	The park is open to faithful followers year-round.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS852
SOMEONE Mee and his two kids still live on the grounds.
WE_BOUGHT_A_ZOO_DVS853
Next year, they plan to add giraffes.