The man breezes through donning a bicycle helmet.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS45
He faces her with an eager smile, then dumps his stuff as she serves up his breakfast.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS46
The man flops down at the table, his T-shirt reading, "Save The Fucking Earth. "
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS48
The woman sits facing him.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS49
Later, a door labeled "6C" opens.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS50
The bicyclist steps out, carrying a wok and a toothbrush, then turns back to face the blonde.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS51
He heads off.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS52
Across the way, the door to 6A opens. A strikingly handsome man steps out naked, covering his genitals with a dishrag.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS53
Getting a newspaper, he notices the blonde and smiles. She stares, then shuts her door. Now outside, she uses her cell.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS54
She greets a delivery man.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS55
Now, SOMEONE emerges from Boston State Street T Station onto a busy sidewalk.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS56
She pauses to get her bearings, then hustles across the street, chomping down a hot dog as she goes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS57
As she reaches the other side, our view lifts to the densely packed skyscrapers lining the street.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS58
Now an elevator opens and SOMEONE hurries out.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS59
Entering a workspace, she passes lettering on a window that reads, "Linsky Solutions. "
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS60
She hurries to her desk.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS61
A coworker faces a windowed office.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS62
A boss taps his fingers under his nose.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS63
The boss faces them through his office window and stands.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS64
They quickly go back to work.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS65
He beckons her into his office, then talks on a phone.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS66
SOMEONE starts to remove her coat.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS67
Now, SOMEONE stands alone at a train platform, holding a box of personal items.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS68
They flashback to the office.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS69
He brings his fingers up to his nose and inhales.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS70
On the T, SOMEONE slumps.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS71
SOMEONE purses her lips receptively, then sweeps her long bangs out of her face.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS73
With a sheepish gaze her boss slowly swivels his chair around, putting his back to her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS75
On the train, SOMEONE sets her box aside, then takes out a magazine and flips through it.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS76
SOMEONE pouts, then slaps the magazine shut and answers her cell with a forced smile.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS77
She ends the call, glancing at an older woman beside her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS78
She opens her magazine to a feature titled "Ten Glam Looks For Office To Evening. "
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS79
Another, "Is This Food Scale Your New Best Friend?"
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS80
She comes across an article titled "What's Your Number?"
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS81
A tagline reads "The average number of lovers women have in their lifetime is 10. 5. "
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS82
The older woman beside her stares.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS83
Turning away, SOMEONE defensively screws her mouth to one side.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS84
She sets the magazine aside, then bites her lip and shifts her calculating gaze.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS85
She reaches into the box and pulls out a small notebook and pen.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS86
Glancing around, she opens it and heads a blank page with the words "People I've Slept With. "
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS87
Now as she enters her apartment building's lobby, her list fades into view.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS89
Finding the elevator out of service, she heads up the winding rectangular staircase.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS91
Now a wall in her apartment shows her shadow as she undresses.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS92
Wearing only panties, she scampers across our view.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS93
Now she showers with the bathroom door open.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS94
She steps out of the shower, obscured by steam, bends over her open notebook, and adds the name to the list.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS95
Now a taxi pulls away revealing SOMEONE in a Navy Blue sheath dress.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS96
She fidgets self-consciously, then takes a breath and trots across a driveway.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS97
Now a door opens and SOMEONE steps inside a foyer.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS98
She climbs a flight of stairs up to a tasteful party where an elegant blonde spots her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS99
They hug.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS100
Her mother disapprovingly adjusts her bangs.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS101
Halfway upstairs, SOMEONE writes in her notebook.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS102
At a mirror, SOMEONE curls her lashes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS103
Perching in an armchair, SOMEONE leans back and peers out a window.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS104
SOMEONE takes her notebook from her purse and writes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS105
As SOMEONE leaves, SOMEONE counts the entries on her list.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS106
SOMEONE grabs a glass of champagne and gulps down half its content
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS107
Now at the party downstairs, her mother taps the side of her wine
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS108
SOMEONE comes down barefooted, swigging champagne from the bottle.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS109
She notices a short man chatting up a model type.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS110
She pats his head.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS111
She pads down the hall and wedges between an attractive young man and woman.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS112
She rounds a corner, then peeks back at the woman with Beau.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS113
SOMEONE hungrily eyes hors d'oeuvres.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS114
The drunk young woman reluctantly makes her way to the center of the party.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS115
Amid a huddle of giggling women, one aims her videophone.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS116
SOMEONE spins to face the engaged couple and flourishes her free hand.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS117
The woman filming her grins and nods.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS118
A woman with long bangs stands sheepishly.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS119
Facing the video camera, she gives a chuckle.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS120
SOMEONE's mother gives an embarrassed smirk and shrug of the head.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS121
SOMEONE shatters a man's glass with her bottle.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS122
SOMEONE smiles comfortingly at his fiancée.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS123
Now at a bar, SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the women from the huddle drink together.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS124
The women drink shots.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS125
Now as a bartender pours a line of shots, SOMEONE's former boss leans into view beside her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS126
He looks at the shots.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS127
Grinning, SOMEONE leaves with the drinks.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS128
Back with the group of women.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS129
SOMEONE draws a slip of paper and reads.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS130
She draws a slip two inches.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS132
SOMEONE unfolds a slip of paper.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS133
SOMEONE's grin fades.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS134
With a forced smile, she reaches into the bowl and picks her own number.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS135
She tears it in half.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS136
SOMEONE downs the shot. Later, she tipsily stands with another.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS137
Now she stands on the bar, the crowd at her feet.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS138
Barefoot on the bar top, SOMEONE downs another drink and bobs her head awkwardly.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS139
Light flashes brightly as in fast motion. She marches up and down the bar.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS140
Amidst the crowd, SOMEONE's former boss bobs his head, watching her with a smile as she dances wildly.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS144
In the morning, SOMEONE sleeps curled up in bed, facing her nightstand.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS145
From behind her, an arm in a blazer flaps into view, its hand latching onto her breast.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS146
SOMEONE wakes, then slowly looks over her shoulder.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS147
Her former boss slumbers on his stomach at her side.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS148
SOMEONE's gaze sweeps down his body and finds him naked from the waist down.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS149
Her jaw drops open and she moves his arm off of her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS150
SOMEONE grabs a T-shirt off the floor and pulls it on.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS151
Creeping past the foot of the bed, she frantically dials a call.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS152
Reaching the bathroom,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS153
she drops down on her knees.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS154
On a beach.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS155
a crisply dressed SOMEONE walks with SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS173
As he gets up, she turns and watches him dress.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS175
He reaches down the front of his pants, then brings his fingers up to his nose.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS177
Later, SOMEONE paces anxiously in her living room.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS178
Her former boss strides in from the bathroom.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS179
SOMEONE opens the door to her neighbor.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS180
She throws a newspaper.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS181
As Roger shakes SOMEONE's hand, SOMEONE cringes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS182
Holding her hands, Roger sniffs his finger.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS183
On his way out, Roger lifts her up and pins her against the wall in an impassioned kiss.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS184
He sets her down and goes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS185
SOMEONE eyes a display of little sculptures.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS186
As Roger saunters to the stairs, a tall glamorous woman comes out of SOMEONE's apartment.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS187
He darts out of view.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS188
SOMEONE eyes the sculptures again.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS189
SOMEONE uses the peephole.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS190
Now at a bakery, SOMEONE makes notes at a table.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS191
Beside her, SOMEONE wolfs down a sample of cake.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS192
SOMEONE faces the entrance and frowns.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS193
An athletic, stylishly unshaven man.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS194
She remembers him as obese.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS195
SOMEONE's fat too.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS196
In the present.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS197
Lingering near the entrance, he flips through a catalog.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS198
SOMEONE wanders over, pretending to browse.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS199
Pausing by a cake,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS200
she looks back at her sister and nods.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS201
Glancing up from the catalog,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS202
SOMEONE notices her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS203
A stunning brunette joins SOMEONE at his side.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS204
They smooch.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS205
Now she leaves with SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS206
SOMEONE halts and her sister faces her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS207
Now at home, she carries a bottle of wine and a stack of keepsake books.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS208
She sets the bottle down with a glass already poured, puts down the books, and sits facing a computer.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS209
She sips wine as she searches.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS210
She unfolds a sheet of paper.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS211
She modifies her search.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS212
A porn site pops up.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS213
In fast motion, she drinks more wine. Later, she passes out with her head on the keyboard.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS214
Now, SOMEONE's computer shows a cartoon of a tiny mushroom-shaped penis situated on an oversized pair of balls.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS215
A friendly little face stares out from its head.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS216
The cartoon taps one testicle and bobs its head in a chipper little dance.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS217
Waking, SOMEONE stares at the cartoon.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS218
It sings.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS219
SOMEONE grabs a sheet of paper and spies SOMEONE opening his door.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS220
She goes out as SOMEONE retrieves his paper in the nude.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS221
She steps closer, averting her gaze.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS222
SOMEONE bites into an apple as he looks over her list.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS223
He lifts the dishrag covering his genitals and dabs at his mouth.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS224
SOMEONE storms back to her apartment
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS225
slams the door.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS226
She slaps the list down by her computer and folds her arms in a pout.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS227
Her eyes widen.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS228
She grabs her jacket and wrenches it on as she races back to SOMEONE's door.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS229
He opens the door.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS230
She encounters SOMEONE's date.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS231
SOMEONE drags SOMEONE out of his apartment and hustles him into her own.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS232
SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a sidelong look.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS233
Now, they get sandwiches to go.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS234
SOMEONE checks out a brunette.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS235
Wearing a T-shirt that reads "Free Licks," SOMEONE looks down at the sandwich, then takes an enormous bite.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS236
SOMEONE rolls her eyes in a good-humored sneer, then steps away.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS237
Now a selection of wedding dresses hangs on a rack.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS238
As SOMEONE looks through them, SOMEONE holds up another.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS239
She points to a sickly green gown.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS240
SOMEONE emerges from a fitting room.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS241
A flashback.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS242
A black-haired bartender wearing eyeliner pulls a quarter out from behind SOMEONE's ear.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS243
With her hair dyed black, she lies beneath him in bed.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS244
He reaches down between her legs and pulls up a handful of quarters.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS245
SOMEONE gives a delighted grin.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS246
In the present, she joins SOMEONE in a booth at a bar.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS247
SOMEONE looks around eagerly.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS248
SOMEONE points.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS249
Turning, SOMEONE finds her now spiky-haired ex behind the bar flourishing his hands at a brunette beauty.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS250
He pulls a coin out from behind her ear.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS251
She leaves and SOMEONE follows her out.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS252
Now, people buy produce at a bustling farmers' market.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS253
In an alley, several kids play with a ball as white clothes hang on a sun-drenched clothesline nearby.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS254
In bed, SOMEONE stirs sleepily.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS255
Waking, she rubs her eye
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS256
She gets up, revealing a tiny T-shirt and boy-cut panties.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS257
Tousling her hair,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS258
she glances through her doorway as she pads down toward the bathroom.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS259
SOMEONE lies on her couch.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS260
She faces SOMEONE's laptop.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS261
Later, she comes up the building's stairs, a new coffee pot tucked under her arm.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS262
SOMEONE holds one up.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS263
Later at SOMEONE's.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS264
As he brings beer to a table set for two, SOMEONE notices a large chart featuring her exes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS265
Later, they eat as they go through his findings.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS266
Now on a cobblestone street.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS267
They enter a house through its open door.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS268
He puts a sandwich down.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS269
As he trots upstairs, SOMEONE comes in with a bag of groceries.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS270
SOMEONE spots a photo of him and SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS271
She pauses on her way out, still holding it.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS272
She sets it down with her sandwich and goes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS273
SOMEONE carries his groceries further inside.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS274
SOMEONE dashes downstairs and out the door.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS275
SOMEONE scrambles back into view, looking around wildly.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS278
As SOMEONE looks away, she notices a man in a stylish cardigan sweater leaving his house.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS281
In a flashback, SOMEONE works as a waitress, wearing a short black dress with a white apron and frilly white hat. She smiles at the dashing Simon.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS286
He raises his eyebrows.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS287
With a wide grin, SOMEONE opens her mouth to speak.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS288
In the present, she shoves SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS292
As they tussle in the middle of the street, Simon notices.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS293
She takes a deep breath and scrunches up her face.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS296
She shoots a look at SOMEONE, who cracks up.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS300
She faces SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS301
Later on the apartment stairs.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS302
In the pub, a dart bounces off the board.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS303
SOMEONE throws another into a shelf of glasses.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS304
Another of her throws bounces off the ceiling.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS305
Simon gives an awkward nod and SOMEONE crosses to her drink at the bar.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS306
Simon eyes her quizzically.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS307
SOMEONE cringes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS308
Simon furrows his brow at her and she gives a little shrug.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS309
In the stairwell.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS310
Nighttime. On the roof, they sit on a couch eating pizza and beer.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS311
SOMEONE pouts and lowers her gaze to her slice of pizza.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS312
In a flashback, a teenaged SOMEONE with chin-length hair and bangs opens her front door.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS313
A dorky guy with large glasses and mismatched clothes stands on the stoop.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS314
SOMEONE slouches against the door, looks down, then gives Gerry a little smile.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS315
Now in bed, Gerry rocks slightly on top of SOMEONE, grimacing with his eyes closed.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS316
A puppet moves in beside them.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS317
Having the same characteristics as Gerry, the puppet looks from SOMEONE to Gerry and back again.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS318
On the roof, SOMEONE bites into her pizza.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS319
SOMEONE leans in to look at a file in SOMEONE's hands.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS320
Daytime. They walk along the harbor.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS321
Later, SOMEONE arrives at a restaurant.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS322
She joins SOMEONE at a table for three.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS323
SOMEONE stands, then slumps back down.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS324
Their mother arrives and kisses SOMEONE's cheek.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS325
She kisses SOMEONE and strokes her hair.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS326
Their mother glares at SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS328
Now a plane touches down on a tarmac. In a doctor's office, SOMEONE slips off her panties from under a hospital gown and shoves them in her bag.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS329
She takes out a SOMEONE purple thong and matching bra, and gently lays them on a chair with her clothes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS330
A clean-cut doctor walks in with his eyes on a file.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS331
She stares, slack-jawed.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS333
SOMEONE cocks his head.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS334
He helps her put a foot in the stirrups.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS335
As he readies a bright light at the end of the exam table, SOMEONE solemnly lies back.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS336
SOMEONE leans down and takes a look between her legs.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS337
In the apartment stairwell.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS338
Now outside, SOMEONE answers her cell.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS339
Later, SOMEONE enters her apartment.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS340
SOMEONE sits uncomfortably next to SOMEONE, who holds a guitar on his bare lap.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS341
He lifts the guitar.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS342
She pulls out a pantsuit.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS343
He leans forward to watch her go.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS344
In Washington.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS345
SOMEONE limps on a crowded walkway.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS346
In a bubble bath, SOMEONE listens and giggles.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS347
A passing woman stares at SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS348
SOMEONE listens to an iPod in one ear.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS349
She ends the call.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS350
SOMEONE takes a picture of himself in the bath, holding up the iPod, with a goofy grin, and sends it to SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS351
She grins at the picture on her phone.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS352
Now, men and women in conservative attire work in a stately two-story library.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS353
SOMEONE enters in her slim gray pantsuit, her hair pulled back into a bun.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS354
She gives a man standing guard a little nod, then heads further in.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS355
Nearing a giant statue in the center of the room, she spots a handsome African-American man reading.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS356
SOMEONE ducks into an alcove, then peers back out at him.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS357
In a flashback, she and SOMEONE hold out clipboards to passersby.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS358
Pressing her lips together, SOMEONE ducks back into the alcove.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS359
Moments later, she casually steps out, pretending to read a book.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS360
As she races for a seat with a good vantage of SOMEONE
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS361
an older gentleman takes it.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS362
SOMEONE gazes across the room at her ex, who sits engrossed in his work.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS363
As a woman leaves a seat across from the first,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS364
SOMEONE and a man both go for it.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS365
SOMEONE sets down her book and sits.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS366
Trying for a better look at SOMEONE,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS367
she leans back to peer around the statue.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS368
She grimaces, then faces the others at the large table.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS369
Later, they all hold the table under the lip and scoot it across the floor.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS370
SOMEONE looks past the statue at SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS371
As they set it down, a lamp falls off the edge.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS373
SOMEONE's jaw goes slack and she looks over at SOMEONE who grins at her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS374
Now in a hotel suite, SOMEONE wears a robe and gets candy from the minibar.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS375
She goes to the door.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS376
Her eyes widen at the sight of a man holding a gift box.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS377
SOMEONE hangs up.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS378
In a lobby, SOMEONE sips a drink.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS379
SOMEONE arrives in the gifted dress, clutching a purse to her chest.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS380
She shuffles forward in the skintight garment and lowers the purse.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS381
Her cleavage overflows.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS382
She links her arm in his.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS383
She fishes out her phone and turns it off.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS384
In Boston on the apartment roof,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS385
SOMEONE lowers his cell phone from his ear.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS386
He looks at it, then thoughtfully rubs it against his chin.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS387
Leaning his elbows on a railing, he looks out the city lights.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS389
At the Washington party, SOMEONE and SOMEONE step out into a hallway.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS390
He takes her hand and pulls her aside.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS391
He mimes penises in his mouth and ears.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS392
She forces a tight-lipped smile.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS393
Now, lit windows in the Boston skyline twinkle in the night sky.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS394
SOMEONE climbs the stairs to her apartment, still in her heels and tight dress.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS395
She gazes up at the landing and finds it empty.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS396
Behind her, a neighbor steps out of an apartment with his dog.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS398
She enters her dark apartment.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS400
She turns on the light at the foyer.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS403
SOMEONE turns on a spotlight, which shines over a group of SOMEONE sculptures.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS404
He lights up another across the room.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS406
Studying the highlighted urban scene, SOMEONE brighten
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS407
She looks over the first group of sculptures, which depicts a wedding party.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS409
He watches her cross the living room and approach the urban scene.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS415
The sculpture depicts a shabby old man.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS417
He heads off.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS418
Later, they eat pizza and drink beer.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS419
SOMEONE throws a crust at him.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS420
He hurries over to a keyboard and grabs an electric guitar.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS421
Still in her tight cocktail dress, SOMEONE dances around the couch and faces SOMEONE, wildly waving her arms overhead and kicking her feet.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS422
She plops on the couch.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS423
She grabs his hands and he helps her up.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS424
Now the near-full moon looms bright over a few
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS426
SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk down a dark corridor.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS427
He flips a switch, turning on a light and SOMEONE's jaw drops.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS428
They continue walking.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS429
She shoots a basket.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS430
He moves to her spot on the court.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS431
He takes a shot.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS432
He unties his shoe.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS433
She bounces the ball off the floor to the backboard and into the hoop.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS434
SOMEONE gives it a try, but misses.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS435
Taking off his socks, he nods.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS436
Tossing the ball backward, SOMEONE sinks another shot.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS437
SOMEONE gives her backward shot a try.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS438
Now, SOMEONE spins the ball on her fingertip. She sinks a shot while sitting on the floor.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS439
SOMEONE helps her up.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS440
Sitting on the floor, he kicks the ball.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS441
SOMEONE reaches to help him up, but pulls away.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS442
She sinks a three-pointer and her now shirtless friend retrieves the ball.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS443
SOMEONE shoots but misses the hoop.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS444
SOMEONE watches as he drops his jeans. Now wearing only boxers, SOMEONE loops the ball under his leg and makes a layup.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS445
Wearing her dress, SOMEONE struggles to match him.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS446
Her dress hits the floor. In her underwear, she returns with the ball.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS447
She throws him the ball. He returns it to her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS448
Now, SOMEONE dribbles around SOMEONE and sinks a layup.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS449
SOMEONE dribbles side to side. He tosses the ball in the net and SOMEONE catches it.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS450
She bounces the ball between his legs and runs around him. The ball drops in the hoop three times. SOMEONE holds her 	side, but SOMEONE pushes him down and takes a shot.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS451
He playfully keeps the ball away, then faces her, holding the ball behind her head.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS452
They share a sensual gaze.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS453
He sinks a shot and she pushes him.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS454
He makes a layup.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS455
A security guard marches down the corridor with a flashlight.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS456
He scans the empty arena, but finds only SOMEONE's red dress hanging from the hoop.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS457
Later at a marina, SOMEONE wears SOMEONE's button-down shirt.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS458
Following him, SOMEONE drops her high heels and loses the button-down shirt.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS459
They each strip out of their underwear, hurry to the edge of the dock, and
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS460
stand side by side.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS461
They share a gaze, then SOMEONE offers his hand, which SOMEONE accepts.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS462
Together, they leap into the water.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS463
They tread water within a circle of moonlight reflected on the rippling surface of the water, then swim for the dock.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS464
Later, they return to SOMEONE's apartment and SOMEONE shuts the door behind them.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS465
As they face each other, he looks into her eyes, then lowers his gaze.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS466
He unbuttons the shirt.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS467
He opens her shirt, looks at her naked body,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS468
then returns his gaze to her eyes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS470
They kiss, wrapping their arms around each other.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS471
She unbuckles his belt and he pulls her close.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS472
She backs into her bedroom and they fall on her bed.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS473
He lies beside her and she covers up a bit.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS474
He measures six inches with his hands.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS475
They share an affectionate gaze,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS476
then he kisses her again.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS477
The next morning, our view descends to the bed, where SOMEONE and SOMEONE sleep facing each other, her hand gently resting on his cheek.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS478
SOMEONE's eyes open gradually and she grows anxious.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS479
She removes her hand from his unshaven face,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS480
then rolls on her back and reaches for the brush on her nightstand.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS481
She looks at him.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS482
Smiling, she turns on her side.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS483
SOMEONE rolls on his back.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS484
He rests his hand on his knee, then pats the bed.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS485
She nods.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS486
She falls off the bed.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS487
She fills her purse with various items including one of two cell phones, then returns to the bed and gives SOMEONE a kiss goodbye.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS488
Later at a flower shop, SOMEONE stands alone with an open binder in her hand.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS489
Gazing thoughtfully,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS491
She notices SOMEONE walking by with a clipboard and returns her attention to the binder.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS493
Now in her apartment, SOMEONE sits at a table.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS494
Under a bright lamp, she painstakingly works on one of her sculptures.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS495
She picks up a cell phone and reads a string of text messages starting with SOMEONE's phone number.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS496
"You owe me big. Thanks. man. Hey SOMEONE, still no call. Did you pass on SOMEONE's number to Ally?"
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS500
He kisses her shoulder.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS501
He hops on the couch, then grabs a magazine from a coffee table and starts to read.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS502
She drops the cell phone on him and walks out.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS503
SOMEONE puts his hands on his hips and hangs his head.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS504
At the kitchen sink, SOMEONE turns on the faucet.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS505
She leaves the room.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS506
SOMEONE nods.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS507
He storms out of her apartment and heads across the hall.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS508
SOMEONE slams his
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS509
door, then SOMEONE does the same.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS510
Now, indigo clouds drift across the sky as a low sun peeks over the horizon.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS511
In her apartment,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS512
SOMEONE paints a sculpture of a bride and groom standing at a wedding,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS513
bearing a resemblance to SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS514
The bride grins as she mashes
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS515
the cake into her husband
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS516
SOMEONE pauses and shifts her gaze.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS518
He uses her cell phone.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS525
Now, a magazine clipping features a model with a poufy updo.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS526
At a dressing table, SOMEONE faces a mirror as she backcombs her hair.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS527
In a closet, our view sweeps over a selection of expensive men's clothes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS528
A hand pulls a suit jacket from a rack.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS529
At Ally's, another magazine photo shows a sleek ponytail.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS530
Facing her mirror, the young woman copies the hairstyle.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS531
She checks her profile and gives a dissatisfied SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS532
SOMEONE picks up a blonde hair extension and brushes it out.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS533
Later, she smiles at the reflection of her long smooth ponytail and flounces it against her back.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS534
Grabbing a can of aerosol hairspray, she sweeps it in broad circles around her head, both clockwise and counter-clockwise.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS535
In a rich man's closet, a hand pulls out a small drawer displaying a selection of expensive watches.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS536
He picks one with a gold face.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS537
Scrutinizing her reflection, SOMEONE tucks a price tag into the back of her slinky black dress.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS538
Now at an upscale restaurant, a fountain stands amid softly lit tables.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS539
SOMEONE sits alone at one of them, nibbling on a dinner roll.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS540
At the table behind her, a waiter presents a dish flambé.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS541
SOMEONE turns and her eyes widen as a well-dressed square-jawed man saunters in.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS542
He pauses to greet acquaintances, then spots her. SOMEONE grins and waves.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS543
The fountain's jets of water blast upward as he approaches. Behind her, the flambé flares.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS544
As he approaches in slow motion, SOMEONE nervously stands.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS545
SOMEONE pauses and turns to greet an acquaintance.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS546
SOMEONE frowns, sniffing the air, and looks around. Her ponytail is on fire.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS547
As smoke wafts around her face, her eyes dart quizzically.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS548
She reaches back and pulls off the hairpiece.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS549
She throws it into the fountain.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS550
SOMEONE joins her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS561
SOMEONE beams.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS563
She strides briskly into a restaurant, where her sister smiles sheepishly at her from a table set for four.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS564
A middle-aged man enters with a young woman.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS565
He holds a Smartphone.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS566
He kisses Jacinda.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS567
Now at their mother's house.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS568
The sisters go inside.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS569
They find her in the living room.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS570
She shows a photo of SOMEONE and SOMEONE as teenagers.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS571
She crosses her finger
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS572
SOMEONE grins at her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS573
SOMEONE looks back and forth between them, working her mouth.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS574
She caresses their faces.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS575
Now a couple runs through tall grass overlooking a beach. Tumbling down beside SOMEONE and SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE make out.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS576
SOMEONE smiles at SOMEONE, then glances uncomfortably at the couple.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS577
Now he and SOMEONE enjoy a date in formal wear.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS578
Later at a formal event,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS579
SOMEONE smiles sheepishly SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS580
She takes a bite.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS581
SOMEONE takes two flutes of champagne from a tray.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS582
Now from outside her apartment, we see her meandering to the window in a plaid shirt.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS583
She sighs as she gazes out pensively.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS584
Our view drifts up the side of the building to the roof
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS585
where we find SOMEONE standing alone.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS586
He stares off,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS587
one hand in his pocket and the other holding a bottle of beer.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS588
Turning away from the view,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS589
he takes a sip and sits on the couch.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS590
SOMEONE takes up his guitar,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS591
removes the pick from the fret board, and plays.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS592
Now SOMEONE's apartment door opens and she steps out carrying a white garment bag.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS593
SOMEONE leaves his apartment in a suit.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS594
Seeing her, he halts.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS595
SOMEONE spots him and hesitates,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS596
then affects a breezy smile.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS597
He heads off.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS598
SOMEONE stops halfway down a flight of stairs.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS599
As he continues down, SOMEONE starts to speak, then stops herself.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS600
She works her mouth, then leans over the banister.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS601
He continues down without looking up.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS602
SOMEONE gazes after him remorsefully.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS603
Now we drift over trees to find an immaculately kept lawn set up for a wedding.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS604
Our view sweeps over the verdant estate to an upper window in SOMEONE's mother's house.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS605
As we drift closer, it offers a glimpse of the bridal party's preparations.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS606
Inside, frantic bridesmaids run amok, while SOMEONE's mother struggles to zip up the bridal gown.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS607
A man with an earpiece arrives.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS608
SOMEONE closes SOMEONE's dress.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS609
SOMEONE pops up from behind a sofa with a Croissan'wich.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS610
SOMEONE grabs it and takes a grateful bite.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS611
Now on the arm of a groomsman, SOMEONE leads the bridal procession down a grassy aisle.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS612
She grins girlishly at SOMEONE, who smiles from his seat among the guests.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS613
Nearby, SOMEONE's father aims his cell phone camera.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS614
The wedding planner plays a tuba.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS615
The guests stand as SOMEONE's mother walks her down the aisle.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS616
The bridal veil catches in a flower arrangement and a guest helps them untangle it.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS617
The bride and groom smile at the officiant, then face each other lovingly, and hold each other's hands.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS618
The beaming bride and groom envelope each other in a passionate kiss, as the guests and bridesmaids cheer 	joyfully.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS619
As the couple lingers in their momentous embrace, SOMEONE sniffles and blinks back tears.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS620
Turning away from SOMEONE, SOMEONE grabs her in a sisterly embrace.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS621
The other bridesmaids quickly join in, making it a group hug as the sisters' father snaps a photo.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS622
Now on a lawn set with tables for an outdoor reception, the wedding guests dance on a large elevated dance floor constructed in the style of a gazebo.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS623
SOMEONE swivels her hips, her back to a groomsman as a live band provides the music.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS624
Amidst the crowd, SOMEONE dances with her father.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS626
He snaps a photo of himself with SOMEONE. Nearby, SOMEONE's mother dances with SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS627
As her mother uninhibitedly jumps up and down, SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE an uneasy glance.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS628
Their expressions grow pensive and they both face the stage.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS629
As Mr. Darling pulls SOMEONE into a fatherly embrace and slow dances with her, SOMEONE works his way over to them.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS630
The father looks from him to SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS631
Mr. Darling gazes wistfully after his daughter.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS632
He plants his lips tenderly on hers.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS633
As they linger in the kiss, SOMEONE's eyes open and shift uncertainly.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS634
Looking on, her mother gives an approving wink and nod.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS635
He leads her from the dance floor.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS636
Nearby, SOMEONE drapes her arms around the shoulders of two groomsmen.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS637
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS638
The wedding planner approaches.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS639
Leaving SOMEONE, SOMEONE follows him across the dance floor.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS640
The wedding planner reaches the stage and gestures furiously at the band.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS641
SOMEONE's mother beckons SOMEONE and kisses his cheek.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS642
The bride beams and her husband tenderly kisses her bare shoulder.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS643
SOMEONE smiles fondly.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS644
SOMEONE bites her lip and her gaze drifts to SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS645
He stands stiffly by her mother,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS646
his lips pressed into a tight smile.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS647
Scanning the crowd, SOMEONE catches sight of her father,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS648
who raises his glass and gives a gentle encouraging nod.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS649
The newlyweds share a joyful kiss. SOMEONE steps forward to meet SOMEONE as she approaches.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS650
She leads him away. On the dance floor, Jacinda dances gracefully with Mr. Darling, who hops around with goofy uninhibited moves.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS651
SOMEONE wedges between the bride and groom, making SOMEONE spill his champagne.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS652
In a guestroom.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS653
SOMEONE takes a seat beside SOMEONE on a single bed.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS654
She glances aside, then lowers her thoughtful gaze.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS655
She purses her lips.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS656
As our view drifts toward her face,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS657
she sits up with a resilient look in her eyes.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS658
Outside, SOMEONE chats with her groom.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS659
SOMEONE joins her mother.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS660
He knocks a glass off a tray.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS661
SOMEONE joins them.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS666
She and SOMEONE share a smile.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS667
SOMEONE embraces her sister.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS669
The bridesmaids gather around SOMEONE for a group hug. The wedding planner confronts a server.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS672
SOMEONE takes the list, then dashes around a few tables, and starts across the lawn. She falls flat on her face, catching everyone's attention.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS673
Getting back up, she tears some gauzy fabric from her pink dress.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS677
She hikes up the skirt.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS679
In slow motion, she runs across the lawn in her high heels.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS680
She sprints past a pond, then heads out through the open gate of a white-picket fence.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS681
At a valet station, she finds the keys of several parked cars.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS682
She grabs a set.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS683
Two lounging valets wave goodbye.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS684
SOMEONE pulls out in a little blue hatchback.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS685
As she drives off, our view rises to glimpse the reception tent across the pond.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS686
Later, the hatchback speeds over to a crowd gathered outside a building.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS689
A photographer takes pictures of a bride and groom. SOMEONE jumps out of her car.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS690
She hurries through the crowd.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS693
A photo shows the smiling wedding party. Two more show SOMEONE standing among them.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS694
The hatchback peels out.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS695
Driving, SOMEONE crosses a third wedding off her list.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS696
Now she runs up the front steps of a church, holding her poufy dress above her ankles.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS697
She hurries inside, to a tall set of wooden doors, and frantically scans the pews.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS698
The doors swing shut behind her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS700
The bride and groom are SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS701
He lays eyes on SOMEONE.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS702
The confused guests watch her run back out through the doors.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS703
Driving again, she violently crosses another wedding off her list.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS704
She cruises across a truss bridge.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS705
At night, a crowd holds a bride and groom up over their shoulders, obstructing a city street.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS706
The hatchback arrives and gets stuck behind traffic.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS707
SOMEONE gets out and runs through the stopped vehicles, then works her way through the lively crowd.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS710
She waves to the bride as she dances her way to the front of the parade, then spots a pizza delivery man's bicycle 	propped against a brick wall, and steals it.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS712
Now, strands of lights adorn a fancy outdoor reception.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS713
Cameras flash as the paparazzi clamors for shots of a couple arriving on a red carpet.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS714
SOMEONE rides up and leaves the pizza-delivery bike with a valet.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS716
She runs past the paparazzi.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS717
At the end of the red carpet, a security guard blocks her path.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS719
As she peers over his shoulder looking for SOMEONE, a second guard approaches.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS720
SOMEONE deflates.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS721
Spotting SOMEONE onstage with his band, SOMEONE beams.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS722
She runs back up the red carpet.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS724
SOMEONE climbs a trellis fence, peeks overtop, and spots the security guards.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS728
Halfway over the fence, her dress gets caught.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS731
The dress tears as she falls into some shrubbery.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS732
Children watch her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS734
SOMEONE runs forward, but finds her path blocked by the crowded dance floor. She waves her arms, trying to catch SOMEONE's attention.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS737
She pops up beside the stage. SOMEONE joins the band, playing a tambourine, but SOMEONE fails to notice her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS738
She pushes a bass player out of the way and sings into a microphone.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS739
SOMEONE sees her.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS740
He tries to wave her off the stage, but she turns to his band. She grabs his microphone.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS742
She takes SOMEONE's hand and leads him off the stage.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS743
As they walk over toward a fountain, four little girls run past.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS745
As she gazes into his eyes, her glossy lips curl into a tight smile.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS746
SOMEONE stares back at her fondly.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS747
She covers his mouth with her hand and shakes her head.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS748
SOMEONE leans in and gives her a kiss.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS750
Behind them, several boys run out to watch, while the wedding guests raise their glasses to the bride and groom.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS752
As the kiss continues, SOMEONE cradles SOMEONE's neck and grabs his shoulder.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS753
Our view pulls back from the couple to reveal more of their romantic surroundings. The four-pillared fountain cascades into a circular pool, under a plethora of globe lights dangling from the surrounding tree branches.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS755
In SOMEONE's apartment, a Mexican wrestling match plays on TV.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS756
Across the room, SOMEONE and SOMEONE lie in bed, smooching.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS757
SOMEONE gets up and jumps on the bed.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS761
We draw back through a window to the building's beige-brick facade.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS762
Our view continues to retract over a neighboring rooftop, until it encompasses several city blocks worth of apartment buildings.
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS763
Beyond the quaint urban neighborhood,
WHATS_YOUR_NUMBER_DVS764
skyscrapers rise from the heart of the city.