Now, a title appears.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS17
Boston. Zacum Bridge at sunrise.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS18
In a residential neighborhood. Words appear, 5 Years Later. SOMEONE steps on to the porch of a modest three-story.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS19
Now, at a junk yard. SOMEONE buys a waist-high tire.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS21
Is guarding a grand entryway. Arched ironwork above reads "Park Zoo".
ZOOKEEPER_DVS22
Now, SOMEONE drives a golf cart with the tire in back.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS23
Habitat enclosure. SOMEONE lowers a drawbridge over a moat and walks over to it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS24
He takes the monkey's hand.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS25
Who wears a patch over one eye.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS28
Worker dumps his bucket of lettuce over a waist-high wall and into the pit.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS29
He unlocks a door which opens at the pit's floor level.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS30
He rolls the tire into a barren habitat. A single shaft of sunlight shines down from the pit's high opening into the otherwise stark enclosure where a gorilla sits with its back to the door. SOMEONE hangs the tire from a rope on a tree.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS32
He Stands then stumbles back over.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS35
Later, in a lab, a willowy, SOMEONE. Long haired woman places an eagle in a cage. She sees SOMEONE standing at a dry erase board labeled Things to do.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS36
He writes, Fix SOMEONE's tree.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS40
A heart monitor shows a flat line.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS42
He opens a drawer and rifles through it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS44
He gets his hand down the lioness’s throat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS45
SOMEONE pulls out a crushed Red Bull can.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS46
That night, a banner hanging over a party over the zoo reads, Congratulations.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS49
His hand and pulls her into a tight embrace. Her eyes widen.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS50
He gives a serious look. SOMEONE smiles politely.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS54
In the icy stand behind him. Scanning the crowd, SOMEONE spots SOMEONE. In his perspective, she appears to pull away from the others around her.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS55
SOMEONE's lips twitch.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS57
Venom cringes while Frankie hits play on a boom box.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS58
SOMEONE strides over to SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS59
He catches SOMEONE eyeing SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS60
Meanwhile, by the giraffe's enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS61
He perks up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS62
SOMEONE, the Monkey watches them chat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS63
Holding the porcupine, SOMEONE turns away. He yanks the quill out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS68
SOMEONE flinches. Smiling, she dabs his cheek. He stares at her with lovelorn eyes. She returns a tender look. SOMEONE, the Monkey watches.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS69
She gives a flirty smile.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS71
She leaves. As SOMEONE stares after her, Floyd shoots a quill into his forehead. SOMEONE chuckles.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS72
SOMEONE winces and grits his teeth. He pulls out the quill.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS76
A net swings from a horizontal arm at its top. The monkey leaps onto it, climbs down the pole and lands in SOMEONE's enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS77
SOMEONE creeps past a man-made waterfall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS78
The panel on it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS79
Swinging it open, he finds a power box inside and
ZOOKEEPER_DVS80
He flips a switch. A dog is licking himself.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS81
on just his hind legs, SOMEONE scurries down a path to a set of heavy iron double doors. He climbs up to the keyhole, glances around, then picks the lock.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS82
Tilts and the doors swing open.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS83
She stretches her neck into another enclosure where the rest of the animals gather at the base of a rock ledge. A lion steps out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS84
He eyes.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS85
The next day, SOMEONE peers into SOMEONE's pit to find SOMEONE hanging a giant whiffle ball from the tree.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS86
He spins it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS87
With a smile, SOMEONE heads away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS88
SOMEONE keeps his back to him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS89
Later, with the giraffe.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS92
SOMEONE gnaws on a carrot as he watches SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk away. The giraffe licks it and he spits it out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS93
She walks away from him and looks at the monkey.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS94
SOMEONE gives a thumbs up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS97
A wire basket drops from his hand.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS98
Flailing his arms. The giraffe looks on.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS99
He drops into the rock ledge and lands on his back.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS100
SOMEONE and SOMEONE board the golf cart. SOMEONE peeks over the rock ledge and watches SOMEONE struggle to his feet.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS101
Lion steps away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS104
His house and shuts the door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS105
Through his window blinds. On TV
ZOOKEEPER_DVS106
Teenage witch listens to her talking cat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS107
The next morning at the zoo, SOMEONE peeks into the lion enclosure and finds SOMEONE lying on his haunches. The zookeeper awkwardly steps out and faces the indifferent lion. Keeping his eyes on the animal, he walks backward out of view again. Now, three kids stand at the lion enclosure. SOMEONE sets down a wheelbarrow, glances around then cautiously approaches. He watches SOMEONE lounge on some rocks. The kids head off.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS108
SOMEONE stares at the indifferent lion.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS109
A couple passes by.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS110
The lion while SOMEONE sweeps the sidewalk behind them. He mouths to SOMEONE, What's up?
ZOOKEEPER_DVS111
Later, a security guard rides a cart.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS113
Exiting through a gate, he finds SOMEONE the Lion waiting for him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS114
Feet and falls on his back. The lion sighs.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS115
SOMEONE lies unconscious under a few swaying elephant toys.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS118
SOMEONE licks his own armpit.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS120
In his pit, SOMEONE the Gorilla glances up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS121
He turns away sadly. On another day, patrons walk around the zoo. SOMEONE enters the gorilla enclosure with a bucket and shuts the door behind him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS122
SOMEONE sits with his back to him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS123
The somber gorilla sniffs the air.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS125
SOMEONE gives no response.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS126
SOMEONE ambles off with a bucket still in hand. The gorilla shifts his gaze.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS127
SOMEONE brightens and glances over his shoulder. The gorilla rocks back and forth as the zookeeper sets the bucket down and exits.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS128
Now, a boy chucks popcorn at the bears from behind a fence.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS130
The boy lands in the enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS131
He notices the two brown bears eyeing him hungrily.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS132
He jumps out of his golf cart. He runs halfway up a staircase.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS133
Standing on their hind legs, the bears swap a look.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS134
He walks the boy through a door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS135
SOMEONE shuts the door, makes sure no one's watching, then approaches the bears.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS136
He walks for them.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS137
SOMEONE lifts his hands.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS138
SOMEONE walks crotch first.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS139
SOMEONE notices the students watching him. SOMEONE stands among them.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS140
He briskly retreats. As the kids disperse, SOMEONE's concerned gaze lingers on her colleague.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS141
In SOMEONE's pit, SOMEONE slides over a bowl of popcorn for the approaching gorilla.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS142
Shane enters through the metal door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS143
He squints at SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS144
Shane glances around then points at the gorilla.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS145
He exits and slides the metal door shut.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS149
SOMEONE turns to leave.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS150
With the wolf.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS153
He pees on a pole.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS154
He faces the pole.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS155
SOMEONE shrugs.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS156
Crosses to a tree.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS157
The wolf crosses to a nearby fence, averting his gaze.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS158
People walk by behind the fence.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS159
The women quickly look away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS160
SOMEONE zips up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS161
The wolf lifts his paw.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS162
He limps around SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS164
SOMEONE and SOMEONE turn their backs. SOMEONE looks at the wolf.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS165
He mouths the word sorry.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS167
Shampoos the wolf's coat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS168
Now, a jazz trio performs at a fancy restaurant. SOMEONE finishes urinating on a potted plant adorned with mini lights.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS169
SOMEONE taps him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS170
Joins SOMEONE at the bar.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS172
As a guy approaches from behind.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS173
SOMEONE heads off.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS174
SOMEONE turns back to SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS176
He furrows his brow as he considers.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS177
SOMEONE sulks off.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS178
Later, at the zoo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS180
Sweeps past SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS181
SOMEONE looks from the giraffe to SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS182
He stands.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS184
He gives a desperate look. Now, SOMEONE pumps his legs as he pedals a recumbent tricycle up a hill. An orange flag waves.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS185
Semi’s trailer.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS186
Face plants on the cement.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS190
As she rides off, SOMEONE screeches to a halt.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS191
He pretends to shoot an arrow.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS192
SOMEONE gives him a baffled frown. SOMEONE mounts his bike then rides away throwing SOMEONE a final glance. Nighttime in the lion enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS194
SOMEONE's eyes narrow.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS195
SOMEONE turns away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS196
SOMEONE nods at the lioness and heads off. Now, as SOMEONE eats her lunch, SOMEONE stands at her desk.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS201
Gorilla stops playing with his swinging ball and turns to find
ZOOKEEPER_DVS202
SOMEONE peering inside.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS203
He enters holding a two-tiered orange cake with lit candles.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS204
Watches with a disbelief.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS205
He starts to turn away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS206
Nighttime. SOMEONE leads SOMEONE up a staircase which emerges by the mouth of the pit.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS207
They bump fists.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS208
SOMEONE heads to a van in a maintenance lot. SOMEONE follows, now wearing a yellow polo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS211
Lights of downtown skyscrapers. SOMEONE points out the illuminated clock on the Custom House Tower.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS212
His head out his window and watches the city whizz past.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS213
SOMEONE bobs his head while SOMEONE holds his hand out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS214
With the music, SOMEONE pushes his door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS216
Grinning, the zookeeper climbs out. He hurries beside SOMEONE who gallops excitedly towards.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS217
Inside, a waitress approaches their booth.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS218
Eyes widen at SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS219
He eyes his polo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS220
The waitress stares at SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS221
SOMEONE closes his menu.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS222
Frowning, the waitress leaves.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS223
Returns from his game of pool and finds SOMEONE slow dancing with a blonde secretary in his arms.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS224
She smiles dreamily and SOMEONE gives SOMEONE a thumbs up. The zookeeper smiles.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS225
The two friends lie side by side on the roof of the van and gaze up at the glowing full moon.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS227
His grin morphs into a frown and he furrows his brow.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS229
Morning. At the zoo, a frog leaps off a ledge.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS231
Puffs out his throat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS232
He bows his head.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS234
At the reptile enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS236
SOMEONE sees an eyeball drawn on Frankie's eye patch.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS237
Venom steps a little closer to SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS238
SOMEONE glances down.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS239
The frowning zookeeper hesitates.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS240
He reaches into Venom's left pants pocket and digs around. SOMEONE shoots his colleague an uncomfortable smile.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS241
The zookeeper reaches into his right pocket. He pulls out the keys.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS246
Nodding along to the beat, he looks to an apartment building.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS247
A woman's shapely legs head down the front steps.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS248
He shifts his eyes pensively.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS249
Wedding reception. Acrobats twirl from long swathes of.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS250
Pictures of the bride and groom.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS251
SOMEONE some champagne.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS252
He spots SOMEONE with SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS256
SOMEONE holds out her open palm.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS257
SOMEONE puts his hand in hers. She places.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS259
Watches them move to the bar.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS260
As SOMEONE's eyes meet his, he quickly looks away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS261
SOMEONE holds a microphone.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS262
To the DJ. SOMEONE briefly hides her face then dramatically gets up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS263
SOMEONE mouths along to the lyrics as the couple starts dancing.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS264
SOMEONE and SOMEONE square off from across the dancefloor.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS265
SOMEONE tries with SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS267
Return to their table.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS268
SOMEONE looks around the ballroom. SOMEONE slouches defeatedly.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS269
She moves off and waves her arms at the DJ on a balcony, then returns to her date.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS270
She takes SOMEONE's arm and leads him to the dancefloor.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS272
SOMEONE grabs two of the hanging silk drapes.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS273
And over one of his shoulders.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS274
Playful smile, she grabs her own pair of drapes.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS276
Then twirls in front of him trying.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS277
Get SOMEONE's gorgeous.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS278
He starts to sway a little.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS279
Off her feet and swings.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS280
He were on a swing.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS281
The other woman at SOMEONE's table turns to watch as well.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS282
Spins around, but she swings over SOMEONE again.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS283
As they move apart, we see SOMEONE watching.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS284
SOMEONE turns to the woman at her table.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS286
He frowns to himself as the groom walks off. SOMEONE comes over and pulls up a chair.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS287
SOMEONE blinks for a moment then sets his chunk of ice on the table.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS288
He gets up from his seat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS289
SOMEONE stares at him aggressively. SOMEONE purses his lips and puffs out his cheeks.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS290
And his pants split.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS291
SOMEONE walks off.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS292
SOMEONE hangs up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS293
Her eyes widen as she swallows some food.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS294
Moving his arms like a robot, he clanks a fork and knife together.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS295
Stabs the steak off SOMEONE's plate.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS296
He points across the ballroom then squints.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS297
Meanwhile, a bartender hands SOMEONE two drinks.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS298
Spots him and heads over. The two rivals.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS299
SOMEONE leans on the bar with a cocky smirk.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS300
He unflinchingly stares down his rival.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS301
SOMEONE leaves him alone. SOMEONE brings cake.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS302
He flails his arms.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS303
As he leaves, SOMEONE puts down the two slices of cake and self-consciously hides her thumb.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS304
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS305
A valet brings them the Mustang and they get in.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS306
His pretty colleague beams.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS307
Finding SOMEONE outside, he rolls down his window.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS308
As he rolls his window back up, SOMEONE frowns slightly. Staring straight ahead, SOMEONE remains motionless in his seat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS309
SOMEONE exits the car.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS310
She holds the door for Griffins ex who climbs in with him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS311
SOMEONE looks up at SOMEONE who nods.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS312
SOMEONE pouts.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS313
She perks up.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS314
At the fashion show, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE towards a man.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS315
hair, who holds a Chinese crested.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS316
SOMEONE leans towards her.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS317
SOMEONE's brow creases.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS318
Eyeing SOMEONE, he rests his lips on his fists as if thinking.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS319
SOMEONE watches anxiously.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS320
They ride in the back of a limo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS321
SOMEONE frowns.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS323
As SOMEONE stares with crestfallen eyes, SOMEONE leans.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS324
He gives a dazed look.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS325
Blinking, he turns away from her. The corner of his mouth lifts into an.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS327
Tosses Glen the keys.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS328
Holsters his invisible guns. As a middle-aged man exams a sports car.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS329
Keeper stares with predatory eyes.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS330
And exchange a glance.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS331
SOMEONE faces the customer.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS332
SOMEONE hits his head on the car's raised scissor door as he tries to climb inside. He hits his rear on the horn as he attempts to back into the seat.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS333
Then finally slides his body.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS334
Now, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE standing outside the new eagle enclosure.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS335
She looks in a cage.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS336
An eagle flies out and perches beside another eagle.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS338
Frowning, SOMEONE shifts her gaze to the eagles.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS339
She scowls at him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS340
She meets his gaze.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS341
Bowing his head, SOMEONE shakes it. As SOMEONE watches expectantly, he lifts his eyes to hers and nods.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS342
Her shoulders sag and she gives a disappointed look.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS343
With a resigned smile, she leans against the railing around the eagle enclosure's glass observation wall and stares out at the birds. SOMEONE blinks at her, his lips parted in a discouraged expression, then glances at the eagles. As he walks off, SOMEONE watches with heartbroken eyes.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS344
Later, SOMEONE slides open the door to SOMEONE's enclosure and peers inside. He enters with a box of popcorn in one hand.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS345
With his back to the former zookeeper, SOMEONE sits facing the enclosure's far wall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS346
SOMEONE checks his phone's caller ID.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS347
SOMEONE drops his pained gaze then returns it to SOMEONE who looks away. Shrugging his hands, the former zookeeper opens his mouth to speak then licks his lips and takes a step toward the door. He shoots the gorilla a final glance then leaves. Stepping into the corridor, he slides the door closed and starts.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS349
He strides over to him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS350
Shane shifts his weight.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS351
Under SOMEONE's firm gaze, Shane swallows hard then nods. He returns a can of pepper spray to its holder on a.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS353
Pushing the Ferrari's passenger seat forward, he indicates the trunk. His gray-haired customer gives an uncertain look. SOMEONE's smirk fades as a bus pauses on the street outside. It bears an.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS354
which reads, The eagles have landed.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS355
Now, at the zoo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS357
Now, Venom holds two lizards as he approaches SOMEONE who stares into SOMEONE's pit.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS358
SOMEONE overhears and frowns.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS359
Venom gazes at her.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS360
Closing his eyes, he puckers his lips and leans toward her. As he draws closer, he opens his mouth.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS361
Later, SOMEONE enters a luxury condo and finds SOMEONE doing yoga.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS362
She beams at three balls in a row.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS363
SOMEONE sits on the middle ball.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS367
SOMEONE faces a floor-to-ceiling window and gazes out at the city. With a dispirited look, he trudges out of the living room. Now.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS368
Door to SOMEONE's enclosure unlocks and the gorilla.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS369
Hopeful eyes. He watches as it slides open and.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS370
Nail tipped stick. SOMEONE turns his back to the goateed zookeeper.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS371
Stepping closer, Shane rests his stick on his shoulder.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS372
He reaches into a pants pocket and withdraws an apple.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS373
He takes a bite then hurls it against the far wall. Apple chunks explode over SOMEONE's head.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS374
Pepper spray. At the dealership, a salesman talks to his colleague.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS375
The salesman's head swivel toward the customer. SOMEONE and Nimer exchange a look then both.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS376
He heads to the door as Nimer greets the high roller.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS377
SOMEONE stands by the door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS379
She opens a velvet box.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS380
Dropping to one knee, SOMEONE falters then straightens.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS381
As SOMEONE stares, a mariachi band enters.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS382
As she leaves the dealership, the band follows. Now SOMEONE sits in his enclosure with his back to the door.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS383
He sniffs the air, his nostrils twitching.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS384
Turning, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE back in a zookeeper’s uniform. He smiles and SOMEONE gives a nod.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS385
The crow lands on the pit wall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS386
SOMEONE runs off.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS387
SOMEONE takes flight.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS388
In a parking lot, SOMEONE the Gorilla crosses to a van and open.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS389
SOMEONE stands behind a fence.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS390
Runs around to the passenger side.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS391
Rolls out, heads into the road and drives straight into the side of a parked.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS392
The van doors open and SOMEONE and SOMEONE step out to switch places. Manny unlocks the.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS393
The gorilla pulls the.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS394
Later, it cruises down a residential street.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS395
The van stops short.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS396
Right past her, he heads upstairs and.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS397
Shane gets up from a computer in his underwear.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS398
Wall which crumbles around him. SOMEONE marches out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS400
Steering wheel turning sharply around a bend.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS401
The road at the scene of an accident.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS402
Apartment buildings. It dead ends in a 15 foot wall. The van.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS403
To a stop and SOMEONE clambers out on all fours. He follows SOMEONE over to the wall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS404
The zookeeper and the gorilla swap a look.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS405
Now, SOMEONE flies over the wall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS406
Meanwhile, SOMEONE steps out of her apartment.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS408
It rounds a corner.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS409
As it drives away.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS410
SOMEONE holds a kayak over his head. He toss.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS411
As the taxi drives alongside the river, SOMEONE and SOMEONE row after it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS413
Support beams to find the kayak arriving below.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS414
Lifts the portly zookeeper up with one arm.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS415
They move for the support beam.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS416
He clings to SOMEONE's back as the gorilla climbs the beam which angles nearly 45 degrees outward. SOMEONE glances around.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS418
SOMEONE reaches back and pulls.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS419
Of a spotlight and rises to his feet with the zoo.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS420
SOMEONE keeps climbing. Our view retracts.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS421
Bridge as they continue up the beam which now slants.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS422
Taxi inches along.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS423
The gorilla dangles above it.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS424
To the road. SOMEONE gasps as he pulls himself up on the hood of her cab. She gets out.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS425
She kisses SOMEONE then wraps her arms around his neck and kisses him again. Our view circles the embracing couple.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS426
In their cars.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS427
Gorilla then glances upward.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS429
Words appear, Six months later.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS430
View of the entire zoo and the.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS431
SOMEONE steps up beside him. SOMEONE blinks emotionally then.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS432
Standing on a tall mound of boulders.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS433
Gentle waterfall.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS434
Smile with SOMEONE.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS435
SOMEONE wraps his arm around him.
ZOOKEEPER_DVS437
A small screen shows the animals singing along with the music.