To a walk then stops. Altogether, his face dripping with sweat.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS23
Later, SOMEONE turns to two younger Marines hanging out by the car next to his. One raises his sports drink in a toast. SOMEONE takes a bag of ice from a cooler, raises it in reply, then holds the ice to his knee. A balding Marine, SOMEONE's age ices his neck.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS25
SOMEONE holds up a document.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS26
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE's signed request.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS27
SOMEONE's stares stoically.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS28
SOMEONE gazes at him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS29
SOMEONE's eyes flicker to his friend's face.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS30
SOMEONE gives him a kind look, then adds his signature to the form. He closes it inside a service record folder and sets it in front of SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS31
Avoiding SOMEONE's gaze, SOMEONE stares downward with a wistful smirk. He nods. With a glance at his friend, SOMEONE reaches for his file and eyes it, his chest heaves.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS32
Now, an American flag flutters beside an air traffic control tower. With his eyes fixed on it, SOMEONE salutes then mutters silent words. He lowers his pained gaze. In a flower shop, a TV shows a cluster of bright splotches in space, their size and intensity greater than the stars behind them.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS33
The mustached trooper, SOMEONE watches with the bald, black Marine in thick-rimmed glasses. SOMEONE sniffs a white carnation.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS35
A woman joins SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS36
SOMEONE's fiancée caresses his neck and ear.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS37
They kiss. SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS39
In a rec room, the African-American Marine Skypes with the young woman.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS40
He punches SOEMONE's arm, then notices the man's hardened stare.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS41
The lanky Marine, SOMEONE grins.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS42
Now, one smooth shaving Marine sits in a psychiatrist's office.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS43
His leg jiggling, he points to a bowl of pastel mints.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS44
The Marine reaches for the bowl.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS45
He withdraws his hand and the doctor smiles.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS46
SOMEONE moves his head.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS47
SOMEONE rumples his lips.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS48
He taps his finger.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS49
The doctor glances at him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS50
He writes notes in the Marine's medical file.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS51
SOMEONE gives a frustrated look.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS52
Rising, SOMEONE takes a handful of the mints. Now, the mocha-skinned Marine holds a golf club as he stands at a gravestone, Cpl. J. SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS53
He lifts the club.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS54
Shifting his gaze, he blinks in the sunlight.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS55
Crouching, he kisses his hand, touches the gravestone, then strolls away.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS56
Night time.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS57
SOMEONE in a golf course with a group of Marines.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS58
Girls approach.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS59
And whispers to another, who grins.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS60
SOMEONE's companion gives an impressed smile.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS61
The boyish Marine swigs a beer.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS63
Its tailgate, the boyish lend a hand and leans forward.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS65
Gold bar she holds in her fingers. Her husband wakes up.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS66
Later, he pins a gold bar to each of his collar flaps.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS68
Stopping at the front door, SOMEONE turns and kisses his wife's pregnant belly.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS69
Now, Marines ride inside a truck following a Humvee across sandy terrain.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS70
Camp Pendleton, Training Grounds.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS71
On foot, He halts. Spotting the Humvee and two transport trucks. He heads down the hill.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS72
Hustling two by two, 20 plus Marines follow the staff sergeant.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS73
They halt on SOMEONE's hand signal. Two men hop out of the vehicles.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS75
Into to the trucks, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS76
They glance skyward.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS77
SOMEONE heads off.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS78
He looks back.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS79
Then shifts his uneasy gaze. Now in a hallway, SOMEONE walks with SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS80
SOMEONE faces the lieutenant.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS81
In the Humvee, SOMEONE rides in the passenger seat while SOMEONE drives.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS82
They cross an airfield.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS83
SOMEONE chuckles and shakes his head. He glances at SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS84
SOMEONE greets SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS87
Bedroom where SOMEONE packs up.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS89
He enters in the next room.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS90
SOMEONE shoos SOMEONE away.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS92
SOMEONE interrupts SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS93
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE walk a hall.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS94
A CNN report.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS95
The Asian Marine chats up Guerrero.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS99
Now units attend a briefing.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS100
SOMEONE and SOMEONE swap a look.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS101
A slide show.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS102
SOMEONE glowers.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS104
The Marines grab their helmets.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS105
A newswoman reports from Santa SOMEONE beach.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS106
Among the troops, SOMEONE watches the news.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS107
Rolled ship, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS108
On screen, a dissipating wave reveals dozens of aliens.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS111
In Camp Pendleton Air Station, California, Marines hustle to waiting helicopter.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS112
SOMEONE shoots his head at Guerrero.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS113
SOMEONE addresses his men.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS114
Blocking Guerrero, on SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS115
Then Marines try to cross the airfield in single file.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS117
Men file aboard.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS119
SOMEONE lingers near SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS123
Stuffing a dog tag under his boot lace.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS124
The uneasy rookie looks at a Marine to his left. SOMEONE chews a golf tee while reading a Bible.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS125
Now it reads, "Through Christ Comes Freedom. "
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS126
Guerrero calls to SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS127
Guerrero averts his gaze. SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE, who shares a tense look with SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS128
Writing a letter, SOMEONE wipes his brow with his thumb. With a black pen he writes, "My dearest wife. "
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS129
Finishing, he folds the page and puts it away.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS130
The nervous lieutenant licks his lips then spots SOMEONE eyeing him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS131
SOMEONE wipes his face. Descending behind the oncoming helicopters.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS133
Over three fading signatures, well in process. SOMEONE gapes, watching with SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS135
It shows craters and burning wreckage. A high aerial view, just after the chopper, shows smoke
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS136
In the cockpit.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS139
SOMEONE looks out a window. The city blocks and crowded injures
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS140
Unit debarks.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS143
The Marines enter a hangar.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS144
The staff sergeant takes off his helmet. As the Marine crosses a busy command station.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS146
SOMEONE checks his watch. SOMEONE shoots his concerned gaze.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS149
The group disperses.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS150
The unit stands outside.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS151
More helicopters descend.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS152
Now words appear, "Lincoln Boulevard: Marine Defensive Line. 2 hours and 47 minutes. until bomb drop. "
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS155
He watches and walks in into the clear sky.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS157
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch civilians pass.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS158
With his child, pass SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS159
SOMEONE advances.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS160
Against the steady flow of evacuees, the unit reaches a street filled with abandoned vehicles. Down the street bombs burst where SOMEONE is.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS161
Unit walks through the thick smoke.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS163
SOMEONE flinches. An object falls from the sky. SOMEONE raises his hand. SOMEONE does the same and the unit halts. SOMEONE signals for them to move on. SOMEONE glances around.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS164
The unit steps out of the alley and crosses an empty street littered with household items.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS166
They pass a pickup truck with an open passenger door. One Marine aims inside then lowers his weapon on finding the charred driver slumped against the wheel.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS167
Now through a thick haze, several advancing Marines gradually appear.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS169
Abandoned cars SOMEONE their path.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS171
SOMEONE looks up from a map. Simmons aims his rifle. Through his scope, he sees a woman's body on the ground. Then a home's burning front steps. The unit moves on, spread out along the hazy street. SOMEONE keeps an alert gaze.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS172
He peers through his scope.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS173
The staff sergeant cautiously approaches a house where a body lies face down on the lawn. The others ready their weapons.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS174
SOMEONE raises his rifle.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS176
Through a scope, they peer across the haze. SOMEONE aims his weapon at a car then shifts his crosshairs through the right. As the German Shepherd trots out, he looks up.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS179
Smaller fireballs in the air.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS181
Guerrero through the haze, bullet shells fall on the dirt. Frozen with fear, SOMEONE looks around.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS182
SOMEONE stands up and barrels through a wooden gate.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS184
He pulls him up.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS186
They go through another door and head down a narrow path.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS187
To an alley. Left behind.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS190
He shuffles through a gate. The others barge in to another house.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS192
He faces the Asian Marine.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS193
SOMEONE swallows then glances aside.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS194
Meanwhile, SOMEONE burst into an apartment building's laundry room. He limps past to rove the washing machines then lowers himself in a corner and uses his radio.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS197
His feet with his gun raised, he knocks over a box of detergent which spills onto his head.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS198
With a terrified look, the young Marine creeps through a blasted out hole in the wall.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS199
With his gun ready, seeing a dryer, he relaxes.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS200
The hole in the wall, firing wildly. Staring outside, he backs up to the laundry room door and feels for its knob. He opens it and then hurries outside. Meanwhile, SOMEONE leads his group into the apartment complex.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS201
The wall riddled with bullets then signals for his men to stop.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS202
SOMEONE gazes up at the building's roof then shares a look with SOMEONE. SOMEONE waves them on. In the courtyard, SOMEONE adjusts the scope on his gun.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS203
Staring down his gun's scope, he feebly sidesteps in front of some stairs which lead up to a pool patio.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS204
Swinging around, he aims his gun at the sky but sees nothing. Behind him, an alien emerges from the pool.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS205
As SOMEONE wheels around.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS206
Then knocked it backwards into the pool. Sitting up, SOMEONE notices smoke rising from his backpack.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS207
As he shakes off the smoldering pack, it fills the air with a thin haze. SOMEONE gets to his feet, his rifle at the ready and limps up the stairs to the patio. Creeping to the edge of the pool, he aims into its rippling murky water.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS208
Shadows move under the surface and he shoots.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS209
Something moves below surface.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS210
SOMEONE approaches him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS211
SOMEONE pulls the pin from his grenade.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS213
Water dives in upward as the grenade explodes. Now SOMEONE spears around the building.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS214
Marine Rally Point, 1. 3 miles to police station.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS215
SOMEONE's group creeps out after him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS216
From across the street, SOMEONE gives a nod. His men move out into the open, one of them limping.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS217
SOMEONE guides Guerrero, who wears a bloody bandage over his eyes. As the Marines head into the street, a fiery projectile streaks down.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS219
SOMEONE presses a dressing to Simmons's charred neck.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS220
He turns away. Through his scope, SOMEONE spots figures in the smoke outside.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS221
He rushes through the open door.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS222
A small group of soldiers emerges from the smoke.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS223
SOMEONE beacons. The four friendlies race across the street and into the Ocean Lounge.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS226
His uniform bears the name SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS227
SOMEONE eyes SOMEONE's gun.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS229
SOMEONE looks over.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS231
Now the group carries Simmons on a stretcher, passed the smoking SOMEONE of the demolished building.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS233
A V formation of fighter jets passes overhead.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS235
The portico at the LAPD's West Los Angeles Station.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS236
They ready their ammo.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS237
The others enter the station.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS238
They sweep the area.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS239
SOMEONE checks a body.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS240
They approaches slowly.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS242
The corporal tosses a grenade. In the station, the men creep down a dark hall.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS243
As they near an open doorway, SOMEONE signals them to halt.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS244
He points to his head then at the adjacent room. Behind him, SOMEONE nods. As they enter, SOMEONE sweeps a light from his rifle scope around the destroyed room.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS245
It passes over legs of some upturned chairs which sit beside a pair of tall cabinets. Spotting movement through a gap between the cabinets, SOMEONE turns off his light. SOMEONE follow suit.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS246
With his gun aimed at the gap, SOMEONE glances at him and points. He gives SOMEONE a nod then creeps closer. Moving past a desk, SOMEONE lowers his gaze to a dead man on the floor. He heads around the other side of the cabinets and turns his rifle's light back on.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS247
The beam glows on a man and woman.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS248
The group carries Simmons over on a stretcher.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS249
They head inside.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS250
They hug.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS252
Lift off the ground, SOMEONE cheerfully eyes his comrades below.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS253
Overhead, a burst of fire explodes through the helicopter's windshield.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS255
Raging flames.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS258
SOMEONE leads the civilians back to their original hiding spot.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS261
SOMEONE and SOMEONE carry the dead man away.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS263
SOMEONE shifts her uncertain eyes.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS264
Now SOMEONE and SOMEONE guard doors at the end of a hall.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS267
His buddy weeps. Meanwhile, SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE who listens to the sat phone.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS271
He hits his chair.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS272
SOMEONE steps closer, his eyes trained on the lieutenant. SOMEONE meets his gaze.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS279
Jets soar through the sky. SOMEONE and SOMEONE take position on the roof.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS280
SOMEONE tosses SOMEONE's helmet then gives him a nod. Now on CNN.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS281
He shines a penlight.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS283
the father and his son find SOMEONE at the fountain.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS284
SOMEONE nods. His face somber.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS285
He points to Hector.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS286
SOMEONE salutes. SOMEONE lifts Hector's hand to return him a gesture. Hector grins. SOMEONE nods at SOMEONE. As the father and son leave, a mournful look crosses the staff sergeant's face. On the roof.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS287
Aliens gear up on another rooftop.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS288
One hovers over the other.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS291
A CNN report.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS292
One of the girls draws at a table.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS293
The aunt holds SOMEONE's gaze for a moment.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS297
From the roof, SOMEONE eyes the destroyed city.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS298
SOMEONE and SOMEONE move away from the others.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS299
watches through his scope as SOMEONE and SOMEONE run outside.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS300
SOMEONE rushes outside.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS301
He leads SOMEONE and SOMEONE to a wounded alien amid charred SOMEONE right outside the station. Examining the body, SOMEONE notes a mechanical piece, seemingly soldered to bone.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS302
SOMEONE pokes the alien with his gun.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS303
SOMEONE shoots it, causing liquid to spurt out.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS305
They drag the alien inside.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS306
SOMEONE rushes over.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS307
The body to the back of the station.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS308
She gives SOMEONE a nod. On the roof, SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch through their scopes as SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb on to the bus. SOMEONE reaches under the dash. In the station, SOMEONE slices open the alien's chest.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS313
SOMEONE stabs it and clear liquid spurts from a mechanical vent.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS314
Stabs again, water spurts from tissue.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS315
Use to hot wire the bus.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS316
He looks at SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS320
The vet leaves.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS322
Now SOMEONE moves down a hall, peering through his rifles.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS325
At the end of SOMEONE's hall, a door swings slightly. An alien pushes through.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS326
SOMEONE pulls away a thin stretchy layer of the alien's body, revealing a large watery sac.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS327
Then fluid spurts out.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS328
Grenade the hall and runs off.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS329
SOMEONE and SOMEONE grab their gear. Outside, the group rushes toward the bus.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS330
They propel down the building.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS331
SOMEONE gets down on the bus floor.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS332
SOMEONE grimaces on the floor. SOMEONE looks around.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS333
Some distant Palm tree.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS334
Fires on the neighborhood below.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS338
They share a grave look. SOMEONE wipes his brow with a gloved finger and stares out the windshield.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS340
At the wheels, SOMEONE's gaze shifts upward. Mottola lifts his eyes from his rifle.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS343
An abrupt stop jostles the passengers. The girls' aunt and SOMEONE stare wide-eyed.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS344
Fly overhead.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS345
The soldiers and civilians alike duck down between the seats as more alien aircraft pass overhead.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS347
Was aiming their rifle skyward, Mottola grips his radio.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS348
The Marines turn off the radio.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS349
SOMEONE focuses on a gas station up ahead.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS350
SOMEONE takes a handheld radio and heads on.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS352
SOMEONE crouches, his mouth agape and looks around.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS354
Meanwhile, SOMEONE skids.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS355
and takes a rubber band from his wrist.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS359
That heads in his direction. The staff sergeant raise.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS362
It arrives at the station, he lobs the grenade.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS364
SOMEONE gapes ahead at the black smoke and flames filling the street. SOMEONE's brow furrows. Behind him, SOMEONE looks out with a worried stare. The blonde little girl lifts her head from the floor. Through the clearing smoke, SOMEONE sees SOMEONE rise.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS365
Obscured briefly by a tall flame whipping in the wind, the staff sergeant heads off. Hoofing it through a trail of flaming debris, he arrives at the destroyed aircraft. Fluid spews from several severed hoses. Aiming his weapon, SOMEONE examines the alien craft.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS366
Later, he steps back on the bus. Leaning against the handrail, he rests his forehead on his hand.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS367
As SOMEONE looks him over, SOMEONE glances up at him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS368
SOMEONE's right hand trembles. SOMEONE gazes wide-eyed at the staff sergeant then looks up to SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS369
SOMEONE looks up at him. His gaze hard and his shake shaking uncontrollably. As he starts to pass by his superior, SOMEONE stops him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS370
SOMEONE nods with a little smile.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS372
As SOMEONE gazes back at SOMEONE, SOMEONE gets the bus moving again. In the back, SOMEONE bats off his helmet and earpiece and makes a fist with his shaking hand.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS373
The vet approaches.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS374
She nods appreciatively. SOMEONE gingerly touches a cut above his eye.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS378
They share a little smile. She looks down at his hand.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS379
She gives him a pat on the shoulder and leaves. Now the bus passes under a highway where several tanks sit burning. As SOMEONE gets up, SOMEONE grabs his arm.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS384
SOMEONE gazes at the tech sergeant then shifts his eyes thoughtfully. Now as the bus runs a corner, SOMEONE studies his map. SOMEONE joins him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS386
As the bus makes its way up a long curved on ramp, a couple of fighter jets soar overhead. On the freeway, littered with abandoned vehicles, the bus knocks cars out of its way as it rolls along.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS387
10 Freeway West, 2. 5 miles to FOB, the bus drives
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS388
The Marines all load fresh ammo clips
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS389
The vet strokes the little girl's blonde hair. SOMEONE looks back.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS391
They pass a clearing in the smoke, to see a huge gap between the freeway and a section of off ramp.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS392
A huge explosion erupts just a few yards in front of the bus. SOMEONE ties Hector's sneaker.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS393
SOMEONE hurries to the front of the bus.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS396
As he peers down from the resulting hole, another solider joins him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS397
Crouched at the bus's front door.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS398
Towards the rest of the civilians.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS399
As he falls, he knocks SOMEONE down
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS401
On the ground, SOMEONE stands up grimacing.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS402
Helicopter. Meanwhile.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS403
Astound an alien, as he hustles up beside
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS404
an 18-caliber machine gun on the roof. Firing at the alien.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS406
The car, SOMEONE smiles and lets out a sigh.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS407
Rocket blast several cars near the tank. SOMEONE's smile fades. SOMEONE and SOMEONE look up from their rifle sights.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS408
Around the little girl's waist.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS409
Lowers his weapon and starts to run.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS410
Blasting the SUV out.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS411
The vehicle flips, crushing the soldier.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS414
As SOMEONE yanks SOMEONE free, he falls back down on the roof.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS415
The alien missile zipping toward
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS417
SOMEONE shakes her head. SOMEONE punches the car.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS419
He checks the progress of the rappel.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS421
Brick of C-4 to a tire, SOMEONE stands.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS422
To another wheel. They move behind another car and add explosives to
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS423
They hustle away. The alien machine fires.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS425
SOMEONE looks him over. By the chopper, an alien bullet
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS426
Behind the helicopter, SOMEONE and the vet help him. SOMEONE sees an alien
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS428
SOMEONE leaves the distracted corpsman and grabs Mottola's gun. He kills the alien.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS429
The vet hurries to him with some bandages. Meanwhile, SOMEONE shoot
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS432
The Marines stare gravely into each other's eyes.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS433
SOMEONE takes the letter from his pocket.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS434
As he passes the letter over, the men grip hands.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS435
SOMEONE looks him in the eye and gives a slight nod.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS436
SOMEONE watches the staff sergeant go.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS437
As TNT sets up.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS438
Takes his pack for more ammo. In the bus aims a bag of C-4.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS439
He aims a bag of C-4.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS440
And watches the aliens draw closer.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS441
He sits back in the doorway, clutching a radio. SOMEONE watches from his position, several yards away.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS442
Then he squeezes the detonator.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS443
Blows the bus apart. SOMEONE shuts his eyes. The smoke clears
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS444
and the Marines lift their heads, looking around. SOMEONE gets up.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS445
As the rest of the group slowly rise to their feet, SOMEONE gazes solemnly toward the bus.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS446
The vet looks over her shoulder. Getting to his feet, SOMEONE squints at the flaming remains of the bus.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS447
SOMEONE stares. His lips parted above his helmet's chin strap.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS448
SOMEONE gingerly approaches the wreckage.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS449
He finds some charred remains by the door.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS450
He lifts his head and gazes over his shoulder and his men.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS451
Lowering his eyes and tightening his lips, he heads back toward the group.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS452
He marches pass the soldiers, who stand there, staring at him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS453
SOMEONE stays motionless, following the staff sergeant with his eyes.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS454
Now, as they walk amid burning buildings, a battle rages overhead.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS455
They arrive in a supermarket.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS460
Several Marines and the vet lower SOMEONE to the floor. The injured man winces, his face pale and sweaty. In a backroom, SOMEONE sweeps his rifle past storage boxes and an office desk. SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS462
She picks up a phone.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS463
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and the vet tend to SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS466
SOMEONE dresses the wound.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS467
SOMEONE softly nods. He helps with the bandage.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS468
The Marines share a look.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS469
The staff sergeant wipes the wounded civilian's brow then sits back and unscrews a water bottle.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS473
SOMEONE lifts his trembling hand. SOMEONE eyes his superior. SOMEONE glances at the Marine and grips the wounded man's hand.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS474
The staff sergeant holds his gaze.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS475
SOMEONE grabs his helmet.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS476
SOMEONE unfolds a foil blanket. Now news footage.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS478
SOMEONE watches on.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS483
On screen, a giant craft hovers.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS485
SOMEONE meets her gaze and she nods.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS487
Put SOMEONE into the backroom.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS488
SOMEONE compares a clock with his watch. SOMEONE checks his watch. SOMEONE grabs his helmet.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS489
SOMEONE adjusts his weapon.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS490
SOMEONE straps on his helmet.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS491
SOMEONE kneels near the vet and her nieces. SOMEONE watches the clock.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS492
The vet kisses one of the crying girls on the head. And then he closes his eyes. Joe, Lockett, and SOMEONE watch the clock.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS493
The second hand ticks toward the 12.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS494
SOMEONE helps shield the girls. SOMEONE clutches his helmet.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS495
Puts his head to his knees.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS496
SOMEONE looks at the clock. The second hand ticks well pass the 12. SOMEONE looks at his wrist watch.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS497
He looks up at the clock. SOMEONE and SOMEONE do the same. SOMEONE stands up.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS499
Hector helps the Marines carry SOMEONE. SOMEONE hurriedly ushers everyone out. Now black smoke fills the night sky. Words appear, "Santa SOMEONE Airport FOB. " Flames rise from the burning wreckage, a various aircraft and vehicles littering the runway. The group stares from a chain-link fence. SOMEONE steps forward, breathing heavily.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS500
A map, later SOMEONE shines a flashlight across the abandoned hangar.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS501
The group enters.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS502
They carry SOMEONE into a tent and set him down. Outside, SOMEONE hangs his hat. SOMEONE paces.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS503
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS505
SOMEONE walks with SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS506
Brightening a little, the staff sergeant flows to a stop.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS507
He crosses the hangar.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS508
SOMEONE leads SOMEONE up a staircase, down an open walkway, overlooking the hangar and into an office.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS509
SOMEONE rifles through paperwork. In the hangar, two Marines set a dead body on the floor with three others. Checking SOMEONE's pulse, SOMEONE looks at Hector.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS510
The boy glances at him as he steps out. Left alone, Hector holds his father's limp hand.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS513
SOMEONE points to a location.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS514
SOMEONE enters and takes off his helmet.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS515
SOMEONE glances out.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS516
SOMEONE and SOMEONE look up from the map and gape at the Marine. SOMEONE drops his head to his hands then pounds on the table.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS517
The frustrated staff sergeant leaves the map and ambles across the office. Reaching the walkway, he watches SOMEONE and Hector through an open flap on the side of the tent.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS518
His chest heaves. Hector sits over his father.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS519
He lays his head on his father's chest. Grimacing, he grabs SOMEONE's shirt.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS520
The vet kneels beside Hector. She gently lays a hand on SOMEONE's forehead and caresses the back of the boy's head with the other.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS521
SOMEONE and SOMEONE cross the hangar.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS522
SOMEONE approaches.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS523
Hector runs out of the tent.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS524
He faces the staff sergeant then hugs him. SOMEONE looks to SOMEONE and the vet.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS525
As the boy clings to him, he glances uncomfortably at the brunette. SOMEONE wanders pass them, holding his helmet.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS526
The vet gives SOMEONE an encouraging nod.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS527
He glances at SOMEONE, who sits nearby with a somber gaze. SOMEONE kneels in front of the boy.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS528
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE look on.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS529
SOMEONE gazes into the boy's eyes.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS530
Across the hangar, SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS531
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch them.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS532
The tearful vet hangs her head.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS533
The boy hugs him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS534
The vet steps in.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS535
She leads Hector to the girls, who sit nearby. SOMEONE remains on one knee. He draws a tense breath then looks at SOMEONE and the other Marines.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS536
He wipes his face then stands up and marches around a media station with a charred map tacked on a board.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS537
He continues past his fellow Marines.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS538
SOMEONE stops and looks back at SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS539
SOMEONE swaps a concerned look with SOMEONE. SOMEONE walks up to the disgruntled Marine and faces him squarely.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS540
On watch duty, SOMEONE and SOMEONE each look back at the hangar.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS541
SOMEONE holds his gaze. SOMEONE spots SOMEONE watching them from the tent.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS542
He points to his temple then gets into SOMEONE's face.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS544
SOMEONE keeps his glaring eyes steady.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS545
SOMEONE steps away from the corporal.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS546
SOMEONE wipes a tear from his scarred cheek and hangs his head.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS547
SOMEONE glances at SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS548
SOMEONE listens.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS549
Later on the tarmac.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS550
SOMEONE collect ammunition from dead bodies.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS551
SOMEONE pockets a magazine. From a watch tower, SOMEONE and SOMEONE look over the extent of the destruction.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS552
SOMEONE peers through binoculars.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS555
SOMEONE lowers his binoculars.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS558
Hops into a Humvee. Inside the LAV, SOMEONE sits behind SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS565
Returns and looks through an opening into the back.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS566
With SOMEONE, the vet nods. SOMEONE studies the map.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS567
SOMEONE cranks the stirring wheel.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS570
Tears on screen.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS571
SOMEONE comforts the blonde girl.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS579
A helicopter hovers overhead. The vet looks up.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS580
SOMEONE climbs out. SOMEONE takes off his helmet. Outside, SOMEONE steps around the Humvee.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS581
They rush to the helicopter, where a crew chief meets them.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS583
SOMEONE spots him.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS584
SOMEONE climbs aboard with the civilians.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS585
His fellow soldiers. Hector sits on the vet's lap.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS587
Staff sergeant looks over the area and glances skyward. The helicopter rises above the sandbag bunker and over the desolate lot.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS588
As SOMEONE peers through a binocular, SOMEONE shifts his troubled gaze. Beyond the chopper, scattered fires light up the sprawling city. In distant downtown skyscrapers burn like Roman candles. SOMEONE adjusts his helmet above his narrowed eyes. The weary, disheveled group sits, huddled in the cabin. As the teary eyed sisters sit together watching the war-torn city, SOMEONE eyes them.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS589
Passengers brace themselves.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS591
SOMEONE peers through his binocular.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS594
The staff sergeant faces forward.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS595
He takes out a folded piece of paper and shows it to the vet.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS596
She glances at the letter then takes it and nods.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS597
Then covers her hand with his own and shakes it. He leaves his seat and taps the crew chief.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS599
He drops a long rope from the side door then faces Hector.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS600
He falls out of the helicopter and slides down the rope to a deserted lot.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS601
The staff sergeant glances around then faces a fire burning several yards away. A second rope drops from above. As SOMEONE heads off, SOMEONE slides to the ground and catches his attention. He watches two more Marines descend from the chopper. SOMEONE lands then trots past his staff sergeant and nods. Two more Marines touch ground.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS602
SOMEONE slides down a rope.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS603
SOMEONE looks over his team and leads them across the lot. The helicopter rises overhead into the night sky.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS604
Now SOMEONE glances around as he leads his unit below an overpass.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS605
He drops to one knee and the others follow suit.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS606
He consults a map.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS607
SOMEONE nods.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS608
SOMEONE shifts her thoughtful eyes.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS609
They rise. Then they run.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS611
They carry equipment into a concrete tunnel.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS613
With glowing orange bases. As the aliens leave, SOMEONE steps out of the shadows. The group creeps forward, passing the glowing cones. Each of which holds three antenna-like spears in its peak. An antenna shaft glows red as a crackle of electricity pulses out of it. Halting the unit, SOMEONE watches the shadow of the departing alien then waves the others forward.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS614
They reach an atrium in the tunnel system, where more of the glowing devices rest on its flooded floor.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS615
SOMEONE glances over his shoulder, his eyes searching the hazy area.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS618
He leans, knocks a panel off a wall as it drops, revealing a room on the other side.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS619
SOMEONE gazes into the high ceiling chamber, where a giant craft sits inside. It shapes similar to a balloon. Two jacking towers jet from its tower, protruding through a hole in the ceiling.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS621
They go away from the opening.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS622
As an alien draws closer, the rest of the unit climbs up the street level.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS624
Holds the pin from a grenade.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS625
The alien scoops it up and then it explodes.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS626
Flames burst into the air behind SOMEONE and his unit.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS628
They take cover behind and SOMEONE assembles a handheld laser target designator.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS629
SOMEONE nods and SOMEONE eyes the others.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS630
SOMEONE glances up at some soaring drums as he makes his way to a crumbled building.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS631
Hide another destroyed building, SOMEONE crouches in a doorway while SOMEONE adjusts her gun.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS632
He climbs the stairs.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS633
Races up the remains of the building's only surviving stairwell, he takes out his radio.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS634
He glances at SOMEONE and blocks it below.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS635
As he discards the radio and peers below.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS636
They shelter behind the slanted concrete slab, SOMEONE turns on the laser designator and aims it.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS637
SOMEONE spots an alien approaching SOMEONE and shoots it.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS638
SOMEONE flinches at the rising bellow of smoke.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS639
SOMEONE squeezes his eye shut and SOMEONE gapes.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS640
And SOMEONE leave their hiding spot and race across the street to join the others.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS641
As an alien steps near, he fires.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS642
SOMEONE checks his watch.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS643
And SOMEONE fire at the approaching craft.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS644
Sergeant rises.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS645
SOMEONE checks his watch again.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS646
SOMEONE re-aims the laser.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS649
SOMEONE's grin fades as the ground quakes.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS652
As it lifts off, chunks of SOMEONE tumble off its enormous brain. SOMEONE adjusts.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS654
SOMEONE works to lift the panel off SOMEONE.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS655
SOMEONE grabs the laser box.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS658
He tosses her a magazine.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS659
SOMEONE struggles to his knees.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS660
SOMEONE lifts a grenade launcher
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS663
Climbing up the concrete's slab, he spot the box
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS664
SOMEONE fires at an alien which explodes and knocks
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS667
SOMEONE grabs the grenade launcher.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS668
And center on the soaring missile hits the craft
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS669
He falls onto his back and watches as fire builds inside the vessel.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS670
Watches the drones, which spin out of control as they descend.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS671
One hits the ground near the group.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS672
He peers at the aliens.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS673
SOMEONE lowers his empty rifle and draw his gun.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS675
The aliens race away from the prevailing humans. And SOMEONE's chest heaves as he watches them disappear around the corner.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS676
He sweeps his gaze over the area, finding it unoccupied then lowers his gun. As drones continue to fall from the sky, columns of black smoke rise into the air from a flaming command center.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS677
Sunlight shines
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS678
Behind SOMEONE's unit. Silhouetting them as they stand amidst the rubble and stare at the destroyed vessel.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS679
Now SOMEONE and a handful of his comrades ride in the cabin of a helicopter.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS682
He jumps down.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS683
More Marines jog pass SOMEONE's group.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS684
A commanding Marine heads over to them.
BATTLE_LOS_ANGELES_DVS685
Now on a tent, SOMEONE chugs a bottle of water while SOMEONE pours one over his head then drinks. With a tired look, SOMEONE sips her own bottle. SOMEONE claps a hand on the back of SOMEONE's neck then they share a look. Tears glisten in SOMEONE's eyes as he shifts his gaze to Harris, who clasps his weapon to his chest and clenches his jaw. The staff sergeant eyes a supply of bullets and a stack of ammunition magazines sitting on a table. He grabs a bullet and loads it into an empty clip. As he fills the magazine, the others and his unit watch with disbelieving eyes. SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a look. And the corpsman shifts his gaze to the staff sergeant. SOMEONE steps up to the table. As he gathers supplies, SOMEONE looks over and the corporal gives him a nod. SOMEONE and SOMEONE join them.