Sunset reception, they wear gold medals.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS15
He place hands and smooth SOMEONE's hair.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS16
They each affect a hunky stance.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS17
The photographer steps away. SOMEONE punches his brother's unflinching stomach.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS18
A well groomed man gives SOMEONE a warm hug.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS19
SOMEONE grabs hors d'oeuvres from a passing waiter.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS20
their rival's cold smile. SOMEONE grins and SOMEONE smirks uneasily.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS21
He holds his medal. Now, a row of cannons fires beside a sign - Baily Yacht Club.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS22
From a deck, the two brothers watch heading out to sea.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS23
He rests his arm on SOMEONE's shoulders as they gaze out at the water.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS24
SOMEONE nods. SOMEONE pulls him into a hug and tousles his hair.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS25
Now, in a car's passenger seat, a blonde uses a vanity mirror to apply lipstick.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS26
SOMEONE looks back and forth between his mother and brother.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS27
Their mother gazes wistfully out her window. Now, the car rolls
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS28
They watch parents enter a school.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS29
She tugs at her cardigan.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS30
He applauds.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS31
At the podium, SOMEONE's sailing partner elbows her. Now, in a lobby, SOMEONE adjusts SOMEONE's tie.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS33
Now, a lighthouse stands in the golden glow of a low sun. Water ripples in a marina. In town a few pedestrians laze along a sidewalk.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS34
waits on the porch of a modest house with a baseball mitt. As SOMEONE comes outside with his own mitt, his brother eyes his watch.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS35
The younger brother pounds his glove.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS36
runs down the driveway and up the street. SOMEONE steps out after him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS37
He beckons the boy. SOMEONE takes a step closer and starts to throw.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS38
The younger brother lumbers over. SOMEONE takes the ball.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS39
As the boy obeys, their mother comes out in scrubs.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS40
She runs after a bus.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS41
Night time. SOMEONE takes notes as he watches a baseball game on TV.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS42
In the kitchen, SOMEONE cooks dinner.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS43
He furiously scribbles notes. Now, outside, SOMEONE climbs out a window and pauses on a ledge. He hops down to the Splendid Splinter which sits with its sails lowered, then jumps down to the shadowy driveway.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS44
Creeping alongside the house, he makes his way to the family car. He quietly opens the driver's side door and gets behind the wheel. As he starts the engine, the headlights reveal SOMEONE standing in his path.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS45
He wears a Red Sox jacket, his mitt,  and a giant foam finger.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS46
SOMEONE glares, then begrudgingly beckons his younger brother.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS47
He gets into the car beside him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS48
He buckles himself in. SOMEONE starts the car, then lightly backhands him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS49
SOMEONE whacks him playfully.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS50
He smacks SOMEONE again.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS51
SOMEONE arches his brow.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS52
SOMEONE settles irritably into his seat. SOMEONE gets in one last punch.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS53
The car slows to a stop as a steady stream of vehicles passes.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS54
He turns the wheels to make a turn.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS55
Cut to black. Now, shiny sparks glimmer in the darkness. As our view passes over them, they reveal themselves to be thousands of glass shards scattered on the inky asphalt. The station wagon lies on its crushed roof and an ambulance arrives down
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS56
he is sitting between his brother's legs.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS57
A paramedic's dark clad legs stride toward the car. He shines a flashlight.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS58
while the paramedic shocks SOMEONE with defibrillator paddles.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS59
He puts his hand on his neck.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS60
He sees his brother beneath a sheet on another gurney.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS62
Back at the scene of the accident,
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS63
It shows wrecked station wagon. A flashlight sweeps over SOMEONE's baseball cap.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS64
SOMEONE cradles SOMEONE's baseball glove against his chest as a white coffin lowers into an open grave.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS65
He's swollen and eyes puffy. He stares of numbly.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS66
He looks up and catches a glimpse of a red shape behind a headstone.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS67
SOMEONE nervously shifts his gaze. He's pallid mother blinks down at the casket. SOMEONE backs away.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS68
As he shuffles off, his mother grabs his arm.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS69
Glancing at SOMEONE's grave over his shoulder, he pulls away, then breaks into a run. He abandons the funeral and sprints into the forest.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS70
More headstones stand.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS71
SOMEONE races pass them.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS72
With his brother's baseball glove, he jogs down a trail.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS73
As the setting sun flares through the trees around him ramming into the path.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS74
He sees the scene of accident.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS75
He starts to push himself up, then lowers his head toward the ground.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS76
The grieving brother crawls onto his hands and knees, then weakly sits up. His chest heaves as he grimaces tearfully and hangs his head. The baseball rolls back out of the forest toward the mitt.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS77
SOMEONE glances at it, then lifts his gaze.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS78
His twisted features relax. SOMEONE stands before him in his Red Sox jacket. SOMEONE gawks at his brother, then quizzically knits his brow.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS79
SOMEONE gives an irritable shrug.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS80
His stunned older brother continues to stare at him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS81
SOMEONE blinks. His lips pressed into a slight pout. SOMEONE earnestly lifts his dark brows.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS82
SOMEONE's gaping mouth curls into a faint smile. His brother gives a sharp nod. The ruddy leather mitt and white baseball lie on the mossy ground between them.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS83
Our view rises into the trees above then soars into the sky.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS84
The forest stretches across rolling hills between streaks of grayish orange clouds. The water catches their reflection in a flame colored.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS85
Words appear - five years
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS86
Now, dull gray clouds hang over the same view of the forest, the bay, and the sea. We glide toward the coastline and dive through the trees to the grassy cemetery. A white headstone reads Samuel St. Cloud.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS90
She awkwardly hikes off. SOMEONE gazes after her.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS91
A marine in dress uniform crouches at one of them. SOMEONE strides toward him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS92
The marine picks at something on the stone, then stands and grins. It's SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS95
SOMEONE picks at bird poop on top of the stone, then studies it on the finger of his white glove.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS96
Elsewhere, SOMEONE carries a crossbow to a tree trunk stump with two arrows. Plopping the weapon on the ground, he quizzically eyes SOMEONE a short distance away. The caretaker stands alone among the headstones, gesturing conversationally and nodding as if talking to someone. SOMEONE keeps his gaze locked on his boss as he uses a pair of pliers to tug a crossbow bolt out of the tree. SOMEONE nods, seemingly to no one.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS98
He beams and strolls off toward the forest. SOMEONE watches tearfully.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS99
SOMEONE steps out of view behind the headstone which reads Timothy Patrick Sullivan, Lieutenant U. S. Marine Corp. Now, SOMEONE strolls into a hobby and toy shop. Three teen girls stand behind the counter.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS107
His uniform work shirt. Wearing a long sleeve T, he tosses down his keys and slides open a drawer. He pulls out
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS108
He pauses at the door to check the Quincy Harbor Sunset chart, then gives it a light tap and exits.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS109
It shows he's moving the toy plane aside the gator.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS110
Now the setting sun flares brightly through the forest.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS111
SOMEONE hikes past a headstone showing a weeping angel trash bags slung over his shoulder while cradling his baseball glove to his chest. Smiling.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS112
He walks in the sunny forest and enters the glade.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS113
He slings down the trash bag, winds up and pitches in the air.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS114
It smacks down into SOMEONE's mitt.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS115
SOMEONE shows the plane.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS116
big brother pounds his fist into his own mitt.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS117
Later, the ball bounces along the ground and SOMEONE catches it. He throws it back. SOMEONE sends him more grounders.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS118
SOMEONE's jaw drops. SOMEONE throws the ball toward him, but he lets it bounce past.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS119
SOMEONE chuckles and shakes his head. SOMEONE remains solemn.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS120
The younger brother swallows. His gaze drifting around the forest. Later, at an inlet.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS121
The toy plane taxis on the water.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS122
SOMEONE's smile falters and he grows thoughtful. His older brother glances skyward.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS123
speeds into the sky. It circles, then flies into the
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS124
light gives way to evening.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS125
flips his hair out of his face. His merry grin fades as he surveys the darkened inlet. Finding himself alone, he idly runs his arms through the water.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS126
Later, he climbs back onto shore. His long sleeved T molding itself to his life muscular
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS127
grieving brother heaves a sigh and stares out at the inlet. Now, a light shines outside the boat shed and a window glows from within. Inside, SOMEONE sketches a sloop in red ink at a drafting table. He marks a star burst on the sail. Now, on another day, the glass door of a shop reflects an image of the street. Opening the door with his back, SOMEONE heads outside
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS128
the pale man grabs SOMEONE's shoulder.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS129
Now, SOMEONE and Ferrente sit in a booth at a coffee shop.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS130
SOMEONE notes a hospital bracelet on the wrist of his frail looking companion.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS131
He lifts his palm skyward and opens them toward SOMEONE. The young man swallows.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS132
Under Ferrente's stare, SOMEONE glances away, then shifts in his seat.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS133
Now, he strides out of the restaurant, his eyes cast downward. As he steps into the street, a fisherman in waterproof bib pants
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS134
slung over his shoulder. Heading toward the harbor, SOMEONE lifts his gaze and stops.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS135
He stares mesmerized out at the water. A beautiful state of the art sloop glides across the harbor. SOMEONE looks away sucking in a breath, then returns his gaze to the sailboat as he sets his bag in the back of his gater.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS136
He glances at his watch. At the dock, a television reporter films a news segment.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS137
SOMEONE passes the news crew and strides down the SOMEONE with his eyes fixed on the boat.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS138
Now, the vessel sits anchored with its foresail folded down and tied. The number 11 adorns the side of its sleek hull. SOMEONE squints at SOMEONE as she commands a small crew.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS139
In the glade, SOMEONE flips through a boating magazine to an article with photos of SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS140
He grabs the magazine and runs off.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS141
He reads the article.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS142
He holds the open magazine against his leg and smooth's its wrinkled pages. Night time. At the cemetery, a light above the boat shed's open barn door illuminates the bow of SOMEONE's neglected sailboat inside. In his work area, he sketches at a drafting table. The boating magazine rests above his paper open to pictures and diagrams of SOMEONE's canting keel. He leans back in his chair and glances around absentmindedly with his pencil.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS143
Later, he rests his head on his hand, his brow furrowed. Lifting his gaze, he strokes his chin thoughtfully and stares at a calendar on the wall. Its monthly picture shows a whale's tail fin curved upward.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS144
Now at the docks, our view glides from the blue and red hull of SOMEONE's sloop to SOMEONE sketching the sailboat.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS145
SOMEONE approaches from behind.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS146
He taps SOMEONE's right shoulder, then leans over the left. SOMEONE flinches.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS147
SOMEONE stares at him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS148
Elsewhere in the tavern, SOMEONE joins SOMEONE at a table.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS149
He shows a weather map.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS151
From the dining area, he points SOMEONE through a window.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS152
He circles his finger by his temple.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS154
Meanwhile clinching his jaw
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS155
She meets his gaze.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS156
SOMEONE looks over.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS157
He grins at SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS158
He punches him in the face.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS159
SOMEONE watches him go. Outside, SOMEONE heads on to the dock with his bag. He glances over his shoulder at some people leaving the tavern, then pauses and examines his right hand.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS160
As he pulls his jacket tight around himself, his gaze freezes and he stares wistfully out at the water.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS161
A lamp at the dock's railing illuminates his lonesome figure.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS162
Now, SOMEONE cautiously grabs a suspended safety wire running along the side of SOMEONE's sloop. He slides his hand across it as he walks the length of the deck. The vessel's lowered sails rest loosely around the boom, their folds draped over the cabin's roof. SOMEONE sweeps his gaze up at taut vertical line,
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS163
then gives it a light karate chop. Grabbing onto it, he jumps up onto the edge of the deck. He leans back and tugs on the line. He remembers holding a line on his own boat.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS164
off the dock as he sees SOMEONE in the cockpit.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS165
He starts to leave.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS166
She smirks at him as she pulls the crank off a winch.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS167
climbs up onto her deck and looks down at SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS168
He averts his gaze and stares off. Shifting her eyes, SOMEONE sucks in a breath, then glances at her shoes.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS169
SOMEONE watches as she jumps into the sunken cockpit and grabs the lip of the cabin's roof. She shoots him a look, then swings into the boat. SOMEONE glances away, then buries his face in his hands. Lifting his gaze again, he swallows hard.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS170
SOMEONE peers out from the cabin.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS171
As she emerges, SOMEONE takes his drawing pad out of his bag. SOMEONE looks down on him from her deck.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS172
He shows her his keel sketch.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS173
He averts his gaze. Crouching beside him, SOMEONE takes the pad. She flips to his drawing of her sloop.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS174
SOMEONE eyes him, her face inches from his.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS175
He steps away.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS176
She looks off, then glances at SOMEONE as he leaves.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS177
Pale sunlight glows on the horizon and shadows hang over the boats at the marina.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS178
An aerial view shows sunbeams leaking through evergreens behind the Quincy lighthouse.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS179
SOMEONE stares out at the inlet where SOMEONE's sloop glides toward the open sea.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS181
the boat which tilts slightly
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS182
billowing sails. A name on its stern
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS183
SOMEONE uses her radio.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS184
She puts down the mic, then eyes her sails.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS185
She pushes the tiller, then pulls on a rope.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS189
Now, in the glade, SOMEONE, on a baseball, He tosses the ball to SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS190
SOMEONE throws back to SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS191
SOMEONE fakes a hard throw.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS192
SOMEONE mocks him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS193
He throws the ball fast
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS194
He holds his glove chest high. As SOMEONE winds up, SOMEONE closes his eyes. SOMEONE pitches the ball into SOMEONE's crotch.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS195
As rain pours down on the brothers, a smile spreads across SOMEONE's face.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS196
SOMEONE dives onto his lid, but goes nowhere. In the cemetery, darkness falls over the statue of a young girl, then the rain ceases as day breaks.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS197
Some geese peck at the grass while SOMEONE peeks out at them from behind a headstone.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS198
He rushes at them, banging his trash can lids together.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS199
SOMEONE spots her.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS200
Colorful flowers line the hedge around the graves.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS201
She stands and winces.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS202
He jogs back to her.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS203
He indicates a wound on her head.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS204
Later, SOMEONE applies antiseptic to her wound.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS205
He lowers her hair back over the cut.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS206
the kitchen. SOMEONE drums on the edge of her chair, then stands and crosses to a window. She notices a framed photo of SOMEONE and SOMEONE on the Splendid Splinter and picks it up.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS207
SOMEONE blinks, his gaze stricken.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS208
She leaves the cabin with a coy smirk. Turning, SOMEONE plants his hands on the kitchen door frame and leans far back. He straightens, checks his watch, and checks the sunset chart. Pounding it with his fist, he pulls a curtain aside and watches SOMEONE walk away through a warped glass window.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS209
He rushes from the cabin to a waterside ridge. Jumping down to the gravel shore, he races after SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS210
He halts in his tracks, gazing helplessly after the departing girl.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS211
She slows as he runs to catch up to her.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS212
Walking away, SOMEONE bites her lip.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS213
She turns back with a warm smirk.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS214
SOMEONE throws to his brother. SOMEONE catches the ball, tosses it from his mitt to his hand, then returns it.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS215
The young boy lowers his doleful gaze.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS216
SOMEONE gives a nod and readies himself for a catch. SOMEONE pounds the ball into his glove, then throws it to him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS217
At dinner,
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS218
SOMEONE goes into the kitchen. Clad in a white halter dress, SOMEONE crosses to a bulletin board covered in sketches of boat designs. She turns abruptly as SOMEONE returns with a glass of white wine for her.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS219
She takes it and points. Stacked boxes fill a corner of the room.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS220
SOMEONE lowers her gaze. Pointing, SOMEONE crosses to a high box.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS221
His gaze distant, the young man sips his wine. SOMEONE points over her shoulder where SOMEONE's sketch of her sloop hangs on the wall.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS222
He looks from the drawing to his date.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS223
She leans back coyly against his drafting table and sips her wine. He steps in close, reaches past her shoulder and takes the sketch down. With a smoldering look, he offers it to her.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS224
She takes it with a coquettish smirk.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS225
As he leans in closer, she brushes past him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS226
She faces a map.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS227
SOMEONE steps in behind her.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS228
He plants a tender kiss on her shoulder.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS229
He turns her to face him and his lips hungrily finds hers. She briefly melts into the kiss, then stops him gently.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS230
SOMEONE reluctantly backs off and she heads for the door.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS231
He plants his hands on the dining table and bends over, leaning his hips back.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS232
He turns, then crosses to the door and opens it. Finding no one there, he hurries back to the table. He grabs a jar containing a burning candle, then ventures out into the darkness.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS233
He shuts the door behind him and looks around.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS234
He proceeds against pale mist.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS235
He turns around.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS236
as tall stone monuments, searching spot and catches a glimpse of SOMEONE proceeds in her direction.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS237
He continues searching.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS238
He turns, she plants a passionate kiss on his lips.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS239
He pulls her close as they tenderly canoodle.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS240
They kiss. But SOMEONE pulls back.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS241
She blows out the candle and runs off.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS243
to a stop, with the angel monument silhouetted behind the head.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS244
SOMEONE waits for him in a clearing between grave plots.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS245
She lays her hands on his chest.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS246
SOMEONE slowly rolls his shoulders back.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS247
Moving as one, they turn on the spot.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS248
sharing a tender gaze.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS249
SOMEONE trails her fingers scars on SOMEONE's upper chest and gives a gentle smile.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS250
SOMEONE's expression darkens and he turns his gaze skyward.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS251
Smiling, she gives him a gentle peck on the lips. SOMEONE pulls her into a long kiss.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS252
SOMEONE lays her head on his shoulder.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS253
deeper into the embrace.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS254
The next morning, SOMEONE sleeps naked amid the grave monuments. His head rolls toward us and his eyes blink open groggily.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS255
He smacks his dry lips. A lone goose stares back at him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS256
Now, in jeans and a T-shirt, SOMEONE hikes up the waterside path leading to the caretaker's grounds. He breaks into a brief jog, rubbing his eyes. Reaching the cabin, he finds a slip of paper tacked to the door bearing a doodle of the Splendid Splinter. A handwritten note on the back reads come find me. Turning the slip over, SOMEONE reads the message and smiles. He jogs toward the boat shed which sits with its barn doors closed. Turning to the bay, he finds SOMEONE manning his old skiff.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS257
SOMEONE glances away pensively. Clad in his buttoned down shirt, SOMEONE smiles at him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS258
In the boat, SOMEONE trails his fingers in the water as the Splendid
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS261
Now, in the golden glow of a low sun, SOMEONE and SOMEONE cuddle at the top of a lighthouse.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS262
SOMEONE nods. SOMEONE faces the water with a smile.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS263
She eyes him quizzically, her smile gradually fading.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS264
He leaves SOMEONE alone at the lighthouse. Now, SOMEONE sprints frantically through the woods following the winding footpath.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS265
Now, SOMEONE sprints frantically through the woods following the winding footpath.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS266
He reaches the glade.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS267
He finds his brother trudging away.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS268
He halts at the edge of the woods and turns back.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS269
Turning, SOMEONE finds SOMEONE behind him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS270
He looks back in SOMEONE's direction.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS271
He finds his brother gone. SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS272
SOMEONE takes his hand and kisses it.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS273
He shakes his head, then yanks his hand from her grasp. SOMEONE blinks tearfully as she watches him turn away. With a resolute expression, he steps further into the glade.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS274
He shuts his eyes. As SOMEONE leaves, he opens them again in a haunted stare.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS275
We peer back at him from the edge of the woods as he stands motionless, his gaze fixed in our direction. Night time. In the caretaker's cabin, SOMEONE sits alone and bleary eyed with a glass of whiskey
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS276
SOMEONE morosely sips his liquor. The next morning, boats languidly sail past the coastal town. In a house overlooking a bay, a golden retriever gnaws on a chew toy in the living room.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS277
SOMEONE pulls on a denim jacket.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS278
SOMEONE eyes the dog, grabs a leash from a hook by the door. Dog runs out a doggie door.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS279
SOMEONE leaves the house.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS280
Meanwhile, SOMEONE lies asleep on his couch. He licks his lips, then groggily lifts his head.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS281
He rises.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS282
He sets a coffee pot in the kitchen sink.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS283
As water fills the carafe, he opens a freezer and takes out a rumpled bag of grounds. He scowls at it, then gives it a shake.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS284
He crumples it. Tosses it
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS285
his shoulder and shuts off the tap.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS286
Now, at a diner counter, SOMEONE sips coffee. SOMEONE joins him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS287
Wearing green sweater, he browses a newspaper.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS288
Two officers step to a prominent spot in the dinning room.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS289
Outside, she runs.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS290
SOMEONE lets the dog run by.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS291
SOMEONE's smile fades as her friend walks past her with no acknowledgement. SOMEONE faces a shop window. Back in the diner
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS292
SOMEONE frowns at the window.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS293
SOMEONE pictures the Carniceria and the brewing squall.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS294
A view from his cottage shows SOMEONE vanish as she walks away.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS295
SOMEONE passes by,
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS296
The Splendid Splinter remains stored inside.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS297
SOMEONE stares at the neglected boat.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS298
Now, in the cemetery, tombstones stand in light and shadow. A distant sprinkler waters the grass. SOMEONE glowers as he strides among the graves. Farther along, our view peers over the headstone in memory of SOMEONE's father. SOMEONE steps into view and crouches down on one knee. The engraved side remains hidden to us, but visible to him.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS299
SOMEONE leans huddled against her father's headstone. SOMEONE's tearful gaze stays on her as she returns a grief stricken look. Her head wound bleeds.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS300
SOMEONE's eyes pool with tears.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS301
His jaw falls slack. He sheds a heavy tear, then blinks his stunned red eyes. He's alone in the hedge lined plot.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS302
SOMEONE bows his head restlessly, then looks up, his face locked in a stiff SOMEONE. In the
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS303
He throws papers and books off his desk
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS304
hunches the sunset charts on the wall
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS305
down onto a table. SOMEONE doubles over the charts, agonizing. He grips the table and presses his forehead to the fallen charts.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS306
He straightens a little, his eyes on the charts. Clad in a deep blue shirt, his strong back flexes as he catches his breath.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS307
SOMEONE opens a bureau drawer.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS308
Reaching inside, he strokes his baseball mitt, then firmly lays it flat. He leans over the open drawer, his eyes un-waveringly on its contents.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS309
Our view of SOMEONE seen from the shoulders up straightens with him and he leaves the cottage.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS310
Now, SOMEONE sits in the woods, his gaze distant.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS311
SOMEONE looks on. His red mitt dangles on his hand at his side.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS312
SOMEONE takes a few steps closer and lets his mitt drop to the ground.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS313
He takes a seat by his big brother.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS314
SOMEONE peers sidelong at his brother who stares off. SOMEONE rests a hand on SOMEONE's leg.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS315
SOMEONE sits frozen in a troubled daze.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS317
Now, at night, his cottage door opens and he turns on the lights.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS318
Later, in the ransacked room, he positions a milk crate on the messy floor and
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS319
some papers into it in a feeble start to cleaning up.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS320
Outside, a woman in a dark knee length dress treads toward the cottage door.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS321
The fair skinned brunette woman reaches out offering the necklace.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS322
SOMEONE reaches out and accepts.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS323
As the widow turns away, SOMEONE fingers the medallion.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS324
Mrs. SOMEONE smiles sadly as she leaves alone and SOMEONE regards the silver quatrefoil pendant. His gaze focuses beyond the medallion to the floor where SOMEONE's note in red ink shows among the cluttered papers. The doodle of the sailboat lies face up. SOMEONE fetches the note.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS325
He meditatively takes a seat and turns the scrap over reading the three word message in SOMEONE's cute handwriting - come find me.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS326
Now, at SOMEONE's.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS327
SOMEONE backs SOMEONE away
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS328
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE enter the convenience type store to finish his transaction, then he faces SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS329
The cruise get closer.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS330
Now, in the full featuring a half dozen rocky humps.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS331
Now, it shows the reflection of sun on the sea.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS332
SOMEONE groggily to his feet.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS333
SOMEONE reluctantly stands.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS334
Outside guy leaving only patches of powder blue. SOMEONE checks his watch.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS336
SOMEONE glances at his friend. His bold gaze drift.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS337
His friend lies down.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS338
SOMEONE keeps his eyes shut and arms crossed.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS339
SOMEONE stares off tearful.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS340
gently ruffled by the wind.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS341
He holds up the St. Jude medallion and gazes at its polished necklace.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS342
It glints in the brilliant.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS343
the necklace with a knit brow, then squeezes.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS344
his fist and turns his resolute glare toward the water.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS345
leaving a wide wake. The setting sun color
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS346
In Quincy, the dock lights turn on and the sunset cannon fires. In the cemetery, shadows stretch over the grass. An old headstone shaped like a Celtic cross towers over the other grave markers. Five geese wander past. In the glade, golden beams of light shine on SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS347
The boy is waiting.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS348
The boy stares expectantly at the other end of the clearing, then shakes his hair out of his eyes.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS349
He gives a slight wince.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS350
His lips pout into a frown. On the boat, golden light bathes SOMEONE's solemn face. In the glade, SOMEONE drops his gaze.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS351
He puts his baseball cap on, then wipes his nose on the back of his hand. Gazing skyward, he adjusts the hat lower on his forehead. Meanwhile, tears well up and glisten
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS352
Several teardrops plummet down his cheeks. In the glade, SOMEONE sadly bows his head. Mustering a brave expression, he punches a fist into his mitt. He glances at the sky, then hikes off into the forest and looks back over his shoulder at waning golden light filling the glade.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS353
A smile breaks across his boyish face.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS354
Big brother playfully swats his cheek.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS355
Back in the forest, the setting sun brightens and SOMEONE's grinning form vanishes. Back at sea, gray clouds darken the orange tinted sky. SOMEONE looks up and finds a shooting across it.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS356
His lips part.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS357
As the sun sinks below the horizon, the shooting star falls to the horizon.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS359
He returns toward the cabin and bangs on the windshield in front of SOMEONE.
CHARLIE_ST_CLOUD_DVS360
closer. The search on a flashlight.