Downstairs, SOMEONE chats with a guest.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS4
As the guest heads off, SOMEONE appears.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS11
SOMEONE leads him into the study where SOMEONE takes in the refined décor.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS15
The dwarf spots a manuscript on the coffee table.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS17
He eyes its title page.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS18
SOMEONE flips the manuscript over.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS38
He takes a seat.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS39
He hands a photo to SOMEONE who sits as he inspects it.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS44
Upstairs, SOMEONE spots his reflection in a mirror.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS45
He staggers back.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS46
Moving closer, he presses his hands to the glass.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS52
SOMEONE lifts his gaze from the photos to SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS57
A sly smile spreads across SOMEONE's face.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS58
SOMEONE follows the dwarf's gaze to a statuette of two naked men wrestling.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS59
He spots a book with Madonna on its cover and another statuette of a naked well-muscled man holding another man upside down.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS60
SOMEONE stands.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS61
SOMEONE eyes one of them.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS62
He tucks it into his breast pocket. Shaking his head he strides to the door and points at SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS63
He hurries out, closes the door behind him and pauses.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS64
As he moves past two chatting guests, one of them stops him.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS65
He breezes through the parlor.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS66
He ignores her.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS68
SOMEONE strolls over and leans against the bathroom door frame.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS69
He shouts through the door.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS71
SOMEONE recoils giddily and claps his hands.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS72
He pouts.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS73
SOMEONE leaves.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS74
SOMEONE shows him the photo.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS75
Inside, SOMEONE sits with SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS76
SOMEONE scratches his wrist.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS77
He forks up a bite of cake then frowns.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS78
SOMEONE leaves. In a nearby corner Uncle SOMEONE awakes.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS79
He spots SOMEONE at the dining table.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS80
He hurries off.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS81
With his cane, Uncle SOMEONE steals his cake and takes a bite.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS82
He takes the cake from his mouth.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS84
SOMEONE rushes off. SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE who sits on a patio couch.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS85
She leaves. SOMEONE notices SOMEONE's pill bottle on the ground.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS87
The guests stare.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS88
SOMEONE shows him the photo again, SOMEONE cringes.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS89
Upstairs in the bathroom, SOMEONE spins in a circle and wraps his entire head in toilet paper.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS90
Outside, SOMEONE searches some bushes.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS91
In the kitchen, the Reverend approaches Uncle SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS92
SOMEONE walks by.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS93
SOMEONE chases after him.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS94
The brothers enter the study and find SOMEONE lounging on a couch reading SOMEONE's manuscript.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS95
SOMEONE snatches it away.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS96
SOMEONE settles into a leather chair.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS97
SOMEONE sits at a desk and takes out a pen.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS98
He fills out a check.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS99
SOMEONE holds up his hands, then turns to SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS100
He looks at SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS101
He rips up the check.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS102
SOMEONE blocks the door.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS103
He reaches into his jacket.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS104
SOMEONE wrestles SOMEONE to the ground.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS105
He adjusts his glasses on his face as he holds SOMEONE down.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS106
As SOMEONE flails his legs, SOMEONE ties a Kirkland rope around his ankles.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS107
Normal forces some pills into SOMEONE's mouth.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS108
In the bathroom, SOMEONE squishes his nose against a window and moves his face up and down.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS109
SOMEONE waits in the adjoining bedroom.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS110
She sinks to the floor, he back pressed against the wall.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS111
Now, SOMEONE opens the window overlooking the backyard and leans out.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS112
Sun shines on his bare back.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS113
Below, oblivious guests sit at tables and mingle.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS114
Gazing around in amazement, SOMEONE reaches his arms out.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS115
His fiancé waits obliviously on the other side of the door.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS116
SOMEONE steps his bare feet out the window, then perches on the slanted roof.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS117
He smiles as the sun glistens on his naked body.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS118
Back in the study room.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS120
SOMEONE hushes them, then leads them into the bathroom. SOMEONE watches suspiciously.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS121
SOMEONE glances at the bound and gagged dwarf.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS122
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exist the study.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS123
The brothers join the Reverend in front of their father's coffin.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS124
She struggles to stand.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS125
He stares off confoundedly.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS126
On his way out SOMEONE glances smugly at her.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS127
On the roof.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS128
SOMEONE childishly claps his bare bent legs together.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS129
He ads to the rhythm by tapping his knees with his hands.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS131
In the kitchen. He finds a half-eaten plate of it by SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS133
He has pensive gaze.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS135
SOMEONE and SOMEONE, lift SOMEONE by his shoulders and ankles.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS136
They toss him behind the couch. SOMEONE hurries over to the door.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS137
SOMEONE jumps over the couch, landing on SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS138
SOMEONE opens the door.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS139
In the sunroom.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS140
He pats SOMEONE's chest.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS141
He knees SOMEONE in the groin.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS142
Doubling over the younger brother punches SOMEONE in the crotch.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS143
A view from the porch shows their silhouettes grappling behind the window shades.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS144
SOMEONE looks in.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS145
SOMEONE comes in and shuts the door.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS146
SOMEONE shows his wife the sex photo.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS147
In the studies adjoining bathroom, Roman hugs SOMEONE over the toilet.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS148
SOMEONE comes out from his hiding place.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS149
Left alone, SOMEONE peeks up from behind the couch, then removes his gag.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS150
Normal lowers SOMEONE onto the toilet.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS151
He yanks his hand out from under SOMEONE. It's covered in diarrhea.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS152
SOMEONE halts in his tracks, shrieking as SOMEONE rinses his hand in the sink.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS153
The getting water splashes the poo in all directions.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS154
SOMEONE turns. Diarrhea smears his face.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS155
Recoiling, SOMEONE holds out a towel.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS156
SOMEONE faces a mirror.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS157
SOMEONE suppresses a sob and Uncle SOMEONE dozes off.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS158
On the couch in the study, SOMEONE dances around in circles. Back in the bathroom, SOMEONE blots his face with a towel.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS159
On the couch, SOMEONE grimaces madly.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS160
SOMEONE falls off the couch.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS161
SOMEONE and SOMEONE peek in to find him lying motionless next to a broken corner of the coffee table.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS162
SOMEONE shuts the bathroom door while SOMEONE gently nudges SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS163
In the sunroom.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS164
SOMEONE storms out leaving the doors to the parlor wide open.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS165
Heading out the brothers spot SOMEONE leaving the study.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS166
He crosses toward them with a frozen grin.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS167
The brothers sniff the air, then following him across the crowded parlor.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS168
SOMEONE opens the study door, ushering them in.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS169
SOMEONE stares.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS170
SOMEONE slaps him.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS172
SOMEONE joins SOMEONE near a window.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS173
SOMEONE shakes her.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS174
He forcibly kisses her.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS175
The struggle takes them to the window and SOMEONE sees them.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS176
She punches SOMEONE and faces a retreating SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS177
She opens the windows.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS178
Below, the  funeral guests gather in the yard to watch.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS179
Climbing higher, SOMEONE takes a tumble.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS180
He stands.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS181
He gazes down from the roofs edge.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS182
Meanwhile in the study.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS183
They carry SOMEONE to the bathroom.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS184
On the toilet SOMEONE wakes.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS185
SOMEONE shuts the door.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS186
As the others carry SOMEONE out of view, SOMEONE opens up a crack.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS187
SOMEONE leans in.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS188
SOMEONE sits on the couch with the others.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS189
SOMEONE leaves and SOMEONE shuts the door.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS190
Racing from the study, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sprint out to the backyard.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS191
SOMEONE climbs out.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS192
She makes her way toward SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS193
Below, SOMEONE taps SOMEONE's shoulder.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS194
In the study, SOMEONE nudges SOMEONE's foot off his leg.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS195
SOMEONE leans forward tentively as SOMEONE lets his brother in.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS196
The brothers lift SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS197
SOMEONE leads them to the deserted parlor.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS198
Standing in the hallway, SOMEONE slides the rooms ornate doors shut.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS199
Just as Reverend Davis arrives.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS200
In the parlor, the brothers maneuver their way past rows of chairs.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS201
In the parlor the brothers struggle unsuccessfully to hold the dwarf and open the coffin at the same time.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS202
They drop him, then lift the coffin's lid.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS203
Back in the hallway.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS204
Meanwhile, the brother's hoist up SOMEONE's limp body again.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS205
They lay him face down in the casket. His feet on either side of SOMEONE's head.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS206
SOMEONE regards the arrangement disapprovingly.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS207
SOMEONE lies with his face buried in SOMEONE's crotch.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS208
The Reverend tries to sneak past SOMEONE who grabs him.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS209
In the parlor.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS210
SOMEONE stares into the coffin where SOMEONE now lies snuggled against SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS211
On the roof.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS212
SOMEONE stares at SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS213
She swallows as she holds his gaze.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS214
Grinning, SOMEONE hugs her.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS215
She rushes to the parlor.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS216
The coffin sits closed behind them. On the roof SOMEONE and SOMEONE kiss.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS217
SOMEONE slips. He grabs the roofs ledge and hangs in front of a window.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS218
SOMEONE vainly struggles to lift his naked body back onto the ledge. Meanwhile, SOMEONE sprints into the house.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS219
SOMEONE rushes up the stairs.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS220
He barrels into the bathroom door. It bursts open and he finds SOMEONE hanging in front of the window.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS221
He grabs onto him.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS222
SOMEONE's crotch presses against SOMEONE's cheek.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS223
He holds SOMEONE right underneath his buttocks.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS224
She watches him slip out of view into the house, then collapses tiredly. In the parlor the guests reconvene.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS225
She eyes him as she sniffs.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS226
She hurries off.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS228
With a smirk, SOMEONE nods at his mother. She glances around, then frowns.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS229
They all look around.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS231
He eyes her belly.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS232
Gurgling mouthwash SOMEONE gives a thumbs up.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS233
As he spits, SOMEONE pats his shoulder.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS234
SOMEONE pushes him off.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS235
SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE's cheek.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS236
He heads off.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS237
She hugs SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS238
In the bedroom SOMEONE pauses.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS239
He searches his pockets. He flinches as SOMEONE grabs him.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS240
As he hurries away, SOMEONE leads SOMEONE out of the bathroom.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS241
They embrace tenderly.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS242
As they part, SOMEONE hugs SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS243
He kisses him.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS244
Downstairs, SOMEONE and SOMEONE rush into the study bathroom.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS245
In the parlor.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS246
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS247
SOMEONE hands SOMEONE the keys then spreads his arms for a hug. SOMEONE pats him instead.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS248
SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS249
Reverend Davis approaches SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS250
SOMEONE stands.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS251
He buttons his jacket as he faces the room.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS252
Then reaches into his pocket and pulls out his notes.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS253
He glances at SOMEONE who nods reassuringly.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS254
With wide eyes he reads.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS255
SOMEONE turns his quizzical gaze to the coffin behind him.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS256
SOMEONE frowns and SOMEONE shifts uneasily.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS257
The coffin shakes.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS258
It opens and SOMEONE sits up.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS259
SOMEONE leans on the coffin's rim and glares out at the room.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS260
SOMEONE claps.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS261
SOMEONE clings to his dead lover as SOMEONE tries to pry him out.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS262
SOMEONE watches with an awed grin.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS263
SOMEONE photos fall at SOMEONE's feet as SOMEONE and SOMEONE drag him away.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS264
SOMEONE, SOMEONE, and SOMEONE fall. SOMEONE picks up the photos.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS265
She turns to SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS266
She charges at him.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS267
Grabbing a guests hat she beats him with it.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS268
SOMEONE gapes. As SOMEONE and SOMEONE try to restrain SOMEONE she swats them away.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS269
SOMEONE tosses his notes.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS270
SOMEONE holds SOMEONE's tearful gaze. She smiles. SOMEONE gives an appreciative nod.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS271
SOMEONE fans himself and wipes away tears. SOMEONE heads down the aisle.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS272
He rests his hand on Uncle SOMEONE's shoulder as he passes by.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS273
He pounds SOMEONE's fist and squeezes his mother's hand.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS274
Smiling SOMEONE sits up and watches SOMEONE exit.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS275
SOMEONE pushes him back down.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS276
Uncle SOMEONE eyes the photo from the Dreamgirls premier.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS277
He shakes his head pensively.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS279
Now, SOMEONE strolls downstairs with a suitcase in each hand and sets them by a table in the foyer.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS280
SOMEONE looks over from the parlor.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS281
He sits beside SOMEONE.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS282
SOMEONE opens the front door and finds Martina waiting outside in a red sports car.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS283
SOMEONE waves.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS284
SOMEONE strolls over.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS285
They hug.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS286
They shake hands and embrace.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS287
SOMEONE bites his lip excitedly as he saunters to Martina's car.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS288
SOMEONE and SOMEONE watch from the doorway.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS289
SOMEONE pauses. Turning, he grins at the couple then gives them a shrug.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS290
As he hurries to the car Martina smiles. Later, SOMEONE and SOMEONE lounge on a couch.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS291
She whispers into his ear.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS292
They kiss.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS293
Grinning, SOMEONE returns his wife's kisses, then pulls away.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS294
On the roof.
DEATH_AT_A_FUNERAL_DVS295
Uncle SOMEONE sits naked above the bathroom window.