They pause at the edge of the clearing where they behold an amazing house made of candy and pastries.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS36
The children cautiously walk through the compound up to the house, looking around as they go.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS37
They stop and exchange a glance before they charge to the door and pound on it.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS39
the boy breaks off a piece of the house and starts to eat it.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS40
The girl picks off a piece near her and tastes it as well.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS42
As the siblings chew, the door to the cottage creaks open.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS43
With an unnerved look at each other, the duo enters the house hesitantly
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS44
and the door slowly closes behind them.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS45
Inside, flames light on candles around the room.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS46
The kids grab hold of one another as they suddenly see the twisted silhouette of a figure watching them.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS47
The siblings clutch each other in fright as a disfigured witch with rotted teeth walks into the light,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS48
eyeing them with an evil smirk.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS49
Later, the young boy is imprisoned in a cage while his shackled sister looks on.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS50
The witch strikes her and she falls.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS51
The witch attempts to force feed the boy.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS52
The girl pulls out a loose nail and pockets it as the witch grabs her and holds a knife to her throat.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS54
Her brother reluctantly eats.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS55
A fire blazes in an oven.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS56
The witch slams her knife into a stool and moves to the cage, grabbing the boy.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS57
As she and the boy struggle, the girl picks the lock on her chain with the nail until it pops open.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS58
The witch then opens the oven door.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS59
The girl runs to the stool and picks up the knife.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS60
The witch slowly turns around to her and fires a bolt from her wand.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS61
It shoots right through the girl doing no harm.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS62
The girl stabs her repeatedly with the knife.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS63
As the hut collapses, the girl frees her brother.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS64
Behind them, the witch slowly gets to her feet spitting blood.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS66
The boy strikes the witch with the log causing her to fall back into the oven.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS68
The siblings yank on a chain that closes the furnace as they watch her burn.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS69
Over a gust of flames,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS73
witch defeated by orphaned siblings.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS74
Town welcomes orphaned siblings after escaping witch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS79
An etching of a town surrounded by mountains.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS86
A lost child poster burns in a dark forest.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS87
A drawing of a monster chasing three children under the headline, "Child Saved by Hansel and Gretel".
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS91
An engraving of hanging witches.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS97
An etching of the two children restraining a witch as she burns over a pyre.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS98
The girl shoots her crossbow and beheads a witch flying on a broomstick.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS102
A silhouette standing in the flames shoots a burning arrow past some towns people.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS103
Town saved by Hansel and Gretel. Witch burned.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS105
Another headline: Meadow witch killed.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS109
'Heroes, Hansel and Gretel, swamp witch dead' over a picture of two young adults spearing a prostrate witch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS112
The numerous dark outlines of trees have missing children posters attached to them.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS113
From out of nowhere, an arrow pins a sheet of paper to a tree.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS115
The poster is consumed by flames.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS116
Many years later, a man unloads jugs of milk featuring a drawing of a young boy's face on them.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS117
A teenage boy grabs one and runs towards a gathering of townspeople.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS118
He immerses the captive woman's head in a barrel of water.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS119
The woman struggles with her captors as a man in his 50s approaches.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS120
He turns to the crowd.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS121
A gun appears at pointblank range near SOMEONE's head.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS122
They disperse as SOMEONE turns to Mina, a young woman with light hair.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS123
SOMEONE headbutts the Sheriff.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS124
His deputies grab their guns but SOMEONE aims at them first.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS125
SOMEONE lowers his gun.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS126
On the ground, SOMEONE grasps his bloody nose.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS127
Gretel, a young woman with dark hair and an athletic build, kicks down the door of an isolated cottage in the woods.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS128
She points her crossbow at a witch with scaly skin and black hair who turns and raises her hands to her head.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS129
The hag throws a dagger at SOMEONE who catches it with the end of her crossbow and shoots at the witch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS130
The witch dodges the bolts, grabs her broom and flies through a window, breaking some wooden panes as she bursts through.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS131
As she soars through the forest,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS132
she is shot and is sent crashing to the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS134
SOMEONE, a young muscular man with dark hair, stands nearby with his gun on his shoulder, his foot resting on the witch's broomstick.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS135
As the witch scurries away, he shoots then runs after her in pursuit.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS136
The witch grabs her wand and fires at him, but the dark energy bounces off him.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS137
She then casts a spell and barrier of tall, thin trees raises in front of him.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS138
SOMEONE weakens the barrier by shooting at it and then runs through.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS139
Nearby, SOMEONE listens to the sounds of battle.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS140
The witch continues on her flight, a demon-like quality giving her speed and agility through the obstacles of the forest
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS141
as SOMEONE pursues closely behind.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS142
As the witch pulls ahead, SOMEONE flies out of the underbrush and tackles her to the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS143
SOMEONE catches up with the witch and the two of them exchange blows.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS144
SOMEONE strikes the witch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS145
SOMEONE is blinded as the hag throws dirt in his eyes.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS146
SOMEONE catches the witch and slams her body into the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS147
The witch gets up and turns to flee.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS149
SOMEONE somersaults, grabs her crossbow and shoots the witch in the ankle.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS150
She heaves the weapon over a branch and pulls on a string attached to the arrow
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS151
Dragging the witch until she hangs suspended in the air by her foot.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS153
SOMEONE snatches the witches wand away from her.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS154
The witch flails in mid-air as the siblings watch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS155
He strikes her with his gun.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS156
SOMEONE unrolls a scroll.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS157
SOMEONE checks his wrist-timer.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS158
He injects a substance into his thigh.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS159
Later, a man fills a water bowl for two dogs.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS160
Inside, He throws the boot on the table.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS161
The Sheriff sits facing a few burly men.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS162
SOMEONE throws a pouch down in front of the men.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS163
Coins spill out catching the mercenaries attention.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS164
Outside, a large man with long, blonde hair takes the dogs and leads the men out of town.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS165
SOMEONE watches then saunters off smoking a pipe.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS166
Deep in the dark forest, an unbroken swathe of trees stretches to the horizon.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS167
A fire is lit in a small clearing.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS168
The light casts eerily shadows into the gloom as the nervous trackers huddle around the meager flames.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS169
One of the men picks up a bone and casts it to the dogs.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS170
The men turn to the ignored bone and notice that the dogs are missing.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS171
They look up to see a beautiful woman with long, dark hair
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS172
standing at the edge of the firelight, flanked by the two dogs.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS173
The slowly get up and approach the stranger.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS175
The woman morphs into a with and the dogs attack their owner.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS176
They scatter.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS177
She casts a spell causing vines to ensnare and suspend a tracker in midair,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS178
Stretching his limbs out in all four directions.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS179
With a sweep of her wand, the man's limbs are torn from his core and drop to the ground with a thud.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS180
The witch then intercepts the remaining hunter.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS181
She touches his forehead and, suddenly, creepy crawlers begin to slither around under his skin.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS182
The hunter's eyes roll slightly as he starts to dig into the mulch and devour the insects within.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS183
The witch watches and snickers.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS184
Later, SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit in a pub.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS185
The survivor from the forest staggers into the pub.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS186
He stumbles toward the center of the pub.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS187
The tracker starts to gag and retch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS188
SOMEONE moves SOMEONE  in front of him as a shield.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS189
The man explodes from his stomach sending gore flying in all directions.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS191
Maggots lie among the remains of the tracker.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS192
SOMEONE wipes away from some SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS193
In the dark forest, amid the dense tangle of narrow trees, a tree root snakes across the ground
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS194
and buries deep into the earth to the witches lair.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS195
It branches out to form cages, which imprison missing children.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS196
They cower in their cells as a monstrous troll passes by throwing food from a bucket into their prisons.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS197
The troll throws the bucket aside
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS198
and stomps into a dining room where the dark haired witch places two bowls in front of her cohorts.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS199
who take them and drink eagerly.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS200
One of the witches, who has short spiky hair, sets her bowl down and raises her hands in wonder.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS201
The head witch grabs her hand and pushes it down into a nearby flame.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS202
The third witch grins.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS203
She cradles her singed hand.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS204
The town is silent under the night sky.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS205
Nothing stirs and only a few flickering lamps release the darkness.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS206
SOMEONE sleeps deeply, her hands folded beneath her head.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS207
She dreams of her mother the night that the siblings were taken into the forest
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS208
and of the father leading them deeper into the woods.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS209
She wakes up and looks down at her brother who is sleeping on the floor.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS210
He rolls over dismissively.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS211
SOMEONE pauses a moment
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS212
then gets out of the bed and walks to the window in her nightdress.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS213
She looks out, her hand resting near the celestial map of the bloodmoon.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS214
In the morning,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS215
SOMEONE's buying clothes at a local shop.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS216
He rolls up the boy's garment as SOMEONE approaches him from behind.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS217
He walks away.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS218
SOMEONE pauses.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS219
He checks his wrist-timer.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS220
He hands a pumpkin and lowers himself carefully onto a stoop.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS221
He removes a syringe from his bag.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS222
SOMEONE injects himself.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS223
He repacks his syringe and gets up, smiling a little awkwardly at SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS224
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE leave.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS226
In the forest, the spiky haired witch examines some frogs clambering in the moss on a tree.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS227
She picks one up.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS228
She approaches the figure of a boy sitting on a fallen tree trunk.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS229
The pumpkin falls from under a wig.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS230
She looks, confused, at a gramophone.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS231
She picks up the record.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS232
SOMEONE and SOMEONE attack the witch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS233
SOMEONE appears from the underbrush.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS234
SOMEONE advances cautiously.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS235
The witch suddenly moves, disarming SOMEONE and aiming her crossbow at SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS236
He swiftly bends backwards, just missing the path of the bolt.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS237
SOMEONE jumps on top of the hag and tries to reach her wand,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS238
but gets thrown off onto SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS239
SOMEONE charges the witch, but she easily fells him and starts to make her escape.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS240
SOMEONE and SOMEONE both follow in hot pursuit.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS241
She grabs her broom and takes flight.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS242
SOMEONE charges ahead and knocks her off mid-air
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS243
using his gun like a baseball bat.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS244
SOMEONE runs up behind the witch and a battle ensues.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS245
When SOMEONE tries to grab his fallen weapon, the witch uses the prongs on the end of her broom to sweep it out of his reach.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS246
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS247
The witch gains the upper hand, knocking down both SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS248
She once again mounts her brom and soars through the forest.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS249
SOMEONE throws out a grappling hook and snags her broom.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS250
He attaches her to his belt and is dragged across the ground behind the fleeing hag.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS251
SOMEONE anchors his feet against two trees causing the broom to pull out from under the witch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS252
She hits a tree and crumples to the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS253
SOMEONE and SOMEONE advance as the witch gets to her feet.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS254
Just as she raises her hand to cast a spell,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS255
SOMEONE jumps out from behind and electrocutes her.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS258
Back in town, SOMEONE watches the Mayor leave and then looks up at the cell where the spiky haired witch is being interrogated by SOMEONE and SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS259
SOMEONE dons a set of brass knuckles.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS261
Blood gurgles from the witches mouth.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS262
SOMEONE rummages through the missing children's files.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS263
SOMEONE rushes out of the room.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS264
High above the town, SOMEONE and her other witch, one with red hair, hover menacingly, surveying the town and its sleeping inhabitants.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS265
The red-haired witch swoops down.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS266
SOMEONE sparks a ball of fire and holds it in her palm.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS267
SOMEONE takes aim and casts the fireball towards the town.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS268
Little SOMEONE sleeps peacefully in her bed.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS269
Outside the bedroom, her older brother and mother keep watch nervously.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS270
In town, people urgently try to douse the blaze of SOMEONE's fireball.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS271
The door explodes open and the red-haired witch stalks into the house.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS272
She hexes the rifle he is holding and forces him to point it towards his mother.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS273
She is blown out of the window.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS274
SOMEONE is thrown in a cage.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS275
The troll closes the cage and lifts it on his back.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS276
SOMEONE locks the spiky-haired witch in a cell.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS277
The door shatters and Muriel, as a woman, saunters through the SOMEONE as Gretel, standing on the balcony, aims her crossbow at her.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS278
SOMEONE picks up a missing child's poster.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS279
With a wicked smile, SOMEONE morphs into a witch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS280
SOMEONE opens fire as SOMEONE charges at the stairs.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS281
The witch grabs him and throws him, shattering the bannister as he falls.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS283
SOMEONE pulls out a knife and swings, but SOMEONE disarms her and grabs her by the throat.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS284
The retreating troll turns to look at SOMEONE
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS285
just as the red-haired witch tackles him to the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS286
They exchange blows.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS287
SOMEONE grabs a milk bottle and uses it to bludgeon the hag
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS288
who then hexes a box and hurls it at SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS289
The crone then grabs her broom and starts to take off.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS290
SOMEONE takes a running jump and catches hold of the broom as the witch flees town.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS291
He slams through part of a roof, which shatters, while he is still clinging to the broom.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS292
In the Sheriff's office,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS293
SOMEONE struggles to his feet.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS294
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE reaching for his gun.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS295
She throw SOMEONE away from her as she turns to divert the bullets.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS297
SOMEONE watches SOMEONE fall.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS299
SOMEONE struggles to reload the shotgun as SOMEONE stalks him.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS300
She casts a spell with her wand
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS302
and slowly directs the barrel of the gun to his head.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS303
SOMEONE looks on, whimpering.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS304
The gun rests under SOMEONE's chin.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS305
SOMEONE uses a wheelbarrow to transport Gretel, injured and unconscious, through the streets.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS307
Inside, SOMEONE frees the horned witch and then looks for SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS308
It's morning and SOMEONE lies sleeping peacefully as a hand with a damp clothe wipes her face.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS309
SOMEONE moistens the cloth and starts to clean her neck.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS310
He looks around for a moment and then proceeds to clean her chest, which rises and falls slowly.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS311
Just as he is about to approach her cleavage with the clothe, she grabs his hand.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS312
She glares at him.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS313
SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a sceptical glance before releasing his hand.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS314
She looks around her and out of the window.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS315
SOMEONE notices a drawing of herself on the wall.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS316
SOMEONE looks at her sheepishly.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS317
SOMEONE looks down as SOMEONE turns to the wall.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS318
At the dining table, SOMEONE reads SOMEONE scrapbook of newspaper clippings.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS319
SOMEONE sets the bowl down and pulls a chair forward.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS320
SOMEONE turns a page and stops to stare at an etching of a woman.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS321
Moving closer to the book, she points to the face.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS322
SOMEONE leans froward.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS323
SOMEONE has flashbacks of her mother.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS324
SOMEONE dangles from a tree, unconscious.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS325
He awakens.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS326
She points to her right.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS327
He falls to the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS328
SOMEONE tramps through another part of the woods.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS329
Twisted roots lie among the towering trees.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS330
SOMEONE cleans SOMEONE's wounds by a body of water situated in a gully.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS331
She dampens the clothe again
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS332
and dabs at his neck with the clothe.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS333
SOMEONE looks at the pool with uncertainty, then back at SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS334
She stands up and starts to disrobe.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS336
SOMEONE gets up and turns his back to her.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS337
Mina, now naked, delicately steps into the pool, her skin glowing.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS338
SOMEONE steals a glance and is transfixed.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS339
SOMEONE smiles at him as he enters the water.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS340
She moves towards SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS341
She kisses him.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS342
They embrace passionately.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS343
SOMEONE continues walking through the woods, looking around.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS344
Nearby, the troll looks up from his meal of wild boar.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS345
SOMEONE stops near a fallen tree.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS346
She notices movement in the distance and cautiously investigates, her crossbow at the ready.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS348
She takes aim and moves silently towards the figure hidden by the branches.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS349
As she draws closer, she pushes the tree limbs aside
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS350
and sees one of the sheriff's deputies standing by the tree.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS351
A man assaults her, forcing her into a clearing.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS352
SOMEONE fights back.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS353
Three deputies restrain her by holding her arms and hair.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS354
The Sheriff approaches.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS355
SOMEONE lunges forward and bites the tip of SOMEONE's nose off, then pulls back and spits the piece in his face.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS358
He approaches her with a bloody face, his teeth clenched in fury and pain, and strikes SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS359
The troll watches from the trees as she falls to the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS360
The Sheriff kicks her in the stomach.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS361
The troll crashes through the tree.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS362
The giant grabs a tree trunk and wields it like a club, smashing two of the deputies.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS363
He clubs another man in the head.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS365
The last deputy tries shooting the troll.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS366
Unfazed by the bullets, he crushes the last deputy's head.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS367
The troll then walks up to SOMEONE, who has fallen on the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS369
The troll stomps on his head, his brains and blood splattering on the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS371
SOMEONE's vision of the monster starts to blur as she passes out.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS372
SOMEONE awakens to the gentle rocking motion of being carried.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS373
She looks behind her to see and unfamiliar path in the woods.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS374
She turns her head to find the side of the troll's head.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS375
SOMEONE closes her eyes and leans her head to rest against the giant's shoulder.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS376
They continue down the path, disappearing into the forest.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS378
Back at the gully, SOMEONE kisses SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS379
The troll settles SOMEONE down by a waterfall.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS380
He sticks his finger into a crevice and pulls out a pale substance.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS381
SOMEONE begins to wake and tries to get away when she sees the giant.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS382
The troll holds her down and wipes the material on her injury.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS383
He then places a dried mushroom under the waterfall like a cup to collect water,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS384
which he then offers to SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS385
She quickly gulps the water down to pacify him and watches the giant with trepidation.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS386
SOMEONE stares wide-eyed as the troll nods in satisfaction and then walks away.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS387
A little while later,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS388
SOMEONE has managed to remove most of the dirt and blood from her face.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS389
The troll sits across from her and she watches him curiously.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS390
He looks down,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS391
then gets up in a huff.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS392
He stops and turns around, her gaze is soft.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS394
With a last look, the troll leaves.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS395
SOMEONE looks around in frustration.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS396
The day passes and gives way to night over the dense forest.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS397
SOMEONE comes to a stop at the edge of a dell when he stops an abandoned cottage.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS398
He looks around with a furrowed brow as he walks towards the house.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS399
He stops midway to the house to pick up a rock, which he hurls at the building.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS400
He bends down and picks up a log to act as a club.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS401
Approaching the cottage with a little more bravado,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS402
he enters, the rusty hedges of the door squeaking in protest.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS404
Inside the house, he walks past two eerily familiar children's beds.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS405
when suddenly, a figure charges at him from behind the door and they both crash through a rotten floorboard into a cave below.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS406
SOMEONE embraces her brother.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS407
Tears fill her eyes as SOMEONE holds her.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS408
With a creased brow, SOMEONE looks around the cave.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS409
With difficulty, he gets to his feet.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS410
They start to investigate the area.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS411
SOMEONE lights a match and then a candle.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS412
The glow of the candle illuminates an ancient text woven with herbs and strange letters.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS413
SOMEONE turns a page.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS414
SOMEONE heaves himself out from the underground dwelling and then reaches down to help SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS415
She then raises the candle to look around the interior.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS416
She turns and walks over to SOMEONE, who is holding a toy and standing at the foot of one of the small beds.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS417
He takes the candle.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS418
He places his hand on a faded drawing on the wall of two kids and an animal.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS419
SOMEONE sits on the bed and leans back.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS420
SOMEONE give SOMEONE a pensive loo and she watches him as he surveys the abandoned cottage.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS421
SOMEONE's expression hardens and he stands up.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS422
She points to the cellar.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS423
SOMEONE throws a metal rod at Muriel, who deflects it with her wand
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS424
and cuts off their escape route through the door.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS425
SOMEONE and SOMEONE exchange and uneasy glance.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS426
She points her wand at the hearth and a fire appears.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS427
A flashback of the siblings youth.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS428
The night of their abandonment.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS431
His feet flail as he dies.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS432
SOMEONE pulls out a knife and battles SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS433
Using her unnatural strength, she grabs SOMEONE and stabs him in the stomach.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS434
She stabs him again and pushes him down into the cellar.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS435
SOMEONE grabs SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS436
It's morning in the abandoned cottage and SOMEONE wakes up to find SOMEONE tending to his wound.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS437
He pushes aside the bowl.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS438
He looks around at the accoutrements of a witch scattered around him.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS439
He stands and lifts his shirt to examine his wound which is almost completely healed.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS440
He pushes past her, confused.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS441
He reveals a cart loaded with armaments and ammunition.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS442
SOMEONE blesses some fluid using an incantation from the book
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS443
and then splashes the liquid liberally all over the ammunition.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS444
The group chooses weapons from the cart.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS445
SOMEONE climbs onto his horse and turns to SOMEONE who  is holding the reigns of the steed.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS446
SOMEONE lets the reigns go and shoots SOMEONE an awkward smile as his eyes dart side to side.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS447
SOMEONE helps SOMEONE mount the horse.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS448
From behind, SOMEONE grasps SOMEONE's gun.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS449
The group leaves town.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS450
SOMEONE regains consciousness and discovers herself imprisoned in the witches lair.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS451
SOMEONE approaches her cell.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS452
A door opens behind them.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS453
SOMEONE looks around and notices the missing children in cages.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS454
She puts her tiny hand on the trolls giant finger.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS455
The spiky-haired witch turns to SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS456
In the forest, late at night, SOMEONE and SOMEONE create a network of tightly stretched thin wires between trees.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS457
They stop and look at the top of a hill where a fire glows in the darkness marking the place of the witches Sabbath.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS458
He gives SOMEONE a gun.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS459
SOMEONE looks up at the full moon as numerous witches glide into the clearing on top of the hill to join the throng.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS460
Castors of all shapes and sizes mingle at the gathering in their outrageous costumes.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS461
SOMEONE is dragged to a dead and deteriorated tree as SOMEONE floats in.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS462
The spiky-haired witch punches her in the stomach before chaining her to the tree.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS463
The assembled witches turn to look at SOMEONE as SOMEONE leads the children into the middle of the gathering.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS464
SOMEONE lights a fire under a giant cauldron and the liquid within begins to bubble.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS465
SOMEONE walks away as SOMEONE looks out at the gathered witches below.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS466
SOMEONE stares at the bloodmoon.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS468
SOMEONE walks into the clearing.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS469
The hags turn to him.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS470
The read-haired witch walks in front of SOMEONE and raises her wand.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS471
Everyone watches the standoff eagerly as neither SOMEONE or the witch budges.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS472
SOMEONE takes off the red-haired witches head with a single shot.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS474
SOMEONE takes the cue and maneuvers the machine gun into position.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS475
The witches are cutdown down in great swathes by the rapid fire.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS477
SOMEONE and the spiky-haired witch dive for cover behind a rock as the other crones start scatter and flee.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS478
Some managing to get on their brooms.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS479
SOMEONE uses a combination of hand grenades and rifle fire to take down the numerous targets
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS480
while SOMEONE starts to pick off the flying hags as they soar away from the clearing.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS482
As the fighting intensifies, SOMEONE uses his rifle and his bayonet to slash and stab the witches.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS483
SOMEONE abandons the children that are huddled against the rock face.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS484
The spiky-haired witch runs toward the children and uses another witch as a shield to avoid being shot by SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS485
Suddenly, her gun jams.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS486
a witch takes flight toward SOMEONE's position.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS487
SOMEONE shoots the attacking witch in the back.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS488
SOMEONE jumps out of hiding as a large witch tries to hex SOMEONE but misses and hits a tree,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS489
which falls and crushes her.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS490
The spiky-haired witch gathers the children as SOMEONE stalks toward SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS491
Just as SOMEONE is about to strike Gretel, SOMEONE blocks her advance and knocks the witch aside.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS492
Right as the horned-witch is about to execute a little girl,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS493
SOMEONE shoots her in the abdomen.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS494
She collapses to the ground and looks up as SOMEONE takes aim at her head.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS495
The onlooking children wince.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS496
SOMEONE pulls apart one of SOMEONE's bindings just as SOMEONE throws him off the cliff with her wand.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS497
SOMEONE wraps a chain around her fist and charges Muriel, knocking her to the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS498
SOMEONE frees the children from their fetters.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS499
SOMEONE swings at SOMEONE with a knife, as SOMEONE frees the last child.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS500
SOMEONE turns to help SOMEONE but is confronted by siamese twin witches joined at the back.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS501
The duo attacks him ferociously with long blades.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS502
SOMEONE grabs some weapons and runs to join the fray.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS503
SOMEONE and SOMEONE fight desperately with SOMEONE gaining the upper hand.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS504
She throw the hunter to the ground and crouches over her with a weapon.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS505
SOMEONE grabs the knife hand and the two struggle for dominance.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS506
The sun starts to rise over the horizon.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS507
SOMEONE headbutts SOMEONE who staggers away and grabs her broom to retreat.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS508
SOMEONE throws a twin crossbow to SOMEONE who catches it
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS509
and dispatches two witches that were charging her from opposite sides.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS510
She then picks up a spiky chain and lassoes at around the abdomen of a fleeing witch, who then explodes into tiny pieces.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS511
One of the twins stabs SOMEONE in the leg and, as he falls, they dart towards him.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS512
But he takes them out with a swing of his foot.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS513
SOMEONE approaches with her crossbow.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS514
In the forest, SOMEONE follows two other witches on their brooms.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS515
They head for the trees with the wires stretched between them,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS516
but the two are unable to stop in time and are sliced to bits by the taut strings.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS518
SOMEONE comes to a halt in front of the trap and starts in another direction right past SOMEONE whose resting against a tree trunk.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS521
He looks over his shoulder eyeing her approach.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS522
He lifts the rifle, takes careful aim and fires.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS523
The spinning bullet unravels and explodes,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS525
expelling bits of shrapnel that knock SOMEONE of her broom.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS526
SOMEONE, SOMEONE and SOMEONE run to the sight of impact which is scattered with shards of Muriels broom.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS527
SOMEONE picks up and pockets one of the pieces.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS528
SOMEONE runs to Edwards side.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS529
She opens her bag and pulls out the stun gun,
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS530
charges the battery quickly
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS531
and administers the electricity.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS532
When the troll doesn't move, she checks his heartbeat and tries again.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS533
She stabs the reeds into Edwards body.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS535
He shakes himself awake as she rests her head on his shoulder in relief.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS536
Meanwhile, SOMEONE and the others track a wounded SOMEONE through the forest.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS537
A bloody handprint on a tree provides a clue.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS538
At the edge of a clearing, the group comes to a halt.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS539
in the overgrown dell stands the derelict gingerbread house where SOMEONE and SOMEONE killed their first witch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS540
They advance cautiously.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS541
Suddenly, SOMEONE is thrown to the ground with a jolt.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS542
SOMEONE whips around, weapon poised, to find SOMEONE holding her wand to SOMEONE's neck.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS543
SOMEONE begins to put the gun on the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS545
He pulls out a pistol from behind his back and accidentally shoots SOMEONE in the shoulder, just missing SOMEONE who then attacks him with enchanted logs.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS548
SOMEONE stands with her wand ready after assaulting SOMEONE with a spell.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS549
He shatters a tree behind SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS551
SOMEONE casts a spell and throws SOMEONE against the house. The evil witch then materialises near SOMEONE and grabs her.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS552
SOMEONE stabs SOMEONE with her wand.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS553
SOMEONE crumples to the ground.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS554
SOMEONE fires at SOMEONE driving her into the pastry house. He runs to SOMEONE's side and turns
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS555
He her over.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS556
Her body relaxes in death.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS557
SOMEONE lowers her corpse and looks toward the house, his expression hardening.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS558
He somersaults into the house where the witch attacks him with a shovel.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS559
The two grapple with each other as SOMEONE comes running up to the clearance.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS561
SOMEONE charges into the house but is swiftly felled by the hag.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS562
SOMEONE grabs a knife from a table and moves in to stab SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS563
They struggle, each trying to gain the upper hand.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS564
SOMEONE leaps into the fight, wrestling with the witch.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS566
SOMEONE throws them onto SOMEONE and punches the both of them in the face.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS568
The crone then tries to break his neck.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS569
SOMEONE jumps onto SOMEONE's back and the trio falls. The witch kicks SOMEONE into the wall and then picks SOMEONE up and throws her against the dusty oven
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS570
knocking her unconscious.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS571
SOMEONE then grabs a cleaver.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS572
SOMEONE heaves a hanging cauldron into the witches face knocking her down.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS573
He then wraps a chain around her neck and hoists her up using the oven door as a pulley.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS574
He starts to punch her relentlessly.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS575
SOMEONE's face softens as she morphs into her human form.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS576
He continues to pummel her and then starts to strangle SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS577
Her demon face reappears.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS578
The witch grasps at SOMEONE's shoulder in a vain attempt to make him let go.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS579
She slowly starts to pas out when SOMEONE's wrist-timer goes off.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS580
He is unable to keep his hold on her and collapses to his knees.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS581
SOMEONE looks for the syringe but cannot find it.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS582
SOMEONE starts to wake up.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS583
She spots his syringe on the ground as SOMEONE kicks SOMEONE aside and tries to free herself.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS585
Reaches for the syringe, drags herself towards her brother and injects him with the liquid.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS586
SOMEONE kicks aside the prop that was keeping the oven door open.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS588
When she frees herself of the chain, she attacks SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS591
SOMEONE beats her with a shovel and stabs her in the neck with the shovel's blade.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS593
SOMEONE struggles as SOMEONE walks up and the siblings loom above her.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS594
SOMEONE stamps hard on the blade severing SOMEONE's head.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS596
SOMEONE runs into the house smiling.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS597
SOMEONE turns around holding SOMEONE's head by the hair.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS598
SOMEONE gulps at the sight.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS599
SOMEONE throws the head into the open oven as the siblings walk past SOMEONE.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS600
SOMEONE picks up SOMEONE's gem and its gem glows.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS601
A crowd of townspeople stand around a large fire.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS602
A man throws a pouch of coins, SOMEONE catches it.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS604
The siblings walk away from the blaze.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS606
In a dry and dusty desert, SOMEONE pulls a cart of dead witches.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS607
They stand outside a witches lair.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS608
SOMEONE pouches on the door which shatters forward.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS609
Hansel and Gretel: Witch Hunters. A blonde witch looks up and snarls at the intruders.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS611
The demon backflips away from SOMEONE, trying to escape her machine gun's bullets.
HANSEL_GRETEL_WITCH_HUNTERS_DVS613
Leaving a trail of dust, she tries to escape out of a window, where SOMEONE clubs her.