Montclair, New Jersey.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS25
He mimes being dead.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS26
At his house in Vail,
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS27
SOMEONE steps forward and embraces SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS28
Now, he and his wife and their party guests raise glasses.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS29
A man with boyish features holds up a hand.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS30
He puts an arm around his wife.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS31
January 1st. SOMEONE pours himself coffee.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS32
Now, four skiers stop on a slope.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS33
SOMEONE and his son take off down the mountainside.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS34
Meanwhile, SOMEONE pulls into the State Park.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS35
He hangs a handicap-parking pass on his rear view mirror, then jumps out of the car.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS36
He races into the woods.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS37
On a mountain, a man spies on a bird.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS38
A skier crashes into him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS39
The girl's father drops his head into his folded arms.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS40
Reaching a lake's edge, she spots a bird through his binoculars.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS42
Turning, he sees a massive birder snapping shots of his find.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS43
In Colorado, SOMEONE and his son ski side by side down a slope.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS44
Swerving off to the side, SOMEONE skids to a stop.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS45
His son looks over.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS46
A tally appears, clicking from zero to one.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS47
The tally ticks to two.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS48
Now, an SUV screeches to a halt and SOMEONE snaps a photo out his window.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS49
The tally clicks to three.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS50
Later, SOMEONE packs his belongings into an SUV.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS51
SOMEONE's Day One tally shows 29.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS52
At the park, SOMEONE returns to his car.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS53
His eyes widen and he races back into the woods. As his camera flashes, his Day One tally clicks from 30 to 31.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS54
Now, a view through binoculars shows a flock of seagulls. Standing at an office window, SOMEONE lowers the binoculars and sighs.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS55
His Day One tally clicks to one.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS56
Later, he sits at the dinner table with his father.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS57
Smiling, SOMEONE's mom sits.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS58
His dad lifts his brow.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS59
SOMEONE releases his fork.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS60
SOMEONE storms off. Now, with his boss.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS61
He shows a photo of two kids.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS62
SOMEONE turns away.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS63
He halts.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS64
February 13th, Day 44.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS65
SOMEONE drives.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS66
He brakes. A plane flies. A car arrives outside a Victorian style house. SOMEONE passes through its gate and spots a sign - Stay on path.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS67
Another reads, please ring bell for key. As an old woman answers the door, words appear- Gibson's, British Columbia.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS68
SOMEONE arrives behind SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS69
SOMEONE runs to the back of the house.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS70
She offers the key, then pulls it back.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS71
SOMEONE climbs over a fence.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS72
SOMEONE runs back to his car, his tally ticking to 159. The woman gives SOMEONE the key.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS73
In the heavy downpour, SOMEONE's car peels away. As SOMEONE follows the drenched path to the fence, he answers his cell phone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS74
The key sticks in the gate's lock.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS75
He tries ramming the gate with his shoulder as his associates listen.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS76
Trying to climb the wood plank fence, SOMEONE steps on a garden gnome posted at the gate. As he scans the garden, the ceramic sculpture shatters under his weight.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS77
SOMEONE turns to find the hummingbird flying over the gate.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS78
His jaw drops as the emerald hued bird hovers over his head.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS79
In slow motion, we watch the beats of its tiny wings. As it flies off, SOMEONE beams after it and his tally ticks up to 158.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS80
February 20th. Joshua Tree, California. SOMEONE snaps photos as a skinny man in a turban seated nearby uses a laptop to write a blog titled The Joy of Birding with Ichabod Cranes.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS81
SOMEONE abruptly turns away, listening.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS82
Climbing down off a boulder, he loses his footing and falls. Landing, he crawls along the ground, then flops over and snaps photos of a bird in flight.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS83
His tally ticks to 132.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS84
February 22nd. Coos Bay, Oregon.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS86
On a dock, SOMEONE's eyes narrow as SOMEONE approaches.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS88
SOMEONE draws a knife.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS89
SOMEONE signs autographs, then faces SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS90
Now, the boat travels over the tranquil waters of the Sound.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS91
On the deck, a mustached birder performs a birdcall for a pretty brunette who listens keenly.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS92
SOMEONE nods humbly. The mustached man looks up.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS93
He moves off and others follow him. Nearby, a man cuts up fish on a board.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS94
SOMEONE notices SOMEONE popping pills nearby. He remembers passing by him at the house in Canada.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS95
The workman dumps fish parts over the rail.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS96
SOMEONE queasily eyes the cutting board, then faces SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS97
The older man vomits over the deck railing.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS98
A workman hands over a crumpled rag.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS99
Later, SOMEONE rests on an indoor bench piled with luggage.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS100
He feebly gives SOMEONE the so-so gesture.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS101
SOMEONE points outside where birders flock around SOMEONE as he does bird calls.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS102
As SOMEONE shakes his head, both their tallies appear.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS104
On land the mustached birder brings coffee.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS105
Now, SOMEONE's mother uses a phone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS106
He angrily ends the call. Our view contracts around an owl in a nearby tapestry.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS107
It comes to life and flies at us.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS108
At the wheel of a car, SOMEONE wakes to find himself in the path of an 18-wheeler.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS109
He wrenches the wheel, waking his companion.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS110
Narrowly avoiding the truck, the car skids off the road and slams sideways into a tree.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS111
Leaving the mustached birder in the passenger seat, SOMEONE lowers his window, then climbs out of the car through it.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS112
He faces the tree, grimly inspecting the damage to the car's back door.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS113
SOMEONE turns wide-eyed.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS114
The champion birder ventures into the thick evergreen forest. In the passenger seat,
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS115
the mustached birder keeps one arm at his side as he starts to turn in his seat.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS116
He winces and unbuckles his seat belt, then reaches into the back.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS117
He comes out following SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS118
The champion looks up. Green leafy branches form a canopy overhead, but give no sign of a bird. He treks further into the woods. Shifting his searching gaze, SOMEONE moves a branch aside, then halts at the side of a black and white woodpecker.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS120
Now, in a humble bathroom, SOMEONE uses his cell phone as his socks dry on a line.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS121
Brownfield, Texas.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS122
A view from her suite shows the Eiffel Tower.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS123
Now, a toilet bursts through a window. It lands outside SOMEONE's house.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS124
SOMEONE Hole, Wyoming.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS125
A handsome man arrives.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS126
At an actual dump, SOMEONE snacks on chips.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS127
Other birders wretch and cover their noses.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS128
Impervious to the stench, SOMEONE photographs a bird among the refuse. His two associates arrive.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS129
He photographs them.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS132
SOMEONE gets in a car.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS133
SOMEONE backs out of his parking spot. Now, April 19th, Day 109. A silver luxury car pulls up in front of the SOMEONE's house. The champion birder gets out to find scaffolding framing the entire left wing of his home.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS134
The upper left quarter stands stripped of its siding.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS135
SOMEONE takes it in unhappily, then pulls his bags from the backseat and approaches the house.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS136
The handsome man stands with an older man.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS137
He goes inside.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS138
He moves through a maze of exposed wood framework.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS139
She emerges from the master bathroom.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS140
She puts on a robe.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS141
He grabs her.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS142
Kissing her, he steers her to the bed.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS143
He pauses from their kiss.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS144
Straddling his lap, she kisses him back. The TV shows a weather report.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS145
SOMEONE's eyes stray to the TV. In a store, SOMEONE watches the same report.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS146
In New York, SOMEONE watches the report on a TV behind his office building security desk.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS147
SOMEONE follows her husband's gaze.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS148
He tosses her onto the bed and runs out. As he climbs into his car, SOMEONE glares down from an open patch in a wall.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS149
She throws up her hands and SOMEONE speeds off.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS150
From the yard, SOMEONE glances up at the disgruntled wife.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS151
Meanwhile, SOMEONE races to his boss's office and bursts in.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS153
SOMEONE stares.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS154
He climbs into a car.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS155
The vehicle peels out.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS156
Later, the three birders talk on their cells.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS157
A red line on a map tracks SOMEONE's progress to High Island.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS158
Now, people in cars flock into a grassy parking lot.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS159
SOMEONE parks amid the crowd and gazes at the sky.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS160
SOMEONE gets out of his car.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS161
Climbing out of his vehicle, SOMEONE breaks into a smile.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS162
Birds fill the sky above the trees, speckling it with clusters of black dots.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS163
Racing to the front of the crowd, SOMEONE crosses in front of a cameraman filming a reporter.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS164
He shoves past two men.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS165
He flips them off as he gazes through his binoculars, then heads away.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS166
Later, birds flit overhead as SOMEONE walks a path in the woods, his eyes fixed skyward.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS167
He lifts his binoculars to watch a red bird in a tree.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS168
Gazing over SOMEONE's shoulder, SOMEONE notices SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS169
They hurry after SOMEONE, who disappears into some trees.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS170
As other birders look through binoculars and snap photos, SOMEONE rushes past them and briefly eyes a bird on a tree.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS171
He runs off.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS172
SOMEONE and SOMEONE stop as well to see the little yellow bird.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS173
Slowing his pace, SOMEONE briefly peers through his binoculars.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS174
He runs off. SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive a moment later.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS175
As they continue after SOMEONE, all of three of their tallies appear, counting up past 300.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS176
Through his binoculars, SOMEONE follows a bird, then spots the pretty brunette from the boat. She sees him and he waves.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS177
SOMEONE steps into his line of sight.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS178
SOMEONE sprints off. At a bridge, he picks up a little girl in a uniform who partially blocks the entrance and sets her aside.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS179
SOMEONE and SOMEONE approach the bridge.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS180
She gestures to a group of girls.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS181
The two birders wait as the uniformed girls pass.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS182
As the last explorer crosses, SOMEONE and SOMEONE hurry down the narrow bridge turning sideways to pass others.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS183
They reach a platform looking out onto a lake.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS184
He strides off. SOMEONE and SOMEONE share an exasperated look.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS185
Later, SOMEONE's two competitors sit at a table in an elegant restaurant.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS186
The waiter heads off and SOMEONE frowns.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS187
SOMEONE bulks at his girth.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS188
The waiter returns.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS189
SOMEONE's face remains blank as he sips his drink.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS190
Lowering the glass, he nods.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS191
SOMEONE takes a long drink.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS192
Later, they stroll outside.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS193
SOMEONE extends his hand to shake, but SOMEONE leans forward and gives him a hug.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS194
At a motel.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS195
She discards a needle.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS196
SOMEONE smiles.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS197
Now, in the deck of her boat, SOMEONE stares through binoculars, then points.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS198
May 8th, Coos Bay, Oregon. SOMEONE writes his find in a daily journal, then notices a man with shaggy brown hair staring through binoculars.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS199
He sets down his journal and walks over.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS200
He nudges the guy.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS201
Turning away from the stranger, SOMEONE staggers briefly, then rests his hand against the ferry’s frame. His eyes widen and he stifles a gag.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS202
As he rushes inside, leaving his belongings behind, Crane creeps over and picks up SOMEONE's journal.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS203
He glances around, then flips through it.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS204
Now, SOMEONE sits in his cubicle at his otherwise vacant workplace and pulls up Crane's blog on his computer. He smiles as he reads.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS205
SOMEONE glares. Now SOMEONE talks on the phone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS206
He checks his call waiting.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS207
SOMEONE switches to the other line.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS209
Now, our view soars over jagged snowy mountains.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS210
May 14th, Day 134.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS211
SOMEONE wears a T-shirt and boxers.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS213
Now, they speed down a highway.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS214
She swerves in front of a car. Meanwhile, a helicopter soars toward New York's towering skyscrapers. On a helipad, a man opens the door.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS215
Later, in the meeting,
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS216
SOMEONE glares and SOMEONE shoots SOMEONE a look.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS217
SOMEONE gives a tight affirming smile.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS218
SOMEONE leans toward SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS219
He stands.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS220
With sagging shoulders, SOMEONE glances at his watch, then gives a resigned nod.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS221
Later, he, SOMEONE and SOMEONE sit at the conference room table while McIntyre talks outside with his associates.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS222
SOMEONE shoots his watch a furtive glance.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS223
McIntyre returns to the conference room.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS224
He stands.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS225
He talks on his cell as he exits the building.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS226
He waits by the curb as his driver pulls the car up beside a row of taxis. He jumps in the back.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS227
He checks the time.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS228
Grimacing, he slumps against the seat.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS229
Now, a small plane sits on a runway. Anchorage, Alaska.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS231
As she turns away, SOMEONE eyes her new husband. He mouths Attu. What were you thinking? But the guy gives a dismissive wave.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS232
SOMEONE stumbles aboard.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS233
He stows his bags on an overhead shelf.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS234
He takes a seat across the aisle from SOMEONE, then notices the champion birder eyeing him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS235
SOMEONE allows a nod, then settles in his seat.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS236
Now, the pilot pushes the plane's throttle and the craft begins to move. In the cabin, SOMEONE turns to SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS237
A taxi skids around the Merrill Airfield hangar, kicking up dust. SOMEONE hurries out with his bags in hand. The plane turns onto a runway. On board, SOMEONE shrugs.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS238
SOMEONE's eyes widen. SOMEONE runs for the plane.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS239
He spies SOMEONE through a window.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS240
The plane lifts off the runway.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS241
SOMEONE drops his bags.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS242
He doubles over defeatedly.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS243
On a map, a red arrow extends from a point on the Alaskan coast to the Aleutian Islands halfway across the ocean.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS244
As we descend toward the farthest one, real clouds blanket our view.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS245
The plane bounces with turbulence.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS246
The plane jostles violently.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS247
Bags fall from the overhead shelves.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS248
Shrieking hysterically, SOMEONE grips the seat in front of her with both hands. The co-pilot glances back from the cockpit.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS249
More luggage falls as the plane swoops through a range of jagged mountains.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS250
SOMEONE tensely looks across the aisle. Calmly nibbling a cookie, SOMEONE returns a cordial smile.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS251
The plane lands roughly.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS252
SOMEONE sobs in her husband's arms while SOMEONE sits frozen with a scowl.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS254
Now, the birders march single file down a path cutting through a field at the base of a mountain.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS255
SOMEONE hikes casually behind the newlyweds, admiring his surroundings.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS256
SOMEONE's duffel bounces against his leg with each stride.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS257
As the birders arrive at a remote compound, an old woman inside peers out a dingy window.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS258
She sits and uses a PA microphone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS259
Now, a pair of doors slides open revealing the inside of a Quonset hut set with two rows of bunk beds.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS260
SOMEONE's husband takes in the crude quarters with a grin, barely registering her glum pout.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS261
SOMEONE steps up behind them.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS262
He strolls pass the bunks, then moves through a humble dining area.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS263
A seated woman high fives him as he passes.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS264
Reaching the room's far wall, he shoves a row of lockers to one side revealing a hidden door.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS265
He opens it with a cocky smirk to reveal a small private room.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS266
The others stare as he sets down his things.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS267
Opening a small chest filled with personal items, he takes out a pair of green drawstring pants.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS268
In the common sleeping area, SOMEONE sets his bags on a lower bunk.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS269
A rat runs along a shelf by the headboard. SOMEONE springs up and hits his head on the top bunk.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS270
He scrambles wildly off the bed, grabbing his duffel and peers after the rat with a fearful stare.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS272
He sees the pretty brunette chatting with a tall guy.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS273
SOMEONE approaches her.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS274
The pretty brunette swings her legs around obliviously kicking him in the face. Recovering, he dances from foot to foot as he tries to find a path to his bunk while the other birders rush past him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS275
Outside, they climb on bikes and ride off.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS276
Munching cereal, SOMEONE lounges in the dining area in his green drawstring pants.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS277
SOMEONE narrows his eyes at him, then rushes out to find the other birders riding off.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS278
Donning a knit hat, he grabs one of the few remaining bikes and awkwardly peddles after them.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS279
Now, on a rugged gravel trail.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS280
The birders turn.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS282
SOMEONE stretches as he strolls outside in his green pants.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS283
Wildlife footage shows a sea bird landing among some penguin stealing their fish and flying off.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS284
Now, the birders use binoculars to scan a snowy field near the base of a mountain. SOMEONE squints in the sunlight.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS285
As he turns hurriedly, his feet slip out from under him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS286
He lands on his back in the snow as his fellow birders rush past him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS288
He peers through his binoculars like the others.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS289
A small flock of birds takes flight, but one lingers behind.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS290
It languidly flutters toward a ridge where SOMEONE photographs it.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS291
The others lower their binoculars.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS292
As he moves on, his tally ticks up to 537.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS293
SOMEONE's tally ticks up to 534. As the birders ride across the mountain valley, hand scrolled bird names appear all around them pointed out by arrows: semipalmated plover, spectacled eider, olive-backed pipit, bean goose, Eurasian widgeon, rock ptarmigan, bufflehead, Arctic loon, Laysan albatross. SOMEONE grimaces with effort as he tries to keep up with the others. They spot more birds in a field in a canyon.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS294
Bar-tailed godwit, hoary redpoll, Lapland longspur, Northern shovelers, spectacled eider, long-toed stint.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS295
Carrying their bikes, they wade across a gentle river. Atop a high ridge, SOMEONE gazes through his binoculars. SOMEONE rides alone through a meadow past one last arrowed label - smew.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS296
Now, storm clouds swirl over the compound.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS297
The rat creeps on to SOMEONE's pillow.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS298
At the Alaska Breeze motel, SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS299
Now, on Attu, SOMEONE rides his bike over a ridge.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS300
Arriving at the compound, he climbs off, walks his bike to a rack and leaves it there.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS301
He picks up his knees as he walks to the building, cooling down his stubby legs.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS302
Going in, he sets down his binoculars.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS303
He starts to remove his jacket, then notices the pretty brunette in the dining area and heads toward her.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS304
Wrenching his jacket back on, he brushes past the older man.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS305
SOMEONE stares after him, then presses his lips together knowingly and follows him out.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS306
SOMEONE walks a bike toward a path.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS307
Passing by, the tall brawny birder eyes them curiously.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS308
Later, low clouds roll over the compound. A freak blizzard bombards the area with driving snow.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS309
A tiny bird shifts its nervous gaze. A bald eagle bares the storm stoically, its feathers ruffled in the wind.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS310
They stand at an icy window.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS312
Now, SOMEONE sips brandy and tells stories. SOMEONE regards him with a distrustful gaze.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS313
Now, SOMEONE hikes across the rugged snowy landscape.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS315
He raises his binoculars to his eyes.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS316
SOMEONE and SOMEONE catch up to him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS317
The two birds clasp each other’s talons, then cartwheel as they plummet from the sky.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS318
SOMEONE turns and heads off.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS319
SOMEONE follows him, but SOMEONE lingers behind to watch the eagles.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS320
He lowers his binoculars with a pensive frown.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS321
Now, in the Quonset hut, the pretty brunette lies on her upper bunk typing on her laptop.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS322
From a table in the dining area, SOMEONE watches her longingly.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS323
He turns away, then gives a brave nod and gets to his feet.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS324
Stuffing his hands in his pockets, he shuffles toward her bunk.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS325
Now, SOMEONE leaves an outhouse with a bird shaped hole carved in its wooden door. Taking in his snow-blanketed surroundings, he finds SOMEONE pumping up a bicycle tire.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS326
SOMEONE rolls his eyes.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS327
He pats SOMEONE's shoulder.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS328
Inside, a knife cuts fish.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS329
He wipes the counter with a scarf.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS330
SOMEONE storms outside with it.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS331
The birders flock to the windows. As SOMEONE takes her scarf to a water pump, gulls swoop down all around her.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS332
She flails wildly in a futile attempt to defend herself.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS333
Her husband rushes out and flings the scarf aside.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS334
She falls on her behind as the birds continue their assault.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS335
Now, as the birders file toward a waiting air taxi, SOMEONE storms past them with her expensive luggage.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS336
One guy looks back and points to a rooftop.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS337
SOMEONE takes down a windsock.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS342
He replaces the windsock with his green pants.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS343
SOMEONE boards the plane.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS344
SOMEONE climbs on as well. Staying behind, SOMEONE jogs away joyfully.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS345
Beneath the cloudy sky, the plane lifts off from the runway.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS346
On board, SOMEONE reaches across the aisle and taps SOMEONE's shoulder.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS347
As he turns, she hands him a slip of paper. He reads it, lifts his brow and glances back at her with a hopeful smile.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS348
A series of scenes highlights his travels.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS349
SOMEONE hikes up to a waterfall where a bird soars among the mist. In a city, SOMEONE uses her cell phone as she peers upward through binoculars. On the other end of the line, SOMEONE strolls through a desert.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS350
Now, a fan boat speeds through the Everglades.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS351
In a swamp, SOMEONE fights his way past a low branch as he rows a small boat.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS352
He spies a flamingo ahead.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS353
At sunset, he watches circling gulls from a sand bar. Now, at work.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS354
SOMEONE answers his cell.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS355
Now, words appear beneath the speeding train. August 20th, Day 232. SOMEONE arrives at Boston South Station.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS356
He spies SOMEONE on the platform.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS357
He disembarks.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS358
He shyly pecks her cheek.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS359
They leave the station and approach a car at the curb.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS360
With a thoughtful look, SOMEONE lowers his phone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS361
His son answers the door to an apartment.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS362
Stepping inside, SOMEONE hugs him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS363
His daughter-in-law cradles her infant son.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS364
The white haired grandfather gives a touched look.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS365
He sits.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS366
He reaches out.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS367
His son snaps photos.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS368
He gives his grandson a broad goofy grin.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS369
SOMEONE arrives.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS370
She watches lovingly from the background.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS371
SOMEONE notices her and smiles.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS372
He jiggles little SOMEONE's hips like a dancer.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS373
Later, he hurries outside.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS374
A cab pulls to a stop.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS375
He loads his bags into the backseat, then turns to his son's apartment and waves good-bye.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS376
His family waves back from a window.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS377
SOMEONE strolls through an Iowa field.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS378
He stands on a beach in Fire Island.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS379
Sitting in an airport shuttle, he eyes his phone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS380
Its display shows the photos of a smiling SOMEONE holding his grandson.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS381
October 2nd. Seattle, Washington.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS382
SOMEONE grins as he sees SOMEONE at the ferry terminal.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS383
SOMEONE approaches with a hand cupped to his ear.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS384
He leaves.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS385
Seeing SOMEONE sprint to his car, they head to the ticket booth.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS386
Pulling his car out of a line of vehicles waiting for the ferry, SOMEONE peels off down the road.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS387
SOMEONE and SOMEONE jump into a gray sedan at the front of the line.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS388
The white haired birder turns his vehicle around and heads after SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS389
As the gray sedan speeds off down the road, SOMEONE's blue car glides back out from behind a bus and returns to its spot in the ferry line.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS390
The champion birder casually gets out.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS391
Glancing over his shoulder, he smirks. Now, at the Skagit Wildlife area.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS392
SOMEONE checks his watch.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS393
SOMEONE nods.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS394
He looks away, then furrows his brow and turns back to SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS395
SOMEONE opens his arms affirmatively.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS396
Now, he consults a map as SOMEONE drives. Later, they paddle a canoe down a stream in Whitefish, Montana.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS397
Now, a car rolls down a dusty road between Rocky Mountains. Later, SOMEONE peers through bushes at water birds.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS398
Holding him on his shoulders, SOMEONE grimaces. Asheville, North Carolina.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS399
A wider view shows an industrial plant beyond the bushes.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS400
SOMEONE stumbles as SOMEONE tries to climb onto his shoulders.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS401
Now, in the car, SOMEONE claps and SOMEONE sings.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS402
Later, they sit at the edge of Lake Tahoe in Nevada.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS403
SOMEONE hurries off.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS404
At a bar, SOMEONE talks on his phone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS405
He hangs up, then turns to SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS406
Now, a helicopter swoops between jagged peaks. Words appear.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS407
SOMEONE Mountains, Nevada.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS408
Sitting beside SOMEONE, the pilot, SOMEONE shifts his eyes to the jagged rocks.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS409
The chopper banks suddenly toward a mountain face, then swerves away at the last second. SOMEONE squeezes his eyes shut.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS410
SOMEONE cackles.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS411
SOMEONE clutches his grab handle. The pilot spots a pale bird dipping below a tree-lined cliff.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS412
The helicopter swings back around with its nose pointed downwards. SOMEONE cringes. SOMEONE wears a queasy look.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS413
SOMEONE spots the snow cock.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS414
The bird nosedives, leaving the chopper headed straight toward a cliff face. The pilot swerves away just in time.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS415
Now, the chopper lands in front of a hangar reading Nevada Aviation.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS416
Crouched to avoid the aircraft's spinning blades, SOMEONE and SOMEONE climb out and hurry to a safe distance.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS417
SOMEONE jumps up and pumps his fists.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS418
SOMEONE kisses the ground. SOMEONE does a wild and crazy version of the twist.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS419
SOMEONE dances with him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS420
SOMEONE stops his disco dancing as he sees SOMEONE's frown.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS421
Now, at a hospital, his mother buttons his father's shirt.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS422
SOMEONE watches worriedly.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS423
Sitting on the edge of the hospital bed, he shoots his son a weary glance.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS424
SOMEONE scrutinizes him, then walks to his bag which rests on a chair.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS425
He grabs a camera.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS426
His dad takes a pair of glasses from his breast pocket.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS427
He clicks to the next image.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS428
He smiles as he gazes at the photo.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS429
His father gives him a thoughtful look.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS430
Now, a car screeches to a halt on a dusty road.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS431
Santa Fe National Forest, New Mexico.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS432
SOMEONE drinks from a canteen as he waits on a rocky mountainside.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS433
He hurries after the sound.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS434
Elsewhere, a portly man makes birdcalls.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS435
SOMEONE hurries over.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS436
SOMEONE eavesdrops.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS437
He hurries ahead.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS438
Now, at Bergen Fertility Clinic, SOMEONE reads through paperwork on a clipboard, then brings it to a reception desk where a dark haired nurse takes it.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS439
She flashes a smile, then returns to her seat in the waiting room.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS440
Meanwhile, SOMEONE races to his car in the airport parking lot.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS441
He stows his bags in the trunk, then climbs in.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS442
As he starts the engine, his wipers clear a layer of dirt off the windshield.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS443
In an exam room at the clinic, the dark haired nurse draws his wife's blood.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS444
SOMEONE winces.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS445
She looks away, her smile fading.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS446
Meanwhile, SOMEONE stops at a parking attendant's booth.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS447
The cashier takes his ticket and the gate's striped arm lifts allowing SOMEONE car to leave the lot.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS448
The blonde birder speeds away from the airport.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS450
He swerves from lane to lane, passing other cars.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS451
At the clinic, SOMEONE now wears a hospital gown as she waits alone in an exam chair.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS452
She extends her legs and anxiously flexes her feet.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS453
As the door opens,
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS454
she sets her feet down with a start.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS455
The nurse backs out of the room.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS456
SOMEONE drops her face in her hand.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS457
Speeding into the clinic's lot, her husband parks crookedly in a space. He races toward the entrance.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS458
He takes out his cell and checks its display, then answers with one hand on the clinic’s door.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS459
SOMEONE checks the time.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS461
In the clinic, SOMEONE makes a call.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS462
He takes a parking ticket as he heads back into the airport lot.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS463
Later, at their house.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS464
Running her hands through her hair, SOMEONE sits heavily on a box in a partially renovated room.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS465
Pastel wallpaper with children's drawings covers the bottom half of the walls.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS466
As SOMEONE rests her head in her hands, SOMEONE Jr. tiptoes in.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS467
He holds out a mug.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS468
He sets it on a table.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS469
He leaves.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS470
Meanwhile at the SOMEONE house, SOMEONE's father reads in the living room.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS471
With an exasperated look, he sets his newspaper aside and grabs his son's backpack off the floor.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS472
He opens its front pocket and rifles through it, taking out packages of snacks and setting them on a coffee table.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS473
Finding SOMEONE's phone, he answers.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS474
SOMEONE comes downstairs.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS475
Now, light snow falls as SOMEONE and his father walk in the woods.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS476
SOMEONE Washington National Forest, Virginia.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS477
Now, autumn leaves add rich color to SOMEONE's street as he gets out of his car.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS478
He goes to the trunk and takes out his bags.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS479
His vanity license plate reads 732.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS481
The champion birder enters his now fully renovated home.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS484
He goes to a nearby room and sets down his green Jet's duffel bag on a table.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS485
He proceeds into a dining area, plants his hands on his hips and looks around. SOMEONE jogs upstairs and strolls along the landing.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS488
Arriving at the door, he leans a hand against the frame and peers in.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS489
Frowning, he heads down the hall.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS490
He arrives in the bedroom and glares at his wife.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS491
Under the covers, she stares up at him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS492
He steps away and she rolls onto her back.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS493
Now, SOMEONE sits gazing ahead with a heart broken scowl.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS494
In a short nightie and open bathrobe,
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS495
SOMEONE pads downstairs.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS497
She sits on the lower steps, regarding him with a gentle expression.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS498
SOMEONE briefly lowers his gaze.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS500
Her arms folded, SOMEONE moves closer to her husband, then takes a seat facing him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS502
She hurries away.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS503
In the forest, the snow falls more heavily.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS504
SOMEONE's father stoops warily as he follows his son through the woods.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS505
SOMEONE surveys the trees as he gives birdcalls.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS506
He notices his father wincing.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS507
He lays a hand on SOMEONE's shoulder.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS508
The younger man regards his father with a concerned frown, then proceeds onward at the gentle snowfall.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS509
An oxygen tank peeking from his backpack.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS510
As their paths take them uphill,
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS512
his father slows to a stop. His son faces him boyishly.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS513
SOMEONE rolls his eyes, then brings the tank over.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS514
Obeying, SOMEONE glances back at his father.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS515
The ailing old man opens the backpack.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS516
With the SOMEONE's.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS517
SOMEONE's eyes gleam meaningfully.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS518
SOMEONE lowers his gaze.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS519
The two stand apart on opposite sides of the kitchen.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS521
Now, in the forest. In the gentle snowfall, SOMEONE raises his binoculars and peers through them at the surrounding trees.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS522
He lowers them and ventures on.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS523
Later, he hikes up a path in the darkening woods.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS524
He halts abruptly, his gaze suddenly worried.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS525
He hurriedly doubles back. Silhouetted against the snowy woods, he runs back to where he left his father. Looking around, he finds no sign of him. SOMEONE's expression grows frantic and he rushes further down the path. He stops periodically to scan the area for his father, then plunges onward. SOMEONE's searching eyes glisten.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS526
His brow furrows fearfully and he races wildly through the darkening wintry forest. Dashing down a ridge, he peers through the snow and finds his father about 20 yards ahead. The old man stoops and sways on his feet. SOMEONE relieved smile fades and he hurries over to his ailing father.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS527
With one hand braced against the tree, his father points upward happily.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS528
Following his gaze, SOMEONE finds a magnificent dark brown owl perched almost directly overhead.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS529
His beaming father claps an arm around him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS530
It gazes down at them serenely. Daytime.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS531
At home, SOMEONE groggily rolls over on his bed and answers his cell phone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS532
Rio Chama River, New Mexico.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS533
Now, as SOMEONE and SOMEONE run along the rainy dock, words appear. November 27th, Day 331.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS534
They spy a sign printed on turkey-themed stationary - No Birding Today. Happy Holidays.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS535
Now, in a car.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS536
Now, SOMEONE opens a door with a wreath on it.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS537
She slams the door in their faces.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS538
As the two friends start to leave the porch, the door flies open behind them.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS539
SOMEONE and SOMEONE nod. Now, on SOMEONE's boat.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS540
Monterrey, California. On a beach, Crane watches SOMEONE. Later, SOMEONE reads his blog.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS541
SOMEONE uses his cell phone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS542
Now, as SOMEONE drives in a snowstorm, words appear. December 24th. Duluth, Minnesota.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS543
He mumbles silently to himself, then peers out his windshield and shifts his pensive gaze.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS544
Now, in a Chinese restaurant, he struggles with his chopsticks. A waiter brings a fork.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS545
The waiter starts to step away.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS546
Later, two waiters eat with him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS547
Chewing, SOMEONE shifts his gaze.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS548
SOMEONE questions his female colleague who shrugs.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS549
Through a window, we watch SOMEONE raise his teacup to his companions.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS551
At home, SOMEONE strides briefly from his office. Words appear, December 29th, Day 363.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS552
SOMEONE returns to his office and answers the phone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS553
SOMEONE mouths nice to Jim, who shrugs.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS554
Through a window, SOMEONE tenderly watches SOMEONE approach the house.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS555
The two cronies pump their fists.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS556
December 30th, in the mountains.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS557
SOMEONE leads his friend up a snowy path.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS558
They proceed over a high ridge.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS559
SOMEONE taps SOMEONE's shoulder and points.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS560
They stop at the crest of a snowy hill and use their binoculars.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS561
A goose bathes in a hot spring.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS562
SOMEONE lowers his binoculars and faces him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS563
SOMEONE grins and lifts his arms triumphantly.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS564
SOMEONE hugs him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS565
He arcs away. The rare goose stands on a rock. Its pink feet exposed.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS566
Now, outside a rustic lodge, a camera flashes in the nearby woods.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS567
SOMEONE emerges from the forest and passes the lodge.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS568
As he scribbles in a notebook, words write out below. December 31st. Snowy owl.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS569
He glances back at people embracing each other at the lodge's porch, then ventures onward.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS570
At SOMEONE's house, snow frosts the branches of the surrounding trees.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS571
Inside, the retired businessman clinks glasses with his son, his arm around his wife.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS572
Now, a TV shows the Time Square celebration.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS573
Our view sweeps around, revealing SOMEONE's parents' living room.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS574
The older couple dozes on the couch while SOMEONE sits in a chair next to them.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS575
He gets up and steps away from his sleeping parents as he answers his cell phone.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS576
Lowering the phone, SOMEONE dances victoriously on his parents' back porch.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS577
He allows a joyful grin.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS578
Our view drifts up to the sky and finds two large birds flying in silhouette against the full moon.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS579
Daytime. A mail truck pulls away from SOMEONE's house. SOMEONE comes out through the automatically opening gates and collects the bundled delivery.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS580
He pulls off a rubber band and sorts through it on his way back to the house.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS581
SOMEONE slows to a stop as he comes to a magazine titled Birding.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS582
A banner across one corner reads Big Year results, page 46.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS584
SOMEONE faces SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS585
SOMEONE tenderly faces his wife who smiles back at him.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS586
SOMEONE approaches SOMEONE.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS587
SOMEONE joyfully runs to him. SOMEONE scoops her up in his arms and spins her around in a warm embrace.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS588
At SOMEONE's, SOMEONE joins her husband at a window and rests her chin on his shoulder.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS589
They both smile.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS590
Now, SOMEONE walks outdoors carrying a toddler.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS591
Little SOMEONE smiles.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS592
He stands at a round doorway overlooking a beautiful landscape. His thoughtful gaze focused on a happy couple with a baby.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS593
SOMEONE and SOMEONE arrive at the edge of a rocky coast.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS594
Through binoculars, we watch gulls.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS595
Lowering his binoculars, SOMEONE regards SOMEONE affectionately as she happily watches the birds.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS597
Words appear. To set the Big Year record, Kenny SOMEONE saw 755 different species of birds including hummingbirds.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS598
A handwritten label accompanies snapshots of the tiny birds.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS599
More photos show auklets.
THE_BIG_YEAR_DVS600
Images of woodpeckers, fly catchers and ducks stack on top of each other.